<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【Domain Name System: The Internet’s Telephone Directory】域名系统：互联网的电话号码簿</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/domain-name-system-the-internets</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at the journey of a DNS query in detail, the various DNS records, and the role of Anycast in DNS.】在本文中，我们将详细了解 DNS 查询的过程、各种 DNS 记录以及 Anycast 在 DNS 中的作用。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Facebook’s Distributed Priority Queue Handles Trillions of Items】Facebook 的分布式优先级队列如何处理数万亿个项目</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-facebooks-distributed-priority</link>
      <description>【In this article, we look at how FOQS is structured, how it processes enqueues and dequeues, and how it maintains reliability.】在本文中，我们将了解 FOQS 的结构、它如何处理入队和出队以及它如何保持可靠性。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Flipkart Built a Highly Available MySQL Cluster for 150+ Million Users】Flipkart 如何为 1.5 亿以上用户构建高可用的 MySQL 集群</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-flipkart-built-a-highly-available</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how Altair works under the hood, the technical decisions Flipkart made to balance availability and consistency, and the engineering trade-offs that come with running relational databases at a massive scale.】在本文中，我们将了解 Altair 的幕后工作原理、Flipkart 为平衡可用性和一致性而做出的技术决策，以及大规模运行关系数据库所带来的工程权衡。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How OpenAI Uses Kubernetes And Apache Kafka for GenAI】OpenAI 如何将 Kubernetes 和 Apache Kafka 用于 GenAI</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-openai-uses-kubernetes-and-apache</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will understand how OpenAI built such a system and the challenges they faced.】在这篇文章中，我们将了解 OpenAI 如何构建这样一个系统以及他们面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP183: MCP vs API: what’s the difference?】EP183：MCP 与 API：有什么区别？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep183-mcp-vs-api-whats-the-difference</link>
      <description>【APIs have been the backbone of software-to-software communication for decades.】几十年来，API 一直是软件间通信的支柱。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Last Call: Enrollment for the AI Engineering Cohort Ends Today】最后的呼吁：人工智能工程队列的报名今天结束</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/last-call-enrollment-for-the-ai-engineering</link>
      <description>【Our very first cohort of Becoming an AI Engineer starts in one day. This is a live, cohort-based course created in collaboration with best-selling author Ali Aminian and published by ByteByteGo.】我们的第一批“成为人工智能工程师”课程将在一天内开始。这是一门基于队列的实时课程，由 ByteByteGo 与畅销书作家 Ali Aminian 合作创建。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Service Discovery 101: The Phonebook for Distributed Systems】服务发现 101：分布式系统的电话簿</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/service-discovery-101-the-phonebook</link>
      <description>【How do all these services find and communicate with each other in this constantly shifting landscape?】在这个不断变化的环境中，所有这些服务如何相互找到并通信？</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Airbnb Runs Distributed Databases on Kubernetes at Scale】Airbnb 如何在 Kubernetes 上大规模运行分布式数据库</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-airbnb-runs-distributed-databases</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how Airbnb implemented this design and the challenges they faced.】在本文中，我们将了解 Airbnb 如何实施这一设计以及他们面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Anthropic’s MCP is a Big Deal】为什么 Anthropic 的 MCP 很重要</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/why-anthropics-mcp-is-a-big-deal</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at MCP in detail and explore what makes it such an important component in the AI landscape.】在本文中，我们将详细研究 MCP，并探讨是什么使它成为人工智能领域如此重要的组成部分。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Grab’s Migration from Go to Rust Cut Costs by 70%】Grab 从 Go 迁移到 Rust 如何将成本降低 70%</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-grabs-migration-from-go-to-rust</link>
      <description>【Grab has long relied on Golang for most of its microservices. In this article, we look at how Grab migrated their counter service from Go to Rust, resulting in a 70% cost reduction.】Grab 长期以来大部分微服务都依赖 Golang。在本文中，我们将了解 Grab 如何将其柜台服务从 Go 迁移到 Rust，从而降低了 70% 的成本。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>