<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Anthropic’s MCP is a Big Deal】为什么人类的MCP很重要</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/why-anthropics-mcp-is-a-big-deal</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at MCP in detail and explore what makes it such an important component in the AI landscape.】在本文中，我们将详细研究MCP，并探索使其成为AI景观中如此重要组成部分的原因。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Grab’s Migration from Go to Rust Cut Costs by 70%】Grab的迁移如何从生锈削减成本70％</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-grabs-migration-from-go-to-rust</link>
      <description>【Grab has long relied on Golang for most of its microservices. In this article, we look at how Grab migrated their counter service from Go to Rust, resulting in a 70% cost reduction.】Grab长期以来一直依赖Golang的大多数微服务。在本文中，我们研究了Grab如何从Rust迁移他们的柜台服务，从而降低了70％的成本。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Last Chance to Enroll | Become an AI Engineer | Cohort-Based Course】注册的最后机会|成为AI工程师|基于队列的课程</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/last-chance-to-enroll-become-an-ai</link>
      <description>【Our very first cohort of Becoming an AI Engineer starts in less than a week. This is a live, cohort-based course created in collaboration with best-selling author Ali Aminian and published by ByteByteGo.】我们成为AI工程师的第一个队列在不到一周的时间内就开始了。这是与畅销书作家阿里·阿米尼亚（Ali Aminian）合作创建的，由Bytebytego出版的实时，基于队列的课程。</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP182: Cookies vs Sessions】EP182：cookie vs sessions</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep182-cookies-vs-sessions</link>
      <description>【Every web app needs a way to remember users after they log in, and the way they manage this makes a big difference in performance, scalability, and security of that web application.】每个Web应用程序都需要一种方法来记住用户登录后，并且他们管理此操作的方式对该Web应用程序的性能，可扩展性和安全性有很大的影响。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 15:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GraphQL 101: API Approach Beyond REST】GraphQL 101：API接近休息</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/graphql-101-api-approach-beyond-rest</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will start with the basic concepts of GraphQL, covering how it works and why it has become so popular. From there, we will look at different ways GraphQL can be used as part of system architecture, from simple deployments to large-scale environments.】在本文中，我们将从GraphQl的基本概念开始，涵盖它的工作原理以及为什么变得如此受欢迎。从那里开始，我们将研究GraphQL可以用作系统体系结构的一部分，从简单部署到大规模环境。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Fine-Tuning Transforms Generic AI Models into Specialists】微调如何将通用AI模型转化为专家</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-fine-tuning-transforms-generic</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will understand how fine-tuning works at a conceptual level, the different approaches available, and breakthrough techniques like LoRA that have democratized access to AI customization.】在本文中，我们将了解微调如何在概念层面，可用的不同方法以及像Lora这样的突破性技术来使AI自定义访问民主化。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How RAG Enables AI For Your Data】RAG如何启用AI的数据</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-rag-enables-ai-for-your-data</link>
      <description>【Large Language Models like GPT-4 and Claude have transformed the way we interact with computers.】GPT-4和Claude等大型语言模型已经改变了我们与计算机互动的方式。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Meta Animates Billions of AI-generated Images】元如何使数十亿个AI生成的图像动画</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-meta-animates-billions-of-ai</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how Meta implemented this feature and the challenges they faced.】在本文中，我们将研究Meta如何实施此功能以及它们面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 15:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP181: How Java Works】EP181：Java如何工作</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep181-how-java-works</link>
      <description>【Ever wondered what happens behind the scenes when you run a Java program?】有没有想过当您运行Java程序时幕后会发生什么？</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 15:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Load Balancers: Traffic Management at Scale】了解负载平衡器：大规模交通管理</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/understanding-load-balancers-traffic</link>
      <description>【When applications grow beyond a single server, they face the challenge of handling more users, more data, and more requests than one machine can manage.】当应用程序超越单个服务器时，他们面临着处理更多用户，更多的数据和更多请求的挑战，而不是一台计算机可以管理的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>