<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【EP199: Behind the Scenes: What Happens When You Enter Google.com】EP199：幕后花絮：进入 Google.com 后会发生什么</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep199-behind-the-scenes-what-happens</link>
      <description>【Most of us hit Enter and expect the page to load instantly, but under the hood, a surprisingly intricate chain of events fires off in milliseconds.】我们大多数人按下 Enter 并期望页面立即加载，但在幕后，一系列令人惊讶的复杂事件在几毫秒内触发。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【We are hiring at ByteByteGo】我们正在 ByteByteGo 招聘</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/we-are-hiring-at-bytebytego</link>
      <description>【I am hiring for 2 roles: Technical Deep Dive Writer (System Design or AI Systems), and Lead Instructor (Building the World&amp;#8217;s Most Useful AI Cohort).】我正在招聘 2 个职位：技术深度作家（系统设计或人工智能系统）和首席讲师（建立世界上最有用的人工智能群体）。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Must-Know Fundamentals of Distributed Systems】分布式系统必须了解的基础知识</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/the-must-know-fundamentals-of-distributed</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at five foundational topics around distributed systems: how computers communicate across networks, the protocols enabling reliable communication, how remote procedure calls abstract complexity, strategies for handling failures, and why time synchronization presents unique challenges.】在本文中，我们将研究围绕分布式系统的五个基本主题：计算机如何跨网络通信、实现可靠通信的协议、远程过程如何调用抽象复杂性、处理故障的策略以及为什么时间同步会带来独特的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Netflix Built a Real-Time Distributed Graph for Internet Scale】Netflix 如何构建适合互联网规模的实时分布式图</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-netflix-built-a-real-time-distributed</link>
      <description>【Disclaimer: This post is based on publicly shared details from the Netflix Engineering Team. Please comment if you notice any inaccuracies.】免责声明：本文基于 Netflix 工程团队公开分享的详细信息。如果您发现任何不准确之处，请发表评论。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Pinterest Built An Async Compute Platform for Billions of Task Executions】Pinterest 如何构建用于数十亿任务执行的异步计算平台</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-pinterest-built-an-async-compute</link>
      <description>【When Pinterest&amp;#8217;s engineering team built their asynchronous job processing platform called Pinlater a few years ago, it seemed like a solid solution for handling background tasks at scale.】几年前，当 Pinterest 的工程团队构建名为 Pinlater 的异步作业处理平台时，它似乎是大规模处理后台任务的可靠解决方案。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why AI Needs GPUs and TPUs: The Hardware Behind LLMs】为什么人工智能需要 GPU 和 TPU：法学硕士背后的硬件</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/why-ai-needs-gpus-and-tpus-the-hardware</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how GPUs and TPUs help build modern LLMs and the architecture behind them.】在本文中，我们将了解 GPU 和 TPU 如何帮助构建现代法学硕士及其背后的架构。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP198: Best Resources to Learn AI in 2026】EP198：2026 年学习人工智能的最佳资源</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep198-best-resources-to-learn-ai</link>
      <description>【The AI resources can be divided into different types such as】AI资源可以分为不同类型，例如</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Last Call: Enrollment for the AI Engineering Cohort 3 Ends Today】最后通知：人工智能工程第三期的报名今天结束</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/last-call-enrollment-for-the-ai-engineering-f1a</link>
      <description>【Our third cohort of Becoming an AI Engineer starts in one day. This is a live, cohort-based course created in collaboration with best-selling author Ali Aminian and published by ByteByteGo.】我们的第三批“成为人工智能工程师”课程将在一天后开始。这是一门基于队列的实时课程，由 ByteByteGo 与畅销书作家 Ali Aminian 合作创建。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Database Sharding】数据库分片指南</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/must-know-message-broker-patterns-4c4</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will learn about database sharding in more detail. We will understand what it is, why it matters, how different approaches work, and what key considerations are important when implementing it.】在本文中，我们将更详细地了解数据库分片。我们将了解它是什么、为什么它很重要、不同的方法如何运作以及实施它时需要考虑哪些关键因素。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Uber Serves over 150 Million Reads per Second from Integrated Cache】Uber 如何通过集成缓存提供每秒超过 1.5 亿次的读取</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-uber-serves-over-150-million</link>
      <description>【In this article, we break down how Uber built this system, the challenges they faced, and the innovative solutions they developed.】在本文中，我们将详细介绍 Uber 如何构建该系统、他们面临的挑战以及他们开发的创新解决方案。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>