<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【EP169: RAG vs Agentic RAG】EP169：抹布与代理抹布</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep169-rag-vs-agentic-rag</link>
      <description>【What else will you add to better understand RAG vs Agentic RAG?】您还可以添加什么以更好地了解RAG与Agentic rag？</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Database Indexing Demystified: Index Types and Use-Cases】数据库索引神秘：索引类型和用例</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/database-indexing-demystified-index</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will explore the basic concept of database indexing and different index types.】在本文中，我们将探讨数据库索引和不同索引类型的基本概念。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 15:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Object Oriented Design Interview Book is here — now available on Amazon!】面向对象的设计采访书在这里 - 现在在亚马逊上可用！</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/object-oriented-design-interview</link>
      <description>【*BIG* announcement: Our new book, Object Oriented Design Interview, is available on Amazon!】* Big*公告：我们的新书，面向对象的设计采访，可在亚马逊上获得！</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【7 Years, 8 Books, 1 Launch. A lot more to come!】7年，8本书，1个发射。还有更多！</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/7-years-8-books-1-launch-a-lot-more</link>
      <description>【7 Years, 8 Books, 1 Launch.】7年，8本书，1个发射。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 15:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Discord Stores Trillions of Messages with High Performance】Discord如何用高性能存储数万亿个消息</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-discord-stores-trillions-of-messages</link>
      <description>【We will walk through how Discord rebuilt its message storage layer from the ground up. We will learn the issues Discord faced with Apache Cassandra&amp;#174; and their shift to ScyllaDB.】我们将介绍如何从头开始重建其消息存储层。我们将学习与ApacheCassandra®及其转向Scylladb所面临的不和谐问题。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Database Replication: Key Concepts and Strategies】数据库复制指南：关键概念和策略</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-guide-to-database-replication-key</link>
      <description>【We will cover single-leader, multi-leader, and leaderless replication models, breaking down how each works, what problems they solve, and where they fall apart.】我们将介绍单个领导者，多领导者和无领导者复制模型，分解每个人的工作方式，他们解决的问题以及它们崩溃的位置。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Spotify Uses GenAI and ML to Annotate a Hundred Million Tracks】Spotify如何使用Genai和ML注释一亿首曲目</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-spotify-uses-genai-and-ml-to</link>
      <description>【This article explains how Spotify addressed these challenges by building an annotation platform designed to scale with its machine learning needs.】本文解释了Spotify如何通过构建旨在按机器学习需求扩展的注释平台来解决这些挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP170: All-in-One Technical Interview Prep Kit】EP170：多合一技术面试准备套件</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep170-best-ways-to-test-system-functionality</link>
      <description>【Testing system functionality&amp;#160;ensures that a system or software application performs as expected, meets user requirements, and operates reliably.】测试系统功能可确保系统或软件应用程序按预期执行，满足用户要求并可靠地运行。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 15:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Inside Airbnb’s AI-Powered Pipeline to Migrate Tests: Months of Work in Days 】在Airbnb的AI驱动管道中，用于迁移测试：几天的工作</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/inside-airbnbs-ai-powered-pipeline</link>
      <description>【This article covers the structure of the automation pipeline, the trade-offs behind prompt engineering vs. brute-force retries, the methods used to handle complex edge cases, and the results that followed.】本文涵盖了自动化管道的结构，迅速工程与蛮力重试的权衡取舍，用于处理复杂边缘案例的方法以及随后的结果。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 15:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP168: AI Vs Machine Learning Vs Deep Learning Vs Generative AI】EP168：AI与机器学习与深度学习与生成AI</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep168-ai-vs-machine-learning-vs-deep</link>
      <description>【What else will you add to understand these concepts better?】您还会添加什么以更好地理解这些概念？</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 15:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>