<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【Last Call: All in One Interview Prep Black Friday Sale Ends Today】最后一次通话：一体化面试准备黑色星期五促销今天结束</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/last-call-all-in-one-interview-prep</link>
      <description>【Yearly Black Friday sale Ends Today! Use code BF2025 at checkout to get 30% off the all-in-one interview prep online courses.】一年一度的黑色星期五促销今天结束！结帐时使用代码 BF2025 即可获得一体化面试准备在线课程 30% 的折扣。</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP191: Virtualization vs. Containerization】EP191：虚拟化与容器化</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep191-virtualization-vs-containerization</link>
      <description>【Before containers simplified deployment, virtualization changed how we used hardware. Both isolate workloads, but they do it differently.】在容器简化部署之前，虚拟化改变了我们使用硬件的方式。两者都隔离工作负载，但做法不同。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【⏳ LIMITED TIME OFFER: All in One Interview Prep Black Friday Sale】⏳ 限时优惠：多合一面试准备黑色星期五促销</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/limited-time-offer-all-in-one-interview</link>
      <description>【Yearly Black Friday sale is now live!】一年一度的黑色星期五促销现已开始！</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Saga Pattern Demystified: Orchestration vs Choreography】传奇模式揭秘：编排与编排</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/saga-pattern-demystified-orchestration</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how the Saga pattern works and the pros and cons of various approaches to implement this pattern.】在本文中，我们将了解 Saga 模式的工作原理以及实现该模式的各种方法的优缺点。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Zalando Delivers Real-Time Insights to Its Partners Brands】Zalando 如何为其合作伙伴品牌提供实时洞察</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-zalando-delivers-real-time-insights</link>
      <description>【Zalando&amp;#8217;s Partner Tech division, responsible for data sharing and collaboration with partners, found itself managing a fragmented and inefficient process.】Zalando 的合作伙伴技术部门负责与合作伙伴的数据共享和协作，但发现自己管理着一个分散且低效的流程。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP190: Cloudflare vs. AWS vs. Azure】EP190：Cloudflare 与 AWS 与 Azure</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep190-cloudflare-vs-aws-vs-azure</link>
      <description>【Cloudflare is much more than just a CDN and DDoS protection service. Let&amp;#8217;s do a quick comparison of Cloudflare, AWS, and Azure.】Cloudflare 不仅仅是 CDN 和 DDoS 保护服务。让我们快速比较一下 Cloudflare、AWS 和 Azure。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 16:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Strategies to Build High Availability Systems】构建高可用性系统的最佳策略</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/top-strategies-to-build-high-availability</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will understand what availability means and look at some of the most popular strategies to achieve high availability.】在本文中，我们将了解可用性的含义，并了解一些最流行的实现高可用性的策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Disney Hotstar (now JioHotstar) Scaled Its Infra for 60 Million Concurrent Users】Disney Hotstar（现为 JioHotstar）如何为 6000 万并发用户扩展基础设施</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-disney-hotstar-now-jiohotstar</link>
      <description>【In this article, we look at how the Disney+ Hotstar engineering team achieved that scale and the challenges they faced.】在本文中，我们将了解 Disney+ Hotstar 工程团队如何实现这一规模以及他们面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Grab Built an AI Foundation Model To Understand Customers Better】Grab 如何构建 AI 基础模型以更好地了解客户</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-grab-built-an-ai-foundation-model</link>
      <description>【In this article, we look at how Grab developed this foundational model and the challenges it faced.】在本文中，我们将了解 Grab 如何开发这一基础模型及其面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP189: How to Design Good APIs】EP189：如何设计好的 API</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep189-how-to-design-good-apis</link>
      <description>【A well-designed API feels invisible, it just works. Behind that simplicity lies a set of consistent design principles that make APIs predictable, secure, and scalable.】设计良好的 API 让人感觉看不见，但它确实有效。这种简单性背后隐藏着一组一致的设计原则，使 API 具有可预测性、安全性和可扩展性。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>