<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【A Deep Dive into HTTP: From HTTP 1 to HTTP 3】深入研究HTTP：从HTTP 1到HTTP 3</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-deep-dive-into-http-from-http-1</link>
      <description>【In this article, we trace the HTTP journey. From the stateless, text-based simplicity of HTTP/1.1 to the encrypted, multiplexed, and mobile-optimized world of HTTP/3.】在本文中，我们追踪HTTP旅程。从HTTP/1.1的无状态，基于文本的简单性到HTTP/3的加密，多路复用和移动优化的世界。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Uber Eats Handles Billions of Daily Search Queries】Uber如何处理数十亿的日常搜索查询</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-uber-eats-handles-billions-of</link>
      <description>【In this article, we look at the breakdown of how Uber Eats rebuilt its search platform to handle this scale without degrading performance or relevance.】在本文中，我们研究了Uber饮食如何重建其搜索平台以处理此规模而不会降低性能或相关性的细分。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SQL vs NoSQL: Choosing the Right Database for An Application】SQL VS NOSQL：为应用程序选择正确的数据库</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/sql-vs-nosql-choosing-the-right-database</link>
      <description>【In this article, we break down the core database paradigms, such as SQL and NoSQL, along with specialized database types and how developers can choose the appropriate database for their requirements.】在本文中，我们分解了诸如SQL和NOSQL之类的核心数据库范例，以及专门的数据库类型，以及开发人员如何为其要求选择适当的数据库。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 15:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Amazon Key Opens 100 Million Doors Every Year】亚马逊钥匙每年如何打开1亿个门</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-amazon-key-opens-100-million</link>
      <description>【We recently had the wonderful opportunity to sit with Kaushik Mani and Vijay Nagarajan from the Amazon Key team to learn how they built this system and the challenges they faced.】最近，我们有一个绝佳的机会与亚马逊钥匙团队的Kaushik Mani和Vijay Nagarajan坐在一起，以了解他们如何构建该系统及其面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP165: AI Agent versus MCP】EP165：AI代理与MCP</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep165-ai-agent-versus-mcp</link>
      <description>【Have you used AI Agents or MCP?】您是否使用过AI代理或MCP？</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 15:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP166: What is Event Sourcing? 】EP166：什么是事件采购？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep166-what-is-event-sourcing</link>
      <description>【The event sourcing paradigm is used to design a system with determinism. This changes the philosophy of normal system designs.】事件采购范式用于设计具有决定论的系统。这改变了正常系统设计的理念。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 15:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Our New Book, Mobile System Design Interview, Is Now Available】我们的新书《移动系统设计采访》现已可用</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/our-new-book-mobile-system-design</link>
      <description>【Our new book, Mobile System Design Interview, is available on Amazon!】我们的新书《移动系统设计采访》可在亚马逊上获得！</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Lyft Uses ML to Make 100 Million Predictions A Day】Lyft如何使用ML每天做出1亿个预测</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-lyft-uses-ml-to-make-100-million</link>
      <description>【In this article, we&amp;#8217;ll look at how Lyft built an architecture to accomplish this requirement and the challenges they faced.】在本文中，我们将研究Lyft如何构建建筑以完成这一要求及其面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 15:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Netflix Runs on Java?】Netflix如何在Java上运行？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-netflix-runs-on-java</link>
      <description>【Netflix is a masterclass in backend engineering at scale. Behind the seamless playback, tailored recommendations, and cross-device consistency lies an intricate architecture powered by Java.】Netflix是大规模后端工程的大师班。在无缝的播放，量身定制的建议和跨设备一致性的背后是由Java提供动力的复杂建筑。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shopify Tech Stack】Shopify Tech堆栈</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/shopify-tech-stack</link>
      <description>【Note: This article is written in collaboration with the Shopify engineering team.】注意：本文是与Shopify工程团队合作编写的。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>