<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【EP192: What is a REST API?】EP192：什么是 REST API？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep192-what-is-a-rest-api</link>
      <description>【REST (Representational State Transfer) is an architectural style for building APIs that use HTTP for communication. To be considered RESTful, an API should follow six key constraints:】REST（表述性状态传输）是一种用于构建使用 HTTP 进行通信的 API 的架构风格。要被视为 RESTful，API 应遵循六个关键约束：</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 16:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How DoorDash Moved to a Service Mesh to Handle 80M Requests/Second】DoorDash 如何迁移到服务网格以每秒处理 80M 请求</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-doordash-moved-to-a-service-mesh</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how DoorDash&amp;#8217;s infrastructure team went through this journey and the difficulties they faced.】在本文中，我们将了解 DoorDash 的基础设施团队如何经历这一历程以及他们面临的困难。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Service Mesh Architectural Pattern】服务网格架构模式指南</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-guide-to-service-mesh-architectural</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will explore the reasons behind the existence of service mesh, its inner workings, and how to determine if it is the right tool for our specific needs.】在本文中，我们将探讨服务网格存在背后的原因、其内部工作原理，以及如何确定它是否是满足我们特定需求的正确工具。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Meta Uses AI Agents for Data Warehouse Access and Security】Meta 如何使用 AI 代理实现数据仓库访问和安全</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-meta-uses-ai-agents-for-data</link>
      <description>【In this article, we look at how Meta redesigned their data warehouse architecture to work with both humans and agents.】在本文中，我们将了解 Meta 如何重新设计其数据仓库架构以与人类和代理一起工作。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Netflix Built a Distributed Write Ahead Log For Its Data Platform】Netflix 如何为其数据平台构建分布式预写日志</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-netflix-built-a-distributed-write</link>
      <description>【Netflix&amp;#8217;s engineering team faced several recurring issues that threatened the reliability of their data.】Netflix 的工程团队面临着几个反复出现的问题，这些问题威胁到了他们的数据的可靠性。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How LLMs Learn from the Internet: The Training Process】法学硕士如何从互联网学习：培训过程</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-llms-learn-from-the-internet</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will walk through the complete journey of how LLMs are trained, from the initial collection of raw data to the final conversational assistant.】在本文中，我们将介绍法学硕士的培训完整过程，从最初的原始数据收集到最终的对话助理。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Last Call: All in One Interview Prep Black Friday Sale Ends Today】最后一次通话：一体化面试准备黑色星期五促销今天结束</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/last-call-all-in-one-interview-prep</link>
      <description>【Yearly Black Friday sale Ends Today! Use code BF2025 at checkout to get 30% off the all-in-one interview prep online courses.】一年一度的黑色星期五促销今天结束！结帐时使用代码 BF2025 即可获得一体化面试准备在线课程 30% 的折扣。</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP191: Virtualization vs. Containerization】EP191：虚拟化与容器化</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep191-virtualization-vs-containerization</link>
      <description>【Before containers simplified deployment, virtualization changed how we used hardware. Both isolate workloads, but they do it differently.】在容器简化部署之前，虚拟化改变了我们使用硬件的方式。两者都隔离工作负载，但做法不同。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【⏳ LIMITED TIME OFFER: All in One Interview Prep Black Friday Sale】⏳ 限时优惠：多合一面试准备黑色星期五促销</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/limited-time-offer-all-in-one-interview</link>
      <description>【Yearly Black Friday sale is now live!】一年一度的黑色星期五促销现已开始！</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Saga Pattern Demystified: Orchestration vs Choreography】传奇模式揭秘：编排与编排</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/saga-pattern-demystified-orchestration</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how the Saga pattern works and the pros and cons of various approaches to implement this pattern.】在本文中，我们将了解 Saga 模式的工作原理以及实现该模式的各种方法的优缺点。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>