<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【A Crash Course in Database Scaling Strategies】数据库扩展策略速成班</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-crash-course-in-database-scaling</link>
      <description>【Databases form the backbone of modern application development. They play a vital role in storing, managing, and retrieving data, enabling applications and services to function effectively. As applications gain popularity and attract a growing user base, databases face the challenge of handling ever-increasing data volumes, concurrent users, and complex queries.】数据库构成了现代应用程序开发的支柱。它们在存储、管理和检索数据、使应用程序和服务有效运行方面发挥着至关重要的作用。随着应用程序越来越受欢迎并吸引不断增长的用户群，数据库面临着处理不断增加的数据量、并发用户和复杂查询的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Stripe Scaled to 5 Million Database Queries Per Second】Stripe 如何扩展到每秒 500 万次数据库查询</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-stripe-scaled-to-5-million-database</link>
      <description>【WorkOS: modern identity platform for B2B SaaS (Sponsored) Start selling to enterprises with just a few lines of code. &amp;#8594; WorkOS provides a complete User Management solution along with SSO, SCIM, RBAC, &amp; FGA. &amp;#8594; Unlike other auth providers that rely on user-centric models, WorkOS is designed for B2B SaaS with an org modeling approach.】WorkOS：B2B SaaS 的现代身份平台（赞助）只需几行代码即可开始向企业销售。 → WorkOS 提供完整的用户管理解决方案以及 SSO、SCIM、RBAC 和 FGA。 → 与其他依赖以用户为中心的模型的身份验证提供商不同，WorkOS 专为采用组织建模方法的 B2B SaaS 设计。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP122: API Gateway 101 】EP122：API网关101</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep122-api-gateway-101</link>
      <description>【This week&amp;#8217;s system design refresher:】本周的系统设计复习：</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP120: What do version numbers mean? 】EP120：版本号是什么意思？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep120-what-do-version-numbers-mean</link>
      <description>【This week&amp;#8217;s system design refresher: Concurrency Vs Parallelism! (Youtube video) What do version numbers mean? Looking for a Job? This Free AI Tool Can Get You More Interviews! Cybersecurity 101 in one picture What is k8s (Kubernetes)? SPONSOR US &amp;#9986;&amp;#65039;Cut your QA cycles down to minutes with automated testing (Sponsored)】本周的系统设计复习：并发与并行！ （Youtube 视频）版本号是什么意思？正在找工作吗？这个免费的人工智能工具可以让你获得更多面试机会！一张图片中的网络安全 101 什么是 k8s (Kubernetes)？赞助我们✂️通过自动化测试将您的 QA 周期缩短至几分钟（赞助）</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 15:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Crash Course on Distributed Systems】分布式系统速成班</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-crash-course-on-distributed-systems</link>
      <description>【A distributed system is a collection of computers, also known as nodes, that collaborate to perform a specific task or provide a service. These nodes are physically separate and communicate with each other by passing messages over a network. Distributed systems can span geographical boundaries, enabling them to utilize resources from different locations.】分布式系统是计算机（也称为节点）的集合，它们协作执行特定任务或提供服务。这些节点在物理上是独立的，并通过网络传递消息来相互通信。分布式系统可以跨越地理边界，使它们能够利用不同位置的资源。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 15:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP119: What do Amazon, Netflix, and Uber have in common?】EP119：亚马逊、Netflix 和 Uber 有什么共同点？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep119-what-do-amazon-netflix-and</link>
      <description>【This week&amp;#8217;s system design refresher: 7 Must-know Strategies to Scale Your Database (Youtube video) What do Amazon, Netflix, and Uber have in common? 100X Postgres Scaling at Figma Best ways to test system functionality SPONSOR US Monitor AI Applications Built with NVIDIA NIM (Sponsored)】本周的系统设计复习：扩展数据库的 7 个必须了解的策略（Youtube 视频）Amazon、Netflix 和 Uber 有什么共同点？ Figma 的 100 倍 Postgres 扩展 测试系统功能的最佳方法 赞助使用 NVIDIA NIM 构建的 US Monitor AI 应用程序（赞助）</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Crash Course on Relational Database Design】关系数据库设计速成班</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-crash-course-on-relational-database</link>
      <description>【In today&#39;s data-driven world, efficient storage and management of information are critical requirements for businesses and organizations of all sizes.】在当今数据驱动的世界中，高效的信息存储和管理是各种规模的企业和组织的关键要求。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 15:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP121: 9 Essential Components of a Production Microservice Application 】EP121：生产微服务应用程序的 9 个基本组件</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep121-9-essential-components-of-a</link>
      <description>【This week&amp;#8217;s system design interview: Linux Crash Course - Understanding File Permissions (Youtube video) 9 Essential Components of a Production Microservice Application Iterative, Agile, Waterfall, Spiral Model, RAD Model... What are the differences?】本周的系统设计面试：Linux速成课程 - 了解文件权限（Youtube视频） 生产微服务应用程序的9个基本组件迭代、敏捷、瀑布、螺旋模型、RAD模型......有什么区别？</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Where to get started with GenAI】从哪里开始使用 GenAI</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/where-to-get-started-with-genai</link>
      <description>【How to monitor AWS container environments at scale (Sponsored) In this eBook, Datadog and AWS share insights into the changing state of containers in the cloud and explore why orchestration technologies are an essential part of managing ever-changing containerized workloads.】如何大规模监控 AWS 容器环境（赞助）在这本电子书中，Datadog 和 AWS 分享了对云中容器不断变化的状态的见解，并探讨了为什么编排技术是管理不断变化的容器化工作负载的重要组成部分。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【&#34;Tidying&#34; Code】“整理”代码</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/tidying-code</link>
      <description>【I&amp;#8217;ve found my new favorite book on refactoring code.】我找到了我最喜欢的关于重构代码的新书。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>