<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Service-to-Service Communication Patterns】最重要的服务间通信模式</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/top-service-to-service-communication</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at the key service-to-service communication patterns along with their advantages and disadvantages.】在本文中，我们将研究关键的服务间通信模式及其优点和缺点。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 04:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What are AI Agents?】什么是人工智能代理？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/what-are-ai-agents</link>
      <description>【In this article, we&amp;#8217;ll explore what AI agents really are, understand the key characteristics that define them, and examine the different types of agents ranging from simple to sophisticated.】在本文中，我们将探讨人工智能代理的真正含义，了解定义它们的关键特征，并研究从简单到复杂的不同类型的代理。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 15:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Evolution of LinkedIn’s Generative AI Tech Stack】LinkedIn 生成式 AI 技术堆栈的演变</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/the-evolution-of-linkedins-generative</link>
      <description>【We&amp;#8217;ll explore how they transitioned from early feature experiments to a robust GenAI platform, and eventually to multi-agent systems capable of reasoning, planning, and collaborating at scale.】我们将探讨它们如何从早期的特征实验过渡到强大的 GenAI 平台，并最终过渡到能够大规模推理、规划和协作的多智能体系统。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Nubank Built an In-house Logging Platform for 1 Trillion Log Entries】Nubank 如何为 1 万亿条日志条目构建内部日志平台</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-nubank-built-an-in-house-logging</link>
      <description>【When a company grows rapidly, its technical systems are often pushed to their limits.】当一家公司快速发展时，其技术系统往往会被推到极限。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP186: Latency vs. Throughput】EP186：延迟与吞吐量</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep186-latency-vs-throughput</link>
      <description>【Ever wondered why your app feels slow even when the bandwidth looks fine? Latency and throughput explain two very different stories of performance.】有没有想过为什么即使带宽看起来不错，您的应用程序仍然感觉很慢？延迟和吞吐量解释了两种截然不同的性能故事。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【API Gateways 101: The Core of Modern API Management &amp; Security】API 网关 101：现代 API 管理和安全的核心</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/api-gateways-101-the-core-of-modern</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at API gateways in detail, along with their architecture and features.】在本文中，我们将详细介绍 API 网关及其架构和功能。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Memory Problem: Why LLMs Sometimes Forget Your Conversation】记忆问题：为什么法学硕士有时会忘记你的谈话</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/the-memory-problem-why-llms-sometimes</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will try to understand why LLMs don&amp;#8217;t actually remember anything in the traditional sense, what context windows are, and why they create hard limits on conversation length.】在本文中，我们将尝试理解为什么法学硕士实际上不记得传统意义上的任何东西，上下文窗口是什么，以及为什么它们对对话长度设置硬性限制。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Pinterest Transfers Hundreds of Terabytes of Data With CDC】Pinterest 如何通过 CDC 传输数百 TB 的数据</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-pinterest-transfers-hundreds</link>
      <description>【Instead of building isolated solutions for each use case, Pinterest created a unified architecture that can support the entire company&amp;#8217;s data needs.】Pinterest 没有为每个用例构建独立的解决方案，而是创建了一个可以支持整个公司数据需求的统一架构。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 15:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What Actually Happens When You Press ‘Send’ to ChatGPT】当您按“发送”至 ChatGPT 时实际会发生什么</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/what-actually-happens-when-you-press</link>
      <description>【Behind this simple interface lies a powerful set of technologies.】这个简单的界面背后隐藏着一组强大的技术。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 17:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP185: Docker vs Kubernetes】EP185：Docker 与 Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep185-docker-vs-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【Docker is a container platform that lets you package applications with their dependencies and run them on a single machine. Here&amp;#8217;s how it works】Docker 是一个容器平台，可让您将应用程序及其依赖项打包并在单台计算机上运行它们。这是它的工作原理</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>