<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【How Zalando Delivers Real-Time Insights to Its Partners Brands】Zalando 如何为其合作伙伴品牌提供实时洞察</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-zalando-delivers-real-time-insights</link>
      <description>【Zalando&amp;#8217;s Partner Tech division, responsible for data sharing and collaboration with partners, found itself managing a fragmented and inefficient process.】Zalando 的合作伙伴技术部门负责与合作伙伴的数据共享和协作，但发现自己管理着一个分散且低效的流程。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP190: Cloudflare vs. AWS vs. Azure】EP190：Cloudflare 与 AWS 与 Azure</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep190-cloudflare-vs-aws-vs-azure</link>
      <description>【Cloudflare is much more than just a CDN and DDoS protection service. Let&amp;#8217;s do a quick comparison of Cloudflare, AWS, and Azure.】Cloudflare 不仅仅是 CDN 和 DDoS 保护服务。让我们快速比较一下 Cloudflare、AWS 和 Azure。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 16:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Strategies to Build High Availability Systems】构建高可用性系统的最佳策略</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/top-strategies-to-build-high-availability</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will understand what availability means and look at some of the most popular strategies to achieve high availability.】在本文中，我们将了解可用性的含义，并了解一些最流行的实现高可用性的策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Disney Hotstar (now JioHotstar) Scaled Its Infra for 60 Million Concurrent Users】Disney Hotstar（现为 JioHotstar）如何为 6000 万并发用户扩展基础设施</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-disney-hotstar-now-jiohotstar</link>
      <description>【In this article, we look at how the Disney+ Hotstar engineering team achieved that scale and the challenges they faced.】在本文中，我们将了解 Disney+ Hotstar 工程团队如何实现这一规模以及他们面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Grab Built an AI Foundation Model To Understand Customers Better】Grab 如何构建 AI 基础模型以更好地了解客户</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-grab-built-an-ai-foundation-model</link>
      <description>【In this article, we look at how Grab developed this foundational model and the challenges it faced.】在本文中，我们将了解 Grab 如何开发这一基础模型及其面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP189: How to Design Good APIs】EP189：如何设计好的 API</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep189-how-to-design-good-apis</link>
      <description>【A well-designed API feels invisible, it just works. Behind that simplicity lies a set of consistent design principles that make APIs predictable, secure, and scalable.】设计良好的 API 让人感觉看不见，但它确实有效。这种简单性背后隐藏着一组一致的设计原则，使 API 具有可预测性、安全性和可扩展性。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 16:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scalability Patterns for Modern Distributed Systems】现代分布式系统的可扩展性模式</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/scalability-patterns-for-modern-distributed</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at the top scalability patterns and their pros and cons.】在本文中，我们将了解最重要的可扩展性模式及其优缺点。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Tinder Decomposed Its iOS Monolith App Handling 70M Users】Tinder 如何分解其处理 7000 万用户的 iOS 整体应用程序</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-tinder-decomposed-its-ios-monolith</link>
      <description>【In Tinder&amp;#8217;s case, deep inter-dependencies between those targets stretched what engineers call the critical path, which is the longest chain of dependent tasks that determines how long a build takes.】在 Tinder 的案例中，这些目标之间的深层相互依赖性延伸了工程师所说的关键路径，这是决定构建需要多长时间的最长的依赖任务链。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Spotify Built Its Data Platform To Understand 1.4 Trillion Data Points】Spotify 如何构建其数据平台来理解 1.4 万亿个数据点</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-spotify-built-its-data-platform</link>
      <description>【This evolution happened organically as Spotify&amp;#8217;s products matured. With each new feature and business need, new data requirements emerged.】随着 Spotify 产品的成熟，这种演变自然发生。随着每一个新功能和业务需求的出现，新的数据需求也随之出现。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Uber Built a Conversational AI Agent For Financial Analysis】Uber 如何构建用于财务分析的对话式人工智能代理</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-uber-built-a-conversational-ai</link>
      <description>【Finch is designed to bring financial intelligence directly into Slack, the communication platform already used by the company&amp;#8217;s teams.】Finch 旨在将金融情报直接引入 Slack（该公司团队已经使用的通信平台）。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>