<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【How WhatsApp Handles 40 Billion Messages Per Day】WhatsApp每天如何处理400亿条消息</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-whatsapp-handles-40-billion-messages</link>
      <description>【In this article, we&amp;#8217;ll take a technical dive into how WhatsApp built its architecture and the challenges the engineering team faced during this journey.】在本文中，我们将研究WhatsApp如何构建其架构以及工程团队在此旅程中面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 15:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Canva Collects 25 Billion Events a Day】帆布如何每天收集250亿个活动</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-canva-collects-25-billion-events</link>
      <description>【This article walks through how Canva structures, collects, and distributes billions of events daily, without drowning in tech debt and increasing cloud bills.】本文介绍了每天如何收集和分发数十亿个事件，而不会淹没技术债务并增加云账单。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP162: 9 Clean Code Principles To Keep In Mind】EP162：9牢记的清洁代码原则</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep162-9-clean-code-principles-to</link>
      <description>【Meaningful Names: Name variables and functions to reveal their purpose, not just their value.】有意义的名称：名称变量和功能以揭示其目的，而不仅仅是其价值。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Halo on Xbox Scaled to 10+ Million Players using the Saga Pattern】Xbox上的光环如何使用SAGA图案缩放到100多百万球员</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-halo-on-xbox-scaled-to-10-million</link>
      <description>【One powerful pattern for solving this problem is the Saga Pattern, a technique originally proposed in the late 1980s but increasingly relevant today.】解决此问题的一种强大模式是传奇模式，这是一种最初提出的技术，最初是在1980年代后期提出的，但今天越来越重要。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Slack Supports Billions of Daily Messages】Slack如何支持数十亿美元的每日消息</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-slack-supports-billions-of-daily</link>
      <description>【At peak weekday hours, Slack maintains over five million simultaneous WebSocket sessions. That&amp;#8217;s not just a metric, but a serious architectural challenge.】在工作日高峰时段，Slack可以同时维持超过500万个Websocket会议。这不仅是一个指标，而且是一个严重的建筑挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Synchronous vs Asynchronous Communication: When to Use What?】同步与异步通信：何时使用什么？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/synchronous-vs-asynchronous-communication</link>
      <description>【At some point, every system has to make a call: Should this interaction happen synchronously or asynchronously?】在某个时候，每个系统都必须呼叫：这种交互是否应该同步或异步发生？</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Meta Built Threads to Support 100 Million Signups in 5 Days】元如何在5天内建立线程以支持1亿个注册</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-meta-built-threads-to-support</link>
      <description>【When a new app hits 100 million signups in under a week, the instinct is to assume someone built a miracle backend overnight.】当一个新应用在一周不到一周的时间内登陆1亿个注册时，本能是假设有人在一夜之间建立了一个奇迹的后端。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Messaging Patterns Explained: Pub-Sub, Queues, and Event Streams】消息传递模式解释了：Pub-Sub，队列和事件流</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/messaging-patterns-explained-pub</link>
      <description>【What happens when the downstream service is overloaded? Or slow? Or down entirely?】下游服务超载时会发生什么？还是慢？还是完全下降？</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Engineering Trade-offs: Eventual Consistency in Practice】工程权衡：实践中最终的一致性</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-guide-to-eventual-consistency-in</link>
      <description>【Modern applications don&amp;#8217;t run on a single database or monolithic backend anymore. They run on event-driven, distributed systems.】现代应用程序不再在单个数据库或整体后端运行。他们在事件驱动的分布式系统上运行。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 15:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP161: A Cheatsheet on REST API Design Best Practices】EP161：关于REST API设计最佳实践的备忘单</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep161-a-cheatsheet-on-rest-api-design</link>
      <description>【Well-designed APIs behave consistently, fair predictably, and grow without friction.】精心设计的API的行为始终如一，可以预见，并且没有摩擦。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 15:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>