<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Strategies to Improve Reliability in Distributed Systems】提高分布式系统可靠性的最佳策略</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/top-strategies-to-improve-reliability</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will take a closer look at strategies that can help improve the reliability of a system.】在本文中，我们将仔细研究可以帮助提高系统可靠性的策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Reddit Delivers Notifications to Tens of Millions of Users】Reddit如何向数千万用户提供通知</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-reddit-delivers-notifications</link>
      <description>【Push notifications carry a double-edged sword in the design of any product. Done well, these notifications reconnect users with content they care about.】推送通知在任何产品的设计中都带有双刃剑。做得很好，这些通知将用户与他们关心的内容重新连接。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How LLMs See Images, Audio, and More】LLM如何查看图像，音频等</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-llms-see-images-audio-and-more</link>
      <description>【Just like how &#34;Hello world!&#34; becomes discrete tokens for text processing, a photograph gets chopped into image patches, and a song becomes a sequence of audio codes.】就像“你好世界”如何！成为用于文本处理的离散令牌，将照片切成图像贴片，歌曲成为一系列音频代码。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP176: How Does SSO Work?】EP176：SSO如何工作？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep176-how-does-sso-work</link>
      <description>【Single Sign-On (SSO) is an authentication scheme. It allows a user to log in to different systems using a single ID.】单登录（SSO）是一种身份验证方案。它允许用户使用单个ID登录到不同的系统。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Top Caching Strategies】顶级缓存策略指南</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-guide-to-top-caching-strategies</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will explore the critical caching strategies that enable fast, reliable systems.】在本文中，我们将探讨能够快速，可靠系统的关键缓存策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Atlassian Migrated 4 Million Jira Databases to AWS Aurora】Atlassian如何将400万JIRA数据库迁移到AWS Aurora</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-atlassian-migrated-4-million</link>
      <description>【Atlassian routinely migrates about 1,000 databases every day as part of its regular operations, and its users never notice.】作为常规操作的一部分，Atlassian通常每天迁移约1,000个数据库，其用户从未注意到。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP175: What is the SOLID Principle?】EP175：坚实的原理是什么？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep175-what-is-the-solid-principle</link>
      <description>【SOLID offers guidelines to create software that is easy to understand, modify, and extend.】SOLID提供指南，以创建易于理解，修改和扩展的软件。</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Scalability Strategies for Real-World Load】现实负载的最高可扩展性策略</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/top-scalability-strategies-for-real</link>
      <description>【In modern distributed systems, scalability is not a nice-to-have. Whether serving a global user base or responding to a viral spike, systems that fail to scale often fail outright.】在现代分布式系统中，可伸缩性不是一个不错的选择。无论是服务全球用户群还是响应病毒峰值，无法扩展的系统通常会完全失败。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Uber Eats Deduplicates Hundreds of Millions of Product Images】Uber如何吃掉数亿个产品图像</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-uber-eats-deduplicates-hundreds</link>
      <description>【At the scale of Uber Eats, image handling is an operational necessity. The platform manages hundreds of millions of product images, with millions of updates flowing through the system every hour.】在Uber Eats的规模上，图像处理是一种操作的必要性。该平台管理数亿个产品图像，每小时会有数百万个更新遍布系统。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How LLMs See the World】LLM如何看世界</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-llms-see-the-world</link>
      <description>【Tokens are what rule the world of LLMs. You send tokens to models, you pay by the token, and models read, understand, and breathe tokens.】令牌是统治LLM的世界。您将令牌发送到模型，由代币付款，模型读取，理解和呼吸令牌。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>