<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ByteByteGo Newsletter</title>
    <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/feed</link>
    <description>Explain complex systems with simple terms, from the authors of the best-selling system design book series. Join over 1,000,000 friendly readers.</description>
    <managingEditor>alex@bytebytego.com</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【EP198: Best Resources to Learn AI in 2026】EP198：2026 年学习人工智能的最佳资源</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep198-best-resources-to-learn-ai</link>
      <description>【The AI resources can be divided into different types such as】AI资源可以分为不同类型，例如</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Last Call: Enrollment for the AI Engineering Cohort 3 Ends Today】最后通知：人工智能工程第三期的报名今天结束</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/last-call-enrollment-for-the-ai-engineering-f1a</link>
      <description>【Our third cohort of Becoming an AI Engineer starts in one day. This is a live, cohort-based course created in collaboration with best-selling author Ali Aminian and published by ByteByteGo.】我们的第三批“成为人工智能工程师”课程将在一天后开始。这是一门基于队列的实时课程，由 ByteByteGo 与畅销书作家 Ali Aminian 合作创建。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Database Sharding】数据库分片指南</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/must-know-message-broker-patterns-4c4</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will learn about database sharding in more detail. We will understand what it is, why it matters, how different approaches work, and what key considerations are important when implementing it.】在本文中，我们将更详细地了解数据库分片。我们将了解它是什么、为什么它很重要、不同的方法如何运作以及实施它时需要考虑哪些关键因素。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Uber Serves over 150 Million Reads per Second from Integrated Cache】Uber 如何通过集成缓存提供每秒超过 1.5 亿次的读取</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-uber-serves-over-150-million</link>
      <description>【In this article, we break down how Uber built this system, the challenges they faced, and the innovative solutions they developed.】在本文中，我们将详细介绍 Uber 如何构建该系统、他们面临的挑战以及他们开发的创新解决方案。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Lyft Built an ML Platform That Serves Millions of Predictions Per Second】Lyft 如何构建每秒可提供数百万次预测的机器学习平台</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-lyft-built-an-ml-platform-that</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how Lyft built this platform and the architecture behind it.】在本文中，我们将了解 Lyft 如何构建这个平台及其背后的架构。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to LLM Evals】LLM 评估指南</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/a-guide-to-llm-evals</link>
      <description>【In this article, we&amp;#8217;ll explore why LLM evaluation is challenging, the different types of evaluations available, key concepts to understand, and practical guidance on setting up an evaluation process.】在本文中，我们将探讨为什么法学硕士评估具有挑战性、可用的不同类型的评估、需要理解的关键概念以及建立评估流程的实用指南。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EP197: 12 Architectural Concepts Developers Should Know】EP197：开发人员应该了解的 12 个架构概念</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/ep197-12-architectural-concepts-developers</link>
      <description>【Which architectural concept will you add to the list?】您会将哪种建筑概念添加到列表中？</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Must-Know Message Broker Patterns】必须了解的消息代理模式</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/must-know-message-broker-patterns</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at each of these patterns in detail and understand the scenarios where they help the most.】在本文中，我们将详细研究每种模式并了解它们最有帮助的场景。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How AI Transformed Database Debugging at Databricks】AI 如何改变 Databricks 的数据库调试</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-ai-transformed-database-debugging</link>
      <description>【In this article, we will look at how the Databricks engineering team built this platform and the challenges faced along the way.】在本文中，我们将了解 Databricks 工程团队如何构建这个平台以及在此过程中面临的挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Google’s Tensor Processing Unit (TPU) Works?】谷歌的张量处理单元（TPU）是如何工作的？</title>
      <link>https://blog.bytebytego.com/p/how-googles-tensor-processing-unit</link>
      <description>【In this article, we look at why Google built custom silicon, and how it works, revealing the physical constraints and engineering trade-offs they had to make.】在本文中，我们将探讨谷歌为何构建定制芯片及其工作原理，揭示他们必须做出的物理限制和工程权衡。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>