<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Performance measurements… and the people who love them】绩效测量…和爱他们的人</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/loving-performance-measurements/</link>
      <description>【 Developers have a gut-felt understanding for performance, but that intuition breaks down when systems reach Cloudflare’s scale. 】开发人员对性能有肠道的了解，但是当系统达到Cloudflare的规模时，直觉会破裂。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Forget IPs: using cryptography to verify bot and agent traffic】忘记IPS：使用密码学验证机器人和代理流量</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/web-bot-auth/</link>
      <description>【 Bots now browse like humans. We&#39;re proposing bots use cryptographic signatures so that website owners can verify their identity. Explanations and demonstration code can be found within the post. 】机器人现在像人类一样浏览。我们正在提议使用加密签名，以便网站所有者可以验证其身份。可以在帖子中找到说明和演示代码。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bringing streamable HTTP transport and Python language support to MCP servers】将流媒体的HTTP传输和Python语言支持带到MCP服务器</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/streamable-http-mcp-servers-python/</link>
      <description>【 We&#39;re continuing to make it easier for developers to bring their services into the AI ecosystem with the Model Context Protocol (MCP) with two new updates. 】我们将继续通过模型上下文协议（MCP）进行两个新更新，使开发人员更容易将他们的服务带入AI生态系统。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling with safety: Cloudflare&#39;s approach to global service health metrics and software releases】安全扩展：CloudFlare的全球服务健康指标和软件发布方法</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/safe-change-at-any-scale/</link>
      <description>【 Learn how Cloudflare tackles the challenge of scaling global service health metrics to safely release new software across our global network. 】了解CloudFlare如何应对扩展全球服务健康指标的挑战，以在我们的全球网络上安全发布新软件。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Your IPs, your rules: enabling more efficient address space usage】您的IPS，您的规则：启用更有效的地址空间使用情况</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/your-ips-your-rules-enabling-more-efficient-address-space-usage/</link>
      <description>【 IPv4 is expensive, and moving network resources around is hard. Previously, when customers wanted to use multiple Cloudflare services, they had to bring a new address range. 】IPv4很昂贵，而移动网络资源很难。以前，当客户想使用多个CloudFlare服务时，他们必须带来一个新的地址范围。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【First-party tags in seconds: Cloudflare integrates Google tag gateway for advertisers 】秒内的第一方标签：CloudFlare集成了广告客户的Google标签网关</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/google-tag-gateway-for-advertisers/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare introduces a one-click integration with Google tag gateway for advertisers. 】CloudFlare与Google Tag Gateway为广告客户提供了一键集成。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MCP Demo Day: How 10 leading AI companies built MCP servers on Cloudflare】MCP演示日：有10家领先的AI公司如何在Cloudflare上构建MCP服务器</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/mcp-demo-day/</link>
      <description>【 We’re teaming up with Anthropic, Asana, Atlassian, Block, Intercom, Linear, PayPal, Sentry, Stripe, and Webflow to launch new remote MCP servers, built on Cloudflare, to enable Claude users to manage 】我们正在与拟人，Asana，Atlassian，Block，Intercom，Linear，Paypal，Sentry，Stripe和WebFlow合作，以启动基于CloudFlare的新远程MCP服务器，以使Claude用户能够管理</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thirteen new MCP servers from Cloudflare you can use today】CloudFlare的13台新的MCP服务器，您今天可以使用</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/thirteen-new-mcp-servers-from-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 You can now connect to Cloudflare&#39;s first publicly available remote Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers from any MCP client that supports remote servers.  】现在，您可以从任何支持远程服务器的MCP客户端中连接到CloudFlare的第一个公开可用的远程模型上下文协议（MCP）服务器。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【QUIC restarts, slow problems: udpgrm to the rescue】Quic重新开始，缓慢的问题：UDPGRM进行营救</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/quic-restarts-slow-problems-udpgrm-to-the-rescue/</link>
      <description>【 udpgrm is a lightweight daemon for graceful restarts of UDP servers. It leverages SO_REUSEPORT and eBPF to route new and existing flows to the correct server instance. 】UDPGRM是一个轻巧的守护程序，用于优雅的UDP服务器。它利用SO_REUSEPORT和EBPF将新的和现有的流程路由到正确的服务器实例。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Vulnerability transparency: strengthening security through responsible disclosure】脆弱性透明度：通过负责任的披露加强安全性</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/vulnerability-transparency-strengthening-security-through-responsible/</link>
      <description>【 In line with CISA’s Secure By Design pledge, Cloudflare shares its vulnerability disclosure process, CVE issuance criteria, and CNA duties.  】根据CISA的设计承诺，CloudFlare共享其脆弱性披露过程，CVE发行标准和CNA职责。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>