<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare incident on September 17, 2024】2024 年 9 月 17 日的 Cloudflare 事件</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-incident-on-september-17-2024</link>
      <description>【 On September 17, 2024, during planned routine maintenance, Cloudflare stopped announcing 15 IPv4 prefixes, affecting some Business plan websites for approximately one hour. During this time, IPv4 traffic for these customers would not have reached Cloudflare and users attempting to connect to websites using addresses within those prefixes would have received errors.  】2024 年 9 月 17 日，在计划的例行维护期间，Cloudflare 停止公布 15 个 IPv4 前缀，影响了一些商业计划网站约一小时。在此期间，这些客户的 IPv4 流量不会到达 Cloudflare，并且尝试使用这些前缀内的地址连接到网站的用户将会收到错误。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bringing insights into TCP resets and timeouts to Cloudflare Radar】将 TCP 重置和超时的见解引入 Cloudflare Radar</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/tcp-resets-timeouts</link>
      <description>【 New TCP resets and timeouts dataset on Cloudflare Radar surfaces connection tampering, scanning, DoS attacks, and more. 】Cloudflare Radar 上的新 TCP 重置和超时数据集揭示了连接篡改、扫描、DoS 攻击等。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A good day to trie-hard: saving compute 1% at a time】努力的一天：一次节省 1% 的计算量</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/pingora-saving-compute-1-percent-at-a-time</link>
      <description>【 Pingora handles 35M+ requests per second, so saving a few microseconds per request can translate to thousands of dollars saved on computing costs. In this post, we share how we freed up over 500 CPU cores by optimizing one function and announce trie-hard, the open source crate that we created to do it. 】Pingora 每秒处理超过 3500 万个请求，因此每个请求节省几微秒可以转化为节省数千美元的计算成本。在这篇文章中，我们分享了如何通过优化一项功能来释放 500 多个 CPU 核心，并宣布了 trie-hard，这是我们为此创建的开源包。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Removing uncertainty through &#34;what-if&#34; capacity planning】通过“假设”容量规划消除不确定性</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/scenario-planner</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare’s Capacity Planning team discusses planning for “what-if” type scenarios, and how they’ve introduced a new “Scenario Planner” system to quickly model hypothetical future changes 】Cloudflare 的容量规划团队讨论了“假设”类型场景的规划，以及他们如何引入新的“场景规划器”系统来快速对假设的未来变化进行建模</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How the Harris-Trump US presidential debate influenced Internet traffic】哈里斯与特朗普美国总统辩论如何影响互联网流量</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-the-harris-trump-us-presidential-debate-influenced-internet-traffic</link>
      <description>【 See how the first 2024 US presidential debate between Kamala Harris and Donald Trump influenced Internet traffic patterns compared to the Biden-Trump debate. We also review email trends and observed attack activity. 】了解卡马拉·哈里斯 (Kamala Harris) 和唐纳德·特朗普 (Donald Trump) 之间的 2024 年首场美国总统辩论与拜登 (Biden) 和特朗普 (Donald Trump) 的辩论相比如何影响互联网流量模式。我们还审查电子邮件趋势并观察攻击活动。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Cloudflare is helping domain owners with the upcoming Entrust CA distrust by Chrome and Mozilla】Cloudflare 如何帮助域名所有者应对 Chrome 和 Mozilla 即将推出的 Entrust CA 不信任问题</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-cloudflare-is-helping-domain-owners-with-the-upcoming-entrust-ca</link>
      <description>【 Chrome and Mozilla will stop trusting Entrust’s public TLS certificates issued after November 2024 due to concerns about Entrust’s compliance with security standards. In response, Entrust is partnering with SSL.com to continue providing trusted certificates. Cloudflare will support SSL.com as a CA, simplifying certificate management for customers using Entrust by automating issuance and renewals. 】由于担心 Entrust 遵守安全标准，Chrome 和 Mozilla 将停止信任 Entrust 在 2024 年 11 月之后颁发的公共 TLS 证书。作为回应，Entrust 正在与 SSL.com 合作，继续提供可信证书。 Cloudflare 将支持 SSL.com 作为 CA，通过自动颁发和续订来简化使用 Entrust 的客户的证书管理。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【More NPM packages on Cloudflare Workers: Combining polyfills and native code to support Node.js APIs】Cloudflare Workers 上的更多 NPM 包：结合 polyfill 和本机代码来支持 Node.js API</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/more-npm-packages-on-cloudflare-workers-combining-polyfills-and-native-code</link>
      <description>【 Workers now supports more NPM packages and Node.js APIs using an overhauled hybrid compatibility layer. 】Workers 现在使用经过彻底修改的混合兼容性层支持更多 NPM 包和 Node.js API。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A global assessment of third-party connection tampering】对第三方连接篡改的全球评估</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/connection-tampering</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare brings visibility to the practice of connection tampering as observed from our global network. 】Cloudflare 使我们能够了解从我们的全球网络观察到的连接篡改行为。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customers get increased integration with Cloudflare Email Security and Zero Trust through expanded partnership with CrowdStrike】通过与 CrowdStrike 扩大合作伙伴关系，客户可以增强与 Cloudflare Email Security 和零信任的集成</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/customers-get-increased-integration-with-cloudflare-email-security-and-zero-trust</link>
      <description>【 This post explains how our integrations with CrowdStrike Falcon® Next-Gen SIEM allow customers to identify and investigate risky user behavior and analyze data combined with other log sources to uncover hidden threats. 】这篇文章解释了我们与 CrowdStrike Falcon® 下一代 SIEM 的集成如何帮助客户识别和调查有风险的用户行为，并结合其他日志源分析数据以发现隐藏的威胁。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Protecting APIs from abuse using sequence learning and variable order Markov chains】使用序列学习和可变阶马尔可夫链保护 API 免遭滥用</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/protecting-apis-from-abuse-using-sequence-learning-and-variable-order-markov</link>
      <description>【 At Cloudflare, we protect customer APIs from abuse. This is no easy task, as abusive traffic can take different forms, from giant DDoS attacks to low-and-slow credential stuffing campaigns. We now address this challenge in a new way: by looking outside typical volumetric measures and using statistical machine learning to find important API client request sequences. 】在 Cloudflare，我们保护客户 API 免遭滥用。这不是一件容易的事，因为滥用流量可以采取不同的形式，从巨大的 DDoS 攻击到低而缓慢的撞库活动。我们现在以一种新的方式应对这一挑战：通过观察典型的体积测量并使用统计机器学习来查找重要的 API 客户端请求序列。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>