<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【The tricky science of Internet measurement】互联网测量的棘手科学</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/tricky-internet-measurement/</link>
      <description>【 The Internet is one big open system composed of many closed boxes — which makes measuring the Internet difficult. In this post we explore Internet measurement as a science. 】互联网是一个由许多封闭盒子组成的大型开放系统，这使得衡量互联网变得困难。在这篇文章中，我们将互联网测量作为一门科学进行探索。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Making the Internet observable: the evolution of Cloudflare Radar】让互联网变得可观察：Cloudflare Radar 的演变</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/evolution-of-cloudflare-radar/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Radar has evolved significantly since its 2020 launch, offering deeper insights into Internet security, routing, and traffic with new tools and data that help anyone understand what&#39;s happening online. 】自 2020 年推出以来，Cloudflare Radar 已取得显着发展，通过新工具和数据提供对互联网安全、路由和流量的更深入见解，帮助任何人了解在线情况。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From .com to .anything: introducing Top-Level Domain (TLD) insights on Cloudflare Radar】从 .com 到 .anything：介绍有关 Cloudflare Radar 的顶级域名 (TLD) 见解</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-tld-insights-on-cloudflare-radar/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Radar has launched a new Top-Level Domain (TLD) page, providing insights into TLD popularity, traffic, and security. The top-ranking TLD may come as a surprise. 】Cloudflare Radar 推出了新的顶级域名 (TLD) 页面，提供有关 TLD 受欢迎程度、流量和安全性的见解。排名最高的 TLD 可能会让人感到意外。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Internet measurement, resilience, and transparency: blog takeover from Cloudflare Research and friends】互联网衡量、弹性和透明度：Cloudflare Research 及其朋友接管博客</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/internet-measurement-resilience-transparency-week/</link>
      <description>【 Coinciding with the ACM’s Internet Measurement Conference, the Cloudflare Research team is publishing a series of posts this week to share their research on building a more measurable, resilient, and transparent Internet. These posts will cover foundational concepts in Internet measurement, Internet resilience, cryptography, and networking.  】与 ACM 互联网测量会议同期，Cloudflare 研究团队本周发布了一系列帖子，分享他们关于构建更可测量、更有弹性和更透明的互联网的研究。这些帖子将涵盖互联网测量、互联网弹性、密码学​​和网络的基本概念。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How does Cloudflare’s Speed Test really work?】Cloudflare 的速度测试到底如何运作？</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-does-cloudflares-speed-test-really-work/</link>
      <description>【 In this blog post we’ll discuss how Cloudflare thinks about measuring Internet quality, how our own Cloudflare speed test works, and our future plans for providing Internet measurement tools that help everyone build a better Internet. 】在这篇博文中，我们将讨论 Cloudflare 如何考虑测量互联网质量、我们自己的 Cloudflare 速度测试如何工作，以及我们未来提供互联网测量工具以帮助每个人构建更好的互联网的计划。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data at Cloudflare scale: some insights on measurement for 1,111 interns】Cloudflare 规模的数据：对 1,111 名实习生进行衡量的一些见解</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/experience-of-data-at-scale/</link>
      <description>【 While large cloud providers hold vast troves of passive network data, analyzing them is complicated. The scale, noise, and absence of definitive ground truth all create major hurdles. Yet by carefully quantifying these constraints and finding alternative forms of evidence, meaningful insights can still emerge. 】虽然大型云提供商拥有大量被动网络数据，但分析它们很复杂。规模、噪音和缺乏明确的事实真相都造成了主要障碍。然而，通过仔细量化这些限制并寻找替代形式的证据，仍然可以出现有意义的见解。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Cloudflare’s client-side security made the npm supply chain attack a non-event】Cloudflare 的客户端安全性如何使 npm 供应链攻击不再发生</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-cloudflares-client-side-security-made-the-npm-supply-chain-attack-a-non/</link>
      <description>【 A recent npm supply chain attack compromised 18 popular packages. This post explains how Cloudflare’s graph-based machine learning model, which analyzes 3.5 billion scripts daily, was built to detect and block exactly this kind of threat automatically. 】最近的一次 npm 供应链攻击破坏了 18 个流行软件包。这篇文章解释了 Cloudflare 基于图形的机器学习模型（每天分析 35 亿个脚本）是如何构建的，以自动检测和阻止此类威胁。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing agentic commerce: helping AI Agents transact with Visa and Mastercard】确保代理商务安全：帮助人工智能代理与 Visa 和 Mastercard 进行交易</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/secure-agentic-commerce/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare is partnering with Visa and Mastercard to help secure the future of agentic commerce. 】Cloudflare 正在与 Visa 和 Mastercard 合作，帮助确保代理商务的未来。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A deep dive into BPF LPM trie performance and optimization】深入探讨 BPF LPM trie 性能和优化</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/a-deep-dive-into-bpf-lpm-trie-performance-and-optimization/</link>
      <description>【 This post explores the performance of BPF LPM tries, a critical data structure used for IP matching.  】这篇文章探讨了 BPF LPM 尝试的性能，这是一种用于 IP 匹配的关键数据结构。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Load Balancing Monitor Groups: Multi-Service Health Checks for Resilient Applications】负载平衡监控组：弹性应用程序的多服务运行状况检查</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/load-balancing-monitor-groups-multi-service-health-checks-for-resilient/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Load Balancing now supports Monitor Groups, allowing you to combine multiple health monitors into a single, logical assessment.  】Cloudflare Load Balancing 现在支持监控组，允许您将多个运行状况监控器组合成单个逻辑评估。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>