<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Improve global upload performance with R2 Local Uploads】使用 R2 本地上传提高全局上传性能</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/r2-local-uploads/</link>
      <description>【 Local Uploads on R2 reduces request duration for uploads by up to 75%. It writes object data to a nearby location and asynchronously copies it to your bucket, all while data is available immediately.  】R2 上的本地上传可将上传请求持续时间缩短高达 75%。它将对象数据写入附近的位置并将其异步复制到您的存储桶，同时数据立即可用。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Google’s AI advantage: why crawler separation is the only path to a fair Internet】谷歌的AI优势：为什么爬虫分离是通往公平互联网的唯一途径</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/uk-google-ai-crawler-policy/</link>
      <description>【 Google&#39;s dual-purpose crawler creates an unfair AI advantage. To protect publishers and foster competition, the UK’s Competition and Markets Authority must mandate crawler separation for search and AI. 】谷歌的两用爬虫创造了不公平的人工智能优势。为了保护出版商并促进竞争，英国竞争和市场管理局必须强制执行搜索和人工智能爬虫分离。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building vertical microfrontends on Cloudflare’s platform】在 Cloudflare 平台上构建垂直微前端</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/vertical-microfrontends/</link>
      <description>【 Deploy multiple Workers under a single domain with the ability to make them feel like single-page applications. We take a look at how service bindings enable URL path routing to multiple projects. 】在单个域下部署多个 Worker，能够使它们感觉像单页应用程序。我们来看看服务绑定如何启用 URL 路径路由到多个项目。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Moltworker: a self-hosted personal AI agent, minus the minis】Moltworker 简介：一个自托管的个人人工智能代理，减去迷你</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/moltworker-self-hosted-ai-agent/</link>
      <description>【 Moltworker is a middleware Worker and adapted scripts that allows running OpenClaw (formerly Moltbot, formerly Clawdbot) on Cloudflare&#39;s Sandbox SDK and our Developer Platform APIs. So you can self-host an AI personal assistant — without any new hardware. 】Moltworker 是一个中间件 Worker 和改编脚本，允许在 Cloudflare 的 Sandbox SDK 和我们的开发者平台 API 上运行 OpenClaw（以前称为 Moltbot、以前称为 Clawdbot）。因此，您可以自行托管人工智能个人助理——无需任何新硬件。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a serverless, post-quantum Matrix homeserver】构建无服务器、后量子 Matrix 家庭服务器</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/serverless-matrix-homeserver-workers/</link>
      <description>【 As a proof of concept, we built a Matrix homeserver to Cloudflare Workers — delivering encrypted messaging at the edge with automatic post-quantum cryptography. 】作为概念验证，我们为 Cloudflare Workers 构建了一个 Matrix 家庭服务器 - 使用自动后量子加密技术在边缘提供加密消息传递。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cable cuts, storms, and DNS: a look at Internet disruptions in Q4 2025】电缆切断、风暴和 DNS：2025 年第四季度互联网中断一览</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/q4-2025-internet-disruption-summary/</link>
      <description>【 The last quarter of 2025 brought several notable disruptions to Internet connectivity. Cloudflare Radar data reveals the impact of cable cuts, power outages, extreme weather, technical problems, and more. 】2025 年最后一个季度的互联网连接出现了几次明显的中断。 Cloudflare Radar 数据揭示了电缆切断、停电、极端天气、技术问题等的影响。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Route leak incident on January 22, 2026】2026年1月22日路由泄露事件</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/route-leak-incident-january-22-2026/</link>
      <description>【 An automated routing policy configuration error caused us to leak some Border Gateway Protocol prefixes unintentionally from a router at our Miami data center. We discuss the impact and the changes we are implementing as a result. 】自动路由策略配置错误导致我们无意中从迈阿密数据中心的路由器泄漏了一些边界网关协议前缀。我们讨论了影响以及我们正在实施的变革。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How we mitigated a vulnerability in Cloudflare’s ACME validation logic】我们如何缓解 Cloudflare ACME 验证逻辑中的漏洞</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/acme-path-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>【 A vulnerability was recently identified in Cloudflare’s automation of certificate validation. Here we explain the vulnerability and outline the steps we’ve taken to mitigate it.  】最近在 Cloudflare 的证书验证自动化中发现了一个漏洞。在这里，我们解释了该漏洞并概述了我们为缓解该漏洞而采取的步骤。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Astro is joining Cloudflare】Astro 即将加入 Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/astro-joins-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 The Astro Technology Company team — the creators of the Astro web framework — is joining Cloudflare. We’re doubling down on making Astro the best framework for content-driven websites, today and in the years to come. 】Astro Technology Company 团队（Astro Web 框架的创建者）即将加入 Cloudflare。我们正在加倍努力，使 Astro 成为当今和未来几年内容驱动网站的最佳框架。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Human Native is joining Cloudflare】Human Native 即将加入 Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/human-native-joins-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare acquires Human Native, an AI data marketplace specialising in transforming content into searchable and useful data, to accelerate work building new economic models for the Internet. 】Cloudflare 收购了 Human Native，这是一个专门将内容转换为可搜索且有用的数据的人工智能数据市场，以加快构建互联网新经济模型的工作。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>