<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【A deep dive into BPF LPM trie performance and optimization】深入探讨 BPF LPM trie 性能和优化</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/a-deep-dive-into-bpf-lpm-trie-performance-and-optimization/</link>
      <description>【 This post explores the performance of BPF LPM tries, a critical data structure used for IP matching.  】这篇文章探讨了 BPF LPM 尝试的性能，这是一种用于 IP 匹配的关键数据结构。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Load Balancing Monitor Groups: Multi-Service Health Checks for Resilient Applications】负载平衡监控组：弹性应用程序的多服务运行状况检查</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/load-balancing-monitor-groups-multi-service-health-checks-for-resilient/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Load Balancing now supports Monitor Groups, allowing you to combine multiple health monitors into a single, logical assessment.  】Cloudflare Load Balancing 现在支持监控组，允许您将多个运行状况监控器组合成单个逻辑评估。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Improving the trustworthiness of Javascript on the Web】提高 Javascript 在 Web 上的可信度</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/improving-the-trustworthiness-of-javascript-on-the-web/</link>
      <description>【 There&#39;s no way to audit a site’s client-side code as it changes, making it hard to trust sites that use cryptography. We preview a specification we co-authored that adds auditability to the web. 】当网站的客户端代码发生变化时，无法对其进行审核，因此很难信任使用加密技术的网站。我们预览了我们共同编写的规范，该规范增加了网络的可审核性。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unpacking Cloudflare Workers CPU Performance Benchmarks】解开 Cloudflare Workers CPU 性能基准</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/unpacking-cloudflare-workers-cpu-performance-benchmarks/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare investigated CPU performance benchmark results for Workers, uncovering and fixing issues in infrastructure, V8 garbage collection, and OpenNext optimizations.  】Cloudflare 调查了 Workers 的 CPU 性能基准测试结果，发现并修复了基础设施、V8 垃圾收集和 OpenNext 优化中的问题。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing REACT: Why We Built an Elite Incident Response Team】REACT 简介：为什么我们建立精英事件响应团队</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-react-why-we-built-an-elite-incident-response-team/</link>
      <description>【 We&#39;re launching Cloudforce One REACT, a team of expert security responders designed to eliminate the gap between perimeter defense and internal incident response. 】我们正在推出 Cloudforce One REACT，这是一支由专家安全响应人员组成的团队，旨在消除外围防御和内部事件响应之间的差距。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How we found a bug in Go&#39;s arm64 compiler】我们如何发现 Go 的 arm64 编译器中的错误</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-we-found-a-bug-in-gos-arm64-compiler/</link>
      <description>【 84 million requests a second means even rare bugs appear often. We&#39;ll reveal how we discovered a race condition in the Go arm64 compiler and got it fixed. 】每秒 8400 万个请求意味着即使罕见的错误也经常出现。我们将揭示如何在 Go arm64 编译器中发现竞争条件并修复它。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Payload on Workers: a full-fledged CMS, running entirely on Cloudflare’s stack】Workers 上的有效负载：成熟的 CMS，完全在 Cloudflare 堆栈上运行</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/payload-cms-workers/</link>
      <description>【 We demonstrate how the open-source Payload CMS was ported to run entirely on Cloudflare&#39;s developer platform. 】我们演示了如何将开源 Payload CMS 移植到完全在 Cloudflare 的开发者平台上运行。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Nationwide Internet shutdown in Afghanistan extends localized disruptions】阿富汗全国互联网关闭扩大了局部中断</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/nationwide-internet-shutdown-in-afghanistan/</link>
      <description>【 On September 29, 2025, Internet connectivity was completely shut down across Afghanistan, impacting business, education, finance, and government services. 】2025 年 9 月 29 日，阿富汗各地的互联网连接完全关闭，影响了商业、教育、金融和政府服务。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【15 years of helping build a better Internet: a look back at Birthday Week 2025】15 年来帮助建设更好的互联网：回顾 2025 年生日周</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/birthday-week-2025-wrap-up/</link>
      <description>【 Rust-powered core systems, post-quantum upgrades, developer access for students, PlanetScale integration, open-source partnerships, and our biggest internship program ever — 1,111 interns in 2026. 】Rust 支持的核心系统、后量子升级、学生开发人员访问权限、PlanetScale 集成、开源合作伙伴关系以及我们有史以来最大的实习计划 - 2026 年将有 1,111 名实习生。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare just got faster and more secure, powered by Rust】由 Rust 提供支持的 Cloudflare 变得更快、更安全</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/20-percent-internet-upgrade/</link>
      <description>【 We’ve replaced the original core system in Cloudflare with a new modular Rust-based proxy, replacing NGINX.  】我们用基于 Rust 的新模块化代理取代了 Cloudflare 中的原始核心系统，取代了 NGINX。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>