<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Is this thing on? Using OpenBMC and ACPI power states for reliable server boot】这个东西开了吗？使用 OpenBMC 和 ACPI 电源状态实现可靠的服务器启动</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-we-use-openbmc-and-acpi-power-states-to-monitor-the-state-of-our-servers</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare’s global fleet benefits from being managed by open source firmware for the Baseboard Management Controller (BMC), OpenBMC. This has come with various challenges, some of which we discuss here with an explanation of how the open source nature of the firmware for the BMC enabled us to fix the issues and maintain a more stable fleet. 】Cloudflare 的全球机群受益于底板管理控制器 (BMC) OpenBMC 的开源固件的管理。这带来了各种挑战，我们在这里讨论其中一些挑战，并解释 BMC 固件的开源性质如何使我们能够解决问题并维持更稳定的车队。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Protect against identity-based attacks by sharing Cloudflare user risk scores with Okta】通过与 Okta 共享 Cloudflare 用户风险评分来防范基于身份的攻击</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/protect-against-identity-based-attacks-by-sharing-cloudflare-user-risk-with-okta</link>
      <description>【 Uphold Zero Trust principles and protect against identity-based attacks by sharing Cloudflare user risk scores with Okta. Learn how this new integration allows your organization to mitigate risk in real time, make informed access decisions, and free up security resources with automation. 】通过与 Okta 共享 Cloudflare 用户风险评分，维护零信任原则并防范基于身份的攻击。了解这种新的集成如何帮助您的组织实时降低风险、做出明智的访问决策并通过自动化释放安全资源。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【4.2 Tbps of bad packets and a whole lot more: Cloudflare&#39;s Q3 DDoS report】4.2 Tbps 的坏数据包以及更多：Cloudflare 的第三季度 DDoS 报告</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ddos-threat-report-for-2024-q3</link>
      <description>【 The number of DDoS attacks spiked in the third quarter of 2024. Cloudflare mitigated nearly 6 million DDoS attacks, representing a 49% increase QoQ and 55% increase YoY. 】2024 年第三季度 DDoS 攻击数量激增。Cloudflare 缓解了近 600 万次 DDoS 攻击，环比增长 49%，同比增长 55%。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The story of web framework Hono, from the creator of Hono】Web框架Hono的故事，来自Hono的创建者</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-story-of-web-framework-hono-from-the-creator-of-hono</link>
      <description>【 Hono is a web framework that is fast, lightweight, and built using the Web Standards API. Hear the story of Hono by the creator of Hono. 】Hono 是一个快速、轻量级的 Web 框架，并且使用 Web 标准 API 构建。聆听 Hono 的创造者讲述 Hono 的故事。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fearless SSH: short-lived certificates bring Zero Trust to infrastructure】无畏的 SSH：短期证书为基础设施带来零信任</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/intro-access-for-infrastructure-ssh</link>
      <description>【 Access for Infrastructure, BastionZero’s integration into Cloudflare One, will enable organizations to apply Zero Trust controls to their servers, databases, Kubernetes clusters, and more. Today we’re announcing short-lived SSH access as the first available feature of this integration.&#xA; 】Access for Infrastructure 是 BastionZero 与 Cloudflare One 的集成，将使组织能够将零信任控制应用于其服务器、数据库、Kubernetes 集群等。今天，我们宣布短期 SSH 访问作为此集成的第一个可用功能。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Billions and billions (of logs): scaling AI Gateway with the Cloudflare Developer Platform】数十亿（日志）：使用 Cloudflare 开发者平台扩展 AI Gateway</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/billions-and-billions-of-logs-scaling-ai-gateway-with-the-cloudflare</link>
      <description>【 How we scaled AI Gateway to handle and store billions of requests, using Cloudflare Workers, D1, Durable Objects, and R2. 】我们如何使用 Cloudflare Workers、D1、Durable Objects 和 R2 扩展 AI Gateway 以处理和存储数十亿个请求。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Analysis of the EPYC 145% performance gain in Cloudflare Gen 12 servers】Cloudflare Gen 12 服务器中 EPYC 145% 性能提升的分析</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/analysis-of-the-epyc-145-performance-gain-in-cloudflare-gen-12-servers</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare’s Gen 12 server is the most powerful and power efficient server that we have deployed to date. Through sensitivity analysis, we found that Cloudflare workloads continue to scale with higher core count and higher CPU frequency, as well as achieving a significant boost in performance with larger L3 cache per core. 】Cloudflare 的 Gen 12 服务器是我们迄今为止部署的最强大、最节能的服务器。通过敏感性分析，我们发现 Cloudflare 工作负载随着核心数量和 CPU 频率的增加而持续扩展，并且通过每个核心更大的 L3 缓存实现性能的显着提升。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Durable Objects aren&#39;t just durable, they&#39;re fast: a 10x speedup for Cloudflare Queues】耐用对象不仅耐用，而且速度快：Cloudflare 队列的速度提高了 10 倍</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-we-built-cloudflare-queues</link>
      <description>【 Learn how we built Cloudflare Queues using our own Developer Platform and how it evolved to a geographically-distributed, horizontally-scalable architecture built on Durable Objects. Our new architecture supports over 10x more throughput and over 3x lower latency compared to the previous version. 】了解我们如何使用自己的开发者平台构建 Cloudflare 队列，以及它如何演变成基于持久对象的地理分布式、水平可扩展的架构。与之前的版本相比，我们的新架构支持的吞吐量提高了 10 倍以上，延迟降低了 3 倍以上。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Training a million models per day to save customers of all sizes from DDoS attacks】每天训练一百万个模型，以保护各种规模的客户免受 DDoS 攻击</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/training-a-million-models-per-day-to-save-customers-of-all-sizes-from-ddos</link>
      <description>【 In this post we will describe how we use anomaly detection to watch for novel DDoS attacks. We’ll provide an overview of how we build models which flag unusual traffic and keep our customers safe. 】在这篇文章中，我们将描述如何使用异常检测来监视新型 DDoS 攻击。我们将概述如何构建标记异常流量并确保客户安全的模型。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build durable applications on Cloudflare Workers: you write the Workflows, we take care of the rest】在 Cloudflare Workers 上构建持久的应用程序：您编写工作流程，我们负责其余的工作</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-workflows-durable-execution-on-workers</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Workflows is now in open beta! Workflows allows you to build reliable, repeatable, long-lived multi-step applications that can automatically retry, persist state, and scale out. Read on to learn how Workflows works, how we built it on top of Durable Objects, and how you can deploy your first Workflows application. 】Cloudflare Workflows 现已开放测试版！工作流允许您构建可靠、可重复、长期存在的多步骤应用程序，这些应用程序可以自动重试、保留状态和横向扩展。请继续阅读以了解工作流的工作原理、我们如何在持久对象之上构建它以及如何部署您的第一个工作流应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>