<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Automatically Secure: how we upgraded 6,000,000 domains by default to get ready for the Quantum Future】自动安全：默认情况下，我们如何升级6,000,000个域以为量子未来做好准备</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/automatically-secure/</link>
      <description>【 After a year since we started enabling Automatic SSL/TLS, we want to talk about these results, why they matter, and how we’re preparing for the next leap in Internet security. 】自从我们开始启用自动SSL/TLS的一年以来，我们想谈论这些结果，为什么重要以及我们如何为下一个Internet安全的飞跃做准备。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A simpler path to a safer Internet: an update to our CSAM scanning tool】更安全的互联网的简单途径：我们的CSAM扫描工具的更新</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/a-simpler-path-to-a-safer-internet-an-update-to-our-csam-scanning-tool/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare has made it even easier to enable our free child safety tooling for all customers. 】Cloudflare使我们更容易为所有客户启用我们的免费儿童安全工具。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing today for the quantum future: WARP client now supports post-quantum cryptography (PQC)】今天确保量子未来：扭曲客户现在支持量词后加密（PQC）</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/post-quantum-warp/</link>
      <description>【 To prepare for a future where powerful quantum computers come online, we&#39;ve upgraded our WARP client with post-quantum cryptography. 】为了准备一个强大的量子计算机在线的未来，我们已经通过后量子加密量升级了翘曲客户端。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【To build a better Internet in the age of AI, we need responsible AI bot principles. Here’s our proposal.】为了在AI时代建立更好的互联网，我们需要负责的AI机器人原则。这是我们的建议。</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-a-better-internet-with-responsible-ai-bot-principles/</link>
      <description>【 We are proposing—as starting points—responsible AI bot principles that emphasize transparency, accountability, and respect for content access and use preferences. 】我们正在提出强调透明度，问责制以及对内容访问和使用首选项的尊重的反应AI机器人原则。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing data in SaaS to SaaS applications】将SaaS中的数据固定到SaaS应用程序</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/saas-to-saas-security/</link>
      <description>【 The recent Salesloft breach taught us one thing: companies do not have visibility over data in SaaS applications. Cloudflare is committing to providing additional security tools for SaaS applications 】最近的SalesLoft违规教会了我们一件事：公司在SaaS应用程序中没有可见性。 CloudFlare致力于为SaaS应用程序提供其他安全工具</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Giving users choice with Cloudflare’s new Content Signals Policy】为用户选择CloudFlare的新内容信号策略</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/content-signals-policy/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare’s Content Signals Policy gives creators a new tool to control use of their content. &#xA; 】CloudFlare的内容信号策略为创建者提供了一种控制其内容使用的新工具。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building unique, per-customer defenses against advanced bot threats in the AI era】在人工智能时代建立针对先进的机器人威胁的独特的，人均防御</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/per-customer-bot-defenses/</link>
      <description>【 Today, we are announcing a new approach to catching bots: using models to provide behavioral anomaly detection unique to each bot management customer and stop sophisticated bot attacks.  】今天，我们宣布了一种新方法来捕捉机器人：使用模型提供每个机器人管理客户独有的行为异常检测并停止复杂的机器人攻击。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare Confidence Scorecards - making AI safer for the Internet】Cloudflare信心记分卡 - 使互联网更安全</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-confidence-scorecards-making-ai-safer-for-the-internet/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Confidence Scorecards are now live in the Application Library. Get transparent risk ratings for SaaS and Gen-AI apps. 】Cloudflare Profure得分卡现在生活在应用程序库中。获得SaaS和Gen-AI应用程序的透明风险评级。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Deploy your own AI vibe coding platform — in one click! 】部署自己的AI Vibe编码平台 - 一键单击！</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/deploy-your-own-ai-vibe-coding-platform/</link>
      <description>【 Introducing VibeSDK, an open-source AI &#34;vibe coding&#34; platform that anyone can deploy to build their own custom platform. Comes ready with code generation, sandbox environment, and project deployment.  】引入VibesDK，一个开源AI“ VIBE编码”平台，任何人都可以部署以构建自己的自定义平台。准备好代码生成，沙盒环境和项目部署。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Cloudflare, Netlify, and Webflow are collaborating to support Open Source tools like Astro and TanStack】为什么CloudFlare，NetLify和WebFlow正在协作以支持Astro和Tanstack等开源工具</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-astro-tanstack/</link>
      <description>【 Today, Cloudflare is proud to announce support for two cornerstone frameworks in the modern web ecosystem: we’re partnering with Webflow to sponsor Astro, and with Netlify to sponsor TanStack. 】如今，CloudFlare自豪地宣布对现代网络生态系统中两个基石框架的支持：我们正在与WebFlow合作以赞助Astro，并与Netlify一起向赞助商Tanstack。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>