<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【How Workers powers our internal maintenance scheduling pipeline】Workers 如何为我们的内部维护计划流程提供支持</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-our-maintenance-scheduler-on-workers/</link>
      <description>【 Physical data center maintenance is risky on a global network. We built a maintenance scheduler on Workers to safely plan disruptive operations, while solving scaling challenges by viewing the state of our infrastructure through a graph interface on top of multiple data sources and metrics pipelines. 】全球网络上的物理数据中心维护存在风险。我们在 Workers 上构建了一个维护调度程序，以安全地计划中断性操作，同时通过多个数据源和指标管道之上的图形界面查看基础设施的状态来解决扩展挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Code Orange: Fail Small — our resilience plan following recent incidents】橙色代码：小失败——我们在最近发生的事件后的恢复计划</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/fail-small-resilience-plan/</link>
      <description>【 We have declared “Code Orange: Fail Small” to focus everyone at Cloudflare on a set of high-priority workstreams with one simple goal: ensure that the cause of our last two global outages never happens again. 】我们宣布了“橙色代码：小规模失败”，让 Cloudflare 的每个人都专注于一组高优先级工作流，其目标很简单：确保我们最近两次全球中断的原因不再发生。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Innovating to address streaming abuse — and our latest transparency report】创新解决流媒体滥用问题——以及我们最新的透明度报告</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/h1-2025-transparency-report/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare&#39;s H1 2025 Transparency Report is here. We discuss our principles on content blocking and our innovative approach to combating unauthorized streaming and copyright abuse. 】Cloudflare 的 2025 年上半年透明度报告位于此处。我们讨论了内容屏蔽的原则以及打击未经授权的流媒体和版权滥用的创新方法。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing support for GROUP BY, SUM, and other aggregation queries in R2 SQL】宣布支持 R2 SQL 中的 GROUP BY、SUM 和其他聚合查询</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/r2-sql-aggregations/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare’s R2 SQL, a distributed query engine, now supports aggregations. Explore how we built distributed GROUP BY execution, using scatter-gather and shuffling strategies to run analytics directly over your R2 Data Catalog. 】Cloudflare 的 R2 SQL（分布式查询引擎）现在支持聚合。探索我们如何构建分布式 GROUP BY 执行，使用分散-聚集和改组策略直接在 R2 数据目录上运行分析。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The 2025 Cloudflare Radar Year in Review: The rise of AI, post-quantum, and record-breaking DDoS attacks】2025 年 Cloudflare Radar 回顾：人工智能的兴起、后量子和破纪录的 DDoS 攻击</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-2025-year-in-review/</link>
      <description>【 We present our 6th annual review of Internet trends and patterns observed across the globe, revealing the disruptions, advances and metrics that defined 2025.  】我们对全球范围内观察到的互联网趋势和模式进行了第六次年度回顾，揭示了 2025 年的颠覆、进步和指标。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ChatGPT&#39;s rivals, Kwai&#39;s quiet rise: the top Internet services of 2025】ChatGPT的竞争对手，快手悄然崛起：2025年顶级互联网服务</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-2025-year-in-review-internet-services/</link>
      <description>【 AI competition intensified in 2025 as ChatGPT gained strong challengers. Instagram climbed, X declined, and platforms like Shopee, Temu, and Kwai reshaped global Internet usage. Our 2025 DNS data shows how Internet patterns evolved. 】2025年，人工智能竞争更加激烈，ChatGPT迎来了强有力的挑战者。 Instagram 上升，X 下降，Shopee、Temu 和 Kwai 等平台重塑了全球互联网使用情况。我们的 2025 年 DNS 数据显示了互联网模式的演变。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【React2Shell and related RSC vulnerabilities threat brief: early exploitation activity and threat actor techniques】React2Shell 和相关 RSC 漏洞威胁简介：早期利用活动和威胁行为者技术</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/react2shell-rsc-vulnerabilities-exploitation-threat-brief/</link>
      <description>【 Early activity indicates that threat actors quickly integrated this vulnerability into their scanning and reconnaissance routines and targeted critical infrastructure including nuclear fuel, uranium and rare earth elements. We outline the tactics they appear to be using and how Cloudflare is protecting customers.  】早期活动表明，威胁行为者迅速将此漏洞整合到他们的扫描和侦察程序中，并瞄准了包括核燃料、铀和稀土元素在内的关键基础设施。我们概述了他们似乎正在使用的策略以及 Cloudflare 如何保护客户。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shifting left at enterprise scale: how we manage Cloudflare with Infrastructure as Code】企业规模左移：我们如何通过基础设施即代码来管理 Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/shift-left-enterprise-scale/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare has shifted to Infrastructure as Code and policy enforcement to manage internal Cloudflare accounts. This new architecture uses Terraform, custom tooling, and Open Policy Agent to enforce security baselines and increase engineering velocity. 】Cloudflare 已转向基础设施即代码和策略执行来管理内部 Cloudflare 帐户。这种新架构使用 Terraform、自定义工具和开放策略代理来实施安全基线并提高工程速度。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python Workers redux: fast cold starts, packages, and a uv-first workflow】Python Workers redux：快速冷启动、包和 uv 优先工作流程</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/python-workers-advancements/</link>
      <description>【 Recent advancements in Cloudflare Python Workers means fast cold starts, comprehensive package support, and a great developer experience. We explain how they were achieved and show how Python can be used to build serverless applications on Cloudflare. 】Cloudflare Python Workers 的最新进展意味着快速冷启动、全面的软件包支持和出色的开发人员体验。我们解释了它们是如何实现的，并展示了如何使用 Python 在 Cloudflare 上构建无服务器应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare outage on December 5, 2025】Cloudflare 于 2025 年 12 月 5 日中断</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/5-december-2025-outage/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare experienced a significant traffic outage on  December 5, 2025, starting approximately at 8:47 UTC. The incident lasted approximately 25 minutes before resolution. We are sorry for the impact that it caused to our customers and the Internet. The incident was not caused by an attack and was due to configuration changes being applied to attempt to mitigate a recent industry-wide vulnerability impacting React Server Components. 】Cloudflare 于 2025 年 12 月 5 日经历了严重的流量中断，大约从世界标准时间 8:47 开始。事件持续了大约25分钟才得到解决。对于这对我们的客户和互联网造成的影响，我们深表歉意。该事件不是由攻击引起的，而是由于应用配置更改来尝试缓解最近影响 React Server 组件的全行业漏洞。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>