<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【React2Shell and related RSC vulnerabilities threat brief: early exploitation activity and threat actor techniques】React2Shell 和相关 RSC 漏洞威胁简介：早期利用活动和威胁行为者技术</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/react2shell-rsc-vulnerabilities-exploitation-threat-brief/</link>
      <description>【 Early activity indicates that threat actors quickly integrated this vulnerability into their scanning and reconnaissance routines and targeted critical infrastructure including nuclear fuel, uranium and rare earth elements. We outline the tactics they appear to be using and how Cloudflare is protecting customers.  】早期活动表明，威胁行为者迅速将此漏洞整合到他们的扫描和侦察程序中，并瞄准了包括核燃料、铀和稀土元素在内的关键基础设施。我们概述了他们似乎正在使用的策略以及 Cloudflare 如何保护客户。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shifting left at enterprise scale: how we manage Cloudflare with Infrastructure as Code】在企业规模上左移：我们如何通过基础设施即代码来管理 Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/shift-left-enterprise-scale/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare has shifted to Infrastructure as Code and policy enforcement to manage internal Cloudflare accounts. This new architecture uses Terraform, custom tooling, and Open Policy Agent to enforce security baselines and increase engineering velocity. 】Cloudflare 已转向基础设施即代码和策略执行来管理内部 Cloudflare 帐户。这种新架构使用 Terraform、自定义工具和开放策略代理来实施安全基线并提高工程速度。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python Workers redux: fast cold starts, packages, and a uv-first workflow】Python Workers redux：快速冷启动、包和 uv 优先工作流程</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/python-workers-advancements/</link>
      <description>【 Recent advancements in Cloudflare Python Workers means fast cold starts, comprehensive package support, and a great developer experience. We explain how they were achieved and show how Python can be used to build serverless applications on Cloudflare. 】Cloudflare Python Workers 的最新进展意味着快速冷启动、全面的软件包支持和出色的开发人员体验。我们解释了它们是如何实现的，并展示了如何使用 Python 在 Cloudflare 上构建无服务器应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare outage on December 5, 2025】Cloudflare 于 2025 年 12 月 5 日中断</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/5-december-2025-outage/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare experienced a significant traffic outage on  December 5, 2025, starting approximately at 8:47 UTC. The incident lasted approximately 25 minutes before resolution. We are sorry for the impact that it caused to our customers and the Internet. The incident was not caused by an attack and was due to configuration changes being applied to attempt to mitigate a recent industry-wide vulnerability impacting React Server Components. 】Cloudflare 于 2025 年 12 月 5 日经历了严重的流量中断，大约从世界标准时间 8:47 开始。事件持续了大约25分钟才得到解决。对于这对我们的客户和互联网造成的影响，我们深表歉意。该事件不是由攻击引起的，而是由于应用配置更改来尝试缓解最近影响 React Server 组件的全行业漏洞。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare WAF proactively protects against React vulnerability】Cloudflare WAF 主动防御 React 漏洞</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/waf-rules-react-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare offers protection against a new high profile vulnerability for React Server Components: CVE-2025-55182. All WAF customers are automatically protected as long as the WAF is deployed. 】Cloudflare 为 React 服务器组件提供针对新的备受瞩目的漏洞的保护：CVE-2025-55182。只要部署了WAF，所有WAF客户都会自动受到保护。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare&#39;s 2025 Q3 DDoS threat report -- including Aisuru, the apex of botnets】Cloudflare 的 2025 年第三季度 DDoS 威胁报告 - 包括僵尸网络的顶峰 Aisuru</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ddos-threat-report-2025-q3/</link>
      <description>【 Welcome to the 23rd edition of Cloudflare’s Quarterly DDoS Threat Report. This report offers a comprehensive analysis of the evolving threat landscape of Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attacks based on data from the Cloudflare network. In this edition, we focus on the third quarter of 2025. 】欢迎阅读第 23 版 Cloudflare 季度 DDoS 威胁报告。本报告基于 Cloudflare 网络的数据，对分布式拒绝服务 (DDoS) 攻击不断演变的威胁形势进行了全面分析。在本期中，我们重点关注 2025 年第三季度。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Replicate is joining Cloudflare】为什么 Replicate 加入 Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/why-replicate-joining-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 Today, we’re excited to announce that Replicate is officially part of Cloudflare. We wanted to share a bit about our journey and why we made this decision.  】今天，我们很高兴地宣布 Replicate 正式成为 Cloudflare 的一部分。我们想分享一些关于我们的旅程以及我们做出这个决定的原因。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Partnering with Black Forest Labs to bring FLUX.2 [dev] to Workers AI】与 Black Forest Labs 合作将 FLUX.2 [dev] 引入 Workers AI</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/flux-2-workers-ai/</link>
      <description>【 FLUX.2 [dev] by Black Forest Labs is now on Workers AI! This advanced open-weight image model offers superior photorealism, multi-reference inputs, and granular control with JSON prompting. 】Black Forest Labs 的 FLUX.2 [dev] 现已在 Workers AI 上发布！这种先进的开放权重图像模型提供卓越的照片级真实感、多参考输入以及带 JSON 提示的精细控制。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Get better visibility for the WAF with payload logging】通过有效负载日志记录获得 WAF 的更好可见性</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/waf-payload-logging/</link>
      <description>【 The WAF provides ways for our customers to gain insight into why it takes certain actions. The more granular and precise the insight, the more reproducible and understandable it is. Revamped payload logging is one such method.  】WAF 为我们的客户提供了深入了解其采取某些操作的原因的方法。洞察力越细致、越精确，它的可重复性和可理解性就越高。改进的有效负载日志记录就是其中一种方法。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare outage on November 18, 2025】Cloudflare 于 2025 年 11 月 18 日中断</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/18-november-2025-outage/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare suffered a service outage on November 18, 2025. The outage was triggered by a bug in generation logic for a Bot Management feature file causing many Cloudflare services to be affected. &#xA; 】Cloudflare 于 2025 年 11 月 18 日发生服务中断。此次中断是由机器人管理功能文件的生成逻辑错误引发的，导致许多 Clo​​udflare 服务受到影响。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>