<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Your frontend, backend, and database — now in one Cloudflare Worker】您的前端，后端和数据库 - 现在在一个Cloudflare工人中</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/full-stack-development-on-cloudflare-workers/</link>
      <description>【 You can now deploy static sites and full-stack applications on Cloudflare Workers. Framework support for React Router v7, Astro, Vue and more are generally available today and Cloudflare Vite plugin.  】现在，您可以在CloudFlare工人上部署静态站点和全堆栈应用程序。今天通常可以使用React Router V7，Astro，Vue等框架支持React路由器V7，以及CloudFlare Vite插件。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Network performance update: Developer Week 2025】网络性能更新：开发人员周2025周</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/network-performance-update-developer-week-2025/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare has been tracking and comparing our speed with other top networks since 2021. Let’s take a look at how things have changed since our last update. 】自2021年以来，CloudFlare一直在跟踪和比较我们的速度与其他顶级网络。让我们来看看自上次更新以来的情况如何变化。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Workers Observability: logs, metrics, and queries – all in one place】介绍工人的可观察性：日志，指标和查询 - 全部在一个地方</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-workers-observability-logs-metrics-and-queries-all-in-one-place/</link>
      <description>【 We’ve improved Observability for Workers by announcing the General Availability of Workers Logs and the introduction of the Query Builder to help you investigate log events across all of your Workers. 】我们通过宣布工人日志的一般可用性和引入查询构建器来帮助您调查所有工人的日志事件，从而提高了工人的可观察性。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Sequential consistency without borders: how D1 implements global read replication】顺序一致性无边界：D1如何实现全局读取复制</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/d1-read-replication-beta/</link>
      <description>【 D1, Cloudflare’s managed SQL database, announces read replication beta. Here&#39;s a deep dive of the read replication implementation and how your queries can remain consistent across all regions. 】D1，CloudFlare的托管SQL数据库，宣布阅读复制Beta。这是对读取复制实现的深入研究，以及您的查询如何在所有地区保持一致。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare Snippets are now Generally Available】Cloudflare片段现在通常可用</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/snippets/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Snippets are now generally available, enabling fast, cost-free JavaScript-based HTTP traffic modifications across all paid plans.  】现在通常可以使用CloudFlare片段，可以在所有付费计划中进行基于JavaScript的快速，基于成本的JavaScript HTTP流量修改。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Make your apps truly interactive with Cloudflare Realtime and RealtimeKit 】使您的应用与CloudFlare实时和Realtimekit真正互动</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-cloudflare-realtime-and-realtimekit/</link>
      <description>【 Announcing Cloudflare Realtime and RealtimeKit, a complete toolkit for shipping real-time audio and video apps in days with SDKs for Kotlin, React Native, Swift, JavaScript, and Flutter. 】宣布CloudFlare实时和RealtimeKit，这是一个完整的工具包，用于与Kotlin，React Native，Swift，JavaScript和Flutter的SDK一起运送实时音频和视频应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Making Super Slurper 5x faster with Workers, Durable Objects, and Queues】用工人，耐用的物体和队列使超级slul 5倍更快地使超级5倍</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/making-super-slurper-five-times-faster/</link>
      <description>【 We re-architected Super Slurper from the ground up using our Developer Platform — leveraging Cloudflare Workers, Durable Objects, and Queues — and improved transfer speeds by up to 5x. 】我们使用开发人员平台（利用Cloudflare工人，耐用的对象和队列）从头开始重新建立了超级sul骨，并提高了高达5倍的传输速度。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Just landed: streaming ingestion on Cloudflare with Arroyo and Pipelines】刚刚降落：与Arroyo和Pipelines在Cloudflare上插入</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-acquires-arroyo-pipelines-streaming-ingestion-beta/</link>
      <description>【 We’ve just shipped our new streaming ingestion service, Pipelines — and we’ve acquired Arroyo, enabling us to bring new SQL-based, stateful transformations to Pipelines and R2. 】我们刚刚运送了新的流摄取服务Pipelines  - 我们已经收购了Arroyo，使我们能够将新的基于SQL的状态转换带到管道和R2。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Cloudflare Secrets Store (Beta): secure your secrets, simplify your workflow】介绍Cloudflare Secrets商店（Beta）：保护您的秘密，简化工作流程</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/secrets-store-beta/</link>
      <description>【 Securely store, manage and deploy account level secrets to Cloudflare Workers through Cloudflare Secrets Store, available in beta – with role-based access control, audit logging and Wrangler support. 】通过CloudFlare Secrets Store（可在Beta中使用）安全地存储，管理和部署帐户级别的秘密，并具有基于角色的访问控制，审计记录和牧马人的支持。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【R2 Data Catalog: Managed Apache Iceberg tables with zero egress fees】R2数据目录：托管Apache冰山桌零出口费</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/r2-data-catalog-public-beta/</link>
      <description>【 R2 Data Catalog is now in public beta: a managed Apache Iceberg data catalog built directly into your R2 bucket. 】R2数据目录现在在公共Beta中：直接构建在R2存储桶中的托管Apache Iceberg数据目录。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>