<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a serverless, post-quantum Matrix homeserver】构建无服务器、后量子 Matrix 家庭服务器</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/serverless-matrix-homeserver-workers/</link>
      <description>【 As a proof of concept, we built a Matrix homeserver to Cloudflare Workers — delivering encrypted messaging at the edge with automatic post-quantum cryptography. 】作为概念验证，我们为 Cloudflare Workers 构建了一个 Matrix 家庭服务器 - 使用自动后量子加密技术在边缘提供加密消息传递。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cable cuts, storms, and DNS: a look at Internet disruptions in Q4 2025】电缆切断、风暴和 DNS：2025 年第四季度互联网中断一览</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/q4-2025-internet-disruption-summary/</link>
      <description>【 The last quarter of 2025 brought several notable disruptions to Internet connectivity. Cloudflare Radar data reveals the impact of cable cuts, power outages, extreme weather, technical problems, and more. 】2025 年最后一个季度的互联网连接出现了几次明显的中断。 Cloudflare Radar 数据揭示了电缆切断、停电、极端天气、技术问题等的影响。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Route leak incident on January 22, 2026】2026年1月22日路由泄露事件</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/route-leak-incident-january-22-2026/</link>
      <description>【 An automated routing policy configuration error caused us to leak some Border Gateway Protocol prefixes unintentionally from a router at our Miami data center. We discuss the impact and the changes we are implementing as a result. 】自动路由策略配置错误导致我们无意中从迈阿密数据中心的路由器泄漏了一些边界网关协议前缀。我们讨论了影响以及我们正在实施的变革。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How we mitigated a vulnerability in Cloudflare’s ACME validation logic】我们如何缓解 Cloudflare ACME 验证逻辑中的漏洞</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/acme-path-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>【 A vulnerability was recently identified in Cloudflare’s automation of certificate validation. Here we explain the vulnerability and outline the steps we’ve taken to mitigate it.  】最近在 Cloudflare 的证书验证自动化中发现了一个漏洞。在这里，我们解释了该漏洞并概述了我们为缓解该漏洞而采取的步骤。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Astro is joining Cloudflare】Astro 即将加入 Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/astro-joins-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 The Astro Technology Company team — the creators of the Astro web framework — is joining Cloudflare. We’re doubling down on making Astro the best framework for content-driven websites, today and in the years to come. 】Astro Technology Company 团队（Astro Web 框架的创建者）即将加入 Cloudflare。我们正在加倍努力，使 Astro 成为当今和未来几年内容驱动网站的最佳框架。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Human Native is joining Cloudflare】Human Native 即将加入 Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/human-native-joins-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare acquires Human Native, an AI data marketplace specialising in transforming content into searchable and useful data, to accelerate work building new economic models for the Internet. 】Cloudflare 收购了 Human Native，这是一个专门将内容转换为可搜索且有用的数据的人工智能数据市场，以加快构建互联网新经济模型的工作。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What came first: the CNAME or the A record?】哪个先出现：CNAME 还是 A 记录？</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cname-a-record-order-dns-standards/</link>
      <description>【 A recent change to 1.1.1.1 accidentally altered the order of CNAME records in DNS responses, breaking resolution for some clients. This post explores the technical root cause, examines the source code of affected resolvers, and dives into the inherent ambiguities of the DNS RFCs.   】最近对 1.1.1.1 的更改意外更改了 DNS 响应中 CNAME 记录的顺序，从而破坏了某些客户端的解析。这篇文章探讨了技术根本原因，检查了受影响解析器的源代码，并深入探讨了 DNS RFC 固有的模糊性。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What we know about Iran’s Internet shutdown】我们对伊朗互联网关闭的了解</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/iran-protests-internet-shutdown/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Radar data shows Internet traffic from Iran has effectively dropped to zero since January 8, signaling a complete shutdown in the country and disconnection from the global Internet.  &#xA; 】Cloudflare Radar 数据显示，自 1 月 8 日以来，来自伊朗的互联网流量实际上已降至零，这表明该国已完全关闭并与全球互联网断开连接。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A closer look at a BGP anomaly in Venezuela】仔细观察委内瑞拉的 BGP 异常</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/bgp-route-leak-venezuela/</link>
      <description>【 There has been speculation about the cause of a BGP anomaly observed in Venezuela on January 2. We take a look at BGP route leaks, and dive into what the data suggests caused the anomaly in question. 】人们对 1 月 2 日在委内瑞拉观察到的 BGP 异常的原因进行了猜测。我们研究了 BGP 路由泄漏，并深入研究了数据表明是什么导致了相关异常。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Workers powers our internal maintenance scheduling pipeline】Workers 如何为我们的内部维护计划流程提供支持</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-our-maintenance-scheduler-on-workers/</link>
      <description>【 Physical data center maintenance is risky on a global network. We built a maintenance scheduler on Workers to safely plan disruptive operations, while solving scaling challenges by viewing the state of our infrastructure through a graph interface on top of multiple data sources and metrics pipelines. 】全球网络上的物理数据中心维护存在风险。我们在 Workers 上构建了一个维护调度程序，以安全地计划中断性操作，同时通过多个数据源和指标管道之上的图形界面查看基础设施的状态来解决扩展挑战。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>