<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s new in Cloudflare: MASQUE now powers 1.1.1.1 &amp; WARP apps, DEX now generally available with Remote Captures】Cloudflare中的新功能：Masque现在为1.1.1.1和Warp应用程序，DEX现在通常可用于远程捕获</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/masque-now-powers-1-1-1-1-and-warp-apps-dex-available-with-remote-captures/</link>
      <description>【 This roundup blog post shares the latest new features and capabilities at Cloudflare. 】该综述博客文章在CloudFlare分享了最新的新功能。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Open source all the way down: Upgrading our developer documentation】一路开源：升级开发人员文档</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/open-source-all-the-way-down-upgrading-our-developer-documentation/</link>
      <description>【 At Cloudflare, we treat developer content like an open source product. This collaborative approach enables global contributions to enhance quality and relevance for a wide range of users. This year, 】在CloudFlare，我们将开发人员的内容视为开源产品。这种协作方法可实现全球贡献，以提高各种用户的质量和相关性。今年，</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Demonstrating reduction of vulnerability classes: a key step in CISA’s “Secure by Design” pledge】展示减少脆弱性课程的减少：CISA“ Secure by Design”承诺的关键步骤</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cisa-pledge-commitment-reducing-vulnerability/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare strengthens its commitment to cybersecurity by joining CISA&#39;s &#34;Secure by Design&#34; pledge. In line with this, we&#39;re reducing the prevalence of vulnerability classes across our products. 】CloudFlare通过加入CISA的“ Secure By Design”承诺来增强其对网络安全的承诺。与此一致，我们正在降低产品中脆弱性类别的流行率。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The forecast is clear: clouds on e-paper, powered by the cloud】预测很清楚：电子纸上的云，由云提供动力</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-forecast-is-clear-clouds-on-e-paper-powered-by-the-cloud/</link>
      <description>【 Follow along as I build a custom weather display using Cloudflare Workers and a popular e-paper display. 】跟随我使用Cloudflare工人和流行的电子纸显示器构建自定义天气显示。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Behind the scenes with Stream Live, Cloudflare’s live streaming service】Cloudflare的现场流媒体服务的Stream Live幕后</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/behind-the-scenes-with-stream-live-cloudflares-live-streaming-service/</link>
      <description>【 Let’s talk about Stream Live’s design, and how it leverages the distributed nature of Cloudflare’s network, rather than centralized locations as many other live services do. 】让我们来谈谈流Live的设计以及它如何利用Cloudflare网络的分布性质，而不是像许多其他实时服务一样集中位置。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multi-Path TCP: revolutionizing connectivity, one path at a time】多路径TCP：革新连接性，一次一条路径</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/multi-path-tcp-revolutionizing-connectivity-one-path-at-a-time/</link>
      <description>【 Multi-Path TCP (MPTCP) leverages multiple network interfaces, like Wi-Fi and cellular, to provide seamless mobility for more reliable connectivity. While promising, MPTCP is still in its early stages, 】多路径TCP（MPTCP）利用多个网络接口（例如Wi-Fi和Cellular）提供无缝的移动性，以提供更可靠的连接性。虽然有前途，但MPTCP仍处于早期阶段，但</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Open sourcing h3i: a command line tool and library for low-level HTTP/3 testing and debugging】开源H3I：低级HTTP/3测试和调试的命令行工具和库</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/h3i/</link>
      <description>【 h3i is a command line tool and Rust library designed for low-level testing and debugging of HTTP/3, which runs over QUIC. 】H3i是一种命令行工具和Rust库，旨在用于低级测试和调试HTTP/3的调试，该测试在QUIC上运行。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The fall and rise of TikTok (traffic)】Tiktok（交通）的跌倒</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-fall-and-rise-of-tiktok-traffic/</link>
      <description>【 On January 19, 2025, ByteDance suspended TikTok and related apps for US users. We examine the 14-hour traffic plunge, recovery near Donald Trump’s inauguration. 】2025年1月19日，Bontedance暂停了Tiktok和相关应用程序的应用程序。我们检查了14小时的交通量，唐纳德·特朗普就职典礼附近的恢复。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Record-breaking 5.6 Tbps DDoS attack and global DDoS trends for 2024 Q4】创纪录的5.6 TBPS DDOS攻击和2024年第四季度全球DDOS趋势</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ddos-threat-report-for-2024-q4/</link>
      <description>【 2024 ended with a bang. Cloudflare mitigated another record-breaking DDoS attack peaking at 5.6 Tbps. 】2024年以轰动结束。 Cloudflare减轻了另一种破纪录的DDOS攻击，达到5.6 TBP。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【TikTok ban takes hold: data reveals sharp traffic decline and rapid shift to alternatives】Tiktok Ban持有：数据揭示了交通急剧下降，并迅速转移到替代方案</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/tiktok-ban-traffic-decline-alternatives-rednote/</link>
      <description>【 On January 19, 2025, ByteDance shut down access to TikTok and other owned/operated apps for US users, causing an 85% traffic plunge and a rapid shift to alternatives like RedNote. 】2025年1月19日，Bytedance关闭了对Tiktok和其他拥有/操作的应用程序的访问，为美国用户造成85％的交通量，并迅速转移到Rednote等替代方案。</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 16:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>