<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【First round of French election: party attacks and a modest traffic dip】法国大选第一轮：政党攻击和流量小幅下降</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/first-round-of-french-election-2024-party-attacks-and-a-modest-traffic-dip</link>
      <description>【 How Cloudflare mitigated DDoS attacks targeting French political parties during the 2024 legislative elections, as detailed in our ongoing election coverage 】Cloudflare 如何在 2024 年立法选举期间缓解针对法国政党的 DDoS 攻击，详情请参阅我们正在进行的选举报道</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare 1.1.1.1 incident on June 27, 2024】2024 年 6 月 27 日的 Cloudflare 1.1.1.1 事件</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-1111-incident-on-june-27-2024</link>
      <description>【 On June 27, 2024, a small number of users globally may have noticed that 1.1.1.1 was unreachable or degraded. The root cause was a mix of BGP (Border Gateway Protocol) hijacking and a route leak 】2024 年 6 月 27 日，全球少数用户可能已经注意到 1.1.1.1 无法访问或降级。根本原因是 BGP（边界网关协议）劫持和路由泄漏的混合</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Declare your AIndependence: block AI bots, scrapers and crawlers with a single click】宣告您的 AIndependence：只需单击一下即可阻止 AI 机器人、抓取工具和爬虫</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/declaring-your-aindependence-block-ai-bots-scrapers-and-crawlers-with-a-single-click</link>
      <description>【 To help preserve a safe Internet for content creators, we’ve just launched a brand new “easy button” to block all AI bots. It’s available for all customers, including those on our free tier 】为了帮助内容创作者维护安全的互联网，我们刚刚推出了一个全新的“简单按钮”来阻止所有人工智能机器人。它适用于所有客户，包括我们的免费套餐客户</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Embedded function calling in Workers AI: easier, smarter, faster】Workers AI 中的嵌入式函数调用：更简单、更智能、更快</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/embedded-function-calling</link>
      <description>【 Introducing a new way to do function calling in Workers AI by running function code alongside your inference. Plus, a new @cloudflare/ai-utils package to make getting started as simple as possible 】通过在推理的同时运行函数代码，引入了一种在 Workers AI 中进行函数调用的新方法。另外，新的 @cloudflare/ai-utils 包使入门尽可能简单</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Supporting Postgres Named Prepared Statements in Hyperdrive】在 Hyperdrive 中支持 Postgres 命名准备语句</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/postgres-named-prepared-statements-supported-hyperdrive</link>
      <description>【 Hyperdrive (Cloudflare’s globally distributed SQL connection pooler and cache) recently added support for Postgres protocol-level named prepared statements across pooled connections. We dive deep on what it took to add this feature 】Hyperdrive（Cloudflare 的全球分布式 SQL 连接池和缓存）最近添加了对跨池连接的 Postgres 协议级命名准备语句的支持。我们深入研究了添加此功能所需的内容</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Helping keep customers safe with leaked password notification】通过密码泄露通知帮助确保客户安全</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/helping-keep-customers-safe-with-leaked-password-notification</link>
      <description>【 To help protect against account compromise via credential stuffing attacks, Cloudflare will notify dashboard users when we detect that a password was found in an external data breach 】为了帮助防止帐户通过撞库攻击而被泄露，当我们检测到在外部数据泄露中发现密码时，Cloudflare 将通知仪表板用户</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 17:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How the first 2024 US presidential debate influenced Internet traffic and security trends】2024 年首场美国总统辩论如何影响互联网流量和安全趋势</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-the-first-2024-us-presidential-debate-influenced-internet-traffic-and-security-trends</link>
      <description>【 See how the first 2024 US presidential debate between Biden and Trump influenced Internet traffic patterns, email trends, and heightened cybersecurity concerns across digital platforms 】了解拜登和特朗普之间的 2024 年首场美国总统辩论如何影响互联网流量模式、电子邮件趋势以及数字平台上日益严重的网络安全问题</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare incident on June 20, 2024】2024 年 6 月 20 日的 Cloudflare 事件</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-incident-on-june-20-2024</link>
      <description>【 A new DDoS rule resulted in an increase in error responses and latency for Cloudflare customers. Here’s how it went wrong, and what we’ve learned 】新的 DDoS 规则导致 Cloudflare 客户的错误响应和延迟增加。这是错误的原因以及我们学到的教训</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 13:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automatically replacing polyfill.io links with Cloudflare’s mirror for a safer Internet】使用 Cloudflare 的镜像自动替换 polyfill.io 链接，以实现更安全的互联网</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/automatically-replacing-polyfill-io-links-with-cloudflares-mirror-for-a-safer-internet</link>
      <description>【 polyfill.io, a popular JavaScript library service, can no longer be trusted and should be removed from websites 】polyfill.io 是一种流行的 JavaScript 库服务，不再受信任，应从网站中删除</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 20:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【UK election day 2024: traffic trends and attacks on political parties】2024 年英国选举日：流量趋势和对政党的攻击</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/uk-election-day-2024-traffic-trends-and-attacks-on-political-parties</link>
      <description>【 Here, we explore the dynamics of Internet traffic and cybersecurity during the UK’s 2024 general election, highlighting late-day traffic changes and a post-vote attack on a political party 】在这里，我们探讨了英国 2024 年大选期间互联网流量和网络安全的动态，重点介绍了晚间流量变化和针对政党的投票后攻击</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>