<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Un experimento rápido: translating Cloudflare Stream captions with Workers AI】快速实验：使用 Workers AI 翻译 Cloudflare Stream 字幕</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/un-experimento-rapido-translating-cloudflare-stream-captions-with-workers-ai/</link>
      <description>【 How I used Workers AI to translate Cloudflare Stream’s auto-generated captions and what I learned along the way. 】我如何使用 Workers AI 翻译 Cloudflare Stream 自动生成的字幕以及我在此过程中学到的东西。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Robotcop: enforcing your robots.txt policies and stopping bots before they reach your website】Robotcop：执行您的 robots.txt 政策并在机器人到达您的网站之前将其阻止</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-audit-enforcing-robots-txt/</link>
      <description>【 Today, the AI Audit dashboard gets an upgrade: you can now quickly see which AI services are honoring your robots.txt policies and then automatically enforce the policies against those that aren’t.&#xA; 】今天，AI 审核仪表板进行了升级：您现在可以快速查看哪些 AI 服务遵守您的 robots.txt 策略，然后自动针对那些不遵守的 AI 服务强制执行这些策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Internationalization and localization: bringing Cloudflare Radar to a global audience】国际化和本地化：将 Cloudflare Radar 带给全球受众</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-radar-localization-journey/</link>
      <description>【 Internationalization and localization require more than translation: tone, images, date/time and number formatting, among other items, need to be considered. 】国际化和本地化需要的不仅仅是翻译：还需要考虑语气、图像、日期/时间和数字格式等。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When the world logs off: Christmas, New Year’s, and the Internet’s holiday rhythm】当世界关闭时：圣诞节、新年和互联网的节日节奏</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/when-the-world-logs-off-christmas-new-years-and-the-internets-holiday-rhythm/</link>
      <description>【 From Christmas Eve dinners in Europe to New Year’s Eve countdowns in Asia, Cloudflare data reveals how global festivities have typically shaped Internet usage and cultural rhythms 】从欧洲的圣诞夜晚餐到亚洲的除夕倒计时，Cloudflare 数据揭示了全球庆祝活动通常如何影响互联网使用和文化节奏</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hi Claude, build an MCP server on Cloudflare Workers】您好，Claude，在 Cloudflare Workers 上构建 MCP 服务器</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/model-context-protocol/</link>
      <description>【 Want Claude to interact with your app directly? Build an MCP server on Cloudflare Workers, enabling you to connect your service directly, allowing Claude to understand and run tasks on your behalf. 】希望 Claude 直接与您的应用程序交互吗？在 Cloudflare Workers 上构建 MCP 服务器，使您能够直接连接您的服务，让 Claude 能够代表您理解和运行任务。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Global elections in 2024: Internet traffic and cyber threat trends】2024 年全球选举：互联网流量和网络威胁趋势</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/elections-2024-internet/</link>
      <description>【 In 2024, as elections took place across over 60 countries, the Internet became both a battleground for cyberattacks and a vital platform for democratic engagement. 】2024 年，随着 60 多个国家举行选举，互联网既成为网络攻击的战场，又成为民主参与的重要平台。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grinch Bots strike again: defending your holidays from cyber threats】Grinch 机器人再次出击：保护您的假期免受网络威胁</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/grinch-bot-2024/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare observed a 4x increase in bot-related traffic on Black Friday in 2024. 29% of all traffic on our network on Black Friday was Grinch Bots wreaking holiday havoc. 】Cloudflare 观察到，2024 年黑色星期五与机器人相关的流量增加了 4 倍。黑色星期五我们网络上的所有流量中有 29% 是 Grinch 机器人造成的节日破坏。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bring multimodal real-time interaction to your AI applications with Cloudflare Calls】通过 Cloudflare Calls 将多模式实时交互引入您的 AI 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/bring-multimodal-real-time-interaction-to-your-ai-applications-with-cloudflare-calls/</link>
      <description>【 Bring ChatGPT to your next video meeting with Cloudflare Calls.  】通过 Cloudflare Calls 将 ChatGPT 带到您的下一次视频会议中。 </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The role of email security in reducing user risk amid rising threats】电子邮件安全在威胁不断增加的情况下降低用户风险的作用</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-role-of-email-security-in-reducing-user-risk-amid-rising-threats/</link>
      <description>【 As threats evolve, SOC teams must adapt their operations. With Cloudflare’s holistic approach to managing user-based risk, SOC teams can operate more efficiently and reduce the likelihood of a breach. 】随着威胁的演变，SOC 团队必须调整其运营。借助 Cloudflare 管理基于用户的风险的整体方法，SOC 团队可以更高效地运营并降低违规的可能性。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Sometimes I cache: implementing lock-free probabilistic caching】有时我缓存：实现无锁概率缓存</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/sometimes-i-cache/</link>
      <description>【 If you want to know what cache revalidation is, how it works, and why it can involve rolling a die, read on. This blog post presents a lock-free probabilistic approach to cache revalidation, along &#xA; 】如果您想了解什么是缓存重新验证、它是如何工作的以及为什么它会涉及掷骰子，请继续阅读。这篇博文提出了一种用于缓存重新验证的无锁概率方法，以及</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>