<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Simple, scalable, and global: Containers are coming to Cloudflare Workers in June 2025】简单，可扩展和全球：2025年6月的集装箱即将到达Cloudflare工人</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-containers-coming-2025/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Containers are coming this June. Run new types of workloads on our network with an experience that is simple, scalable, global and deeply integrated with Workers. 】Cloudflare容器将于今年6月到来。在我们的网络上运行新型的工作负载类型，具有简单，可扩展，全局且与工人深入融合的体验。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why I joined Cloudflare as Chief People Officer — Kelly Russell】为什么我加入Cloudflare担任首席人物 - 凯利·罗素（Kelly Russell）</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/why-i-joined-cloudflare-kelly-russell/</link>
      <description>【 After years navigating the world of high-growth tech, I’ve learned to recognize a special opportunity when I see one. That’s exactly why I’m thrilled to join Cloudflare as Chief People Officer.&#xA; 】经过多年的高增长技术世界，当我看到一个人时，我学会了认识到一个特殊的机会。这就是为什么我很高兴加入Cloudflare担任首席人物。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 19:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why I joined Cloudflare: to build world-class partnerships in EMEA 】为什么我加入CloudFlare：在EMEA建立世界一流的合作伙伴关系</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/why-i-joined-cloudflare-to-build-world-class-partnerships-in-emea/</link>
      <description>【 The EMEA region is a patchwork of diverse markets, industries, and regulatory environments, and it demands a partner-centric approach. That’s why I joined Cloudflare as VP of EMEA Partnerships. 】EMEA地区是各种市场，行业和监管环境的拼凑而成，它需要以合作伙伴为中心的方法。这就是为什么我加入CloudFlare担任EMEA合作伙伴关系副总裁。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How the April 28, 2025, power outage in Portugal and Spain impacted Internet traffic and connectivity】2025年4月28日，葡萄牙和西班牙的停电如何影响互联网流量和连通性</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-power-outage-in-portugal-spain-impacted-internet/</link>
      <description>【 A massive power outage struck significant portions of Portugal and Spain at 10:34 UTC on April 28, disrupting everyday activities and services. 】4月28日，UTC的大量停电袭击了葡萄牙和西班牙的大部分，破坏了日常活动和服务。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New year, no shutdowns: the Q1 2025 Internet disruption summary】新年，没有关闭：Q1 2025 Internet中断摘要</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/q1-2025-internet-disruption-summary/</link>
      <description>【 In Q1 2025, we observed Internet disruptions around the world caused by cable damage, power outages, natural disasters, fire, a cyberattack, and technical problems. 】在2025年第1季度，我们观察到由电缆损坏，停电，自然灾害，火灾，网络攻击和技术问题引起的世界各地的互联网中断。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Startup spotlight: building AI agents and accelerating innovation with Cohort #5】启动聚光灯：建立AI代理商并加速与队列的创新</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-agents-and-innovation-with-launchpad-cohort5/</link>
      <description>【 Discover how developers are using Cloudflare to scale AI workloads and streamline automation and how participants in Workers Launchpad Cohort #4 have built, and startups participating in Cohort #5 】查找开发人员如何使用CloudFlare来扩展AI工作负载和简化自动化以及工人的参与者如何构建了Launchpad Cohort＃4，以及参与COHORT＃5的初创公司</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Developer Week 2025 wrap-up】开发人员第2025周总结</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/developer-week-2025-wrap-up/</link>
      <description>【 We’ve closed out Developer Week 2025. Here’s a quick recap of the announcements and in-depth technical explorations that went out during the week. 】我们已经关闭了第2025周的开发人员。这是对一周内进行的公告和深入的技术探索的快速回顾。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Targeted by 20.5 million DDoS attacks, up 358% year-over-year: Cloudflare’s 2025 Q1 DDoS Threat Report】由2050万个DDOS攻击的目标，同比增长358％：Cloudflare的2025 Q1 DDOS威胁报告</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ddos-threat-report-for-2025-q1/</link>
      <description>【 DDoS attacks are surging. In 2025 Q1, Cloudflare blocked +20M attacks (a 358% YoY spike) along with 5.6 Tbps and 4.8 Bpps record-breaking attacks. 】DDOS攻击正在激增。在2025年第1季度，Cloudflare与5.6 TBP和4.8 BPP的创纪录攻击相同，阻塞了 +20m攻击（358％的尖峰）。</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bringing streamable HTTP transport and Python language support to MCP servers】将流媒体的HTTP传输和Python语言支持带到MCP服务器</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/streamable-http-mcp-servers-python/</link>
      <description>【 We&#39;re continuing to make it easier for developers to bring their services into the AI ecosystem with the Model Context Protocol (MCP) with two new updates. 】我们将继续通过模型上下文协议（MCP）进行两个新更新，使开发人员更容易将他们的服务带入AI生态系统。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A global virtual private cloud for building secure cross-cloud apps on Cloudflare Workers】用于在Cloudflare工人上构建安全横云应用程序的全局虚拟私有云</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-virtual-private-cloud/</link>
      <description>【 We’re announcing Workers VPC: a global private network that allows applications deployed on Cloudflare Workers to connect to your legacy cloud infrastructure.  】我们宣布工人VPC：一个全球专用网络，允许在CloudFlare工人上部署的应用程序连接到您的传统云基础架构。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>