<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Message Signatures are now part of our Verified Bots Program, simplifying bot authentication】消息签名现在是我们的认证机器人计划的一部分，简化了机器人身份验证</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/verified-bots-with-cryptography/</link>
      <description>【 Bots can start authenticating to Cloudflare using public key cryptography, preventing them from being spoofed and allowing origins to have confidence in their identity. 】 Bots can start authenticating to Cloudflare using public key cryptography, preventing them from being spoofed and allowing origins to have confidence in their identity. </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing pay per crawl: Enabling content owners to charge AI crawlers for access】Introducing pay per crawl: Enabling content owners to charge AI crawlers for access</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-pay-per-crawl/</link>
      <description>【 Pay per crawl is a new feature to allow content creators to charge AI crawlers for access to their content.  】按爬取付费是一项新功能，允许内容创作者对其内容的访问向AI爬虫收费。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How TimescaleDB helped us scale analytics and reporting】时间序列数据库如何帮助我们扩展分析和报告</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/timescaledb-art/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare chose TimescaleDB to power its Digital Experience Monitoring and Zero Trust Analytics products.  】Cloudflare选择TimescaleDB来为其数字体验监控和零信任分析产品提供支持。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing simple and secure egress policies by hostname in Cloudflare’s SASE platform】通过主机名在Cloudflare的SASE平台上引入简单且安全的出站策略</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/egress-policies-by-hostname/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare&#39;s SASE platform now offers egress policies by hostname, domain, content category, and application in open beta. 】Cloudflare的SASE平台现在在公开测试版中提供基于主机名、域名、内容类别和应用的出口策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Control content use for AI training with Cloudflare’s managed robots.txt and blocking for monetized content】使用 Cloudflare 的托管 robots.txt 和付费内容阻止功能来控制内容使用以用于 AI 训练</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/control-content-use-for-ai-training/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare is making it easier for publishers and content creators of all sizes to prevent their content from being scraped for AI training by managing robots.txt on their behalf.  】Cloudflare 正在使所有规模的出版商和内容创作者更容易防止他们的内容被用于人工智能训练的抓取，方法是代表他们管理 robots.txt。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Celebrate Micro-Small, and Medium-sized Enterprises Day with Cloudflare 】庆祝中小微企业日与Cloudflare一起</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/celebrate-micro-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-day-with-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 To celebrate United Nations Micro, Small, and Medium Sized Enterprises Day, Cloudflare is sharing success stories of small businesses building and growing on our platform. 】为庆祝联合国中小微企业日，Cloudflare正在分享在我们的平台上建立和成长的小企业成功故事。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Quicksilver v2: evolution of a globally distributed key-value store (Part 1)】闪电侠v2：全球分布式键值存储的演进（第一部分）</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/quicksilver-v2-evolution-of-a-globally-distributed-key-value-store-part-1/</link>
      <description>【 This blog post is the first of a series, in which we share our journey in redesigning Quicksilver — Cloudflare’s distributed key-value store that serves over 3 billion keys per second globally.  】这篇博文是系列文章的第一篇，我们将分享重新设计Quicksilver——Cloudflare的分布式键值存储系统——的历程，该系统每秒在全球范围内处理超过30亿个键。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Googlebot to GPTBot: who’s crawling your site in 2025】从Googlebot到GPTBot：2025年谁在爬取您的网站</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/from-googlebot-to-gptbot-whos-crawling-your-site-in-2025/</link>
      <description>【 From May 2024 to May 2025, crawler traffic rose 18%, with GPTBot growing 305% and Googlebot 96%. 】从2024年5月到2025年5月，爬虫流量增长了18%，其中GPTBot增长了305%，Googlebot增长了96%。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Content Independence Day: no AI crawl without compensation!】内容独立日：没有补偿，不许AI抓取！</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/content-independence-day-no-ai-crawl-without-compensation/</link>
      <description>【 It’s Content Independence Day: Cloudflare, along with a majority of the world&#39;s leading publishers and AI companies, is changing the default to block AI crawlers unless they pay creators for content. 】这是内容独立日：Cloudflare 与世界上大多数领先的出版商和人工智能公司一起，正在将默认设置更改为阻止人工智能爬虫，除非它们为内容支付给创作者。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The crawl before the fall… of referrals: understanding AI’s impact on content providers】跌倒前的爬行……推荐的衰落：理解人工智能对内容提供者的影响</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-search-crawl-refer-ratio-on-radar/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Radar now shows how often a given AI model sends traffic to a site relative to how often it crawls that site. This helps site owners make decisions about which AI bots to allow or block.&#xA; 】Cloudflare Radar现在显示给定AI模型相对于该网站爬取频率向该网站发送流量的频率。这有助于网站所有者决定允许或阻止哪些AI机器人。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>