<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Monitoring AS-SETs and why they matter】监视ASTES以及它们重要的原因</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/monitoring-as-sets-and-why-they-matter/</link>
      <description>【 We will cover some of the reasons why operators need to monitor the AS-SET memberships for their ASN, and now Cloudflare Radar can help.  】我们将介绍运营商需要监视其ASN的ASET成员资格的一些原因，而现在CloudFlare Radar可以提供帮助。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare just got faster and more secure, powered by Rust】Cloudflare刚刚变得更快，更安全，由Rust提供动力</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/20-percent-internet-upgrade/</link>
      <description>【 We’ve replaced the original core system in Cloudflare with a new modular Rust-based proxy, replacing NGINX.  】我们用新的基于模块化的锈蚀代理代替了Cloudflare的原始核心系统，以取代Nginx。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Observatory and Smart Shield — see how the world sees your website, and make it faster in one click】介绍天文台和智能盾牌 - 查看世界如何看待您的网站，并在一次点击中更快地使其更快</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-observatory-and-smart-shield/</link>
      <description>【 We&#39;re announcing two enhancements to our Application Performance suite that&#39;ll show how the world sees your website, and make it faster with one click - available Cloudflare Dashboard! 】我们宣布了我们的应用程序性能套件的两个增强功能，这些增强功能将显示世界如何看待您的网站，并通过一键单击 - 可用的Cloudflare仪表板更快！</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【An AI Index for all our customers】我们所有客户的AI指数</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/an-ai-index-for-all-our-customers/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare will soon automatically create an AI-optimized search index for your domain, and expose a set of ready-to-use standard APIs and tools including an MCP server, LLMs.txt, and a search API. 】CloudFlare将很快为您的域名创建AI优化的搜索索引，并揭示一组现成的标准API和包括MCP Server，LLMS.TXT和搜索API在内的现成标准API和工具。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Network performance update: Birthday Week 2025】网络绩效更新：2025年生日周</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/network-performance-update-birthday-week-2025/</link>
      <description>【 On the Internet, being fast is what matters and at Cloudflare, we are committed to being the fastest network in the world. 】在Internet上，快速至关重要，在Cloudflare中，我们致力于成为世界上最快的网络。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing new regional Internet traffic and Certificate Transparency insights on Cloudflare Radar】在Cloudflare Radar上引入新的区域互联网流量和证书透明度见解</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/new-regional-internet-traffic-and-certificate-transparency-insights-on-radar/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Radar now offers a Certificate Transparency dashboard for monitoring TLS certificate activity,  and new regional traffic insights for a sub-national perspective on Internet trends. 】CloudFlare Radar现在提供了一个证书透明度仪表板，用于监视TLS证书活动，以及新的区域交通见解，以对Internet趋势的次国家视角。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Eliminating Cold Starts 2: shard and conquer】消除寒冷开始2：碎片和征服</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/eliminating-cold-starts-2-shard-and-conquer/</link>
      <description>【 We reduced Cloudflare Workers cold starts by 10x by optimistically routing to servers with already-loaded Workers. Learn how we did it here. 】我们将Cloudflare工人的冷速度降低了10倍，通过与已经负载工人的服务器进行乐观的路由。了解我们在这里做的。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Code Mode: the better way to use MCP】代码模式：使用MCP的更好方法</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/code-mode/</link>
      <description>【 It turns out we&#39;ve all been using MCP wrong. Most agents today use MCP by exposing the &#34;tools&#34; directly to the LLM. 】事实证明，我们都在使用MCP错误。如今，大多数代理商通过将“工具”直接暴露于LLM来使用MCP。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Cloudflare uses the world’s greatest collection of performance data to make the world’s fastest global network even faster】CloudFlare如何使用世界上最大的性能数据集来使世界上最快的全球网络更快</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-cloudflare-uses-the-worlds-greatest-collection-of-performance-data/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare is using its vast traffic to send responses faster than ever before, by learning the characteristics of each individual network and tuning our congestion control system.    】通过学习每个单独的网络的特征并调整我们的拥塞控制系统，CloudFlare正在使用其庞大的流量来更快地发送响应。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Every Cloudflare feature, available to everyone】每个Cloudflare功能，每个人都可以使用</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/enterprise-grade-features-for-all/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare is making every feature available to any customer. 】CloudFlare正在为任何客户提供所有功能。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>