<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Trapping misbehaving bots in an AI Labyrinth】在AI迷宫中捕获不良的机器人</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-labyrinth/</link>
      <description>【 How Cloudflare uses generative AI to slow down, confuse, and waste the resources of AI Crawlers and other bots that don’t respect “no crawl” directives. 】CloudFlare如何使用生成的AI减慢，混淆和浪费不尊重“无爬行”指令的AI爬网机的资源和其他机器人的资源。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Improved Bot Management flexibility and visibility with new high-precision heuristics】通过新的高精度启发式方法提高了机器人管理的灵活性和可见度</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/bots-heuristics/</link>
      <description>【 By building and integrating a new heuristics framework into the Cloudflare Ruleset Engine, we now have a more flexible system to write rules and deploy new releases rapidly. 】通过将新的启发式框架构建和集成到Cloudflare Ruleset引擎中，我们现在有一个更灵活的系统来编写规则并迅速部署新版本。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How we train AI to uncover malicious JavaScript intent and make web surfing safer】我们如何训练AI发现恶意的JavaScript意图并使网络冲浪更安全</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-we-train-ai-to-uncover-malicious-javascript-intent-and-make-web-surfing-safer/</link>
      <description>【 Learn more about how Cloudflare developed an AI model to uncover malicious JavaScript intent using a Graph Neural Network, from pre-processing data to inferencing at scale.  】了解有关CloudFlare如何开发AI模型的更多信息，以使用图形神经网络（从预处理数据到大规模推论）发现恶意JavaScript意图。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Extending Cloudflare Radar’s security insights with new DDoS, leaked credentials, and bots datasets】使用新的DDO，泄漏的凭据和机器人数据集扩展CloudFlare Radar的安全见解</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-radar-ddos-leaked-credentials-bots/</link>
      <description>【 For Security Week 2025, we are adding several new DDoS-focused graphs, new insights into leaked credential trends, and a new Bots page to Cloudflare Radar.  】在2025年安全周中，我们正在添加几个新的以DDOS为中心的图形，对泄漏凭证趋势的新见解以及新的机器人页面为CloudFlare Radar。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare enables native monitoring and forensics with Log Explorer and custom dashboards】CloudFlare可以使用Log Explorer和自定义仪表板启用本机监视和取证</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/monitoring-and-forensics/</link>
      <description>【 Today we are excited to announce support for Zero Trust datasets, and custom dashboards where customers can monitor critical metrics for suspicious or unusual activity.  】今天，我们很高兴宣布对零信任数据集的支持，以及客户可以监视关键指标的可疑或异常活动的自定义仪表板。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare for AI: supporting AI adoption at scale with a security-first approach】AI的CloudFlare：以安全优先的方法进行大规模支持AI采用</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-for-ai-supporting-ai-adoption-at-scale-with-a-security-first-approach/</link>
      <description>【 With Cloudflare for AI, developers, security teams and content creators can leverage Cloudflare’s network and portfolio of tools to secure, observe and make AI applications resilient and safe to use. 】借助AI的CloudFlare，开发人员，安全团队和内容创建者可以利用Cloudflare的网络和工具组合来保护，观察和使AI应用程序具有弹性且安全使用。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unleashing improved context for threat actor activity with our Cloudforce One threat events platform】使用我们的Cloudforce一个威胁事件平台释放提高的威胁参与者活动的上下文</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/threat-events-platform/</link>
      <description>【 Gain real-time insights with our new threat events platform. This tool empowers your cybersecurity defense with actionable intelligence to stay ahead of attacks and protect your critical assets. 】通过我们的新威胁事件平台获得实时见解。该工具通过可行的情报使您的网络安全防御能力保持领先地位并保护您的关键资产。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【An early look at cryptographic watermarks for AI-generated content】早期查看AI生成内容的加密水印</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/an-early-look-at-cryptographic-watermarks-for-ai-generated-content/</link>
      <description>【 It&#39;s hard to tell the difference between web content produced by humans and web content produced by AI. We&#39;re taking new approach to making AI content distinguishable without impacting performance.  】很难说出人类生成的Web内容与AI生产的Web内容之间的区别。我们正在采用新的方法来使AI内容可区分不影响性能。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Upgraded Turnstile Analytics enable deeper insights, faster investigations, and improved security】升级的旋转门分析可实现更深入的见解，更快的调查和改进的安全性</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/upgraded-turnstile-analytics-enable-deeper-insights-faster-investigations/</link>
      <description>【 Introducing new Turnstile Analytics: Gain insight into your visitor traffic, bot behavior patterns, traffic anomalies, and attack attributes. 】引入新的旋转门分析：洞悉访客流量，机器人行为模式，流量异常和攻击属性。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Take control of public AI application security with Cloudflare&#39;s Firewall for AI】使用Cloudflare的防火墙来控制公共AI应用程序安全</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/take-control-of-public-ai-application-security-with-cloudflare-firewall-for-ai/</link>
      <description>【 Firewall for AI discovers and protects your public LLM-powered applications, and is seamlessly integrated with Cloudflare WAF. Join the beta now and take control of your generative AI security. 】AI的防火墙发现并保护您的公共LLM驱动应用程序，并与Cloudflare WAF无缝集成。立即加入Beta，并控制您的生成AI安全性。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>