<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Get better visibility for the WAF with payload logging】通过有效负载日志记录获得 WAF 的更好可见性</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/waf-payload-logging/</link>
      <description>【 The WAF provides ways for our customers to gain insight into why it takes certain actions. The more granular and precise the insight, the more reproducible and understandable it is. Revamped payload logging is one such method.  】WAF 为我们的客户提供了深入了解其采取某些操作的原因的方法。洞察力越细致、越精确，它的可重复性和可理解性就越高。改进的有效负载日志记录就是其中一种方法。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare outage on November 18, 2025】Cloudflare 于 2025 年 11 月 18 日中断</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/18-november-2025-outage/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare suffered a service outage on November 18, 2025. The outage was triggered by a bug in generation logic for a Bot Management feature file causing many Cloudflare services to be affected. &#xA; 】Cloudflare 于 2025 年 11 月 18 日发生服务中断。此次中断是由机器人管理功能文件的生成逻辑错误引发的，导致许多 Clo​​udflare 服务受到影响。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Replicate is joining Cloudflare】Replicate 正在加入 Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/replicate-joins-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 Bringing Replicate’s tools into Cloudflare will continue to make our Workers Platform the best place on the Internet to build and deploy any AI or agentic workflow.&#xA; 】将 Replicate 的工具引入 Cloudflare 将继续使我们的 Workers Platform 成为互联网上构建和部署任何 AI 或代理工作流程的最佳场所。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Finding the grain of sand in a heap of Salt】在盐堆中寻找沙粒</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/finding-the-grain-of-sand-in-a-heap-of-salt/</link>
      <description>【 We explore the fundamentals of Saltstack and how we use it at Cloudflare. We also explain how we built the infrastructure to reduce release delays due to Salt failures on the edge by over 5%.  】我们探索 Saltstack 的基础知识以及如何在 Cloudflare 中使用它。我们还解释了我们如何构建基础设施，以将由于边缘 Salt 故障而导致的发布延迟减少 5% 以上。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Connecting to production: the architecture of remote bindings】连接到生产：远程绑定的架构</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/connecting-to-production-the-architecture-of-remote-bindings/</link>
      <description>【 Remote bindings allow you to connect your local Worker code to deployed Cloudflare resources like R2 and D1. Come along on the technical journey of how we built this feature to create a seamless local development experience. 】远程绑定允许您将本地 Worker 代码连接到已部署的 Cloudflare 资源（例如 R2 和 D1）。跟随我们的技术之旅，了解我们如何构建此功能以创建无缝的本地开发体验。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A closer look at Python Workflows, now in beta】仔细研究 Python 工作流程，现在处于测试阶段</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/python-workflows/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Workflows, our durable execution engine for running multi-step applications, now supports Python. That means less friction, more possibilities, and another reason to build on Cloudflare. 】Cloudflare Workflows 是我们用于运行多步骤应用程序的持久执行引擎，现在支持 Python。这意味着更少的摩擦、更多的可能性，也是在 Cloudflare 上构建的另一个原因。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DIY BYOIP: a new way to Bring Your Own IP prefixes to Cloudflare】DIY BYOIP：将您自己的 IP 前缀引入 Cloudflare 的新方法</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/diy-byoip/</link>
      <description>【 Announcing a new self-serve API for Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP), giving customers unprecedented control and flexibility to onboard, manage, and use their own IP prefixes with Cloudflare&#39;s services. 】宣布推出用于自带 IP (BYOIP) 的新自助服务 API，为客户提供前所未有的控制力和灵活性，让他们能够通过 Cloudflare 的服务加入、管理和使用自己的 IP 前缀。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Extract audio from your videos with Cloudflare Stream】使用 Cloudflare Stream 从视频中提取音频</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/extract-audio-from-your-videos-with-cloudflare-stream/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Stream provides a unified platform for video storage, encoding, and delivery. We are now enabling developers to seamlessly extract audio from videos. 】Cloudflare Stream 提供了一个用于视频存储、编码和传输的统一平台。我们现在使开发人员能够从视频中无缝提取音频。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Async QUIC and HTTP/3 made easy: tokio-quiche is now open-source】异步 QUIC 和 HTTP/3 变得简单：tokio-quiche 现已开源</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/async-quic-and-http-3-made-easy-tokio-quiche-is-now-open-source/</link>
      <description>【 We’re excited to announce the open sourcing of tokio-quiche, our async QUIC library built on quiche and tokio. Relied upon in our services such as iCloud Private Relay and our next-generation Oxy-based proxies, tokio-quiche handles millions of HTTP/3 requests per second with low latency and high throughput.  】我们很高兴地宣布 tokio-quiche 开源，这是我们基于 quiche 和 tokio 构建的异步 QUIC 库。依赖于我们的 iCloud Private Relay 和下一代基于 Oxy 的代理等服务，tokio-quiche 每秒可处理数百万个 HTTP/3 请求，并且具有低延迟和高吞吐量。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Workers VPC Services connects to your regional private networks from anywhere in the world】Workers VPC 服务如何从世界任何地方连接到您的区域专用网络</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-vpc-open-beta/</link>
      <description>【 Workers VPC Services enter open beta today. We look under the hood to see how Workers VPC connects your globally-deployed Workers to your regional private networks by using Cloudflare&#39;s global network, while abstracting cross-cloud networking complexity. 】Workers VPC 服务今天进入公开测试版。我们深入了解 Workers VPC 如何使用 Cloudflare 的全球网络将全球部署的 Workers 连接到您的区域专用网络，同时抽象出跨云网络的复杂性。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>