<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【DIY BYOIP: a new way to Bring Your Own IP prefixes to Cloudflare】DIY BYOIP：将您自己的 IP 前缀引入 Cloudflare 的新方法</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/diy-byoip/</link>
      <description>【 Announcing a new self-serve API for Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP), giving customers unprecedented control and flexibility to onboard, manage, and use their own IP prefixes with Cloudflare&#39;s services. 】宣布推出用于自带 IP (BYOIP) 的新自助服务 API，为客户提供前所未有的控制力和灵活性，让他们能够通过 Cloudflare 的服务加入、管理和使用自己的 IP 前缀。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Extract audio from your videos with Cloudflare Stream】使用 Cloudflare Stream 从视频中提取音频</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/extract-audio-from-your-videos-with-cloudflare-stream/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Stream provides a unified platform for video storage, encoding, and delivery. We are now enabling developers to seamlessly extract audio from videos. 】Cloudflare Stream 提供了一个用于视频存储、编码和传输的统一平台。我们现在使开发人员能够从视频中无缝提取音频。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Async QUIC and HTTP/3 made easy: tokio-quiche is now open-source】异步 QUIC 和 HTTP/3 变得简单：tokio-quiche 现已开源</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/async-quic-and-http-3-made-easy-tokio-quiche-is-now-open-source/</link>
      <description>【 We’re excited to announce the open sourcing of tokio-quiche, our async QUIC library built on quiche and tokio. Relied upon in our services such as iCloud Private Relay and our next-generation Oxy-based proxies, tokio-quiche handles millions of HTTP/3 requests per second with low latency and high throughput.  】我们很高兴地宣布 tokio-quiche 开源，这是我们基于 quiche 和 tokio 构建的异步 QUIC 库。依赖于我们的 iCloud Private Relay 和下一代基于 Oxy 的代理等服务，tokio-quiche 每秒可处理数百万个 HTTP/3 请求，并且具有低延迟和高吞吐量。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Workers VPC Services connects to your regional private networks from anywhere in the world】Workers VPC 服务如何从世界任何地方连接到您的区域专用网络</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-vpc-open-beta/</link>
      <description>【 Workers VPC Services enter open beta today. We look under the hood to see how Workers VPC connects your globally-deployed Workers to your regional private networks by using Cloudflare&#39;s global network, while abstracting cross-cloud networking complexity. 】Workers VPC 服务今天进入公开测试版。我们深入了解 Workers VPC 如何使用 Cloudflare 的全球网络将全球部署的 Workers 连接到您的区域专用网络，同时抽象出跨云网络的复杂性。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a better testing experience for Workflows, our durable execution engine for multi-step applications】为工作流程构建更好的测试体验，工作流程是我们针对多步骤应用程序的持久执行引擎</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/better-testing-for-workflows/</link>
      <description>【 End-to-end testing for Cloudflare Workflows was challenging. We&#39;re introducing first-class support for Workflows in cloudflare:test, enabling full introspection, mocking, and isolated, reliable tests for your most complex applications. 】Cloudflare Workflows 的端到端测试具有挑战性。我们在 cloudflare:test 中引入了对工作流程的一流支持，为您最复杂的应用程序提供全面的内省、模拟和独立、可靠的测试。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fresh insights from old data: corroborating reports of Turkmenistan IP unblocking and firewall testing】旧数据的新见解：证实土库曼斯坦 IP 解锁和防火墙测试的报告</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/fresh-insights-from-old-data-corroborating-reports-of-turkmenistan-ip/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare used historical data to investigate reports of potential new firewall tests in Turkmenistan. Shifts in TCP resets/timeouts across ASNs corroborate large-scale network control system changes.&#xA; 】Cloudflare 使用历史数据来调查土库曼斯坦潜在的新防火墙测试报告。 ASN 中 TCP 重置/超时的变化证实了大规模网络控制系统的变化。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【BGP zombies and excessive path hunting】BGP 僵尸和过度路径搜索</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/going-bgp-zombie-hunting/</link>
      <description>【 A BGP “zombie” is essentially a route that has become stuck in the Default-Free Zone (DFZ) of the Internet, potentially due to a missed or lost prefix withdrawal. We’ll walk through some situations where BGP zombies are more likely to rise from the dead and wreak havoc.&#xA; 】BGP“僵尸”本质上是一条被困在互联网默认自由区 (DFZ) 中的路由，可能是由于错过或丢失了前缀撤销而导致的。我们将介绍一些 BGP 僵尸更有可能起死回生并造成严重破坏的情况。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go and enhance your calm: demolishing an HTTP/2 interop problem】去增强你的冷静：解决 HTTP/2 互操作问题</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/go-and-enhance-your-calm/</link>
      <description>【 HTTP/2 implementations often respond to suspected attacks by closing the connection with an ENHANCE_YOUR_CALM error code. Learn how a common pattern of using Go&#39;s HTTP/2 client can lead to unintended errors and the solution to avoiding them. 】HTTP/2 实现通常通过使用 ENHANCE_YOUR_CALM 错误代码关闭连接来响应可疑的攻击。了解使用 Go 的 HTTP/2 客户端的常见模式如何导致意外错误以及避免这些错误的解决方案。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond IP lists: a registry format for bots and agents】超越 IP 列表：机器人和代理的注册表格式</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/agent-registry/</link>
      <description>【 We propose an open registry format for Web Bot Auth to move beyond IP-based identity. This allows any origin to discover and verify cryptographic keys for bots, fostering a decentralized and more trustworthy ecosystem. 】我们为 Web Bot Auth 提出了一种开放的注册表格式，以超越基于 IP 的身份。这使得任何来源都可以发现和验证机器人的加密密钥，从而培育一个去中心化且更值得信赖的生态系统。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Anonymous credentials: rate-limiting bots and agents without compromising privacy】匿名凭证：在不损害隐私的情况下限制机器人和代理的速率</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/private-rate-limiting/</link>
      <description>【 As AI agents change how the Internet is used, they create a challenge for security. We explore how Anonymous Credentials can rate limit agent traffic and block abuse without tracking users or compromising their privacy. 】随着人工智能代理改变互联网的使用方式，它们给安全带来了挑战。我们探讨匿名凭证如何在不跟踪用户或损害其隐私的情况下限制代理流量并阻止滥用。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>