<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Wrapping up another Birthday Week celebration】结束另一个生日周庆祝活动</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/birthday-week-2024-wrap-up</link>
      <description>【 Recapping all the big announcements made during 2024’s Birthday Week. 】回顾 2024 年生日周期间发布的所有重大公告。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Builder Day 2024: 18 big updates to the Workers platform】2024 年建造者日：Workers 平台的 18 项重大更新</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/builder-day-2024-announcements</link>
      <description>【 To celebrate Builder Day 2024, we’re shipping 18 updates inspired by direct feedback from developers building on Cloudflare. This includes new capabilities, like running evals with AI Gateway, beta products like Queues and Vectorize graduating to GA, massive speed improvements to KV and Workers AI, pricing simplifications, and bringing key features from Pages into Workers. 】为了庆祝 2024 年 Builder Day，我们发布了 18 项更新，这些更新的灵感来自于在 Cloudflare 上构建的开发人员的直接反馈。这包括新功能，例如使用 AI Gateway 运行评估、队列和 Vectorize 等测试版产品升级为 GA、KV 和 Workers AI 的大幅速度改进、定价简化以及将 Pages 的关键功能引入 Workers。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Our container platform is in production. It has GPUs. Here’s an early look】我们的容器平台正在生产中。它有 GPU。这是早期的样子</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/container-platform-preview</link>
      <description>【 We’ve been working on something new — a platform for running containers across Cloudflare’s network. We already use it in production, for AI inference and more. Today we want to share an early look at how it’s built, why we built it, and how we use it ourselves.&#xA; 】我们一直在致力于开发新的东西——一个在 Cloudflare 网络上运行容器的平台。我们已经在生产中使用它，用于人工智能推理等。今天我们想分享一下它是如何构建的、我们为什么构建它以及我们如何自己使用它。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reaffirming our commitment to free】重申我们对免费的承诺</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflares-commitment-to-free</link>
      <description>【 Today Cloudflare reaffirms its commitment to offering a robust Free service tier that continues to improve. We share why Free is a cornerstone of our business strategy, and how it contributes to building a better Internet.&#xA; 】今天，Cloudflare 重申其致力于提供持续改进的强大免费服务层的承诺。我们分享为什么免费是我们业务战略的基石，以及它如何为建设更好的互联网做出贡献。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advancing cybersecurity: Cloudflare implements a new bug bounty VIP program as part of CISA Pledge commitment】推进网络安全：Cloudflare 实施新的错误赏金 VIP 计划，作为 CISA Pledge 承诺的一部分</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cisa-pledge-commitment-bug-bounty-vip</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare strengthens its commitment to cybersecurity by joining CISA&#39;s &#34;Secure by Design&#34; pledge. In line with this commitment, we&#39;re enhancing our vulnerability disclosure policy by launching a VIP bug bounty program, giving top researchers early access to our products. Keep an eye out for future updates regarding Cloudflare&#39;s CISA pledge as we work together to shape a safer digital future. 】Cloudflare 通过加入 CISA 的“安全设计”承诺，加强了其对网络安全的承诺。根据这一承诺，我们正在通过启动 VIP 漏洞赏金计划来增强我们的漏洞披露政策，让顶尖研究人员能够尽早访问我们的产品。请密切关注有关 Cloudflare CISA 承诺的未来更新，我们将共同努力塑造更安全的数字未来。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Empowering builders: introducing the Dev Alliance and Workers Launchpad Cohort #4】为构建者赋权：引入开发联盟和 Workers Launchpad Cohort #4</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/launchpad-cohort4-dev-starter-pack</link>
      <description>【 Empowering developers with the Dev Starter Pack and Workers Cohort #4: get free or discounted access to essential developer tools and meet the latest set of incredible startups building on Cloudflare. 】通过 Dev Starter Pack 和 Workers Cohort #4 为开发人员提供支持：免费或以折扣价访问基本开发人员工具，并会见在 Cloudflare 上构建的最新一批令人难以置信的初创公司。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Impact of Verizon’s September 30 outage on Internet traffic】Verizon 9 月 30 日断电对互联网流量的影响</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/impact-of-verizons-september-30-outage-on-internet-traffic</link>
      <description>【 On Monday, September 30, customers on Verizon’s mobile network in multiple cities across the United States reported experiencing a loss of connectivity. HTTP request traffic data from Verizon’s mobile ASN (AS6167) showed nominal declines across impacted cities.&#xA; 】9 月 30 日星期一，美国多个城市的 Verizon 移动网络客户报告称遇到了连接中断的情况。来自 Verizon 移动 ASN (AS6167) 的 HTTP 请求流量数据显示受影响城市的名义流量有所下降。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Everywhere with the WAF Rule Builder Assistant, Cloudflare Radar AI Insights, and updated AI bot protection】借助 WAF 规则生成器助手、Cloudflare Radar AI Insights 和更新的 AI 机器人防护，AI 无处不在</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/bringing-ai-to-cloudflare</link>
      <description>【 This year for Cloudflare’s birthday, we’ve extended our AI Assistant capabilities to help you build new WAF rules, added new AI bot &amp; crawler traffic insights to Radar, and given customers new AI bot blocking capabilities 】今年是 Cloudflare 的生日，我们扩展了 AI 助手功能，帮助您构建新的 WAF 规则，为 Radar 添加了新的 AI 机器人和爬虫流量洞察，并为客户提供了新的 AI 机器人拦截功能</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Network trends and natural language: Cloudflare Radar’s new Data Explorer &amp; AI Assistant】网络趋势和自然语言：Cloudflare Radar 的新数据浏览器和 AI 助手</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-data-explorer-ai-assistant</link>
      <description>【 The Cloudflare Radar Data Explorer provides a simple Web-based interface to build more complex API queries, including comparisons and filters, and visualize the results. The accompanying AI Assistant translates a user’s natural language statements or questions into the appropriate Radar API calls. 】Cloudflare Radar Data Explorer 提供了一个简单的基于 Web 的界面来构建更复杂的 API 查询（包括比较和过滤器）以及可视化结果。随附的 AI 助手将用户的自然语言陈述或问题翻译为适当的 Radar API 调用。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Expanding Cloudflare&#39;s support for open source projects with Project Alexandria】通过 Project Alexandria 扩展 Cloudflare 对开源项目的支持</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/expanding-our-support-for-oss-projects-with-project-alexandria</link>
      <description>【 At Cloudflare, we believe in the power of open source. With Project Alexandria, our expanded open source program, we’re helping open source projects have a sustainable and scalable future, providing them with the tools and protection needed to thrive. 】在 Cloudflare，我们相信开源的力量。通过我们扩展的开源项目 Alexandria 项目，我们正在帮助开源项目拥有可持续和可扩展的未来，为它们提供蓬勃发展所需的工具和保护。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>