<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare’s 2024 Transparency Reports - now live with new data and a new format】Cloudflare的2024年透明度报告 - 现在使用新数据和新格式</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-2024-transparency-reports-now-live-with-new-data-and-a-new-format/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare’s 2024 Transparency Reports are now live — with new topics, new data points, and a new format, consistent with the EU’s Digital Services Act 】CloudFlare的2024年透明度报告现已发挥作用 - 具有新的主题，新的数据点和新格式，与《欧盟的数字服务法》一致</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【QUIC action: patching a broadcast address amplification vulnerability】QUIC操作：修补广播地址放大漏洞</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/mitigating-broadcast-address-attack/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare was recently contacted by researchers who discovered a broadcast amplification vulnerability through their QUIC Internet measurement research. We&#39;ve implemented a mitigation. 】最近，研究人员联系了Cloudflare，他们通过其Quic Internet测量研究发现了广播放大漏洞。我们已经实施了缓解措施。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automatic Audit Logs: new updates deliver increased transparency and accountability】自动审核日志：新更新提供了提高的透明度和问责制</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/introducing-automatic-audit-logs/</link>
      <description>【 We’re excited to announce the beta release of Automatic Audit Logs, offering greater transparency and control. 】我们很高兴宣布Beta版本的自动审核日志发布，提供更大的透明度和控制。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Some TXT about, and A PTR to, new DNS insights on Cloudflare Radar】关于Cloudflare Radar的新DNS见解，还有一些txt和PTR</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/new-dns-section-on-cloudflare-radar/</link>
      <description>【 The new Cloudflare Radar DNS page provides increased visibility into aggregate traffic and usage trends seen by our 1.1.1.1 resolver 】新的CloudFlare Radar DNS页面提供了对总流量和使用趋势的可见性，我们的1.1.1.1解析器可见</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Searching for the cause of hung tasks in the Linux kernel】在Linux内核中搜索悬挂任务的原因</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/searching-for-the-cause-of-hung-tasks-in-the-linux-kernel/</link>
      <description>【 The Linux kernel can produce a hung task warning. Searching the Internet and the kernel docs, you can find a brief explanation that the process is stuck in the uninterruptible state. 】Linux内核可以发出悬挂的任务警告。在搜索Internet和内核文档时，您可以简要说明该过程陷入了不间断的状态。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Keep AI interactions secure and risk-free with Guardrails in AI Gateway】通过AI网关中的护栏保持AI相互作用安全且无风险</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/guardrails-in-ai-gateway/</link>
      <description>【 Deploy AI safely with built-in Guardrails in AI Gateway. Flag and block harmful or inappropriate content, protect personal data, and ensure compliance in real-time 】在AI网关中使用内置的护栏安全部署AI。标记并阻止有害或不适当的内容，保护个人数据，并确保实时合规</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Offline celebrations: how Christmas, NYE, and Lunar New Year festivities shape online behavior】离线庆祝活动：圣诞节，NYE和LUNAR新年庆祝活动如何塑造在线行为</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/offline-celebrations-how-christmas-nye-and-lunar-new-year-festivities-shape-online-behavior/</link>
      <description>【 This blog examines how diverse cultural celebrations — from Western Christmas to Orthodox and Lunar New Year festivities — shape global Internet traffic. 】该博客探讨了各种文化庆典（从西部圣诞节到东正教和农历新年庆祝活动）如何塑造全球互联网流量。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Helping civil society monitor cyber attacks with the CyberPeaceTracer and Cloudflare Email Security 】帮助民间社会通过网络配置器和CloudFlare电子邮件安全性监测网络攻击</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/helping-civil-society-monitor-attacks-with-the-cyberpeacetracer-and-cloudflare-email-security/</link>
      <description>【 We’re proud to collaborate with CyberPeace Institute by powering its latest initiative, the CyberPeace Tracer, a platform that enables civil society organizations to proactively report cyber threats. 】我们很荣幸通过为网络和平研究所合作，通过为Cyber​​peace Tracer提供动力，该计划使民间社会组织能够主动报告网络威胁。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Making Cloudflare the best platform for building AI Agents】使CloudFlare成为建立AI代理的最佳平台</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/build-ai-agents-on-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 Today we’re excited to share a few announcements on how we’re making it even easier to build AI agents on Cloudflare. 】今天，我们很高兴分享一些关于我们如何使在Cloudflare上构建AI代理商变得更加容易的公告。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Banish bots from your Waiting Room and improve wait times for real users】从候车室驱逐机器人，改善了真正用户的等待时间</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/banish-bots-from-your-waiting-room-and-improve-wait-times-for-real-users/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare Waiting Room is improving the user experience through the addition of Turnstile and Session Revocation, keeping wait times low and protecting against bot traffic. 】CloudFlare等候室通过添加旋转门和会话撤销来改善用户体验，使等待时间较低并防止机器人流量。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>