<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【BGP zombies and excessive path hunting】BGP 僵尸和过度路径搜索</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/going-bgp-zombie-hunting/</link>
      <description>【 A BGP “zombie” is essentially a fancy name for a route that has become stuck in the Default-Free Zone (DFZ) of the Internet, potentially due to a missed or lost prefix withdrawal. &#xA;&#xA;In this post, we will walk through some situations where BGP zombies are more likely to rise from the dead and wreak havoc, how excessive path hunting can contribute to longer periods of impact, and some recommendations and follow-ups we have put together to make them less likely. &#xA; 】BGP“僵尸”本质上是一个奇特的名称，指的是一条陷入互联网默认自由区 (DFZ) 的路由，可能是由于错过或丢失了前缀撤销而导致的。 &#xA;&#xA;在这篇文章中，我们将介绍 BGP 僵尸更有可能死而复生并造成严重破坏的一些情况，过度的路径搜索如何导致更长的影响时间，以及我们为降低这种可能性而汇总的一些建议和后续措施。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go and enhance your calm: demolishing an HTTP/2 interop problem】去增强你的冷静：解决 HTTP/2 互操作问题</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/go-and-enhance-your-calm/</link>
      <description>【 HTTP/2 implementations often respond to suspected attacks by closing the connection with an ENHANCE_YOUR_CALM error code. Learn how a common pattern of using Go&#39;s HTTP/2 client can lead to unintended errors and the solution to avoiding them. 】HTTP/2 实现通常通过使用 ENHANCE_YOUR_CALM 错误代码关闭连接来响应可疑的攻击。了解使用 Go 的 HTTP/2 客户端的常见模式如何导致意外错误以及避免这些错误的解决方案。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond IP lists: a registry format for bots and agents】超越 IP 列表：机器人和代理的注册表格式</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/agent-registry/</link>
      <description>【 We propose an open registry format for Web Bot Auth to move beyond IP-based identity. This allows any origin to discover and verify cryptographic keys for bots, fostering a decentralized and more trustworthy ecosystem. 】我们为 Web Bot Auth 提出了一种开放的注册表格式，以超越基于 IP 的身份。这使得任何来源都可以发现和验证机器人的加密密钥，从而培育一个去中心化且更值得信赖的生态系统。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Anonymous credentials: rate-limiting bots and agents without compromising privacy】匿名凭证：在不损害隐私的情况下限制机器人和代理的速率</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/private-rate-limiting/</link>
      <description>【 As AI agents change how the Internet is used, they create a challenge for security. We explore how Anonymous Credentials can rate limit agent traffic and block abuse without tracking users or compromising their privacy. 】随着人工智能代理改变互联网的使用方式，它们给安全带来了挑战。我们探讨匿名凭证如何在不跟踪用户或损害其隐私的情况下限制代理流量并阻止滥用。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Policy, privacy and post-quantum: anonymous credentials for everyone】政策、隐私和后量子：每个人的匿名凭证</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/pq-anonymous-credentials/</link>
      <description>【 The world is adopting anonymous credentials for digital privacy, but these systems are vulnerable to quantum computers. This post explores the cryptographic challenges and promising research paths toward building new, quantum-resistant credentials from the ground up. 】世界正在采用匿名凭证来保护数字隐私，但这些系统很容易受到量子计算机的攻击。这篇文章探讨了密码学挑战和从头开始构建新的抗量子凭证的有前途的研究路径。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to build your own VPN, or: the history of WARP】如何建立自己的VPN，或者：WARP的历史</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-to-build-your-own-vpn-or-the-history-of-warp/</link>
      <description>【 WARP’s initial implementation resembled a VPN that allows Internet access through it. Here’s how we built it – and how you can, too.  】WARP 的最初实现类似于允许通过它访问互联网的 VPN。以下是我们如何构建它——以及您也可以如何构建它。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【So long, and thanks for all the fish: how to escape the Linux networking stack】这么久了，感谢所有的鱼：如何逃离 Linux 网络堆栈</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/so-long-and-thanks-for-all-the-fish-how-to-escape-the-linux-networking-stack/</link>
      <description>【 Many products at Cloudflare aren’t possible without pushing the limits of network hardware and software to deliver improved performance, increased efficiency, or novel capabilities such as soft-unicast, our method for sharing IP subnets across data centers. Happily, most people do not need to know the intricacies of how your operating system handles network and Internet access in general. Yes, even most people within Cloudflare. But sometimes we try to push well beyond the design intentions of Linux’s networking stack. This is a story about one of those attempts. 】Cloudflare 的许多产品如果不突破网络硬件和软件的限制，就不可能提供改进的性能、更高的效率或新颖的功能，例如软单播（我们在数据中心之间共享 IP 子网的方法）。令人高兴的是，大多数人不需要了解操作系统如何处理网络和互联网访问的复杂性。是的，甚至 Cloudflare 内的大多数人也是如此。但有时我们试图远远超出 Linux 网络堆栈的设计意图。这是一个关于其中一次尝试的故事。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【One IP address, many users: detecting CGNAT to reduce collateral effects】一个IP地址，多个用户：检测CGNAT以减少附带影响</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/detecting-cgn-to-reduce-collateral-damage/</link>
      <description>【 IPv4 scarcity drives widespread use of Carrier-Grade Network Address Translation, a practice in ISPs and mobile networks that places many users behind each IP address, along with their collected activity and volumes of traffic. We introduce the method we’ve developed to detect large-scale IP sharing globally and mitigate the issues that result.  】IPv4 的稀缺性推动了运营商级网络地址转换的广泛使用，这是 ISP 和移动网络中的一种做法，它将许多用户及其收集的活动和流量置于每个 IP 地址后面。我们介绍了我们开发的用于检测全球大规模 IP 共享并缓解由此产生的问题的方法。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Measuring characteristics of TCP connections at Internet scale】测量 Internet 规模的 TCP 连接特性</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/measuring-network-connections-at-scale/</link>
      <description>【 Researchers and practitioners have been studying connections almost as long as the Internet that supports them. Today, Cloudflare’s global network receives millions of connections per second. We explore various characteristics of TCP connections, including lifetimes, sizes, and more. 】研究人员和从业者对连接的研究几乎与支持连接的互联网一样长。如今，Cloudflare 的全球网络每秒接收数百万个连接。我们探索 TCP 连接的各种特征，包括生命周期、大小等。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Defending QUIC from acknowledgement-based DDoS attacks】保护 QUIC 免受基于确认的 DDoS 攻击</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/defending-quic-from-acknowledgement-based-ddos-attacks/</link>
      <description>【 We identified and patched two DDoS vulnerabilities in our QUIC implementation related to packet acknowledgements. Cloudflare customers were not affected. We examine the &#34;Optimistic ACK&#34; attack vector and our solution, which dynamically skips packet numbers to validate client behavior.  】我们在 QUIC 实现中发现并修复了两个与数据包确认相关的 DDoS 漏洞。 Cloudflare 客户没有受到影响。我们检查“乐观 ACK”攻击向量和我们的解决方案，该解决方案动态跳过数据包编号以验证客户端行为。 </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>