<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Gateway now gives you access to your favorite AI models, dynamic routing and more — through just one endpoint】AI网关现在使您可以访问您喜欢的AI模型，动态路由等等 - 仅通过一个端点</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-gateway-aug-2025-refresh/</link>
      <description>【 AI Gateway now gives you access to your favorite AI models, dynamic routing and more — through just one endpoint. 】AI网关现在使您可以通过一个端点访问您喜欢的AI模型，动态路由等。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How we built the most efficient inference engine for Cloudflare’s network 】我们如何为Cloudflare网络构建最有效的推理引擎</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflares-most-efficient-ai-inference-engine/</link>
      <description>【 Infire is an LLM inference engine that employs a range of techniques to maximize resource utilization, allowing us to serve AI models more efficiently with better performance for Cloudflare workloads. 】Infire是一种LLM推理引擎，采用了一系列技术来最大程度地利用资源利用，从而使我们能够更有效地为Cloudflare工作负载提供更好的AI模型。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Cloudflare runs more AI models on fewer GPUs: A technical deep-dive 】CloudFlare如何在更少的GPU上运行更多的AI模型：技术深度暗示</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/how-cloudflare-runs-more-ai-models-on-fewer-gpus/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare built an internal platform called Omni. This platform uses lightweight isolation and memory over-commitment to run multiple AI models on a single GPU. 】Cloudflare构建了一个名为Omni的内部平台。该平台使用轻巧的隔离和内存过度承诺来在单个GPU上运行多个AI模型。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【State-of-the-art image generation Leonardo models and text-to-speech Deepgram models now available in Workers AI】最先进的图像生成Leonardo模型和文本到语音深集模型现已在工人AI中使用</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-ai-partner-models/</link>
      <description>【 We&#39;re expanding Workers AI with new partner models from Leonardo.Ai and Deepgram. Start using state-of-the-art image generation models from Leonardo and real-time TTS and STT models from Deepgram.  】我们正在通过Leonardo.ai和Deepgram的新合作伙伴模型来扩展工人AI。开始使用Leonardo的最新图像生成模型以及Deepgram的实时TTS和STT模型。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing the AI Revolution: Introducing Cloudflare MCP Server Portals】确保AI革命：引入CloudFlare MCP服务器门户网站</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/zero-trust-mcp-server-portals/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare MCP Server Portals are now available in Open Beta. MCP Server Portals are a new capability that enable you to centralize, secure, and observe every MCP connection in your organization. 】CloudFlare MCP服务器门户网站现在可在Open Beta中使用。 MCP服务器门户是一种新功能，使您能够集中，安全并观察组织中的每个MCP连接。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ChatGPT, Claude, &amp; Gemini security scanning with Cloudflare CASB】Chatgpt，Claude和Gemini安全扫描与Cloudflare CASB</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/casb-ai-integrations/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare CASB now scans ChatGPT, Claude, and Gemini for misconfigurations, sensitive data exposure, and compliance issues, helping organizations adopt AI with confidence.&#xA; 】Cloudflare CASB现在扫描Chatgpt，Claude和Gemini是否有错误的配置，敏感的数据暴露和合规性问题，帮助组织充满信心地采用AI。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Block unsafe prompts targeting your LLM endpoints with Firewall for AI】阻止不安全的提示针对AI的防火墙针对LLM端点</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/block-unsafe-llm-prompts-with-firewall-for-ai/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare&#39;s AI security suite now includes unsafe content moderation, integrated into the Application Security Suite via Firewall for AI.  】CloudFlare的AI安全套件现在包括不安全的内容审核，通过防火墙集成在应用程序安全套件中。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Best Practices for Securing Generative AI with SASE】用Sase确保生成AI的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/best-practices-sase-for-ai/</link>
      <description>【 This guide provides best practices for Security and IT leaders to securely adopt generative AI using Cloudflare’s SASE architecture as part of a strategy for AI Security Posture Management (AI-SPM). 】本指南为安全提供了最佳实践，IT领导者可以使用CloudFlare的Sase Architecture安全地采用生成AI，作为AI安全姿势管理策略（AI-SPM）的一部分。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Cloudflare Application Confidence Score For AI Applications】引入AI应用程序的CloudFlare应用程序置信度得分</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/confidence-score-rubric/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare will provide confidence scores within our application library for Gen AI applications, allowing customers to assess their risk for employees using shadow IT.  】CloudFlare将在我们的应用程序库中为Gen Gen Applications提供信心分数，使客户能够使用Shadow IT评估员工的风险。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unmasking the Unseen: Your Guide to Taming Shadow AI with Cloudflare One】揭露看不见的：您用Cloudflare驯服影子AI的指南</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/shadow-AI-analytics/</link>
      <description>【 Don&#39;t let &#34;Shadow AI&#34; silently leak your data to unsanctioned AI. This new threat requires a new defense. Learn how to gain visibility and control without sacrificing innovation. 】不要让“ Shadow AI”默默地泄漏您的数据以未经批准的AI。这种新威胁需要新的防御。了解如何在不牺牲创新的情况下获得可见性和控制。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>