<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Robotcop: enforcing your robots.txt policies and stopping bots before they reach your website】Robotcop：执行您的 robots.txt 政策并在机器人到达您的网站之前将其阻止</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-audit-enforcing-robots-txt/</link>
      <description>【 Today, the AI Audit dashboard gets an upgrade: you can now quickly see which AI services are honoring your robots.txt policies and then automatically enforce the policies against those that aren’t.&#xA; 】今天，AI 审核仪表板进行了升级：您现在可以快速查看哪些 AI 服务遵守您的 robots.txt 策略，然后自动针对那些不遵守的 AI 服务强制执行这些策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Global elections in 2024: Internet traffic and cyber threat trends】2024 年全球选举：互联网流量和网络威胁趋势</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/elections-2024-internet/</link>
      <description>【 In 2024, as elections took place across over 60 countries, the Internet became both a battleground for cyberattacks and a vital platform for democratic engagement. 】2024 年，随着 60 多个国家举行选举，互联网既成为网络攻击的战场，又成为民主参与的重要平台。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The role of email security in reducing user risk amid rising threats】电子邮件安全在威胁不断增加的情况下降低用户风险的作用</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-role-of-email-security-in-reducing-user-risk-amid-rising-threats/</link>
      <description>【 As threats evolve, SOC teams must adapt their operations. With Cloudflare’s holistic approach to managing user-based risk, SOC teams can operate more efficiently and reduce the likelihood of a breach. 】随着威胁的演变，SOC 团队必须调整其运营。借助 Cloudflare 管理基于用户的风险的整体方法，SOC 团队可以更高效地运营并降低违规的可能性。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From ChatGPT to Temu: ranking top Internet services in 2024】从ChatGPT到Temu：2024年顶级互联网服务排名</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-2024-year-in-review-internet-services/</link>
      <description>【 The 2024 popular Internet services landscape highlights rising generative AI, e-commerce shifts, and the continued dominance of platforms like Google and Facebook, as revealed by Cloudflare’s rankings 】Cloudflare 的排名显示，2024 年流行的互联网服务格局凸显了生成式人工智能的崛起、电子商务的转变以及 Google 和 Facebook 等平台的持续主导地位</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bring multimodal real-time interaction to your AI applications with Cloudflare Calls】通过 Cloudflare Calls 将多模式实时交互引入您的 AI 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/bring-multimodal-real-time-interaction-to-your-ai-applications-with-cloudflare-calls/</link>
      <description>【 Bring ChatGPT to your next video meeting with Cloudflare Calls.  】通过 Cloudflare Calls 将 ChatGPT 带到您的下一次视频会议中。 </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From deals to DDoS: exploring Cyber Week 2024 Internet trends】从交易到 DDoS：探索 2024 年网络周互联网趋势</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/from-deals-to-ddos-exploring-cyber-week-2024-internet-trends/</link>
      <description>【 How significant are Cyber Week shopping days on the Internet? Is it a global phenomenon? Does E-commerce interest peak on Black Friday or Cyber Monday, and are attacks increasing during this time? We try to answer these questions and more.&#xA; 】网络周网上购物日有多重要？这是一个全球现象吗？电子商务兴趣是否在黑色星期五或网络星期一达到顶峰，并且在此期间攻击是否有所增加？我们试图回答这些问题以及更多问题。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare 2024 Year in Review】Cloudflare 2024 年回顾</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/radar-2024-year-in-review/</link>
      <description>【 The 2024 Cloudflare Radar Year in Review is our fifth annual review of Internet trends and patterns at both a global and country/region level. 】2024 年 Cloudflare Radar 年度回顾是我们对全球和国家/地区层面的互联网趋势和模式的第五次年度回顾。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Internationalization and localization: bringing Cloudflare Radar to a global audience】国际化和本地化：将 Cloudflare Radar 带给全球受众</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-radar-localization-journey/</link>
      <description>【 Internationalization and localization require more than translation: tone, images, date/time and number formatting, among other items, need to be considered. 】国际化和本地化需要的不仅仅是翻译：还需要考虑语气、图像、日期/时间和数字格式等。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hi Claude, build an MCP server on Cloudflare Workers】您好，Claude，在 Cloudflare Workers 上构建 MCP 服务器</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/model-context-protocol/</link>
      <description>【 Want Claude to interact with your app directly? Build an MCP server on Cloudflare Workers, enabling you to connect your service directly, allowing Claude to understand and run tasks on your behalf. 】希望 Claude 直接与您的应用程序交互吗？在 Cloudflare Workers 上构建 MCP 服务器，使您能够直接连接您的服务，让 Claude 能够代表您理解和运行任务。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grinch Bots strike again: defending your holidays from cyber threats】Grinch 机器人再次出击：保护您的假期免受网络威胁</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/grinch-bot-2024/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare observed a 4x increase in bot-related traffic on Black Friday in 2024. 29% of all traffic on our network on Black Friday was Grinch Bots wreaking holiday havoc. 】Cloudflare 观察到，2024 年黑色星期五与机器人相关的流量增加了 4 倍。黑色星期五我们网络上的所有流量中有 29% 是 Grinch 机器人造成的节日破坏。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>