<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare protects against critical SharePoint vulnerability, CVE-2025-53770】Cloudflare 保护防止关键 SharePoint 漏洞 CVE-2025-53770</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-protects-against-critical-sharepoint-vulnerability-cve-2025-53770/</link>
      <description>【 Microsoft disclosed two critical vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-53771 and CVE-2025-53770, that are exploited to attack SharePoint servers. 】 Microsoft disclosed two critical vulnerabilities, CVE-2025-53771 and CVE-2025-53770, that are exploited to attack SharePoint servers. </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare recognized as a Visionary in 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for SASE Platforms】Cloudflare 被列为 2025 年 Gartner® 魔力象限™ SASE 平台的愿景者</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-sase-gartner-magic-quadrant-2025/</link>
      <description>【 Gartner has recognized Cloudflare as a Visionary in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for SASE Platforms report. 】 Gartner has recognized Cloudflare as a Visionary in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for SASE Platforms report. </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hyper-volumetric DDoS attacks skyrocket: Cloudflare’s 2025 Q2 DDoS threat report】超体积DDoS攻击激增：Cloudflare 2025年第二季度DDoS威胁报告</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ddos-threat-report-for-2025-q2/</link>
      <description>【 June was the busiest month for DDoS attacks in 2025 Q2, accounting for nearly 38% of all observed activity. 】 June was the busiest month for DDoS attacks in 2025 Q2, accounting for nearly 38% of all observed activity. </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Quicksilver v2: evolution of a globally distributed key-value store (Part 2)】闪电侠v2：全球分布式键值存储的演进（第2部分）</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/quicksilver-v2-evolution-of-a-globally-distributed-key-value-store-part-2-of-2/</link>
      <description>【 This is part two of a story about how we overcame the challenges of making a complex system more scalable. 】这是关于我们将复杂系统变得更可扩展的过程中克服挑战的故事的第二部分。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Jetflow: a framework for flexible, performant data pipelines at Cloudflare】构建Jetflow：Cloudflare的灵活高效数据管道框架</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/building-jetflow-a-framework-for-flexible-performant-data-pipelines-at-cloudflare/</link>
      <description>【 Faced with a data-ingestion challenge at a massive scale, Cloudflare&#39;s Business Intelligence team built a new framework called Jetflow. 】面对大规模数据摄取挑战，Cloudflare 的商业智能团队构建了一个名为 Jetflow 的新框架。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The White House AI Action Plan:  a new chapter in U.S. AI policy】白宫人工智能行动计划：美国人工智能政策的新篇章</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-white-house-ai-action-plan-a-new-chapter-in-u-s-ai-policy/</link>
      <description>【 The White House AI Action Plan is a pivotal policy document outlining the current administration&#39;s priorities and deliverables in AI to establish American AI as the gold standard for AI worldwide. 】白宫人工智能行动方案是一项关键政策文件，概述了当前政府在人工智能领域的优先事项和成果，以确立美国人工智能作为全球人工智能的黄金标准。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 01:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Explore your Cloudflare data with Python notebooks, powered by marimo】使用 Python 笔记本探索您的 Cloudflare 数据，由 marimo 驱动</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/marimo-cloudflare-notebooks/</link>
      <description>【 We’ve partnered with marimo to bring their best-in-class Python notebook experience to your Cloudflare data. 】我们已与 marimo 合作，将他们一流的 Python 笔记本体验带入您的 Cloudflare 数据中。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Serverless Statusphere: a walk through building serverless ATProto applications on Cloudflare’s Developer Platform】无服务器状态球：在Cloudflare开发者平台上构建无服务器ATProto应用程序的指南</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/serverless-atproto/</link>
      <description>【 Build and deploy real-time, decentralized Authenticated Transfer Protocol (ATProto) apps on Cloudflare Workers. 】在Cloudflare Workers上构建和部署实时的、去中心化的认证传输协议（ATProto）应用。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare 1.1.1.1 incident on July 14, 2025】2025年7月14日Cloudflare 1.1.1.1事件</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-1-1-1-1-incident-on-july-14-2025/</link>
      <description>【 July 14th, 2025, Cloudflare made a change to our service topologies that caused an outage for 1.1.1.1 on the edge, causing downtime for 62 minutes for customers using the 1.1.1.1 public DNS Resolver. 】2025年7月14日，Cloudflare对其服务拓扑进行了更改，导致边缘的1.1.1.1出现中断，使用1.1.1.1公共DNS解析器的客户因此出现了62分钟的停机时间。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shutdown season: the Q2 2025 Internet disruption summary】停机季节：2025年第二季度互联网中断摘要</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/q2-2025-internet-disruption-summary/</link>
      <description>【 In Q2 2025, we observed Internet disruptions around the world resulting from government-directed shutdowns, power outages, cable damage, a cyberattack, and technical problems. 】在2025年第二季度，我们观察到由于政府主导的断网、停电、电缆损坏、网络攻击和技术问题，全球出现了互联网中断的情况。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>