<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title> The Cloudflare Blog </title>
    <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/</link>
    <description> Get the latest news on how products at Cloudflare are built, technologies used, and join the teams helping to build a better Internet. </description>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloudflare’s 2025 Annual Founders’ Letter】Cloudflare的2025年年度创始人信</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/cloudflare-2025-annual-founders-letter/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare launched 15 years ago. We like to celebrate our birthday by launching new products that give back to the Internet. But we&#39;ve also been thinking a lot about what&#39;s changed on the Internet. 】Cloudflare于15年前推出。我们喜欢通过推出回馈互联网的新产品来庆祝生日。但是我们也一直在考虑互联网上发生的变化。</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【You don’t need quantum hardware for post-quantum security】您不需要量子硬件即可进行量子后安全</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/you-dont-need-quantum-hardware/</link>
      <description>【 Post-quantum cryptography protects against quantum threats using today’s hardware. Quantum tech like QKD may sound appealing, but it isn’t necessary or sufficient to secure organizations. 】量子后密码学可保护使用当今硬件的量子威胁。像QKD这样的量子技术听起来可能很吸引人，但没有必要或足以保护组织。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Connect and secure any private or public app by hostname, not IP — free for everyone in Cloudflare One】通过主机名连接并保护任何私人或公共应用程序，而不是IP-对于CloudFlare中的每个人免费</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/tunnel-hostname-routing/</link>
      <description>【 Tired of IP Lists? Securely connect private networks to any app by its hostname, not its IP address. This routing is now built into Cloudflare Tunnel and is free for all Cloudflare One customers. 】厌倦了IP列表？通过其主机名而不是其IP地址将专用网络安全地连接到任何应用程序。该路由现在内置在Cloudflare隧道中，对于所有CloudFlare One客户都是免费的。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The RUM Diaries: enabling Web Analytics by default】朗姆酒日记：默认启用Web分析</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/the-rum-diaries-enabling-web-analytics-by-default/</link>
      <description>【 On October 15th 2025, Cloudflare is enabling Web Analytics for all free domains by default—helping you see how your site performs around the world in real time, without ever collecting personal data. 】默认情况下，CloudFlare在2025年10月15日为所有自由域启用了Web分析，您可以看到您的网站在无需收集个人数据的情况下实时地在世界范围内的表现。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 19:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating CrowdStrike Falcon Fusion SOAR with Cloudflare’s SASE platform】将CrowdStrike Falcon Fusion与Cloudflare的Sase平台集成</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/integrating-crowdstrike-falcon-fusion-soar-with-cloudflares-sase-platform/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare and CrowdStrike have partnered to help SOC teams minimize manual bottlenecks. By combining Cloudflare’s SASE platform with CrowdStrike’s Falcon® Fusion SOAR, security teams can now detect  】Cloudflare和CrowdStrike已合作，帮助SOC团队最大程度地减少手动瓶颈。通过将Cloudflare的Sase平台与CrowdStrike的Falcon®融合Soar相结合，安全团队现在可以检测到</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A deep dive into Cloudflare’s September 12, 2025 dashboard and API outage】深入研究Cloudflare的2025年9月12日仪表板和API中断</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/deep-dive-into-cloudflares-sept-12-dashboard-and-api-outage/</link>
      <description>【 Cloudflare’s Dashboard and a set of related APIs were unavailable or partially available for an hour starting on Sep 12, 17:57 UTC.  The outage did not affect the serving of cached files via the  】从9月12日，17:57 UTC开始，Cloudflare的仪表板和一组相关的API不可用或部分可用。  中断不会影响通过</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 07:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bringing Node.js HTTP servers to Cloudflare Workers】将Node.js HTTP服务器带到Cloudflare工人</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/bringing-node-js-http-servers-to-cloudflare-workers/</link>
      <description>【 We&#39;ve implemented the node:http client and server APIs in Cloudflare Workers, allowing developers to migrate existing Node.js applications with minimal code changes. 】我们已经在CloudFlare工人中实现了节点：HTTP客户端和服务器API，使开发人员能够以最小的代码更改迁移现有Node.js应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Addressing the unauthorized issuance of multiple TLS certificates for 1.1.1.1】解决未经授权的1.1.1.1的多个TLS证书的发行</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/unauthorized-issuance-of-certificates-for-1-1-1-1/</link>
      <description>【 Unauthorized TLS certificates were issued for 1.1.1.1 by a Certification Authority without permission from Cloudflare. These rogue certificates have now been revoked. 】未经Cloudflare许可，未经授权的TLS证书以1.1.1.1颁发。这些流氓证书现在已被撤销。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Week 2025: Recap】AI周2025年：回顾</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/ai-week-2025-wrapup/</link>
      <description>【 How do we embrace the power of AI without losing control? That was one of our big themes for AI Week 2025. Check out all of the products, partnerships, and features we announced. 】我们如何在不失去控制的情况下拥抱AI的力量？那是我们2025年AI周的大主题之一。查看我们宣布的所有产品，合作伙伴关系和功能。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The impact of the Salesloft Drift breach on Cloudflare and our customers】Salesloft Drift违规对Cloudflare和我们的客户的影响</title>
      <link>https://blog.cloudflare.com/response-to-salesloft-drift-incident/</link>
      <description>【 An advanced threat actor, GRUB1, exploited the integration between Salesloft’s Drift chat agent and Salesforce to gain unauthorized access to Salesforce tenants of Cloudflare and many other companies. 】一位高级威胁参与者GRUB1利用了Salesloft的漂移聊天代理和Salesforce之间的集成，以获得未经授权的Cloudflare和许多其他公司的Salesforce租户的访问。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>