<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://cloudys-rsshub-ab061133bcab.herokuapp.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【How OTel Community Day Enriched my Open Source Career: A Tale of Community and Connection】奥特尔社区日如何丰富我的开源职业：社区和联系的故事</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/13/how-otel-community-day-enriched-my-open-source-career-a-tale-of-community-and-connection/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;My name is Diana Todea. I’m originally from Romania and have been living in Spain for the past nine years. I have worked as a Senior Site Reliability Engineer specializing in Observability for the last three years and my OpenTelemetry (OTel) journey began in 2024 with my first community contributions. What started as a simple curiosity quickly turned into a passion for open source. In 2025, my talk about my journey with OpenTelemetry was selected for &lt;strong&gt;OTel Community Day&lt;/strong&gt;, part of the &lt;strong&gt;Open Observability Summit&lt;/strong&gt; in Denver, Colorado. I was thrilled to participate as a speaker, this moment felt like a meaningful recognition of my contributions to the OpenTelemetry project and the broader Cloud Native community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Takeaways from OTel Community Day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OTel Community Day was an enriching experience. From the supporting members of the open source community who organized and ran the event to meeting so many active contributors to the OTel project, the energy and collaboration were palpable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I attended several insightful talks that highlighted how much the project has grown in just one year. Speakers discussed the current pain points, the project’s direction, and how the community is continuing to drive improvements through new integrations and features. I also had the chance to speak directly with OTel maintainers and offer feedback on areas I believe need improvement. As a member of the &lt;strong&gt;#otel-localization-es&lt;/strong&gt; SIG, I shared updates on our efforts to translate the official OTel documentation into Spanish. It was a great opportunity to invite new contributors to join our localization initiative and help make the project more accessible to a global audience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many presentations focused on exciting, upcoming contributions that are just beginning to emerge and will soon become public. Connecting with peers at the event was invaluable, it gave me insight into where I can contribute next and which SIGs could use more support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Continued Journey in Open Source&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OTel Community Day wasn’t just an event, it became a turning point in my career and life. Inspired by the experience and the community, I decided to apply for the &lt;strong&gt;CNCF Ambassador&lt;/strong&gt; program. I believe this role plays a key part in motivating others to begin their own journeys into open source. Thanks to the support and spirit of the Cloud Native community, I have embraced a mindset of collaboration, mentorship and continuous learning. My career has evolved significantly this year and I’m now focusing more on &lt;strong&gt;open source Developer Advocacy&lt;/strong&gt; and finding new ways to support and uplift the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The event reignited my motivation to invest my technical skills in open source, give more talks on OpenTelemetry and other open source projects and share my experience with wider audiences. It’s given me the confidence to continue advocating for open standards and community-driven Development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OTel Community Day truly strengthened my connection to the cloud native and open source ecosystems. It reminded me how impactful individual contributions can be and how important it is to nurture and support the local communities that make it all possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我叫戴安娜·托迪亚（Diana Todea）。我最初来自罗马尼亚，在过去的九年中一直在西班牙生活。在过去的三年中，我曾担任专门研究可观察性的高级站点可靠性工程师，而我的Opentelemetry（Otel）旅程始于2024年，我的首次社区贡献。最初的好奇心迅速变成了对开源的热情。在2025年，我对我与OpentElemetry的旅程进行了讨论，以&lt;strong&gt; Otel社区日&lt;/strong&gt;，这是科罗拉多州丹佛市&lt;strong&gt;公开可观察性峰会的一部分。我很高兴能参加演讲者，这一刻感觉就像我对Opentelemetry项目和更广泛的云土著社区的贡献有意义的认识。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Otel社区日的关键要点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;奥特尔社区日是一种丰富的经历。从组织和举办活动的开源社区的支持成员到与奥特尔项目的许多积极贡献者见面，能源和协作都可以显而易见。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我参加了几次有见地的演讲，这些演讲强调了该项目在短短一年内增长了多少。演讲者讨论了当前的痛点，项目的方向以及社区如何通过新的整合和功能继续改进。我也有机会直接与Otel维护者交谈，并就我认为需要改进的领域提供反馈。作为&lt;strong&gt;＃＃Otel-Localization-es &lt;/strong&gt; Sig的成员，我分享了我们将官方Otel文档转化为西班牙语的努力的最新信息。这是一个很好的机会，邀请新贡献者加入我们的本地化计划并帮助使该项目更容易被全球受众访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多演讲着重于令人兴奋的，即将出现的贡献，这些贡献刚刚开始出现，并将很快公开。在活动中与同行建立联系是无价的，它使我深入了解了下一步可以贡献的地方，哪些SIG可以使用更多的支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我在开源&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;的持续旅程&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;奥特尔社区日不仅是一个活动，还成为我职业和生活的转折点。受到经验和社区的启发，我决定申请&lt;strong&gt; CNCF大使&lt;/strong&gt;计划。我相信，这个角色在激励他人开始自己的旅程中扮演开源的关键。得益于云土著社区的支持和精神，我接受了协作，指导和持续学习的心态。今年我的职业生涯已经大幅度发展，我现在更多地关注&lt;strong&gt;开源开发者倡导&lt;/strong&gt;，并找到了支持和提升社区的新方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这次活动重新激发了我将我的技术技能投入开源的动机，对Opentelemetry和其他开源项目进行更多谈判，并与我分享我的经验更广泛的受众。我有信心继续倡导开放标准和社区驱动的发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;最终思想&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;奥特尔社区日确实加强了我与云原生和开源生态系统的联系。它使我想起了个人贡献的影响力，以及培养和支持使一切可能的当地社区的重要性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Gear Up for the 5th Annual KCD Washington DC!】为第五届KCD华盛顿特区准备好准备！</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/16/gear-up-for-the-5th-annual-kcd-washington-dc/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We’re so thrilled to be organizing another year of cloud native community in the Nation’s Capital.&amp;nbsp; Past years have witnessed amazing presentations ranging from core Kubernetes topics to emerging trends in ML/AI, sustainability, virtual clusters and more.&amp;nbsp; This year promises to be even more amazing.&amp;nbsp; Our program is set, and includes two new innovations for our KCD:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For the first time, we’re offering a &lt;strong&gt;hands-on workshop&lt;/strong&gt; covering basic and intermediate topics on using &lt;strong&gt;Prometheus&lt;/strong&gt; in your observability practice. The curriculum covers 20-25% of the Linux Foundation’s Prometheus Certified Associate (PCA) course.&amp;nbsp; While this workshop does not lead to certification, and is not a substitute for the PCA course, it will give you a solid working knowledge for getting started and perhaps help you decide if you’d like to pursue certification separately – if you do, you’ll be ahead of the game with this solid foundation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We’re adding a &lt;strong&gt;government-focused cybersecurity keynote&lt;/strong&gt; by our special guest, Ashley Jones, Cybersecurity Advisor for Region III of the Department of Homeland Security, Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special Government &amp;amp; Cybersecurity Focus – and free admission for our government employee community members!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You won’t want to miss Ashley Jones’ keynote if you’re a cybersecurity professional or involved in government technology in any way. A limited number of free tickets will be available soon for our community members working for federal, state or local government agencies. You can request a free government ticket here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/aLNfRwpvFn3vQ5Vo8&#34;&gt;https://forms.gle/aLNfRwpvFn3vQ5Vo8&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plus our regular program is amazing!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;All of that rests on top of our regular program that includes presentations like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry perspective: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Scaling Cloud Native: Reaching the Next 10 Million Users&lt;/em&gt; by Lin Sun at Solo.io&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;K8s in the Enterprise: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Silos to SIGs: Building Kubernetes Community in the Enterprise&lt;/em&gt; by Jason Stryker&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inclusivity: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unleash Your Inner Ally: Let’s Make Open Source Radically Welcoming!&lt;/em&gt; by Catherine Paganini and Christopher Khanoyan advocate for inclusivity in open source. (This talk willwith be interpreted for the hearing-impaired)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;AI on Lockdown: Deploying ML Pipelines in Controlled Government Spaces&lt;/em&gt; by Kumuda Sreenivasa&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;….and a whole lot more, which you can see in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://kcd-washington-dc-2025.sessionize.com/&#34;&gt;Full Schedule&lt;/a&gt; [https://kcd-washington-dc-2025.sessionize.com/]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And there’s plenty of food, drinks and networking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once again, we plan on hosting an evening &lt;strong&gt;Social Hour&lt;/strong&gt; free for all attendees where you can meet fellow attendees, speakers, and sponsors, in a relaxed, community environment while enjoying drinks and appetizers.&amp;nbsp; And, of course, you can enjoy all-day snacks, beverages (tea, coffee, soft drinks) and a nutritious lunch, all included with your one-day ticket.&amp;nbsp; That’s a pretty good value for $75, and to make it even more inviting, we’re offering 25% for all CNCF readers using code FRIENDS25 when you &lt;a href=&#34;https://bit.ly/KCDDC2025&#34;&gt;Get Tickets&lt;/a&gt; [https://bit.ly/KCDDC2025] today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;True community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, we know the current job market and economic times are difficult for many of our most vulnerable community members.&amp;nbsp; We also want to encourage participation from under-represented minority (URM) groups.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, we’re proud to offer a number of free tickets to community members in need or who are in URM groups. You can request a free community ticket here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/aLNfRwpvFn3vQ5Vo8&#34;&gt;https://forms.gle/aLNfRwpvFn3vQ5Vo8&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we have been collaborating with the CNCF Deaf and Hard of Hearing Working Group to ensure this year’s event has live captioning throughout the day and interpretation services for our special presentation on inclusivity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s KCD Washington DC promises to be our biggest and best yet, packed with insightful sessions, hands-on workshops, inclusive community and invaluable networking opportunities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re also once again co-locating with DevOpsDays DC for their auspicious 10&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; editioniteration in the DMV, and third annual event joining forces with us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you on September 16&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; at the historic American Red Cross headquarters!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴在美国首都组织另一年的云土著社区。  过去几年见证了从核心库伯尼（Kubernetes）主题到ML/AI的新兴趋势，可持续性，虚拟集群等的惊人演讲。  今年有望变得更加惊人。  我们的程序已设置，并为我们的KCD提供了两个新的创新：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;第一次，我们提供了&lt;strong&gt;动手研讨会&lt;/strong&gt;涵盖有关在您的可观察性实践中使用&lt;strong&gt; Prometheus &lt;/strong&gt;的基本和中间主题。该课程涵盖了Linux基金会的Prometheus认证合伙人（PCA）课程的20-25％。  虽然该研讨会不会导致认证，也不能代替PCA课程，但它将为您提供扎实的工作知识，以便您开始分别寻求认证 - 如果您这样做，那么您将获得此坚实的基础。&lt;/li&gt;，您将领先于游戏。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我们正在添加&lt;strong&gt;政府以政府为中心的网络安全主题演讲&lt;/strong&gt;由我们的特别嘉宾，Ashley Jones，国土安全部，网络安全和基础设施安全局（CISA。）的网络安全顾问Ashley Jones，&lt;/li&gt;）&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;特别政府和网络安全重点 - 我们的政府员工社区成员免费入场！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您是网络安全专业人员或以任何方式参与政府技术，您将不想错过Ashley Jones的主题演讲。在联邦，州或地方政府机构工作的社区成员很快将提供有限的免费门票。您可以在此处要求免费的政府票：&lt;a href =“ https://forms.gle/alnfrwpvfn3vq5vo8”&gt; https://forms.gle/alnfrwpvfn3vq5vq5vo8 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;加上我们的常规程序很棒！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;所有这些都取决于我们的常规计划，其中包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;行业视角：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;缩放云本机：lin sun in solo.io &lt;/li&gt;触及接下来的1000万用户&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k8s企业中的K8：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;从孤岛到信号：在企业中建立kubernetes社区&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; by Jason Stryker &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;包容性：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;释放了您的内在盟友：让凯瑟琳·帕加尼尼（Catherine Paganini）和克里斯托弗·哈诺诺（Christopher Khanoyan）倡导开源的开源欢迎！&lt;/em&gt;。 （这次演讲将以听力受损的解释）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;人工智能（AI）：锁定：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; ai：在受控的政府空间中部署ML管道&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; by kumuda sreenivasa &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;…。还有很多，您可以在&lt;a href =“ https://kcd-washington-dc-20255.sessionize.com/”&gt;完整的时间表&lt;/a&gt; [https://kcd-washington-dc-20255.sessionize.com/] &lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;和很多食物，D溜冰场和网络&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;再次，我们计划举办夜晚&lt;strong&gt;社交时光&lt;/strong&gt;免费的所有与会者，您可以在轻松的社区环境中与同伴，演讲者和赞助商见面，同时享受饮料和开胃菜。  而且，当然，您可以享受全天的小吃，饮料（茶，咖啡，软饮料）和营养午餐，全部包括一日票。  75美元的价值是一个相当不错的价值，为了使其更具吸引力，当您&lt;a href =“ https://bit.ly/kcddc2025”时，我们将为所有CNCF读取器提供25％的价格，以提供25％的读者。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;真正的社区&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后但并非最不重要的一点是，我们知道当前的就业市场和经济时代对于许多最脆弱的社区成员来说都是困难的。  我们还希望鼓励来自代表性不足的少数民族（URM）群体的参与。  因此，我们很自豪地为有需要的社区成员或在URM团体中提供许多免费门票。您可以在此处请求免费的社区票：&lt;A href =“ https://forms.gle/alnfrwpvfn3vq5vo8”&gt; https://forms.gle/alnfrwpvfn3vq5vo8 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，我们还与CNCF聋哑人合作，并难以听力工作组，以确保今年的活动全天都有现场字幕，并为包容性的特别演讲提供了解释服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在结论中&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;今年的KCD华盛顿特区有望成为我们迄今为止最大，最好的，充满有见地的会议，动手讲习班，包容性社区和宝贵的网络机会。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还再次与DevOpsdays DC共同订立了他们的吉祥10 &lt;sup&gt; th &lt;/sup&gt;在DMV中的版本，以及与我们的第三次年度活动。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们期待在9月16日与您与历史悠久的美国红十字会总部见面！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Combining GenAI &amp; Agentic AI to build scalable, autonomous systems】将Genai＆Agesic AI相结合以构建可扩展的自主系统</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/18/combining-genai-agentic-ai-to-build-scalable-autonomous-systems/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A common pattern in today’s AI adoption is that businesses are investing heavily in GenAI capabilities, yet many are leaving significant value on the table by failing to pair it with Agentic AI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This matters because while GenAI can generate content, ideas, or responses, it can’t act on them. However, when combined with Agentic AI, your systems shift from being reactive and prompt-driven to autonomous and outcome-oriented.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article aims to help senior technology leaders better understand the value Agentic AI can add to existing AI infrastructure, while outlining key considerations to determine whether its implementation aligns with your business needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Understanding Agentic AI&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdK_MTJsDbf-762dNxU9eeSNBT3MNJaoPxFvS8z3GqUeDcUbpuSI1dfo3sw6NSIvLJ_LaMarkzvCDtMVvSnrrWrwvSHj9OvfxWcUeAE5rkbzcQ1HzjX4hetnrrqbX35C5r1Gx_CXQ?key=xgu2lQTqMaowWCibuTxnzqRW&#34; alt=&#34;Image caption: Core components of an Agentic AI Architecture from Markovate.&amp;nbsp;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image caption: Core components of an Agentic AI Architecture from &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://markovate.com/blog/agentic-ai-architecture/?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Markovate.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Agentic AI systems are designed to operate autonomously, perceiving their environment, making decisions, and executing actions without continuous human oversight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This autonomy enables businesses to streamline operations, reduce costs, and enhance scalability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The image above illustrates how the following systems function:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perception layer:&lt;/strong&gt; This layer involves collecting data from various sources i.e. sensors, cameras, microphones, and digital inputs, to understand the current state of the environment. For businesses, this means real-time monitoring of operations, customer interactions, and market trends, facilitating proactive decision-making and rapid response to changing conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognition layer:&lt;/strong&gt; Once data is collected, the cognition layer processes this information to interpret context, recognise patterns, and determine the best course of action. This analysis automates complex decision-making processes and reduces reliance on manual interventions, minimising the risk of human error.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Action layer: &lt;/strong&gt;After determining the appropriate response, the action layer executes the decision i.e. adjusting system parameters, initiating workflows, or communicating with stakeholders. This capability ensures quick implementation of decisions to enhance operational efficiency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, Agentic AI systems are equipped with learning mechanisms that improve over time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through techniques like reinforcement learning, where the system learns from the outcomes of its actions, and supervised or unsupervised learning, where it identifies patterns in data, the AI adapts to new situations and refines its decision-making processes.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;GenAI is great at creation, while Agentic AI brings decision-making and execution&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most disruptive AI solutions over the next few years will combine GenAI with Agentic AI, and the key to achieving better business outcomes is knowing when to use one, the other, or both.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not every use case requires a full agentic system, but many businesses will be surprised at how many should.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GenAI alone:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GenAI excels at generating new content from existing data patterns, significantly boosting creativity and productivity across various domains. In software engineering, tools like GitHub Copilot are increasingly used to automate routine tasks such as generating boilerplate code. This enables engineers to avoid repetitive work and focus on more complex, high-impact challenges. While a human-in-the-loop remains essential to ensure code quality and alignment, GenAI is already improving engineering efficiency and accelerating delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In data science and engineering, GenAI supports teams facing surging data demands by improving accessibility and streamlining processing. Large language models (LLMs) help optimise how data is queried and managed, enabling faster and more accurate insights.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GenAI tools also enhance data analysis and application development by allowing users to interact with data through natural language processing (NLP), unlocking insights without requiring SQL expertise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the case of Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG), GenAI can efficiently access relevant data sources to assist customer service agents, or any customer-facing teams in responding to user queries with greater speed and accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agentic AI Alone for autonomous decision-making and actions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Agentic AI is best suited for automating complex, multi-step processes like supply chain management or customer service workflows.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tasks that require real-time decision-making and adaptation to changing environments benefit from Agentic AI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, a logistics company can implement Agentic AI to autonomously manage inventory levels, reorder supplies, and optimise delivery routes based on real-time data. This leads to improved operational efficiency, reduced errors, and faster response times.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Merging GenAI and Agentic AI:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The combined approach is best used when your business requires systems that generate content and autonomously act upon it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The goal is to create end-to-end automated solutions that handle creation and execution, enhancing customer experiences through personalised interactions and proactive services.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example is when an e-commerce platform uses GenAI to create personalised product recommendations. Agentic AI automatically adjusts pricing and inventory based on customer behaviour and purchasing trends.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This combined approach delivers better customer engagement through personalised and timely interactions, helping the business achieve greater agility in responding to market demands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why human oversight matters in enterprise-scale AI systems:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In high-risk decision-making environments like finance or healthcare, AI systems aren’t always the right decision, but when they do make sense to implement, it’s essential to maintain a human-in-the-loop approach. This is especially important for models prone to errors or “hallucinations,” as inaccuracies can have significant consequences in these sectors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Industries governed by strict regulations often face challenges when implementing AI systems that lack transparency. The opaque nature of some AI models can hinder compliance efforts and erode stakeholder trust.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, deploying and maintaining advanced AI systems, such as GenAI and Agentic AI can be resource-intensive, requiring substantial computational power and specialised expertise. This complexity reinforces the need for human oversight to ensure smooth implementation and to mitigate potential risks that could strain organisational resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For organisations with limited resources, adopting simpler AI solutions that address specific needs without the complexity of full integration may be more practical. Certain tasks inherently require human intuition, empathy, and ethical judgment, which are qualities that AI currently cannot replicate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Strategic considerations for tech leaders&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As technology leaders, it’s essential to move beyond static GenAI chatbots and assess whether integrating GenAI and Agentic AI aligns with your organisation’s objectives. Evaluate the specific operational tasks within your organisation to determine if a combined AI approach is necessary or if a more straightforward solution would be more appropriate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ensure your organisation possesses the appropriate infrastructure and expertise to support complex AI systems. This includes robust data architectures, scalable computing resources, and a skilled workforce adept in AI technologies. Equally important is the prioritisation of AI solutions that offer transparency and explainability. In regulated industries, understanding the decision-making processes of AI systems is crucial to maintaining compliance and building trust with stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当今AI采用的一种普遍模式是，企业在Genai的功能上投资了大量投资，但是许多人未能将其与Agentic AI配对，在桌面上留下了巨大的价值。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这很重要，因为尽管Genai可以产生内容，想法或响应，但它不能对它们作用。但是，当与代理AI结合使用时，您的系统从反应性和及时驱动到以自主性和结果为导向。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文旨在帮助高级技术领导者更好地了解价值代理AI可以添加到现有的AI基础架构中，同时概述了关键注意事项以确定其实施是否符合您的业务需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;了解代理AI &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdk_mtjsdbf-762dnxu9eesnbt3mnjaopxfvs8z3gquedcubpusi1dfo3 sw6nsivlj_lamarkzvcdtmvvsnrrwrwvshj9ovfxwcueae5rkbzcq1hzjx4hetnrrqbx35c5r1gx_cxq_ke = key = xgu2lqtqmaowwcmaowwcmaowwcmaowwcibutxnzqrw oke alt =“图像字幕：来自Markovate的代理AI架构的核心组件。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;图像标题：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a的代理AI架构的核心组件href =“ https://markovate.com/blog/agentic-ai-Architecture/?utm_source=chatgpt.com”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; markovate&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;代理AI系统旨在自主操作，感知他们的环境，做出决定并执行行动而无需连续的人类监督。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种自主权使企业能够简化运营，降低成本并提高可扩展性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上图说明了以下系统的功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;感知层：&lt;/strong&gt;该层涉及从各种来源（即传感器，相机，麦克风和数字输入）收集数据，以了解环境的当前状态。对于企业而言，这意味着对运营，客户互动和市场趋势的实时监控，促进积极的决策和对变化条件的快速响应。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;认知层：&lt;/strong&gt;一旦收集数据，认知层就会处理此信息以解释上下文，识别模式并确定最佳的作用方案。该分析可自动化复杂的决策过程，并减少对手动干预的依赖，从而最大程度地减少人为错误的风险。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;动作层：&lt;/strong&gt;确定适当的响应后，操作层执行决策，即调整系统参数，启动工作流或与利益相关者进行通信。这种能力可确保快速实施决策以提高运营效率。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终，代理AI系统配备了随着时间的推移改善的学习机制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过技术就像加强学习一样，系统从其行动的结果中学习，监督或无监督的学习，在此识别数据中的模式，AI也适应了新的情况并完善了其决策过程。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; genai擅长创建，而代理AI带来了决策和执行&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;未来几年中最具破坏性的AI解决方案将与Genai与代理AI结合使用，实现更好的业务成果的关键是知道何时使用一种，另一个或两者兼而有之。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;并非每种用例都需要一个完整的代理系统，但是许多企业会对多少企业感到惊讶。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; genai：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Genai擅长从现有数据模式中生成新内容，从而显着提高各个领域的创造力和生产力。在软件工程中，诸如GitHub Copilot之类的工具越来越多地用于自动执行常规任务，例如生成样板代码。这使工程师能够避免重复的工作，并专注于更复杂，高影响力的挑战。尽管人类在确保代码质量和对齐方面仍然至关重要，但Genai已经在提高工程效率和加速交付。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在数据科学和工程学中，Genai通过改善可访问性和简化处理来支持面临飙升数据需求的团队。大型语言模型（LLMS）有助于优化如何查询和管理数据，从而更快，更准确。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; genai工具还通过允许用户通过自然语言处理（NLP）与数据进行交互，解锁见解而无需SQL专业知识来增强数据分析和应用程序的开发。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在检索功能生成（RAG）的情况下，Genai可以有效访问相关的数据源以帮助客户服务代理商或任何面向客户的团队以更高的速度和准确性响应用户查询。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;仅用于自主决策和行动的代理AI：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;代理AI最适合自动化复杂的多步骤过程，例如供应链管理或客户服务工作流程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需要实时决策和适应不断变化环境的任务受益于代理AI。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，物流公司可以实施代理AI来自主管理库存级别，重新订购供应并根据实时数据优化交货路线。这会提高操作效率，降低错误和更快的响应时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;合并Genai和Agent AI：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您的业务需要生成内容并自主对其作用的系统时，最好使用合并的方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目标是创建端到端自动化解决方案，以处理创建和执行，通过个性化INT增强客户体验磨难和主动服务。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个例子是，当电子商务平台使用Genai创建个性化产品建议时。代理AI会根据客户行为和购买趋势自动调整定价和库存。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种合并的方法通过个性化和及时的互动来提供更好的客户参与度，帮助企业在响应市场需求方面实现了更大的敏捷性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么人类的监督在企业规模的AI系统中很重要：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在金融或医疗保健等高风险的决策环境中，AI系统并不总是正确的决定，但是当它们确实有意义地实施时，维护人类的方法至关重要。这对于容易出现错误或“幻觉”的模型尤其重要，因为不准确可能会对这些部门产生重大影响。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;受严格法规管辖的行业在实施缺乏透明度的AI系统时通常会面临挑战。某些AI模型的不透明性质可以阻止合规性并侵蚀利益相关者的信任。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，部署和维护高级AI系统，例如Genai和AgentIC AI可能是资源密集的，需要实质性的计算能力和专业知识。这种复杂性加强了对人类监督的需求，以确保平稳的实施并减轻可能损害组织资源的潜在风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于资源有限的组织而言，采用更简单的AI解决方案，这些解决方案在没有完全集成的情况下解决特定需求可能更实用。某些任务固有地需要人类的直觉，同理心和道德判断，这是AI当前无法复制的素质。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;技术领导者的战略考虑&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为技术领导者，必须超越静态Genai聊天机器人，并评估将Genai和Agent AI整合到您组织的目标中是否一致。评估组织内的特定操作任务，以确定合并的AI方法是否需要，或者更直接的解决方案更合适。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确保您的组织拥有适当的基础架构和专业知识来支持复杂的AI系统。这包括强大的数据体系结构，可扩展的计算资源以及熟练的AI技术熟练劳动力。同样重要的是提供透明度和解释性的AI解决方案的优先级。在受管制的行业中，了解AI系统的决策过程对于维持与利益相关者的合规性和建立信任至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud Native in the City of Kings】国王市的云本地人</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/14/cloud-native-in-the-city-of-kings/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Lima, Peru — the “Ciudad de los Reyes” — hosted one of the most energized and well-attended Kubernetes Community Days (KCD) in the region this past weekend. From the start, it was clear that this was a gathering shaped by international collaboration and a shared passion for cloud native technologies across Latin America.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speakers and attendees came from Brazil, Argentina, Chile, Colombia, Guatemala, Venezuela, the United States, and Peru. The diverse representation showed how deeply connected the region is around open source, with community members from different countries actively contributing to shared growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The event was at capacity, and every session was packed. What stood out to me was how the attendees approached it with the same enthusiasm and energy as a KubeCon + CloudNativeCon—only this time, it was happening right in Lima. The atmosphere was electric from the moment I walked into the venue. We estimated, over 600 people joined us throughout the day. Even after we ran out of swag and lanyards halfway through the event, the energy never dropped. In fact, by the time Pavel Puclla hosted the closing raffle with incredible enthusiasm, the room felt even more packed than it did in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On Friday night, we gathered for the speaker reception. We shared a meal of delicious local food and attended a cultural performance that depicted the stories, struggles, and triumphs of the Peruvian people. It was a powerful way to connect with the local community and culture. That evening, we discussed how our cloud native communities operate in our respective countries, the challenges we face, and the strategies we’re exploring to grow participation and adoption. We also shared success stories on how we’ve used cloud native tools to drive meaningful outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Getting to meet with representatives from PUCP, the event host, was another highlight. They expressed interest in expanding their work with cloud native technologies, and I was able to share some insight into the broader community and Peru’s leadership in the region. Peru has made impressive strides in cultivating new contributors—particularly within the growing group of Kubestronauts—and has become a central hub for Latin America’s momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the son of Honduran immigrants, this event held deep personal meaning for me. I have always hoped to see more cloud native leaders emerge from Latin America and take their place in the global open source ecosystem. KCD Lima was a clear step toward that goal. The event didn’t just highlight regional talent—it elevated it. It gave us a space to collaborate, learn, and lead together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also had the privilege of moderating a panel on cloud native in the enterprise. The conversation focused on real-world challenges, success stories, and best practices. Panelists represented a wide range of industries including banking, consulting, mining, education, training, and government. While the list of sectors involved is far from exhaustive, it reflects how deeply cloud native practices are taking root across Latin America.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The level of coordination across countries and the collective investment in KCD Lima made it clear that this is a regional movement. The event highlighted the scale, talent, and dedication of the Latin American cloud native ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Acknowledgments&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A heartfelt thank you to the organizers:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Carol Valencia (CNCF Ambassador)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pavel Puclla (CEO at Se.Colectiva)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jean Paul Lopez (Senior Consultant at Red Hat)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Juan Manuel Chavez (Product Owner at BCP)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ronald Requena (Senior Engineer at Mibanco)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you to PUCP for hosting us and supporting community growth in Peru.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And a sincere thank you to all the speakers who made this event possible:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speakers&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Almendra Paz Rodriguez, Bianca Torres, Bruno Lopes, Caio Medeiros Pinto, Cami Martins, Carlos Martin Candela Espichan, Carolina Herrera Monteza, Daniel Román, Dante Medico Mejia, David Dali Susanibar Arce, Diana Alfaro, Eddú Meléndez Gonzales, Edmar Campos Cardoso, Edson Ferreira, Eduardo Munari, Eduardo Spotti, Emma Flores, Enzo Venturi, Ernesto Cardenas, Francisco Meneses, Gabriel Gómez de la Torre Parodi, Geoffroy Meder, Gina Alegre Milla, Glisse Lisbeth Jorge Malca, Gustavo Carvalho, Hugo Guerrero, Igor Eulálio, Ivan Contreras, Jack Torpoco, Jake Pineda, Jean Paul López, Jhon Inga, Jorge Luis Eduardo Avila Celada, Josef Calderon, Josua Castro, Juan Carlos Salvador, Juan Manuel Chávez, Jürgen Anders Guerra Ramos, Ken Esparta, Luis Falero Otiniano, Luis Rojas, Max Zeballos Torres, Nefi Arroyo, Nelson Luis Contreras Centeno, Paul Escarcena, Peter Lescano, Rafael Brito, Roberto Magallanes Martinez, Rodolfo Barzola Valdez, Rodrigo Alvarez, Sebastián Burgos, Sergio Méndez, Stanislav Yanallalli Emeliev, Stevenson Ramirez, Valeria Alexandra Villacorta Landeo, Willian Marchan Aranda, Yahaira Lisseth Perez Becerra.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for sharing your expertise and helping grow this community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud native in Latin America has a bright future, and events like KCD Lima continue to carry that momentum forward. If you are considering being part of the Latin American cloud native community, come for the food, but stay for the expertise. You’ll be glad you did!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;利马，秘鲁 - “ Ciudad de los Reyes”，主办了上周末在该地区该地区充满活力和吸引人的Kubernetes社区日（KCD）之一。从一开始，很明显，这是一场由国际合作所塑造的，对拉丁美洲的云土著技术的共同热情。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;演讲者和与会者来自巴西，阿根廷，智利，哥伦比亚，危地马拉，委内瑞拉，美国和秘鲁。多样化的代表性表明了该地区围绕开源的联系程度，来自不同国家的社区成员积极促进共同的增长。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;活动是有能力的，每个会议都被包装了。对我来说，引人入胜的是，与会者如何以与库贝肯 + Cloudnativecon相同的热情和精力来对待它，而这次是在利马发生的。从我走进地点的那一刻起，气氛就开始了。我们估计，全天有600多人加入了我们。即使我们在活动中途跑出了赃物和挂绳，精力也从未下降。实际上，当Pavel Puclla以令人难以置信的热情接待了闭合抽奖活动时，房间感觉比早上更加包装。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在星期五晚上，我们聚集在一起参加演讲者的接待。我们分享了一顿美味的当地美食，并参加了秘鲁人民的故事，挣扎和胜利的文化表演。这是与当地社区和文化建立联系的有力方法。那天晚上，我们讨论了我们的云土著社区如何在各自的国家，我们面临的挑战以及我们正在探索的策略发展参与和采用的策略。我们还分享了有关如何使用云本机工具推动有意义结果的成功故事。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与活动主持人PUCP的代表会面是另一个亮点。他们表示有兴趣通过云土著技术扩展自己的工作，我能够对更广泛的社区和秘鲁在该地区的领导地位进行一些见识。秘鲁在培养新的贡献者方面取得了令人印象深刻的进步，尤其是在不断增长的kubestronauts中，并且已成为拉丁美洲势头的中心枢纽。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为洪都拉斯移民的儿子，这次活动对我具有深厚的个人意义。我一直希望看到更多的云土著领导者从拉丁美洲出现，并在全球开源生态系统中占据一席之地。 KCD Lima是朝着这一目标迈出的明确一步。该活动不仅强调了地区人才，还提高了它。它为我们提供了合作，学习和领导的空间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我也有特权在企业中的云本地主持面板。谈话重点是现实世界中的挑战，成功案例和最佳实践。小组成员代表各种行业，包括银行，咨询，采矿，教育，培训和戈弗nment。虽然所涉及的部门列表远非详尽，但它反映了拉丁美洲的云原生实践的扎根。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;各国之间的协调水平以及KCD利马的集体投资明确表明，这是一个区域运动。该活动强调了拉丁美洲云本土生态系统的规模，才华和奉献精神。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;确认&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;衷心感谢组织者：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Carol Valencia（CNCF大使）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; pavel puclla（se.colectiva的首席执行官）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让·保罗·洛佩兹（Red Hat的高级顾问）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Juan Manuel Chavez（BCP的产品主）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Ronald Requena（Mibanco的高级工程师）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;感谢PUCP接待我们并支持秘鲁的社区增长。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;衷心感谢所有使此活动成为可能的演讲者：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;扬声器&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Almendra Paz Rodriguez, Bianca Torres, Bruno Lopes, Caio Medeiros Pinto, Cami Martins, Carlos Martin Candela Espichan, Carolina Herrera Monteza, Daniel Román, Dante Medico Mejia, David Dali Susanibar Arce, Diana Alfaro, Eddú Meléndez Gonzales, Edmar Campos Cardoso, Edson Ferreira, Eduardo Munari, Eduardo Spotti, Emma Flores, Enzo Venturi, Ernesto Cardenas, Francisco Meneses, Gabriel Gómez de la Torre Parodi, Geoffroy Meder, Gina Alegre Milla, Glisse Lisbeth Jorge Malca, Gustavo Carvalho, Hugo Guerrero, Igor Eulálio, Ivan Contreras, Jack Torpoco, Jake Pineda, Jean Paul López, Jhon Inga, Jorge Luis Eduardo Avila Celada, Josef Calderon, Josua Castro, Juan Carlos Salvador, Juan Manuel Chávez, Jürgen Anders Guerra Ramos, Ken Esparta, Luis Falero Otiniano, Luis Rojas, Max Zeballos Torres, Nefi Arroyo, Nelson Luis Contreras Centeno, Paul Escarcena, Peter Lescano, Rafael Brito, Roberto Magallanes Martinez, Rodolfo Barzola Valdez, Rodrigo Alvarez, Sebastián Burgos, Sergio Méndez, Stanislav Yanallali Emeliev，Stevenson Ramirez，Valeria Alexandra Villacorta Landeo，Willian Marchan Aranda，Yahaira Lisseth Perez Becerra。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;感谢您分享您的专业知识并帮助发展这个社区。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;拉丁美洲的云本地人有光明的未来，像KCD Lima这样的事件继续推动这种势头。如果您正在考虑成为拉丁美洲云土著社区的一部分，请来吃食物，但要求助于专业知识。您会很高兴您做到了！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PaC and AI】pac和ai</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/12/pac-and-ai/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In part three of this series on Policy as Code, we’ll look at the intersection between PaC and AI coding assistants. AI coding tools have fundamentally changed software development. “Vibe coding” or chat-based coding, where you ask the LLM to write code, and then you feed it the results and ask it to make changes in a continuous loop is fairly commonplace. But this creates a challenge; as development teams are under more pressure to code deliver faster and with smaller (human-based) team sizes, how can teams maintain expected levels of security and quality?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, like humans, AI tools are just as susceptible to writing vulnerable code – either using libraries in an unsafe way, implementing business logic flaws due to not properly understanding the context, or creating overly complex point solutions when an organization already has a defined design pattern or library to solve a certain problem, with centralized logic and expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They also can make changes to both the code and the tests, meaning that the bugs they introduce are often subtle &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; don’t fail the corresponding tests. With small changes, this is easily caught during a review, but with larger updates (as is typical when vibe coding) these bugs can easily slip through.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Automated Governance&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enter the concept of Automated Governance, which uses code to oversee changes, such as ones from AI coding tools, and can be implemented with Policy as Code.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the TAG-Security’s recent &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/community/resources/automated-governance-maturity-model/&#34;&gt;Automated Governance Maturity Model&lt;/a&gt;, we broke this down into four components:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy&lt;/strong&gt;: Traditional governance relies on static documents that quickly become outdated. With PaC, policies become code, so they can be appropriately versioned, tested, and continuously improved. This also means that it becomes a single source of truth for use by both humans and compute, guiding decision-making, risk management, and compliance activities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation&lt;/strong&gt;: Automated evaluation provides continuous assessment across all of your software repositories and runtime environments, providing feedback loops that help to refine governance strategies. An evaluation targets a specific application or service, and can be composed of multiple assessments, with each assessment having one or more steps corresponding to an assessment requirement in a control that is deemed applicable according to organizational policy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enforcement&lt;/strong&gt;: Instead of humans manually implementing controls, PaC enables automated enforcement at scale. Non-compliant resources are automatically remediated or blocked from deployment, creating a self-healing environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Audit&lt;/strong&gt;: With PaC, audit becomes a byproduct of standard operations, not an independent exercise. When policies are code and enforcement is automated, evidence collection happens continuously, allowing you to avoid unplanned work asking for audit evidence.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are a number of ways Policy as Code can help govern and oversee AI-generated code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Code Quality &amp;amp; Maintainability&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Complexity Limits&lt;/strong&gt;: Automatically enforce maximum cyclomatic and cognitive complexity thresholds to prevent AI from generating unmaintainable “spaghetti code”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Naming Convention Compliance&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensure AI-generated code follows your organization’s naming standards for variables, functions, and classes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documentation Standards&lt;/strong&gt;: Enforce proper commenting and documentation for AI-generated functions and classes to ensure future maintainability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Security &amp;amp; Compliance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure Defaults&lt;/strong&gt;: Verify that AI-generated code uses secure default configurations and avoids leaving in temporary code for local testing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sensitive Data Handling&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensure that encryption, logging, authorization, classification, and overall data handling and integrations are aligned with company expectations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous Compliance&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensure that compliance frameworks, new contracts, upcoming regulations, product requirements, and other needs are brought to the attention of developers while features and fixes are occurring in that part of the code base to reduce rework and overhead, and optimize cognitive load&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Architectural Standards &amp;amp; Resilience&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approved Components&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensure the appropriate use of existing/internal packages, services, or design or architectural patterns to improve consistency and avoid sprawl.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Domain Model Adherence&lt;/strong&gt;: Verify that AI-generated code correctly implements your domain model and business rules&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observability Standards&lt;/strong&gt;: Require implementation of proper metrics, logging, and tracing according to your observability strategy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resilience Patterns&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensure implementation of circuit breakers, retries, and other resilience patterns according to your standards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Feedback &amp;amp; Continuous Improvement&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous Improvement&lt;/strong&gt;: Identify opportunities to continuously improve code bases as they’re touched, such as revising comments to ensure they’re still accurate, re-aligning code with recent company decisions, or identifying opportunities to perform a root cause analysis or blameless postmortem on mistakes or issues with a significant impact.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy Effectiveness Metrics&lt;/strong&gt;: Measure and report on which policies are catching the most issues to focus improvement efforts as well as to feed information back upstream to the policy decision-making process, ensuring better-aligned governance with the real world.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Model Feedback Loop&lt;/strong&gt;: Provide feedback to AI coding assistants based on policy violations to improve future code generation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Automated controls allow you to govern better how your engineers use AI solutions on a daily basis. AI solutions evolve fast (and faster each day that goes by), so, having in place good guardrails at the platform level, will allow you to address security concerns that appear with the usage of agentic solutions and won’t drive your engineers’ evolution back.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;How does this apply to Cloud Native?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Platform-level, automated controls let engineers move quickly with AI assistants without taking on risks that the responsible engineers aren’t fully informed of. Because policies are code, they evolve at exactly the same speed as the platform changes themselves. This frees developers to stay “in flow,” while the platform quietly blocks unsafe patterns and highlights areas for improvement, no context-switching required.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deterministic policy engines such as Kyverno and Open Policy Agent (OPA) excel at clear yes/no rules (“No public S3 buckets,” “Image must be signed”). But AI-generated changes frequently blur those lines. While there is no one-click, end-to-end solution for this today, covering that gray area can be done using a layered approach including Deterministic PaC, LLM-based reviews, and Human-in-the-Loop reviews.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本系列的第三部分中，我们将研究PAC和AI编码助手之间的交集。 AI编码工具从根本上改变了软件开发。 “ Vibe编码”或基于聊天的编码，您要求LLM编写代码，然后将其馈送结果并要求它在连续循环中进行更改是相当普遍的。但这会带来一个挑战。随着开发团队面临更大的压力，要求代码更快，并且具有较小的（人类）的团队规模，团队如何保持预期的安全和质量水平？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，像人类一样，AI工具同样容易撰写脆弱的代码 - 要么以不安全的方式使用库，因此由于无法正确理解上下文而实现业务逻辑缺陷，或者在组织已经有一个定义的设计模式或图书馆来解决某个集中的逻辑和期望时，就可以创建过度复杂的点解决方案。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他们还可以对代码和测试进行更改，这意味着他们引入的错误通常是微妙的&lt;em&gt;和&lt;/em&gt;不会使相应的测试失败。有了微小的更改，这很容易在审核中捕获，但是随着更新的更新（典型的氛围编码时），这些错误很容易通过。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;自动治理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;输入自动治理的概念，该概念使用代码来监督更改，例如AI编码工具的更改，并且可以用策略作为代码来实现。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Tag-security的最新&lt;a href =“ https://tag-security.cncf.io/community/community/resources/automated-governance-maturity-model/&gt;自动化治理成熟模型&lt;/a&gt;我们将其分解为四个组合：&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;政策&lt;/strong&gt;：传统治理依赖于迅速过时的静态文件。使用PAC，政策成为代码，因此可以适当地版本，测试并不断改进。这也意味着它成为人类使用和计算，指导决策，风险管理和合规活动的单一真实来源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;评估&lt;/strong&gt;：自动化评估提供了所有软件存储库和运行时环境的持续评估，提供了有助于完善治理策略的反馈循环。评估针对特定的应用程序或服务，可以由多次评估组成，每个评估都有一个或多个步骤，与对控制中的评估要求相对应，该要求认为根据组织政策适用于适用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;执行&lt;/strong&gt;：PAC可以大规模地实现自动执法，而不是人类手动实施控件。不合格的资源会自动修复或阻止部署，创建一个自我修复的环境。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;审核&lt;/strong&gt;：使用PAC，审核成为标准OP的副产品兴趣，不是独立的练习。当政策是代码并自动执行时，证据收集不断发生，使您可以避免计划外的工作要求审计证据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;政策有多种方式可以帮助管理和监督AI生成的代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;代码质量和可维护性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;复杂性限制&lt;/strong&gt;：自动执行最大的循环和认知复杂性阈值，以防止AI生成无与伦比的“意大利面代码” &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;命名惯例合规性&lt;/strong&gt;：确保AI生成的代码遵循您组织的变量，功能和类的命名标准&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;文档标准&lt;/strong&gt;：为AI生成的功能和类执行适当的评论和文档，以确保将来可维护性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;安全与合规性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;安全默认值&lt;/strong&gt;：验证AI生成的代码是否使用安全的默认配置，并避免将临时代码留在本地测试&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;敏感数据处理&lt;/strong&gt;：确保加密，记录，授权，分类以及整体数据处理和集成与公司的期望保持一致&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;连续合规&lt;/strong&gt;：确保合规框架，新合同，即将到来的法规，产品需求和其他需求引起开发人员的注意，而在代码基础的功能和修复程序中，要减少重做和高架的该部分，并优化认知负载&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;建筑标准和弹性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;批准的组件&lt;/strong&gt;：确保适当使用现有/内部软件包，服务或设计或建筑模式以提高一致性并避免蔓延。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;域模型依从性&lt;/strong&gt;：验证AI生成的代码是否正确实现了您的域模型和业务规则&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可观察性标准&lt;/strong&gt;：需要根据您的可观察性策略实施适当的指标，记录和跟踪&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;弹性模式&lt;/strong&gt;：确保根据您的标准实施断路器，检索和其他弹性模式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;反馈和连续改进&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;持续改进&lt;/strong&gt;：确定机会在触摸时不断改善代码库，例如修订评论以确保它们仍然准确，将代码与最近的公司决策重新调整，或者确定进行根本原因分析或无罪的邮政事态的机会，以实现误入歧途或具有重大影响的误入为&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; pol冰冷的有效性指标&lt;/strong&gt;：衡量和报告哪些政策正在捕捉最多的问题，以重点改进工作，以及在政策决策过程中以上游的方式提供信息，从而确保与现实世界更加统一的治理。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; AI模型反馈循环&lt;/strong&gt;：基于违反政策的AI编码助理的反馈，以改善未来代码生成&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自动控件使您可以更好地管理工程师每天使用AI解决方案的方式。 AI解决方案快速发展（每天都在使用），因此，在平台级别上拥有良好的护栏，您将使您能够解决使用代理解决方案使用的安全问题，并且不会推动工程师的演变。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-teading”&gt;这如何适用于云本机？&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;平台级别的自动控件使工程师可以迅速与AI助手一起移动，而无需承担责任工程师没有充分了解的风险。由于策略是代码，因此它们以与平台自行更改的速度完全相同。该平台悄悄地阻止了不安全的模式，并突出了需要改进的区域，而无需上下文切换。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确定性政策引擎（例如Kyverno和Open Policy Agent（OPA））在Clear是/否规则（“否公共S3存储桶”，“必须签署图像”）。但是AI生成的变化经常模糊这些线路。虽然今天没有一键单击的端到端解决方案，但可以使用分层方法（包括确定性PAC，基于LLM的评论和人类在循环评论）完成灰色区域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Imagine Learning Reduced Operational Overhead by 20% With Linkerd】How Imagumity学习与Linkerd的运营开销减少了20％</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/15/innovating-with-a-rock-solid-foundation-while-saving-40-on-networking-costs-imagine-learnings-journey-with-linkerd/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imaginelearning.com/&#34;&gt;Imagine Learning&lt;/a&gt;, we strive to empower educators and inspire breakthrough moments for over 18 million students across the United States. As a digital-first education solutions provider, our mission is to deliver robust, reliable, and secure experiences to support the boundless potential of K-12 learners. Achieving this at scale—spanning hundreds of thousands of daily users—requires a technical foundation as innovative as our products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;To meet these demands, our engineering team has embraced modern cloud-native technologies. The cornerstone of our infrastructure is &lt;a href=&#34;https://linkerd.io/&#34;&gt;Linkerd&lt;/a&gt;, supported by Buoyant, running on Amazon’s Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS). Linkerd gives us the critical capabilities that we need to scale effortlessly while maintaining the performance and reliability that our users depend on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Delivering Reliability and Security at Scale&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our users—students and educators—depend on fast, reliable, and secure access to our digital tools. Dropped traffic, slow load times, or security issues in the face of ever-evolving threats would disturb the user experience, potentially leading to customer churn. For that reason, reliability and security are a top priority for Imagine Learning. As our platform grew to include hundreds of microservices deployed across several Kubernetes clusters on AWS EKS, managing communications at scale to avoid these problems became extremely challenging. We needed a solution that would:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Encrypt traffic seamlessly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simplify service-to-service communication.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Provide deep observability into application-layer (L7) networking.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, we needed a service mesh.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Linkerd: Opting for Simplicity, Performance, and Security&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After evaluating multiple service mesh options, Linkerd stood out due to its simplicity, performance, and security. Unlike other solutions, Linkerd uses a tiny &lt;a href=&#34;https://linkerd.io/2020/07/23/under-the-hood-of-linkerds-state-of-the-art-rust-proxy-linkerd2-proxy/&#34;&gt;Rust-based sidecar microproxy&lt;/a&gt;, offering a small compute footprint, significantly reduced CVEs, and enhanced overall security. Linkerd’s ease of configuration allowed us to deploy it reliably and scale it within hours, enabling our team to focus on delivering value to our customers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Building a Scalable and Observable Platform&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our engineering team integrated Linkerd with several other CNCF tools to create a robust platform:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Argo CD: Enables GitOps workflows, ensuring consistent deployment of Linkerd across all clusters.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Argo Rollouts: Enable us to roll out to customers progressively using Linkerd’s Gateway API Integration informed by metrics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcbBSsu283QNrhenBD5EaTzmlNXwUrNnMlJV5mY1WjOFgz3BC9HXvjv9MK14bcI2TcGBhceZWvgflsxvvilNJLs9OGX7ghSMK5qCOmNKqCLCCR8ZrMc8f4VICiz_BJ8fqdKuYovoQ?key=_fhJw1ohr7wmtuIs99B5_25z&#34; alt=&#34;Spoke Clusters graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started the implementation by adopting the &lt;a href=&#34;https://glossary.cncf.io/gitops/&#34;&gt;GitOps&lt;/a&gt; mindset: our Kubernetes manifests are stored in Git, and we use &lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/&#34;&gt;Argo&lt;/a&gt; CD to deploy resources into our Kubernetes clusters. Argo CD manages Linkerd, Argo Rollouts, the microservices our application teams build, and the other components needed for our platform.&amp;nbsp; Once deployed, all meshed pods were automatically mTLSed!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, we started leveraging the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway-api.sigs.k8s.io/&#34;&gt;Gateway API &lt;/a&gt;in our environment to use Argo Rollouts with their Gateway API plugin. We now use Argo Rollouts for canary deployments, enabling controlled rollout of new application versions to our customers. Linkerd seamlessly changes the amount of traffic going to the new version based on Argo Rollouts’ instructions, and Argo Rollouts uses Linkerd’s HTTP metrics to understand whether a rollout is going successfully. This allows us to minimize the impact customers could experience due to a release deficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Together, these tools in this architecture allow us to maintain a highly observable and manageable Kubernetes environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Transformational Gains&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The adoption of Linkerd has yielded significant technological and business benefits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduced Operational Overhead by 20%: By streamlining service mesh management, we’ve cut the time spent on operational tasks by a substantial margin.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced Efficiency: Linkerd’s lightweight design reduced the compute requirements of our service mesh by over 80% compared to our previous service mesh implementation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved Reliability: Real-time observability ensures rapid issue resolution, translating to better user experiences and fewer disruptions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved Security: Linkerd has reduced the amount of service mesh-related CVEs we have been exposed to by 97% in 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On a personal level, these improvements mean fewer fire drills for our engineers, allowing them to focus on innovation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Looking Ahead&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we continue to scale, Imagine Learning remains committed to leveraging cloud-native technologies like Linkerd to deliver exceptional educational experiences. With a solid foundation powered by cloud-native software, including Linkerd, we are poised to inspire breakthrough moments for millions of students every day. to leveraging cloud-native technologies like Linkerd to deliver exceptional educational experiences. We are poised to inspire breakthrough moments for millions of students every day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; at &lt;a href =“ https://www.imaginelearning.com/”&gt;想象学习&lt;/a&gt;，我们努力增强教育者的能力并激发了美国超过1800万学生的突破性时刻。作为数字优先的教育解决方案提供商，我们的使命是提供强大，可靠和安全的经验，以支持K-12学习者的无限潜力。在规模上实现这一规模（涵盖数十万每日用户），这是我们产品和我们产品一样创新的技术基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;为了满足这些要求，我们的工程团队已经接受了现代云本地技术。我们的基础架构的基石是&lt;a href =“ https://linkerd.io/”&gt; Linkerd &lt;/a&gt;在Buoyant支持的，在Amazon的Elastic Kubernetes Service（EKS）上运行。 Linkerd为我们提供了至关重要的功能，我们需要毫不费力地进行扩展，同时保持用户依赖的性能和可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;按比例提供可靠性和安全性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的用户（学生和教育者）取决于快速，可靠和安全访问我们的数字工具。面对不断发展的威胁时，流量下降，加载时间缓慢或安全问题会干扰用户体验，可能导致客户流失。因此，可靠性和安全性是想象学习的重中之重。随着我们的平台的发展，包括在AWS EKS上部署了数百个在Kubernetes群集中部署的微服务，因此大规模管理通信以避免这些问题变得极具挑战性。我们需要一个可以：&lt;/p&gt;的解决方案&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;无缝加密流量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;简化服务到服务通信。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在应用程序层（L7）网络中提供深刻的可观察性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;简而言之，我们需要一个服务网格。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; Linkerd：选择简单，性能和安全性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;评估了多个服务网格选项后，Tlinkerd由于其简单性，性能和安全性而脱颖而出。 Unlike other solutions, Linkerd uses a tiny &lt;a href=&#34;https://linkerd.io/2020/07/23/under-the-hood-of-linkerds-state-of-the-art-rust-proxy-linkerd2-proxy/&#34;&gt;Rust-based sidecar microproxy&lt;/a&gt;, offering a small compute footprint, significantly reduced CVEs, and enhanced overall security. Linkerd的易于配置使我们能够可靠地部署它并在几个小时内进行扩展，从而使我们的团队能够专注于为客户提供价值。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;构建一个可扩展且可观察的平台&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的工程团队集成了Linkerd与其他几种CNCF工具来创建一个强大的平台：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Argo CD：启用Gitops工作流程，确保在所有群集中的Linkerd一致部署。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Argo推广：使我们能够使用Linkerd的网关API集成逐步向客户推出，该集成由指标告知。&lt;/ &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcbbssu283qnrhenbd5eatzmlnxwurnnmljv5my1wjofgz3bc9hxvjjvjjv9m K14BCI2TCGBHCEZWVGFLSXVVILNJLS9OGX7GHSMK5QCOMNKQCLCCLCCR8ZRMC8F4F4VICIZ_BJ8FQDKUYOVOQ？ alt =“ spoke簇图形” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们通过采用&lt;a href =“ https://glossary.cncf.io/gitops/”&gt; gitops &lt;/a&gt; Mindset：我们的Kubernetes表现存储在git中，我们使用&lt;a href =” https://argoproj.github.io &lt;/a&gt; Kubernetes集群。 Argo CD管理Linkerd，Argo推出，我们的应用团队构建的微服务以及我们平台所需的其他组件。  部署后，所有网状豆荚都会自动mtlss！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，我们开始利用&lt;a href =“ https://gateway-api.sigs.k8s.io/”&gt; Gateway API &lt;/a&gt;在我们的环境中使用Argo推出和他们的Gateway API插件。现在，我们使用Argo推广进行金丝雀部署，从而为客户提供了新的应用程序版本的控制。 Linkerd根据Argo推出的说明无缝地更改将进入新版本的流量，Argo推出使用Linkerd的HTTP指标来了解是否成功进行了推广。这使我们能够最大程度地减少客户由于释放不足而产生的影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一起，这些架构中的这些工具使我们能够保持高度可观察到的Kubernetes环境。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;变换式增益&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过Linkerd的采用带来了巨大的技术和业务利益：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将操作开销降低了20％：通过简化服务网格管理，我们将花费的时间削减了大量的利润。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;提高效率：Linkerd的轻量级设计将我们的服务网格的计算要求降低了80％以上。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可靠性的可靠性：实时可观察性可确保问题快速解决，转化为更好的用户体验和更少的中断。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;改进的安全性：Linkerd已减少了我们在2024年接触的网状网络相关CVE的数量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在个人层面上，这些改进意味着我们的工程师更少的消防演习，使他们可以专注于创新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;向前看&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着我们继续扩展，想象学习仍然致力于利用Linkerd等云本地技术提供出色的教育经验。凭借由Linkerd在内的云原生软件提供支持的坚实基础，我们准备激发每天数百万学生的突破性时刻。利用Linkerd等云本地技术提供出色的教育经验。我们准备每天激发数百万学生的突破性时刻。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dragonfly v2.3.0 has been released】蜻蜓v2.3.0已发布</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/15/dragonfly-v2-3-0-has-been-released/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Dragonfly v2.3.0 is released! 🎉🎉🎉 Thanks to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly/graphs/contributors&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;contributors&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;who made this release happen. We welcome you to visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://d7y.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;d7y.io&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;website to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;persistent-cache-task&#34;&gt;Persistent Cache Task&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It designs to provide persistent caching for tasks. This tool can import file and export file in P2P network. The solution is specifically engineered for high-speed read and write operations. This makes it particularly advantageous for scenarios involving large files, such as machine learning model checkpoints, where rapid, reliable access and distribution across the network are critical for training and inference workflows. By leveraging P2P distribution and persistent caching, dfcache significantly reduces I/O bottlenecks and accelerates the lifecycle of large data assets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p1-1335923b71b6d0b8ab79985b83eed63f.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p1&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For documentation on how to use the dfcache command-line tool, please refer to the following link:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://d7y.io/docs/next/reference/commands/client/dfcache/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;dfcache&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ dfcache import /tmp/file.txt&lt;br&gt;⣷ Done: 2229733261&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;dfcache export 2229733261 -O /tmp/file.txt&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p2-3402280ce745b9211bef72483d4fc62b.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p2&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;resource-search-tasks-and-persistent-cache-tasks&#34;&gt;Resource Search (Tasks and Persistent Cache Tasks)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Resource Search feature enables seamless querying of tasks, including files, images, and persistent cache tasks. It optimizes resource access, improving task management and retrieval efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p3-77f7c55ff5b0787bf3eb301576c498b2.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p3&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;vortex-a-p2p-file-transfer-protocol-based-on-tlv&#34;&gt;Vortex: A P2P File Transfer Protocol Based on TLV&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vortex protocol is a high-performance peer-to-peer (P2P) file transfer protocol implementation in Rust, designed as part of the Dragonfly project. It utilizes the TLV (Tag-Length-Value) format for efficient and flexible data transmission, making it ideal for large-scale file distribution scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Packet Format:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Packet Identifier (8 bits): Uniquely identifies each packet&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tag (8 bits): Specifies data type in value field&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Length (32 bits): Indicates Value field length, up to 4 GiB&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Value (variable): Actual data content, maximum 1 GiB Protocol Format:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;|                            |                   |                    |                         |&lt;br&gt;| Packet Identifier (8 bits) |    Tag (8 bits)   |  Length (32 bits)  |   Value (up to 4 GiB)   |&lt;br&gt;|                            |                   |                    |                         |&lt;br&gt;-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information, please refer to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/vortex/blob/main/docs/README.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Vortex Protocol&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;enhanced-large-file-distribution&#34;&gt;Enhanced Large File Distribution&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release significantly enhances Dragonfly’s large file distribution capabilities, delivering improved efficiency and performance. We’ve revamped our scheduling algorithms for large file scenarios to ensure smarter resource and task allocation. Additionally, new mechanisms now more effectively balance the load across peers during large file transfers. Optimizations to the peer-to-peer (P2P) protocol and network transport layers further boost transmission efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These improvements include performance optimizations for both&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/client&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Client&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Scheduler&lt;/a&gt;. You can find more details in the project’s pull request.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;support-scopes-for-personal-access-tokens-pats&#34;&gt;Support scopes for Personal Access Tokens (PATs)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By enabling users to define specific access rights (scopes) for each PAT, we significantly enhance the security of Open API interactions. Instead of granting broad permissions, PATs can now be limited to only the necessary privileges required for a particular integration or task.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p4-50172b3cd7db0a786cfbf4506b4e7116.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p4&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;enhanced-preheating&#34;&gt;Enhanced Preheating&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;implement-distributed-rate-limiting-for-preheating-tasks&#34;&gt;Implement Distributed Rate Limiting for Preheating Tasks&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By limiting the rate at which preheating requests are initiated across the distributed system, it prevents excessive preheating activities from stressing the origin. This enhancement ensures a more stable preheating.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p5-12503b56433f8c57d422b5ca2db2e145.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p5&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;support-to-set-piece-length-for-preheating&#34;&gt;Support to set piece length for preheating&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By allowing adjustment of the piece size, users can optimize data transfer efficiency, particularly in scenarios involving large files.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p6-6397a374653fe6ea336bf72b5dbe53ed.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p6&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;flexible-preheating-set-peer-scope-by-percentage-or-count&#34;&gt;Flexible Preheating: Set Peer scope by Percentage or Count&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature enhances preheating capabilities by allowing users to specify the preheating scope more precisely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p7-4dc878da5c69ce9ff8dc35580d147b1d.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p7&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;implement-audit-logging-for-user-operations&#34;&gt;Implement Audit Logging for User Operations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature introduces comprehensive audit logging capabilities to track user operations within the system. Audit logs will record critical actions performed by users, such as initiating preheating tasks, deleting task caches, and other significant system interactions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p8-8a4d2b4938e85eb0a0370132120ada6c.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p8&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;garbage-collection&#34;&gt;Garbage Collection&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dragonfly supports Garbage Collection (GC) Audit Logs and GC Job Records to track and manage garbage collection activities. The Manager enables automated GC retention, allowing records to be preserved for a configurable time period. Additionally, it provides the capability to manually trigger forced GC operations as needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature ensures efficient monitoring and management of GC processes, offering flexibility through automated retention policies and manual intervention for immediate GC execution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p9-67adc683dc9a948cb38c167bb3df3f17.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p9&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;optimized-file-download-with-hard-link&#34;&gt;Optimized File Download with Hard Link&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;File download needs to be done in a way that is efficient and secure. If users are downloading a large file, it is not efficient to download the file and copy to the output path. Instead, we can create a hard link to the file and send the link to the user. This way, we can avoid copying the file and save time and resources. If hard link fails (e.g. due to different file systems), dfdaemon will fallback to copying the file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information, please refer to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/design/blob/main/systems-analysis/file-download-workflow-with-hard-link/README.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;file download workflow&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;hardware-acceleration-for-piece-hash-computation&#34;&gt;Hardware Acceleration for Piece Hash Computation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature enables hardware-accelerated Piece hash computation, significantly boosting performance and efficiency. By utilizing specialized hardware, the hash computation process is accelerated, allowing faster processing of large file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;advanced-storage-management&#34;&gt;Advanced Storage Management&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;disk-space-validation-for-operations&#34;&gt;Disk Space Validation for Operations&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature enhances the client’s storage functionality by implementing disk space validation. When insufficient disk space is detected, the client will return a failure response, preventing potential data corruption or incomplete operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;disk-garbage-collection-management&#34;&gt;Disk Garbage Collection Management&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature enhances Peer’s disk management by introducing configurable garbage collection (GC) thresholds based on disk usage. The distThreshold parameter allows users to define a specific disk capacity (e.g., 10TiB) as the base for calculating GC trigger points. If set, the distHighThresholdPercent (e.g., 80%) and distLowThresholdPercent (e.g., 60%) are applied relative to this capacity. If distThreshold is not provided or set to 0, these percentages are calculated based on the total actual disk space. When disk usage exceeds the high threshold, Dragonfly triggers GC(LRU) to reclaim space. GC stops when usage falls below the low threshold. This enables efficient management of a logical disk portion for caching, improving resource utilization and system performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p10-e2bde82dadf23237d62d46e83089bed3.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p10&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;support-for-opentelemetry-tracing&#34;&gt;Support for OpenTelemetry Tracing&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dragonfly supports for tracing based on OpenTelemetry, covering the Manager, Scheduler, and Peers. This enables end-to-end visibility into the download process, allowing users to query detailed information, such as overall download latency, using a specific task ID. The integration ensures efficient monitoring and performance analysis across the entire system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Add tracing configuration as follows (in Manager, Scheduler and Peer):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p11-04e5650a0acfbc8de252d1a5ad21ff63.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p11&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can access the Jaeger UI to visualize the traces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://d7y.io/assets/images/p12-0f1e72863018cdbe7b81c43fc57c4ab8.webp&#34; alt=&#34;p12&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information, please refer to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://d7y.io/docs/next/operations/best-practices/observability/tracing/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Tracing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;security-enhancements&#34;&gt;Security Enhancements&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We extend our sincere gratitude to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;CNCF TAG Security&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for their collaboration on a joint security audit. Their expertise and thorough review were invaluable in helping us identify areas for security improvement within Dragonfly. For detailed information on the specific security issues addressed and the corresponding fixes, please refer to the following issue:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly/issues/3811&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;#3811&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;nydus&#34;&gt;Nydus&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;significant-bug-fixes&#34;&gt;Significant bug fixes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed memory leaks and file descriptor leaks caused by&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;sysinfo&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;library.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cleans up the Unix domain socket (UDS) to prevent dfdaemon startup crashes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Prevent client from repeatedly downloading the same piece from multiple parents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;others&#34;&gt;Others&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;CHANGELOG&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dragonfly Website:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://d7y.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://d7y.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dragonfly Repository:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dragonfly Client Repository:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/client&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/client&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dragonfly Console Repository:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/console&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/console&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dragonfly Charts Repository:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/helm-charts&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/helm-charts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dragonfly Monitor Repository:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/monitoring&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://github.com/dragonflyoss/monitoring&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;蜻蜓v2.3.0已发行！ 🎉🎉🎉感谢&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly/graphs/contributors” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt;贡献者&lt;/a&gt;谁使此释放发生了。我们欢迎您访问&lt;a href =“ https://d7y.io/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; d7y.io &lt;/a&gt;网站以了解更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”“ id =“ features”&gt;功能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它设计的是为任务提供持久的缓存。该工具可以在P2P网络中导入文件和导出文件。该解决方案专门设计用于高速读写操作。这使得它对于涉及大型文件（例如机器学习模型检查点）的方案尤其有利，在网络上快速，可靠的访问和分发对于培训和推理工作流程至关重要。通过利用P2P分布和持续的缓存，DFCache显着降低了I/O瓶颈并加速了大数据资产的生命周期。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/p1-1335923b71b6d0b6d0b7999985b83eedb83eedb83eed63f.webp.webp” alt alt alt alt alt alt al p1 po1“ crererpolry =”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关如何使用DFCache命令行工具的文档，请参阅以下链接：&lt;a href =“ https://d7y.io/docs/next/next/reference/commands/commands/client/client/dfcache/”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ dfcache import/tmp/file.txt &lt;br&gt;⣷完成：2229733261 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; dfcache导出2229733261 -o/tmp/file.txt&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io.io/assets/images/p2-3402280ce745b92211bef72483d45483d4fc62b.webp.webp a alt&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;资源搜索功能可以无缝查询任务，包括文件，图像和持续的缓存任务。它优化了资源访问，提高任务管理和检索效率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/images/p3-77f7c55b0787bf3eb301576c498b2.webp.2.webp.webp”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ wortex-a-p2p-file-transfile-transcol-protocol-in-tlv”&gt; vortex：基于tlv &lt;/h3&gt;的P2P文件传输协议&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Vortex协议是在Rust中的高性能对等（P2P）文件传输协议实现，该协议是Dragonfly Project的一部分。它利用TLV（标签长度值）格式进行有效且灵活的数据传输，使其非常适合大规模文件分布场景。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据包格式：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;数据包标识符（8位）：独特标识每个数据包&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;标签（8位）：指定值字段中的数据类型&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;长度（32位）：指示值字段长度，最多4个gib &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;值（变量）：实际数据内容，最大1 GIB协议格式：&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------ &lt;br&gt; |                            |                   |                    |                         | &lt;br&gt; |数据包标识符（8位）|    标签（8位）|  长度（32位）|   值（最多4个GIB）| &lt;br&gt; |                            |                   |                    |                         | &lt;br&gt; ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关更多信息，请参阅&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/vortex/vortex/blob/main/main/docs/readme.md” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本大大增强了蜻蜓的较大文件分配功能，从而提高了效率和性能。我们已经对大型文件方案进行了修改，以确保资源和任务分配更明智。此外，在大型文件传输过程中，新机制现在更有效地平衡了同行的负载。对点对点（P2P）协议和网络传输层的优化进一步提高了传输效率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些改进包括&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/client” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; client &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ NOOPENER“&gt;调度程序&lt;/a&gt;。您可以在项目的拉请求中找到更多详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“ support-scopes for-personal-access-tokens-pats”&gt;用于个人访问令牌（PATS）&lt;/h3&gt;的支持范围&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过使用户能够为每个PAT定义特定的访问权限（SCOPE），我们可以显着提高开放API交互的安全性。 PATS现在只能仅限于特定集成或任务所需的必要特权，而不是授予广泛的权限。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io.io/assets/images/p4-50172b3cd7db0a786cfbfbfbfbf4506b4506b4 e7116b4e7116.webp”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block-neading” id =“实现 - 分布限制限制 -   - 划分 - 划分任务”&gt;实现预热任务的分布率限制&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过限制在分布式系统中启动预热请求的速率，它可以防止过度的预热活动强调原点。这种增强的ensu重新加热更稳定。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/p5-12503b5643b56433f8c57d4222b5ca2b5ca2db2 e145.webp”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头” id =“支撑对 - 件式的长度 - 划线”&gt;支持预热&lt;/h4&gt;的零件长度&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过调整件尺寸，用户可以优化数据传输效率，尤其是在涉及大文件的情况下。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/p6-6397a374653fe6ae336bf72bf72b5dbe53ed.webp”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ flexible-preeheating-set-per-scope-scope-by-％或计数”&gt;柔性预热：按百分比设置对等范围&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能通过允许用户更精确地指定预热范围来增强预热功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/images/p7-4dc878da5c69ce9ff8dc355555580d147b147b1d147b1d.webp.webp”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ Impart-audit-logging-user-user-operations”&gt;实施用户操作的审计记录&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能介绍了全面的审核记录功能，以跟踪系统内的用户操作。审核日志将记录用户执行的关键操作，例如启动预热任务，删除任务库和其他重要的系统交互。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io.io/assets/images/p8-8a4da4d2b4938e85eb0a0a0a0a0a0a0370132120a666c.webp = bp ply =”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“垃圾收集”&gt;垃圾收集&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;蜻蜓支持垃圾收集（GC）审核日志和GC工作记录，以跟踪和管理垃圾收集活动。管理器启用自动GC保留，允许在可配置的时间段内保存记录。此外，它提供了手动触发强制GC操作的能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能可确保对GC流程的有效监控和管理，从而通过自动保留策略和手动干预提供灵活性，以立即执行GC。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/images/p9-67adc683dc9a948cb38c167bbbbb3df3f3f3f3f3f3f17.webp17.webp”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“优化文件 - 降低链接 - 链接”&gt;优化的文件下载带有硬链接&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;文件下载需要以高效且安全的方式进行。如果用户正在下载大文件，则下载文件并将其复制到输出路径不高。相反，我们可以创建到文件的硬链接并将链接发送给用户。这样，我们可以避免复制文件并节省时间和资源。如果硬链路失败（例如，由于不同ent文件系统），dfdaemon将退缩以复制文件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关更多信息，请参阅&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/design/design/blob/main/main/systems-analysis/file-download-workflow-workflow-with-with-with-nard-nard-link/readme.md-hard-link/readme.md-&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能启用了硬件加速片段的哈希计算，可显着提高性能和效率。通过使用专门的硬件，哈希计算过程加速了，可以更快地处理大型文件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“高级存储管理”&gt;高级存储管理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头” id =“磁盘 - 空间验证 - 操作”&gt;用于操作的磁盘空间验证&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能通过实现磁盘空间验证来增强客户端的存储功能。当检测到磁盘空间不足时，客户将返回故障响应，防止潜在的数据损坏或不完整的操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能通过基于磁盘用法引入可配置的垃圾收集（GC）阈值来增强PEER的磁盘管理。 Distthreshold参数允许用户定义特定的磁盘容量（例如10TIB）作为计算GC触发点的基础。如果设定，则相对于此能力，将使用二十三位（例如80％）和迪斯特雷斯特雷斯特（Distlowthresterpercent）（例如60％）。如果未提供或设置为0，则这些百分比是根据总磁盘空间计算的。当磁盘使用率超过高阈值时，蜻蜓触发了GC（LRU）来收回空间。当使用情况低于低阈值时，GC停止。这可以有效地管理用于缓存，改善资源利用率和系统性能的逻辑磁盘部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/images/p10-e2bde82bde82daddadf23237d62d62d62d46e83089 bed3.webp” alt alt alt alt alt alt =“ p10”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“支持 -  opentelemetry-tracing”&gt;支持OpentElemetry Tracing &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;蜻蜓支持基于OpentElemetry的跟踪，涵盖经理，调度程序和同行。这可以使下载过程的端到端可见性，使用户可以使用特定的任务ID查询详细信息，例如总体下载延迟。集成确保整个系统的有效监视和性能分析。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;添加跟踪配置如下（在Manager，Scheduler和Peer中）：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/images/p11-04e5650a0acfbc8de25252521a521a5ad21ff61ff633.webp63.webp” alt alt alt alt alt alt alt =“ p11” noonererpoler =“  - 图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以访问Jaeger UI以可视化痕迹。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://d7y.io/assets/images/p12-0f1e72863018cdbe7b81c43fc43fc57c43fc57c4ab8.webp8.webp”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关更多信息，请参阅&lt;a href =“ https://d7y.io/docs/next/next/next/poperations/best-practices/observication/tracibility/tracing/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; noreferrer noopener“&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“安全性增强”&gt;安全增强&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们衷心感谢&lt;a href =“ https://tag-security.cncf.io/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; cncf标签标签安全性&lt;/a&gt;他们在共同的安全审计方面的协作。他们的专业知识和彻底的审查在帮助我们确定蜻蜓内安全性的领域非常宝贵。有关解决的特定安全问题和相应修复程序的详细信息，请参阅以下问题：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly/issues/3811” target =“ _ slank” rel =“ rel =” noreferrer noopener noopener noopener noopener noopener“&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”“ id =“ nydus”&gt; nydus &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;固定内存泄漏和文件描述符泄漏由&lt;code&gt; sysinfo &lt;/code&gt;库。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;清理UNIX域插座（UDS），以防止DFDAEMON启动崩溃。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;防止客户反复从多个父母那里下载同一件作品。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”“ id =“其他”&gt;其他&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以看到&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly/blob/main/main/changelog.md” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; changElog &lt;/a&gt;有关更多详细信息。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”“ id =“ links”&gt;链接&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;蜻蜓网站：&lt;a href =“ https://d7y.io/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; https://d7y.io/ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;蜻蜓存储库：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonfly” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; https://github.com/github.com/dragonflyoss/dragonflyoss/dragonfly &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;蜻蜓客户库存储库：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/client” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; https://github.com/github.com/dragonflyoss/client/client &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;蜻蜓控制台存储库：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/console” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; https：//github.com/github.com/dragonflyoss/console &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;蜻蜓图表存储库：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/helm-charts” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; https://github.com/github.com/dragonflyoss/helm-chelm-chelm-helm-charts &lt;/helm-charts &lt;/lie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;蜻蜓监视库存储库：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/dragonflyoss/monitoring” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; https：//github.com/github.com/dragonflyoss/monitoring &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style =“高度：80px” aria-hidded =“ true“ class =” WP-block-pacer是风格的80-120&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Code: Open Source, Mentorship and Microcks】超越代码：开源，指导和Microcks</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/14/beyond-code-open-source-mentorship-and-microcks/</link>
      <description>【&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdmD9uMfsXK5PGrWMp3iKML56KdSqvMzeFtXL--zETrPIKYAwizNfmxM8xWaJpR_1rIY-oZ2O50EQncuL49ZdL0VfS5QLWjqp6jufitC1GTWW7JTCzt-DNhoGWA5gedNfONXMkgig?key=Wt8RVK4vQ6IWAEi65VQhyQ&#34; style=&#34;&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of large puzzle pieces&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pexels.com/photo/close-up-photo-of-people-holding-puzzle-pieces-6147381/&#34;&gt;Photo by Diva Plavalaguna from Pexels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Open source software proves that collective contribution creates collective value. However, as a contributor to Microcks, I have observed a concerning pattern that threatens the sustainability of the project and countless others in the open source ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Reality Behind the Code&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For years, the Microcks team of contributors and maintainers has dedicated countless hours to creating, enhancing, and maintaining Microcks. They have handled complex bugs, responded to support requests, and continuously improved the platform to satisfy the expanding demands of API mocking and testing. This work has been done without financial compensation, driven purely by our passion for creating valuable tools for the developer community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The numbers tell a story: thousands of downloads, hundreds of GitHub stars, and a growing user base that spans startups to enterprise organizations. Microcks has become integral to many development workflows, saving teams countless hours and enabling better API development practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Silent Users&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yet, despite this widespread adoption, we’ve noticed something troubling. Many users remain silent beneficiaries, downloading, deploying, and benefiting from Microcks, but their engagement ends there. When we reach out for community input, request feedback on new features, or seek help with documentation, the response is often silence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This silence creates a challenging paradox for open source maintainers. While seeing download metrics and usage statistics climb feels validating, the lack of community engagement makes it difficult to prioritize development efforts, understand real-world pain points, and build the collaborative ecosystem that makes open source projects truly sustainable. We find ourselves making decisions in a vacuum, uncertain whether we’re solving the right problems or building features that actually matter to our users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This isn’t about demanding gratitude or expecting every user to become a contributor. We understand that not everyone has the time, skills, or resources to contribute code. But there’s a vast middle ground between passive consumption and active development that many of our users could occupy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Cost of Silence&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This one-sided relationship creates several challenges:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sustainability concerns&lt;/em&gt;: When maintainers burn out or move on to other projects, there’s often no one ready to step up. The knowledge and passion that built the project can disappear overnight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Innovation stagnation:&lt;/em&gt; Without diverse input from real users, we’re essentially developing in an echo chamber. We miss crucial use cases, overlook pain points, and may focus on features that sound good in theory but don’t address real-world needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Community fragmentation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;:&lt;/em&gt; A healthy open source project builds a community, not just a user base. Without engaged users, we risk losing the collaborative spirit that makes open source powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recognition deficit:&lt;/em&gt; While we don’t seek fame, visibility helps attract new contributors, secures funding opportunities, and validates the time we invest in the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Simple Ways to Give Back&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Contributing to Microcks (and any open source project) doesn’t require being a coding wizard. Here are meaningful ways to support the community:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spread the word:&lt;/em&gt; Share your success stories, write blog posts about how Microcks solved your problems, or mention it in relevant discussions. Word-of-mouth is incredibly powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Engage authentically:&lt;/em&gt; Star the repository, participate in discussions, attend community calls, or join our Slack/Discord. Your presence and voice matter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Documentation contributions: &lt;/em&gt;Did you find something confusing? Noticed a gap in our docs? Even minor improvements to documentation help countless future users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Report issues thoughtfully:&lt;/em&gt; When you encounter bugs, report them with details. Good bug reports are contributions that help everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Answer questions:&lt;/em&gt; Share your knowledge if you see someone struggling with something you’ve figured out. Peer support strengthens the entire community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Join the adopter community:&lt;/em&gt; If Microcks helps your organization, join the public adopter list: &amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/microcks/.github/blob/main/ADOPTERS.md&#34;&gt;https://github.com/microcks/.github/blob/main/ADOPTERS.md&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;A Sustainable Future&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re not asking for charity, we’re asking for partnership. Open source works best when it’s truly collaborative, when users become stakeholders in the project’s success. The most successful open source projects aren’t just tools; they’re communities of people who care about solving problems together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microcks has reached a critical juncture. We can continue growing as a community-driven project or remain a tool maintained by a few for the benefit of many. The choice isn’t ours alone—it belongs to everyone who has ever&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;benefited from our work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Your Turn – Join Me in Building These Resources&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If Microcks has helped you ship better software, meet deadlines, or solve API testing challenges, I have specific ways you can help make it even better for everyone. As part of my LFX mentorship project, I’m working on critical resources our community desperately needs, but I can’t complete them without your real-world insights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how you can contribute right now:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Share Your Deployment Details&lt;/em&gt; – Help us build the&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/microcks/community/issues/85&#34;&gt; Compatibility Matrix (#85)&lt;/a&gt; by sharing which versions of Kubernetes, MongoDB, and Keycloak work with your Microcks setup. Your configuration details help others avoid compatibility headaches.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Contribute Performance Data&lt;/em&gt; – Join our&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/microcks/community/issues/86&#34;&gt; Sizing Guide initiative (#86)&lt;/a&gt; by running our k6 benchmarks and sharing your results. Whether you’re running Microcks on a laptop or enterprise Kubernetes, your performance data helps teams right-size their deployments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Share Security Solutions&lt;/em&gt; – If you’ve figured out how to secure Microcks mock endpoints with API gateways, please contribute to our&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/microcks/community/issues/51&#34;&gt; Security Documentation (#51)&lt;/a&gt;. Your Kong/ AWS API Gateway/ Traefik or NGINX configurations could save someone days of troubleshooting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These aren’t just documentation requests – they’re opportunities to ensure that the challenges you’ve already solved don’t need to be solved again by the next user.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The next time you see these issues or similar calls for help, don’t scroll past.&lt;/strong&gt; Your experience is precisely what we need to build resources that genuinely serve the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our GitHub repository is at&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/microcks/community&#34;&gt; microcks/community&lt;/a&gt;. The community is waiting for your insights to help ensure these initiatives succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The future of Microcks depends not just on code commits, but on community commits. Are you ready to make yours?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Blog by Krishi Agrawal (LFX’25 mentee @Microcks)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quote:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yacine Kheddache – Microcks’ maintainer&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;“As a maintainer of the Microcks project and mentor to Krishi during the 3 month LFX mentorship program, I was both glad and impressed to see how clearly she articulated one of the core challenges many open source projects face: the gap between being a good open source citizen and users who remain passive or silent. The project she worked on was a perfect example of something maintainers often can’t take on themselves, as our focus must remain on the project’s core objectives. After all, Microcks is an open source initiative, not a commercial product. This means adopters and the community must take responsibility for their deployment environments and requirements. That’s exactly why Krishi initiated the community repository and installation documentation, which we hope the community will continue to maintain and grow. Sharing is caring.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;h1 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdmd9umfsxk5pgrwmphmphmp3ikml56kdsqvmzeftxl--zetrpikyawiznfmxm 8XWAJPR_1RIY-OZ2O50EQNCUL49ZDL0VFS5QLWJQP6JUFITC1GTWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW7JTCZT-DNHOGWA5GEDNFONXMKGIG？ style =“” alt =“大型拼图的图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.pexels.com/photo/photo/close-up-photo-ople-people-holding-holding-puzzle-puzzle-puzzle-puzzle-pukees-6147381/&gt; pex plavalaguna的照片&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开源软件证明了集体贡献创造集体价值。但是，作为Microcks的贡献者，我观察到了一种关于项目的可持续性和在开源生态系统中的无数其他模式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;代码背后的现实&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多年来，贡献者和维护者的Microcks团队拥有无数小时的时间来创建，增强和维护Microcks。他们处理了复杂的错误，对支持请求做出了响应，并不断改进了平台，以满足API模拟和测试的不断扩展的需求。这项工作是在没有经济薪酬的情况下完成的，这纯粹是我们对开发人员社区创造有价值工具的热情驱动的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数字讲述了一个故事：数千个下载，数百个GitHub星星以及不断增长的用户群，将初创公司跨越企业组织。 Microcks已成为许多开发工作流程不可或缺的一部分，为团队节省了无数小时并实现了更好的API开发实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;无声用户&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，尽管采用了广泛的采用，但我们注意到了一些令人不安的事情。许多用户仍然保持沉默的受益人，下载，部署并从Microcks中受益，但他们的参与度结束了。当我们接触社区输入，请求对新功能的反馈或寻求文档帮助时，响应通常是沉默的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种沉默为开源维护者创造了一个具有挑战性的悖论。在看到下载指标和使用统计数据攀登感到有效的同时，缺乏社区参与使得很难确定开发工作，了解现实世界中的痛苦点并建立协作生态系统，从而使开源项目真正可持续。我们发现自己在真空中做出决定，不确定我们是在解决正确的问题还是构建对用户至关重要的功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这不是要对感激之情或期望每个用户成为贡献者。我们了解到，并非每个人都有时间，技能或资源来贡献代码。但是，在被动消费和积极发展之间存在着巨大的中间立场，我们的许多用户可能会占据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;沉默的成本&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种单方面关系造成了几个挑战：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;可持续性关注&lt;/em&gt;：当维护者烧毁或进入其他项目时，通常没有人准备加强。建立该项目的知识和热情可能会在一夜之间消失。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;创新停滞：&lt;/em&gt;没有来自真实用户的多种投入，我们基本上是在回声室中发展的。我们错过了关键用例，忽略疼痛点，并可能专注于理论上听起来不错但不能满足现实需求的功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;社区碎片&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;：&lt;/em&gt;健康的开源项目建立了一个社区，而不仅仅是用户群。没有参与的用户，我们可能会失去使开源力量强大的协作精神。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;认可赤字：&lt;/em&gt;虽然我们不寻求名望，但可见性有助于吸引新的贡献者，获得资金机会并验证我们投资于该项目的时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;简单的回馈&lt;/h2&gt;的方法&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为Microcks（和任何开源项目）做出贡献，不需要作为编码向导。这是支持社区的有意义的方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;传播一词：&lt;/em&gt;分享您的成功案例，写有关Microcks如何解决您的问题的博客文章，或在相关讨论中提及它。口碑非常强大。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;真正的参与：&lt;/em&gt;明星存储库，参加讨论，参加社区电话或加入我们的休闲/不和谐。您的存在和声音很重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;文档贡献：&lt;/em&gt;您发现某些令人困惑的东西吗？注意到我们的文档存在差距吗？即使对文档的微小改进也有助于无数未来的用户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;周到地报告问题：&lt;/em&gt;遇到错误时，请提供详细信息。好的错误报告是帮助所有人的贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;回答问题：&lt;/em&gt;如果您看到有人在遇到的东西，请分享您的知识。同伴支持增强了整个社区。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;加入采用者社区：&lt;/em&gt;如果Microcks帮助您的组织，请加入公共采用者列表：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/microcks/.github/blob/main/adopters.md”&gt; https://github.com/microcks/microcks/.github/blob/blob/main/main/adopters.md.md &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;可持续的未来&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们不是在要求慈善机构，我们要求建立合作伙伴关系。当用户成为项目成功的利益相关者时，开源效果最好。最成功的开源项目不仅仅是工具。他们是关心共同解决问题的人的社区。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Microcks达到了关键时刻。我们可以继续作为一个社区驱动的项目成长，或者仍然是少数人维护的工具，以使许多人受益。选择不是我们一个人，它属于&lt;/p&gt;的每个人&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从我们的工作中受益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;您的轮流 - 加入我构建这些资源&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果Microcks帮助您运送更好的S最终，满足截止日期或解决API测试挑战，我有特定的方法可以帮助每个人都更好。作为我的LFX指导项目的一部分，我正在为社区迫切需要的关键资源致力于，但是如果没有您的真实见解，我无法完成它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是您现在可以做出贡献的方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;分享您的部署详细信息&lt;/em&gt;  - 帮助我们构建&lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/microcks/microcks/community/issues/85”&gt;兼容性矩阵（＃85）&lt;/a&gt;通过共享Kubernetes，mongocks，keycaraks和keycarak，keycarak，keycock和keycock，keycock和key keke your your your your your your your your your keycock your keycaraks＆k.您的配置详细信息可帮助他人避免兼容性头痛。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt;贡献绩效数据&lt;/em&gt;  - 加入我们的&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/microcks/community/issues/86”&gt; sizing指南intiative（＃86）&lt;/a&gt;通过运行我们的K6基准标和共享结果。无论您是在笔记本电脑还是企业Kubernetes上运行Microcks，您的性能数据都可以帮助团队正确大小的部署。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt;共享安全解决方案&lt;/em&gt;  - 如果您已经弄清了如何使用API网关模拟Microcks模拟端点，请为我们的&lt;a a href =“ https://github.com/microck.com/microcks/community/issues/issues/issues/51”&gt; Security Docording（＃51）&lt;/a&gt;。您的kong/ aws api网关/ traefik或nginx配置可以节省某人的故障排除。&lt;/ li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些不仅仅是文档请求 - 它们是确保您已经解决的挑战不需要再次被下一个用户解决的机会。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;下次您看到这些问题或类似的帮助时，请不要滚动。&lt;/strong&gt;您的经验正是我们建立真正为社区服务的资源所需的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的github存储库位于&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/microcks/community”&gt; microcks/community &lt;/a&gt;。社区正在等待您的见解，以帮助确保这些举措成功。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Microcks的未来不仅取决于代码提交，还取决于社区提交。您准备好制作自己的吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class =“ wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Krishi Agrawal的博客（LFX’25 Mentee @microcks）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Quote：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; yacine kheddache  -  Microcks的维护者&lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt;“作为Microcks项目的维护者和Krishi的指导者，在3个月的LFX指导计划中，我很高兴和印象深刻地，她很高兴看到她在许多开放式挑战中表达出了一个良好的开放式挑战，而在某些开放式公民方面的差异是一个良好的开放式挑战：在良好的开放式公民方面，她是一个良好的项目，或者是一个不断的态度，而这些项目的差距是她的一个差异，而这些项目的差异是一个善于态度，而这些项目的差异是她的依据，而这些挑战是一个依据的人，或者是一个依据的人，而这些挑战却是一个依据，那就是她们的差异是一个善于选择的人。毕竟，由于我们的核心目标是我们的核心目标。和要求。这就是克里希（Krishi）启动社区存储库和安装文档的原因，我们希望社区能够继续维护和发展。共享很关心。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OpenKruise v1.8 Unlocking Infinite Possibilities in Cloud-Native Application Management】OpenKruise v1.8在云本地应用程序管理中解锁无限可能性</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/13/openkruise-v1-8-unlocking-infinite-possibilities-in-cloud-native-application-management/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openkruise/kruise&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;OpenKruise&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;is an open-source cloud-native application automation management suite. It is also a current incubating project hosted by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF). It is a standard extension component based on Kubernetes that is widely used in production of internet scale company. It also closely follows upstream community standards and adapts to the technical improvement and best practices for internet-scale scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In February 2025, OpenKruise released its latest version 1.8[2]. This version brings many important updates and enhancements, aimed at further improving the efficiency, elasticity, and reliability of cloud-native application management. This article provides a comprehensive overview of the new version.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1. Embrace In-Place VPA: Unlock New Potential in Resource Management&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Authors:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/LavenderQAQ&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;@LavenderQAQ,&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ABNER-1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;@ABNER-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Kubernetes 1.27, the significant enhancement of&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;InPlacePodVerticalScaling&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;(In-Place VPA) was introduced to boost the flexibility and efficiency of resource management. This feature has recently advanced to Beta in Kubernetes 1.33, reflecting its improved stability and suitability for production environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kruise is dedicated to boosting users’ workload management capabilities. In Kruise 1.8, we first integrated InPlacePodVerticalScaling with our advanced workload types like CloneSet, Advanced StatefulSet, and Advanced DaemonSet. Users can directly modify the resource settings in the workload to perform in-place resizing of resources for all pods under the workload without restarts, or simultaneously resources resize and upgrade images during in-place pod upgrades without recreating pods. This integration delivers a unique and optimized resource management experience that has not yet been incorporated into native Kubernetes workloads, offering users a distinct advantage in leveraging this innovative feature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1.1 Core Highlights&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Easier and More Stable Implementation of Specification Changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Historically, both manual user-initiated and VPA-recommended resource adjustments triggered instance recreation, potentially introducing operational disruptions or system instability. This approach poses critical risks in high-load scenarios — upgrading database resources during peak demand becomes a high-stakes endeavor with potential cascading effects. Furthermore, the current VPA implementation relies on webhook modifications for newly scaled instances, creating specification drift between runtime configurations and pod templates. This architectural limitation impedes visibility and often prevents intended resource optimizations from materializing effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Future Integration with VPA for More Stable Vertical Scaling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By leveraging workload controllers’ inherent capability to orchestrate pod lifecycle operations, we can implement coordinated change management with built-in availability safeguards. Our strategic roadmap includes enabling VPA to initiate resource adjustments through standardized workload interfaces, ensuring consistent configuration updates across both existing and newly provisioned instances. This controller-centric approach eliminates direct pod manipulation, mitigating availability degradation risks caused by conflicting modifications from concurrent controllers while maintaining strict service level objectives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1.2 Enabling the Feature&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1. Ensure Kubernetes Cluster Support&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Verify that your Kubernetes cluster has the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;InPlacePodVerticalScaling&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;feature enabled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2. Enable During Kruise Installation/Upgrade&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When installing or upgrading Kruise, enable&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;InPlaceWorkloadVerticalScaling.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;3. Configure Update Strategy&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Set the update strategy to either&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;InPlaceIfPossible&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;InPlaceOnly&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1.3 Current Capabilities and Limitations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Supported Resource Types&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Only CPU and memory resources can be adjusted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Environment Constraints&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Certain limitations exist when operating in a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Cgroupv1&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Adjustment Restrictions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If resource adjustments result in changes to a Pod’s Quality of Service (QoS), Kruise-manager will automatically revert to recreating the Pod.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1.4 Example Configuration&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: apps.kruise.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: CloneSet&#xA;spec:&#xA;  template:&#xA;    spec:&#xA;      containers:&#xA;        - name: example-container&#xA;          resources:&#xA;            requests:&#xA;              memory: &#34;512Mi&#34;&#xA;              cpu: &#34;500m&#34; # Adjusted from 1 -&amp;gt; 500m / 2&#xA;  updateStrategy:&#xA;    type: InPlaceIfPossible&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Key Considerations:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;● The&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;InPlacePodVerticalScaling&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;feature in Kubernetes is still evolving. Carefully assess its suitability before deploying it in production environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;● Keep up-to-date with the latest developments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2. Redefining Storage Management for Stateful Workloads&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Authors:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ABNER-1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;@ABNER-1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Throughout the evolution of Kubernetes, the Volume Expansion feature[6] was introduced in version 1.8 and became a General Availability (GA) feature in version 1.24. However, Persistent Volume Claims (PVCs) managed by the built-in StatefulSet have not fully leveraged this feature. Users have had to manually batch update PVCs for capacity maintenance, while newly added PVCs retain the original configuration, making the storage management for stateful workloads complex and inefficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Starting from its early versions, Kruise allowed users to manage the capacity of new PVCs by directly modifying the volume template of StatefulSet. In the latest Kruise 1.8, we have introducing&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;in-place volume expansion support&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;for StatefulSet, aiming to revolutionize the storage management of stateful applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2.1 Core Highlights: Seamless Expansion, Simplified Operations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. In-place Expansion:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;No Pod Restart or Data Migration Required&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For stateful applications, storage capacity expansion often entails high maintenance costs and potential application downtime risks. Kruise 1.8’s in-place expansion feature allows users to directly increase the PVC capacity managed by Advanced StatefulSet without restarting pods or migrating data. This not only significantly reduces application downtime but also greatly simplifies the storage management process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Gradual Changes:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Combined with Rolling Update Strategy&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kruise 1.8 also introduces a gradual change mechanism combined with the pod rolling sequence. Through this method, users can gradually and safely apply storage capacity expansion to existing PVCs, ensuring a smooth and reliable change process that minimizes the impact on business operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Automated Management:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;No Manual Operations&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the past, users needed to manually batch update PVC configurations, which was cumbersome and prone to errors. Now, with Kruise’s automated management capabilities, you can easily achieve unified management for both new and existing PVCs, significantly enhancing operational efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2.2 Feature Limitations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Kubernetes cluster in use must enable Volume Expansion or be above version 1.24.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The storage class of the PVC to be expanded must be managed by CSI and support volume expansion. You can check the allowVolumeExpansion field of the storage class object to determine this.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To use this feature, you need to enable the StatefulSetAutoResizePVCGate Feature Gate when installing or upgrading Kruise.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2.3 Usage Example&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Control the volume update strategy through the volumeClaimUpdateStrategy field, including two modes: OnPodRollingUpdate and OnDelete.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OnPodRollingUpdate mode allows automatic adjustment of PVC size during pod rolling updates, whereas the OnDelete mode requires manual deletion of old PVC before using the new volume template to recreate the PVC. This feature greatly enhances the flexibility and efficiency of managing stateful application storage, allowing easier adjustments when storage requirements change. Example configuration is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: apps.kruise.io/v1beta1&#xA;kind: StatefulSet&#xA;spec:&#xA;  # ...&#xA;  volumeClaimUpdateStrategy:&#xA;    # Options are OnPodRollingUpdate and OnDelete&#xA;    #   OnPodRollingUpdate: controller will automatically expand PVC during pod upgrade&#xA;    #   OnDelete: controller will only use the new volume claim template to reconstruct PVC after PVC deletion&#xA;    #             i.e., the default PVC update strategy before Kruise version 1.7.&#xA;    type: OnPodRollingUpdate &#xA;  volumeClaimTemplates:&#xA;    # ...&#xA;    spec:&#xA;      resources:&#xA;        requests:&#xA;          storage: 2Gi # 1Gi -&amp;gt; 2Gi&#xA;      storageClassName: allow-volume-expansion&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After modifying the advanced statefulset spec, you can observe the changes in the status to monitor the PVC change situation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;status:&#xA;  #...&#xA;  volumeClaimTemplates:&#xA;    - compatibleReadyReplicas: 0 # Number of PVCs with completed changes&#xA;      compatibleReplicas: 1 # Number of PVCs with updated spec sizes&#xA;      volumeClaimName: data0&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;3. Empowering AI Workloads with WorkloadSpread’s Capabilities&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Authors:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/AiRanthem&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;@AiRanthem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the Kubernetes ecosystem, multi-region management and flexible scheduling have always been core needs for complex workloads. Since the introduction of WorkloadSpread in Kruise 0.10.0, this feature has provided users with a non-intrusive way to enable detailed management of workloads across regions and nodes. Whether it’s spreading workloads horizontally by host or availability zone, or partition management by proportion and priority, WorkloadSpread demonstrates its powerful flexibility and adaptability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, in practical applications, we found that not all workloads could fully meet the assumptions of WorkloadSpread. For example, AI workloads (such as TFJob in KubeFlow), due to their multi-role design, do not implement the Kubernetes Scale subinterface, making them unable to directly utilize the capabilities provided by WorkloadSpread. These workloads often need to span dedicated hardware or different availability zones to achieve better performance and flexibility, making the demand for multi-region management particularly urgent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Kruise 1.8, we have made significant upgrades targeting this pain point—supporting workloads that have not implemented the Scale subinterface. With the newly added&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;targetFilter&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;configuration, users can now easily apply WorkloadSpread’s capabilities to complex AI workloads like TFJob, enabling more efficient resource allocation and management.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below is a sample configuration for WorkloadSpread’s&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;targetFilter&lt;/code&gt;. For more detailed documentation, please refer to the WorkloadSpread documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: apps.kruise.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: WorkloadSpread&#xA;spec:&#xA;  # ...&#xA;  targetRef:&#xA;    apiVersion: kubeflow.org/v1alpha1&#xA;    kind: TFJob&#xA;    name: tfjob-demo&#xA;  # Use targetFilter to provide support for workloads without the Scale subinterface&#xA;  targetFilter: &#xA;    selector:&#xA;      # Use selector to filter instances managed by targetRef&#xA;      matchLabels:&#xA;        role: worker&#xA;    replicasPathList:&#xA;      # Use replicasPathList to specify the total number of replicas needed by targetRef&#xA;    - spec.tfReplicaSpecs.Worker.replicas&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;4. Custom Probing: Injecting New Vitality into Serverless Scenarios&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Authors:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/zmberg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;@zmberg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since the introduction of the PodProbeMarker custom probing feature in Kruise 1.3, it has rapidly become a trusted tool among developers due to its flexible extension capabilities and wide range of applications. Specifically, in game solutions&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;OpenKruise Game&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;(OKG), the service quality probing capabilities based on PodProbeMarker have helped numerous game developers achieve efficient and stable service management, making it the preferred tool in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, in&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;serverless scenarios&lt;/strong&gt;, PodProbeMarker’s custom probing capabilities once faced challenges. Before Kruise version 1.8, the implementation of PodProbeMarker relied on the node component&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Kruise-Daemon,&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;which could not be deployed in a serverless environment, thereby limiting its probing abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, with the release of Kruise 1.8, this issue has finally been resolved! The Kruise team has optimized for serverless scenarios, extending the PodProbeMarker protocol to serverless pods, providing new possibilities for custom probing. You can now fully utilize resources in serverless scenarios while enjoying high-quality custom service probing capabilities, safeguarding your service operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The extension of the PodProbeMarker protocol in serverless scenarios is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Kruise-manager adds the required probe via the annotation&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;kruise.io/podprobe&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;on serverless pods.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The serverless PodProbeMarker implementation reads the probe information from the annotation&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;kruise.io/podprobe&lt;/code&gt;, executes the probe, and writes the results to&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;.status.conditions[x]&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;of the pod.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Kruise-manager recognizes the probe execution results from&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;.status.conditions[x]&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;in serverless pods and performs the marking actions defined in&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;markerPolicy&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more detailed protocols and a list of supported container service providers, please refer to the PodProbeMarker documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;5. SidecarSet Gradual Injection: More Granular Version Control&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Authors:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/AiRanthem&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;@AiRanthem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the cloud-native ecosystem of Kubernetes,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;SidecarSet&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;has become one of the most popular features of Kruise, serving as a powerful tool for simplifying the management and operations of sidecar containers. Whether it’s for log collection, monitoring agents, or service mesh components, SidecarSet’s elegant design helps users easily handle complex production environment requirements. However, in previous versions, support for gradual injection scenarios was somewhat lacking, causing some inconvenience for users requiring fine-grained version control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, Kruise 1.8 introduces new enhancements by adding&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;gradual injection capabilities&lt;/strong&gt;, providing SidecarSet with unprecedented flexibility and control. Whether you wish to gradually verify the stability of a new version or need to implement complex release strategies, Kruise 1.8 offers robust support. Here is an example configuration:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: apps.kruise.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: SidecarSet&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: sidecarset&#xA;spec:&#xA;  # ...&#xA;  injectionStrategy:&#xA;    revision:&#xA;      # Specify the version to inject&#xA;      revisionName: revision-a&#xA;      # Options: Always and Partial&#xA;      #  Always: Always inject the specified version, in this case, revision-a&#xA;      #  Partial: Combine injection with the partition percentage to control the percentage of the specified version injected&#xA;      policy: Partial&#xA;  updateStrategy:&#xA;    partition: 70%&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This configuration allows you to control the injection of sidecar containers with precision, supporting advanced deployment strategies tailored to your specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;6. Helm Pre-delete Hook: Kruise Accidental Deletion Protection&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Authors:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/AiRanthem&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;@AiRanthem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In versions prior to Kruise 1.7.3, there was a significant risk involved in using Helm to uninstall Kruise, as this operation would remove Kruise itself, its custom resource definitions (CRDs), and the associated custom resources (CRs).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Starting from Kruise 1.7.3, a pre-delete hook has been introduced in the Helm uninstall process. This hook checks for the presence of custom resources managed by Kruise within the cluster uninstallation. If such resources are found, the uninstall process is stopped, preventing data loss and service interruptions due to accidental uninstallation. This improvement significantly enhances the security of managing Kruise with Helm.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Future Outlook&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For comprehensive upgrade and usage guidelines, please refer to the official&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openkruise.io/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Kruise documentation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;[4]. We believe that Kruise 1.8 will empower you to manage your cloud-native applications more effectively and elevate your application management experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Continuous Technological Evolution&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kruise is committed to providing users with exceptional cloud-native solutions. To achieve this vision, we have outlined three exciting upcoming releases:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1. Release 1.9:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Integrate LWS with Advanced StatefulSet for in-place upgrade capabilities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Develop solutions for in-place upgrade restart limitations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Implement gradual change strategies for ConfigmapSet&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2. Release 2.0:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Upgrade Kruise API to v1beta1&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;3. Release 2.1:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Develop minimalist Kruise component deployment solutions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Introduce new Liveness Probe features&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Get Involved&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to get involved with OpenKruise by joining us in Github/Slack/DingTalk/WeChat. Have something you’d like to broadcast to our community? Share your voice at our Bi-weekly community meeting (Chinese) [3], or through the channels below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;● Join the community on Slack (English) [5].&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;● Join the community on DingTalk: Search GroupID&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;23330762&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Chinese).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;● Join the community on WeChat (new): Search User&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;openkruise&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;and let the robot invite you (Chinese).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;● [1]&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openkruise/kruise&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;OpenKruise github repo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;● [2]&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openkruise/kruise/blob/master/CHANGELOG.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;ChangeLog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;● [3]&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://alidocs.dingtalk.com/i/nodes/14dA3GK8gjnMXbzEIoej1BL5J9ekBD76&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Bi-weekly community meeting (Chinese)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;● [4]&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openkruise.io/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Kruise docs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;● [5]&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.slack.com/channels/openkruise&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Slack channel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;● [6]&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/05/05/volume-expansion-ga/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;kubernetes volume-expansion ga&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/openkruise/kruise” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; openkruise &lt;/a&gt;是一个开放式云云本地应用程序自动化管理套件。它也是由云本机计算基础（CNCF）托管的当前孵化项目。它是基于Kubernetes的标准扩展组件，可在Internet规模公司的生产中广泛使用。它还仔细遵循上游社区标准，并适应了互联网规模场景的技术改进和最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2025年2月，OpenKruise发布了最新版本1.8 [2]。此版本带来了许多重要的更新和增强功能，旨在进一步提高云本地应用程序管理的效率，弹性和可靠性。本文提供了新版本的全面概述。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 1。拥抱现场VPA：解锁资源管理中的新潜力&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作者：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/lavenderqaq” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt;@lavenderqaq，&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href =“ noopener“&gt;@abner-1 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Kubernetes 1.27中，引入了&lt;code&gt; InplacePodverticalScaling &lt;/code&gt;（现场VPA）的显着增强，以提高资源管理的灵活性和效率。该功能最近已在Kubernetes 1.33中推进了Beta，反映了其对生产环境的提高稳定性和适合性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kruise致力于提高用户的工作负载管理功能。在Kruise 1.8中，我们首先将InplacePodVerticalsscaling与高级工作负载类型集成在一起，例如克隆，高级状态填充和高级Daemonset。用户可以直接修改工作负载中的资源设置，以执行无需重新启动工作负载下的所有POD的资源调整大小，或者在无需重新创建POD的情况下同时调整和升级图像大小和升级图像。这种集成提供了独特而优化的资源管理体验，尚未将其纳入本地Kubernetes工作量中，从而为用户提供了利用这一创新功能的明显优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 1.1核心亮点&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&lt;strong&gt;规格更改更容易，更稳定的实现&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;历史上，手动用户启动和VPA启用的资源调整都触发了实例娱乐，可能引入操作中断或系统不稳定性。这种方法在高负载方案中构成了关键风险 - 高峰需求期间的数据库资源成为一项高风险的努力，具有潜在的级联效应。此外，当前的VPA实现依赖于新缩放实例的Webhook修改，从而在运行时配置和POD模板之间创建规范漂移。这种建筑限制阻碍了可见性，并且通常阻止预期的资源优化有效实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&lt;strong&gt;将来与VPA的未来集成，以进行更稳定的垂直缩放&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过利用工作负载控制器的固有功能来编排POD生命周期操作，我们可以通过内置可用性保障实施协调的变更管理。我们的战略路线图包括使VPA能够通过标准化的工作负载界面启动资源调整，从而确保在现有和新提供的实例中均保持一致的配置更新。这种以控制器为中心的方法消除了直接的POD操纵，从而减轻了由并发控制器进行冲突的修改而导致的可用性降解风险，同时保持严格的服务级别目标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 1.2启用功能&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 1。确保Kubernetes群集支持&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;验证您的Kubernetes群集具有&lt;strong&gt; InplacePodVerticalScaling &lt;/strong&gt;启用功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 2。在Kruise安装/升级期间启用&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;安装或升级kruise时，启用&lt;strong&gt; Inplaceworkloadverticalsscaling。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 3。配置更新策略&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将更新策略设置为&lt;strong&gt; Inplaceifpopible &lt;/strong&gt;或&lt;strong&gt; Inplaceonly &lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt; 1.3当前功能和限制&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&lt;strong&gt;支持的资源类型&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;只能调整CPU和内存资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&lt;strong&gt;环境约束&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;strong&gt; cgroupv1 &lt;/strong&gt;环境中运行时存在某些限制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●&lt;strong&gt;调整限制&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果资源调整导致POD服务质量（QoS）的变化，Kruise-Manager将自动恢复以重新创建POD。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 1.4示例配置&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：apps.kruise.io/v1alpha1&#xA;善良：克隆&#xA;规格：&#xA;  模板：&#xA;    规格：&#xA;      容器：&#xA;         - 名称：示例包机&#xA;          资源：&#xA;            请求：&#xA;              内存：“ 512mi”&#xA;              CPU：“ 500m”＃从1-&gt; 500m / 2调整&#xA;  UpdateTrategy：&#xA;    类型：Inplaceifbleble &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;关键因素：&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●Kubernetes中&lt;strong&gt; InplacePodverticalsscaling &lt;/strong&gt;仍在发展。在将其部署在生产环境中之前，请仔细评估其适用性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●保持最新的发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 2。重新定义已陈述工作负载的存储管理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作者：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/abner-1” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt;@abner-1 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;在Kubernetes的整个演变中，在版本1.8中介绍了音量扩展功能[6]，并成为版本1.24的一般可用性（GA）功能。但是，由内置状态填充设置管理的持续数量索赔（PVC）尚未完全利用此功能。用户必须手动批处理更新PVC以维护能力维护，而新添加的PVC则保留了原始配置，使状态工作负载的存储管理复杂且效率低下。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从早期版本开始，Kruise允许用户通过直接修改状态满集的卷模板来管理新PVC的容量。在最新的kruise 1.8中，我们引入了&lt;code&gt;现场卷扩展支持&lt;/code&gt; for StateFultet，旨在彻底改变状态应用程序的存储管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 2.1核心亮点：无缝扩展，简化操作&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。现场扩展：&lt;/strong&gt;无POD重新启动或需要数据迁移&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于已陈述的应用程序，存储容量的扩展通常需要高维护成本和潜在的应用停机风险。 Kruise 1.8的现场扩展功能允许用户直接增加由高级状态满足器管理的PVC容量，而无需重新启动POD或迁移数据。这不仅大大减少了应用程序停机时间，而且还大大简化了存储管理过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 2。逐渐更改：&lt;/strong&gt;结合滚动更新策略&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kruise 1.8还引入了逐渐变化的机制与吊舱滚动序列相结合。通过这种方法，用户可以逐渐安全地将存储容量扩展到现有的PVC，从而确保平稳可靠的变更过程，以最大程度地减少对业务运营的影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 3。自动化管理：&lt;/strong&gt;无手动操作&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去，用户需要手动批处理更新PVC配置，这很麻烦且容易出错。现在，借助Kruise的自动化管理功能，您可以轻松地实现新的和现有PVC的统一管理，从而大大提高运营效率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt; 2.2特征限制&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用的Kubernetes群集必须启用卷扩展或高于版本1.24。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要扩展的PVC的存储类必须由CSI管理和支持卷扩展。您可以检查存储类对象的允许Volumeexpansion字段以确定。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要使用此功能，您需要在安装或升级kruise时启用statefulsetautoresizepvcgate功能门。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 2.3用法示例&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过卷dateStratesgy字段控制卷更新策略，包括两种模式：onpodrollingupdate和ondelete。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OnPodrollingUpdaTE模式允许在POD滚动更新期间自动调整PVC大小，而耗尽模式则需要在使用新的音量模板重新创建PVC之前手动删除旧PVC。此功能极大地提高了管理状态应用程序存储的灵活性和效率，从而在存储需求发生变化时可以更轻松地进行调整。示例配置如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：apps.kruise.io/v1beta1&#xA;善良：状态满&#xA;规格：&#xA;  ＃...&#xA;  卷发播：&#xA;    ＃选项是OnPodrollingupdate和OnDelete&#xA;    ＃OnPodrollingupdate：控制器将在POD升级期间自动扩展PVC&#xA;    ＃onDelete：控制器将仅使用新的卷声明模板来重建PVC删除后PVC&#xA;    ＃，即Kruise 1.7版之前的默认PVC更新策略。&#xA;    类型：OnPodrollingUpdate &#xA;  卷序列：&#xA;    ＃...&#xA;    规格：&#xA;      资源：&#xA;        请求：&#xA;          存储：2GI＃1GI-&gt; 2GI&#xA;      StorageClassName：wile-volume-expansion &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;修改高级状态满集规范后，您可以观察状态的更改以监视PVC变更情况：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt;状态：&#xA;  ＃...&#xA;  卷序列：&#xA;     -  compatiblereadyreplicas：0＃具有完整更改的PVC数量&#xA;      compatiblereplicas：1＃具有更新规格大小的PVC数&#xA;      FOLUMECLAIMNAME：DATA0 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 3。使用WorkloadSpread的功能授权AI工作负载&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作者：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/airanthem” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt;@airanthem &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Kubernetes生态系统中，多区域管理和灵活的计划一直是复杂工作负载的核心需求。自从在Kruise 0.10.0中引入Workloadspread以来，此功能为用户提供了一种非侵入性的方法，可以详细管理各个区域和节点的工作负载。无论是通过主机或可用性区域水平扩散工作负载，还是按比例和优先级进行分区管理，都表明了其强大的灵活性和适应性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，在实际应用中，我们发现并非所有工作负载都可以完全满足工作负载的假设。例如，AI工作负载（例如KubeFlow中的TFJOB）由于其多角色设计，因此无法实现Kubernetes Scale Supinterface，因此它们无法直接利用WorkloadSpread提供的功能。这些工作负载通常需要跨越专用的硬件或不同的可用性区域，以实现更好的性能和灵活性，从而使对多区域管理的需求特别紧急。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Kruise 1.8中，我们针对这个疼痛点进行了重大升级，这是尚未实现刻度子界面的工作负载。新添加的&lt;code&gt; targetFilter &lt;/code&gt; confgiuration，用户现在可以轻松地将Workloadspread的功能应用于复杂的AI工作负载，例如TFJOB，从而实现了更有效的资源分配和管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是Workloadspread的&lt;code&gt; TargetFilter &lt;/code&gt;的示例配置。有关更多详细的文档，请参阅Workloadspread文档。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：apps.kruise.io/v1alpha1&#xA;KINT：Workloadspread&#xA;规格：&#xA;  ＃...&#xA;  Targetref：&#xA;    apiversion：kubeflow.org/v1alpha1&#xA;    KINT：TFJOB&#xA;    名称：tfjob-demo&#xA;  ＃使用TargetFilter提供对工作负载的支持，而无需刻度子接口&#xA;  TargetFilter： &#xA;    选择器：&#xA;      ＃使用选择器过滤TargetRef管理的实例&#xA;      MatchLabels：&#xA;        角色：工人&#xA;    ReplicasPathlist：&#xA;      ＃使用replicasPathlist来指定targetRef所需的复制品总数&#xA;     -  spec.tfreplicaspecs.worker.replicas &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 4。自定义探测：将新活力注入无服务器方案&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作者：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/zmberg” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt;@zmberg &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自KRUISE 1.3中引入PodProbeMarker自定义探测功能以来，由于其灵活的扩展功能和广泛的应用程序，它已迅速成为开发人员中可信赖的工具。具体来说，在游戏解决方案&lt;Code&gt; OpenKruise Game &lt;/code&gt;（OKG）中，基于PodProbeMarker的服务质量探测功能帮助众多游戏开发人员实现了高效且稳定的服务管理，使其成为行业中的首选工具。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，在&lt;strong&gt;无服务器方案&lt;/strong&gt;中，PodProbemarker的自定义探测功能曾经面临挑战。在Kruise 1.8版之前，PodProbeMarker的实现依赖于节点组件&lt;strong&gt; kruise-daemon，&lt;/strong&gt;无法在无服务器环境中部署，从而限制了其探测能力。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，随着Kruise 1.8的发布，此问题终于解决了！ KRUISE团队已针对无服务器方案进行了优化，将PODProbeMarker协议扩展到了无服务器吊舱，为自定义探测提供了新的可能性。现在，您可以在无服务器方案中充分利用资源，同时享受高质量的自定义服务探索功能，保护您的服务操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在无服务器方案中podprobemarker协议的扩展如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Kruise-Manager通过注释&lt;Code&gt; kruise.io/podprobe &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/li&gt;添加了所需的探针。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;无服务器podprobemarker实现从注释中读取探针信息&lt;code&gt; kruise.io/podprobe &lt;/code&gt;，执行探针，并将结果写入&lt;code&gt; .status.condition.condition.conditions.conctions [x] &lt;/code&gt; pod。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Kruise-Manager识别探针执行结果来自&lt;code&gt; .status.conditions [x] &lt;/code&gt;在无服务器吊舱中，并执行&lt;code&gt; MarkerPolicy &lt;/code&gt;中定义的标记操作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关更详细的协议和受支持的容器服务提供商列表，请参考podprobemarker文档。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 5。 SideCarset逐渐注入：更多颗粒状版本控制&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作者：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/airanthem” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt;@airanthem &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Kubernetes的云本地生态系统中，&lt;strong&gt; sideCarset &lt;/strong&gt;已成为Kruise最受欢迎的功能之一，它是简化SideCar容器的管理和操作的强大工具。无论是用于日志收集，监视代理还是服务网格组件，SideCarset的优雅设计都可以帮助用户轻松应对复杂的生产环境需求。但是，在以前的版本中，缺乏对逐渐注入方案的支持，这给需要细粒度控制的用户带来了一些不便。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，Kruise 1.8通过添加&lt;strong&gt;逐渐注入能力&lt;/strong&gt;引入了新的增强功能，从而提供了前所未有的灵活性和控制力。无论您是想逐步验证新版本的稳定性还是需要实施复杂的发布策略，Kruise 1.8都提供了强大的支持。这是一个示例配置：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：apps.kruise.io/v1alpha1&#xA;种类：侧盘&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：侧列集&#xA;规格：&#xA;  ＃...&#xA;  注射术：&#xA;    修订：&#xA;      ＃指定注射版本&#xA;      修订名称：修订-A&#xA;      ＃选项：总是和部分&#xA;      ＃始终：始终注入指定的版本，在这种情况下为revision-a&#xA;      ＃部分：将注入与分区百分比结合在一起，以控制注入指定版本的百分比&#xA;      政策：部分&#xA;  UpdateTrategy：&#xA;    分区：70％&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种配置使您可以精确地控制辅助容器的注入，并支持针对您的特定需求量身定制的高级部署策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 6。舵前剥夺钩：kruise意外删除保护&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作者：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/airanthem” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt;@airanthem &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Kruise 1.7.3之前的版本中，使用Helm卸载Kruise有很大的风险，因为此操作将删除Kruise本身，其自定义资源定义（CRD）和相关的自定义资源（CRS）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从Kruise 1.7.3开始，在Helm卸载过程中引入了预削弱的钩子。此挂钩检查在集群卸载中，Kruise管理的自定义资源的存在。如果找到了这样的资源，则停止卸载过程，以防止数据丢失和服务中断离子由于意外卸载。这种改进大大提高了用掌舵管理Kruise的安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;未来Outlook &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关全面的升级和使用指南，请参阅官方&lt;a href =“ https://openkruise.io/docs/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; kruise文档&lt;/a&gt; [4]。我们认为，Kruise 1.8将使您更有效地管理云本地应用程序并提高应用程序管理经验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-teading”&gt;连续技术进化&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kruise致力于为用户提供出色的云本地解决方案。为了实现这一愿景，我们概述了三个令人兴奋的即将发布的版本：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 1。版本1.9：&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将LW与Advanced Statefles集成以实地升级功能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;开发用于原位升级重新启动限制的解决方案&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;实施configmapset的渐进变更策略&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 2。版本2.0：&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将kruise api升级为v1beta1 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 3。版本2.1：&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;开发极简主义Kruise组件部署解决方案&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;介绍新的livese探针功能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;参与&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;欢迎加入Github/Slack/dingtalk/Wechat，欢迎参与OpenKruise。您想向我们社区广播的东西吗？在我们每两周举行的社区会议（中文）[3]或通过下面的渠道分享您的声音：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●加入Slack（英语）[5]。&lt;/p&gt;的社区&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●加入社区dingtalk：搜索groupid &lt;strong&gt; 23330762 &lt;/strong&gt;（中文）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●加入微信（新）上的社区：搜索用户&lt;code&gt; OpenKruise &lt;/code&gt;，让机器人邀请您（中文）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class =“ wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;●[1] &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/openkruise/kruise” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; opentkruise github repo &lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://github.com/openkruise/kruise/kruise/blob/master/changelog.md” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; changelog&gt; href =“ https://alidocs.dingtalk.com/i/nodes/14da3gk8gk8gjnmxbzeioej1bl5j9ekbd76” target =“ _ blank” re =“ noreferrer noopener” href =“ https://openkruise.io/docs/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; kruise docs &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;●[5] &lt;A href =“ nooopener“&gt;松弛通道&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;●[6] &lt;a href =“ https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/05/05/05/volume-expansion-ga/ target =“ _ blank”&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style =“高度：80px” aria-hidded =“ true”class =“ WP-block-pacer是风格的80-120”&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring Cloud Native Projects in Sandbox: 13 Arrivals from 2024 H2】在沙箱中探索云本地项目：2024 H2的13个到达</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/11/exploring-cloud-native-projects-in-sandbox-13-arrivals-from-2024-h2/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Originally posted on the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.palark.com/cncf-sandbox-2024-h2/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Palark blog&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article covers the second half of the new Open Source projects accepted to the CNCF Sandbox last year. They were added as a result of the CNCF TOC (Technical Oversight Committee) votes performed in August, September, and October. The projects below are listed according to their formal categories, starting with those featuring more items.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security &amp;amp; Compliance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Ratify&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ratify.dev/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/notaryproject/ratify&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;250+ GH stars, 40+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Aug 13, 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Deis Labs (acquired by Microsoft in 2017)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/96&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/133&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ratify.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Ratify, you can improve your software supply chain security by verifying artifact security metadata against specific policies. When used in Kubernetes, it leverages Gatekeeper as the admission controller.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Ratify design is based on a framework that follows the provider model and supports two types of providers, internal (built-in) and external (plugins). Essential framework components include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;stores&lt;/em&gt; that can store and distribute OCI artifacts;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;verifiers&lt;/em&gt; that are responsible for verifying a specific artifact type based on the provided configuration;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;executors&lt;/em&gt; that are the “glue,” linking all Ratify plugin-based components such as the verifiers, referrer stores, and policy providers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since there are plugin providers, it’s easy to integrate custom stores and verifiers for your needs. Ratify will orchestrate various verifiers to obtain a final verification result using your policy. Then, admission controllers can rely on the given result at different stages to decide whether the verification was successful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ratify has plugins for ORAS as a store as well as for various verifiers: Notation from the Notary project and Cosign from sigstore, verifiers for vulnerability reports (including those generated by Trivy or Grype) and schema, and an alpha plugin for SBOM.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Cartography&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cartography.dev/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cartography-cncf/cartography&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3400+ GH stars, 100+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Mar 2, 2019&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Lyft&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Python&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/58&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/135&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cartography.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cartography is a tool for IT asset inventory focused on security risks. Basically, it explores your existing infrastructure components and builds a map representing your assets and their dependencies as a graph.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cartography covers numerous infrastructure providers, from Kubernetes and cloud accounts (AWS, Azure, DigitalOcean, GCP, Oracle Cloud) to GitHub, PagerDuty, and AI vendors (Anthropic, OpenAI). Security-related providers it supports include the NIST CVE database, Trivy security scanner, and Crowdstrike Falcon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All you need to use Cartography is to configure your data sources — i.e. provide access to the services you use (e.g., by configuring relevant API tokens) — and run a CLI command. When it’s done, you can view your infrastructure graph via a web browser. Cartography leverages the Neo4j database to store and display the data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfDl-DX1-rt523A8pxNJHCkrUHWOzzybBA2kSZ45i_s2mSUMXrsnNqKpGlTfJBFi42r8ZflDESGfogrswc9PRR2tX_DCiakOXDs3lDc7POJDRVijRYTJY_RX2IoDHPaagVPkLycIA?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of Cartography configuring your data sources &#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The latter is significant since you can perform powerful queries to get any information about your resources. That’s why the project offers a usage tutorial showcasing several typical queries you might need, such as finding the EC2 instances that are directly exposed to the internet and S3 buckets allowing anonymous access, or which dependencies are used across all GitHub repos.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cartography has a drift detection module to help you record data changes over time. Using it, you can specify a Neo4j query for validation to run periodically and track changes in its results from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scheduling &amp;amp; Orchestration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. HAMi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://project-hami.io/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Project-HAMi/HAMi&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;~1800 GH stars, 70+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Sep 8, 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: 4paradigm&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/97&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/132&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hami.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project was originally known as k8s-vGPU-scheduler. Today, HAMi stands for &lt;strong&gt;H&lt;/strong&gt;eterogeneous &lt;strong&gt;A&lt;/strong&gt;I computing virtualization &lt;strong&gt;Mi&lt;/strong&gt;ddleware. It aims to simplify and automate managing devices used for GenAI needs (GPUs, NPUs, and MLUs) in Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HAMi improves resource efficiency by sharing the same devices for various parallel tasks running in Kubernetes Pods. You can select specific types of devices or target a concrete device. It also allows you to control allocated memory, enforce hard limits on streaming multiprocessors, and perform MIG adjustments (via mig-parted for dynamic-mig).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a high-level architecture of HAMi:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXe4Tmq4qR-ZNL1eS7s1ft1IOKdKU_G0P2byH1IAVLYc2tef0XMGcpyPCNNzDv_bxbHhhCIxoRtQjblq2jERF_-N_2S0xFXK3IGctbVJX2ilEcMkbGeoE2vFEDVXw4xnWP4jzN7lHA?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of high-level architecture of HAMi&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mutating Webhook checks if there are required resources available to process a task.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scheduler assigns tasks to nodes and devices.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Device plugin maps the needed device to a container according to the schedule.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;HAMi-Core monitors resource usage in the container and ensures isolation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project also features a web UI to visualize and manage resources, their usage, and tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, HAMi supports devices from NVIDIA, Cambricon, Hygon, Huawei Ascend, Iluvatar, Mthreads, Metax, and Enflame.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Kubernetes AI Toolchain Operator (KAITO)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kaito-project/kaito&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;600+ GH stars, 30+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Jul 28, 2023&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: MIT&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Microsoft&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/106&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/298&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kaito.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As it’s easy to see in the name, KAITO is an operator assisting in working with AI/ML workloads — performing model inference and tuning workloads — in Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since it originated in the Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) team, the project is focused on using managed K8s from this cloud provider. However, the documentation includes instructions for installing KAITO using an AWS EKS cluster as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KAITO implements the container-based model management, which leverages an OpenAI-compatible server to perform inference calls. The project simplifies deploying models by offering easy-to-use built-in configurations and automatic provisioning of required GPU nodes (in Azure). For inference runtimes, it works with &lt;em&gt;vLLM&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;transformers&lt;/em&gt; from Hugging Face.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s an overall KAITO architecture:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXermuBJVaYTAc7BhvHsUe_iyL3AHVXFDv7iPtyG6XkbwO0pNauGpPhf4aFBqzBAGWQrZhlw94gC3ZUUDKpWFeezRNw0Pm_uZSiSoP4W_3W_oGbRjicQqmYLacxe5yYGx0y0oc1inA?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of overall KAITO architecture&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KAITO’s two main components, Workspace controller and Node provisioner, are deployed on a system node. The former is responsible for processing a custom resource provided by the user, creating a machine CRD for node auto-provisioning, and creating the required workload for inference or tuning. The latter uses the machine CRD (from Karpenter) and requests Azure Resource Manager to add GPU nodes to the AKS cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the inference and fine-tuning features, KAITO also offers RAG (Retrieval-augmented generation),&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kaito-project/kaito/issues/734&#34;&gt; starting&lt;/a&gt; from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kaito-project/kaito/releases/tag/v0.5.0&#34;&gt;recent v0.5.0&lt;/a&gt; release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Mesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Kmesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kmesh.net/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kmesh-net/kmesh&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;600+ GH stars, 40+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Oct 8, 2022&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Huawei&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go, C&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/108&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/132&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hami.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kmesh is a high-performance data plane for service mesh that aims to reduce latency overhead at the proxy layer and minimize resource consumption. To do so, it leverages eBPF to implement traffic orchestration, including dynamic routing, authorization, and load balancing. Importantly, no code changes in the end-user applications are needed to benefit from the optimizations that Kmesh brings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kmesh uses Istio as its control plane and can operate in two modes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kernel-native mode that provides the full experience. It delegates L4 and HTTP traffic governance to the kernel and, thus, doesn’t need to pass the data through the proxy layer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dual-engine mode, which is for those who prefer an incremental transition. It adds Waypoint to manage L7 traffic. For this mode, running Istio in ambient mode is required.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kmesh operating in the dual-engine mode. The flow for the kernel-native mode is similar, with no Waypoint involved&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To evaluate the performance and resource consumption gains with Kmesh, its authors provide&lt;a href=&#34;https://kmesh.net/docs/performance/&#34;&gt; relevant instructions&lt;/a&gt; in the project’s documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Sermant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sermant.io/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sermant-io/Sermant&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1300+ GH stars, ~30 contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Sep 7, 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Huawei&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Java&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/99&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/300&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sermant.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sermant is a proxyless service mesh that leverages Java bytecode enhancement to solve service governance issues in large-scale Java applications built as microservices (based on Spring Cloud, Apache Dubbo, etc.). It provides numerous features, such as dynamic configuration, messaging, heartbeat, service registration, load balancing, tag-based routing, flow control, distributed tracing, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of these features are implemented on the framework level, while others are available as plugins. The project’s documentation&lt;a href=&#34;https://sermant.io/en/document/plugin/&#34;&gt; lists&lt;/a&gt; existing plugins split by categories: service discovery and real-time configuration; limiting, downgrading and serviceability; application traffic routing; application observability. There’s also a developer guide for creating new plugins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Architecturally, Sermant is shaped by three main components:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdhsB-eYraB0RxkPbwOeIL8wqN87UtK40V23DgwsfMFGSF8NSwlTTtGy0DNJ1zyelxm8qkHZSMBCgc5ES9BOkXRHEUKY0LMXvgym2n0FzQk6Ysgwn-jHFQblrfidN9WR-XA4UZD?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of Sermant shaped by three main components&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;JavaAgent&lt;/em&gt; that instruments the application to benefit from the service governance;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Backend&lt;/em&gt; that connects all JavaAgents and pre-processes the uploaded data;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dynamic Configuration Center&lt;/em&gt; that dynamically updates the configuration in JavaAgents. This component is not a part of Sermant. Using existing Open Source solutions, such as ZooKeeper, ServiceComb Kie, or Nacos, is implied.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the implementation of the xDS protocol in Sermant, integration with the Istio service mesh is possible. In this case, Sermant will communicate directly with Istio’s control plane and replace Envoy as Istio’s data plane for service governance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Proxy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. LoxiLB&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.loxilb.io/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/loxilb-io/loxilb&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;~1700 GH stars, 20+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Jul 1, 2022&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Netlox&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/9&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/139&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://loxilb.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LoxiLB is a feature-rich load balancer for Kubernetes that aims to be infrastructure-agnostic (i.e. support on-prem, public and hybrid cloud environments), performant, and programmable. It is primarily focused on operating as a service-type load balancer, yet other cases are supported as well. The project leverages eBPF as its core engine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LoxiLB comes with its Go-based control plane components, eBPF-based data-path implementation, integrated GoBGP-based routing stack, a Kubernetes operator (kube-loxilb), and Kubernetes ingress implementation. Here’s the diagram of a typical Kubernetes cluster with LoxiLB in use:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcADRfCQB_-YvGO7SERCZux5BXlsOisRkePV2IwgQpMFc4I2dJug_RuDAK5TN6WXwmhTpC0at46yj-yBX-XEdGBdhfwT6UC54kfBiTZTPOXGRG8n_61kQ1FFIYlQLb37KKZVj0T9g?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Diagram of a typical Kubernetes cluster with LoxiLB in use&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LoxiLB is not only capable of being installed in various infrastructures, but also works with any Kubernetes distributions and CNIs (including Flannel, Cilium, and Calico). It supports dual-stack with NAT64 and NAT66 for Kubernetes and a broad spectrum of protocols: TCP, UDP, SCTP, QUIC, etc. Its numerous features include kube-proxy replacement with eBPF (full cluster-mesh for K8s), high availability with fast failover detection, extensive and scalable endpoint liveness probes, and stateful firewalling with IPsec/WireGuard support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get started with LoxiLB, you can choose from a &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.loxilb.io/latest/#getting-started-with-different-k8s-distributions-tools&#34;&gt;variety of guides&lt;/a&gt; depending on the mode you want to run it in: external cluster, in-cluster, service proxy, Kubernetes Ingress, Kubernetes Egress, or standalone (without Kubernetes at all).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. OVN-Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ovn-kubernetes.io/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ovn-kubernetes/ovn-kubernetes&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;900+ GH stars, ~160 contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Aug 15, 2016&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Red Hat&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/111&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/302&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ovnkubernetes.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OVN-Kubernetes is a CNI (Container Network Interface) plugin for Kubernetes clusters implementing OVN (Open Virtual Networking), which is an abstraction on top of Open vSwitch (Open Virtual Switch). It aims to enhance K8s networking by offering advanced features for enterprise and telco use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of these features include fine-grained cluster egress traffic controls, support for creating secondary and local networks (e.g., for multihoming), hybrid networking for mixed Windows/Linux clusters (using VXLAN tunnels), and offloading networking tasks from CPU to NIC. It also enables live migrations for KubeVirt-managed virtual machines by keeping established TCP connections alive. You can find a detailed list of features in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://ovn-kubernetes.io/features/network-security-controls/admin-network-policy/&#34;&gt;project’s documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OVN-Kubernetes supports two deployment modes with varying architecture: default (centralized control plane) and interconnect (distributed control plane). The latter one involves connecting multiple OVN deployments via OVN-managed GENEVE tunnels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The architecture for the default mode involves:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;control plane: ovnkube-master Pod (it watches for K8s objects and translates them into OVN logical entities), OVN NBDB database (stores these logical entities), northd (converts the entities to OVN logical flows), and sbdb (stores the flows);&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;data plane: ovnkube-node Pod (it runs the CNI executable), ovn-controller (converts logical flows from sdbd into OpenFlows), and ovs-node Pod (OVS daemon and database, virtual switch).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXd1z5jf2qAibD5J1OhH-4pEQZWsGQKYh8m5BDPUZf8Csqp6pI3etTQLyAyH8zyyyCL7Uq_xsox3c1uaadBHmw1gLUYiI7UyfWfN6kNJl3IDqZrhX4lsvtRS3IeAvRE1JNg1_ZmRMQ?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic visualizing ovnkube-master Pod&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OVN-Kubernetes is the default CNI in Red Hat’s OpenShift Container Platform (valid for the 4.19 version released last month) and boasts having NVIDIA as another well-known adopter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. Perses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://perses.dev/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/perses/perses&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1400+ GH stars, 50+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Jan 27, 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Amadeus IT Group&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go, TypeScript&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/93&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/134&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://perses.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Perses is an observability visualization project that is developing a dashboard tool with bigger plans in mind. It aims to provide a standardized dashboard specification to improve interoperability across various observability tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can easily deploy Perses dashboards as Custom Resources in Kubernetes by leveraging&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/perses/perses-operator&#34;&gt; Perses operator&lt;/a&gt;. The project also calls itself GitOps-friendly since it has everything you need to manage your dashboards in Git: static validation, a CLI to perform actions in CI/CD pipelines, CI/CD libraries, and SDKs (in Go and in CUE).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which observability data can Perses visualize? Currently, it supports Prometheus metrics and Tempo traces. The authors plan to add more data sources, naming logs — particularly stored in OpenSearch and Loki — as one of their priorities. Supporting ClickHouse as an observability backend is another item in the project’s roadmap.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfbs2Z64-DJqcRHJewXybj2l_ZAaz8bRvYJTbZLwbGpPy0pXfdn69QzgSeVEi3kMZvId1D2lBO85iPr3sUB0_V34bY_wivOAJQtinxNa4_QUKRbUoqlUtM5ZRlv5XA9Y8fZxYq1Yg?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Data persing graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Perses’ design allows you to use it as a standalone tool or embed the panels and dashboards in other UIs (by using npm packages). The project follows a plugin-based architecture, with its core plugins available in a separate&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/perses/plugins&#34;&gt; GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://perses.dev/perses/docs/plugins/creation/&#34;&gt;guidance&lt;/a&gt; on creating custom plugins for any specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application Definition &amp;amp; Image Build&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10. Shipwright&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://shipwright.io/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/shipwright-io&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;700+ GH stars, 50+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Feb 6, 2020&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Red Hat&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/85&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/131&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://shipwrightcncf.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shipwright is a framework for building container images on Kubernetes by leveraging existing tools. The project implies using a simple YAML configuration (via CRDs) describing which applications with which tools will be built.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Basically, with Shipwright, you will need to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Define what you’re building: the source of the image (Git repository or OCI artifact, Dockerfile, etc.), required volumes, the container registry to push the resulting image, and so on. You can also enable a vulnerability scan for newly generated images.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Define how you will build it, i.e., which tool you will use. Shipwright supports the following builders: Buildah, BuildKit (from Docker), Buildpacks, Kaniko, ko, and S2I (Source-To-Image from OpenShift). Each backend offers distinct features and limitations. You can control the building process by specifying relevant values (directly or via Kubernetes ConfigMaps and Secrets) for each build.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Run the build process. Thanks to the triggers, it can also be event-driven. Notably, you can react to events from GitHub Webhooks or watch for Tekton Pipelines.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Everything happens in Kubernetes, and therefore, this whole workflow is managed by a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/shipwright-io/operator&#34;&gt;Kubernetes operator&lt;/a&gt;. The project also has a CLI tool that can be used as a standalone binary or kubectl plugin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In terms of observability, Shipwright exposes several Prometheus metrics — such as total builds and build duration — and supports a &lt;em&gt;pprof&lt;/em&gt; profiling mode.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automation &amp;amp; Configuration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11. KusionStack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kusionstack.io/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/KusionStack&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;~1500 GH stars, 30+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: May 16, 2022&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Ant Group&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Go&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/83&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/295&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kusionstack.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KusionStack offers a variety of tools focused on building an Internal Developer Platform (IDP). Its core is a platform orchestrator called&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/KusionStack/kusion&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Kusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Declarative and intent-driven, it revolves around a single specification where developers define the workload and all dependencies required for the application deployment. Kusion will do the rest to ensure the application runs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How will this magic happen? You’ll need the platform engineers to create the so-called Kusion modules. Those are the project’s basic building blocks, implementing the actual infrastructure abstracted away from the developers and required by the application, such as databases, networking services, etc. Each module can be made up of one or several Kubernetes or Terraform resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcXUw8XBJ0wkDRrnTQrXYqwyDhECRGdST-lKklgRNSrysOww1OQ51MoJtjfpBnpYJqSY1lHKR5bxryQgi-knl_nfBvlez-B8GoVQjIlJz4lzL3-CTip_hNp5BmjbsfANqnG80J6SQ?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Kusion modules graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Originally, interacting with Kusion was possible only through a CLI tool, but since the recent v0.14.0 release (January 2025), the project introduced Kusion Server, featuring a Developer Portal and RESTful APIs for managing Kusion objects. Additionally, this web UI visualizes the topology of application resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other notable KusionStack tools are Karpor and Kuperator.&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/KusionStack/karpor&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Karpor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which boasts even more GitHub stars than the main Kusion repo, is a web UI for Kubernetes focused on three main features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Search: powerful SQL-style queries to quickly select any Kubernetes resources you need from multi-cluster setups.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Insights for Kubernetes resources: a dashboard showcasing existing issues* and an interactive topology view.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;AI: GenAI-based interpretations for existing issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;* All the abovementioned issues Karpor currently displays rely on the output from the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;kubeadit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; tool. However, the authors&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/KusionStack/karpor/issues/454&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;are considering&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; adding other tools (such as Trivy, Kubescape, and Falco) for this functionality.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfFRhgIBNV7BdX0acAifR4VxWvhERlDfY4HJTAqYf1hx5qheLrR689cOAif_BlZgLqocAV5xCe6FaHONgFOAHEYpVIQg9FthW4PZohNic8-y0OSU-jaECeR9i_pxNqt1KsdvPYawQ?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Karpor dashboard graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally,&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/KusionStack/kuperator&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Kuperator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a set of workloads and operators “aiming to bridge the gap between platform development and Kubernetes.” They include controllers for workload lifecycle management, injecting specific configurations to Pods that meet certain criteria, performing one-shot operational tasks on a batch of Pods, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Container Runtime&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12. youki&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youki-dev.github.io/youki/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/youki-dev/youki&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;~6800 GH stars, ~130 contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Mar 27, 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: Toru Komatsu (individual)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Rust&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/103&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/297&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youki.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought of a container runtime written in Rust? That’s precisely what youki is. It started as a hobby project exploring container runtimes and eventually grew into a significant community effort (see the impressive GitHub stats above!). As the author highlights, thanks to being fast and requiring not much memory, youki can be a good candidate for environments with strict resource limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;youki is an OCI-compliant, &lt;em&gt;low-level&lt;/em&gt; runtime, which can be used directly to create, start, and run containers. However, it is more convenient to combine it with a higher-level runtime (such as Docker or Podman). Some other facts about youki:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It can work in a rootless mode.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Currently, it works only on Linux. Using it on other platforms is possible with virtualization involved, and there’re ready-to-use Vagrantfiles for VM setups with Vagrant.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It supports WebAssembly, meaning you can build a container image with the WebAssembly module and then run this container with youki.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native Storage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;13. OpenEBS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openebs.io/&#34;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openebs/openebs&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;~9400 GH stars, 200+ contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initial commit: Aug 1, 2016&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;License: Apache 2.0&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Original owner/creator: MayaData (acquired by DataCore in 2021)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Rust, Go&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF Sandbox:&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/104&#34;&gt; sandbox request&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/299&#34;&gt; onboarding issue&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openebs.devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; DevStats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenEBS is a persistent storage solution for Kubernetes workloads. Its story of (re-)joining the CNCF Sandbox is unique:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Originally, OpenEBS was accepted into the CNCF as a Sandbox project in 2019.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;However, in 2023, a public discussion on archiving this project — due to a lack of activity —&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/issues/1051&#34;&gt; was raised&lt;/a&gt;. In February 2024, it was archived indeed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Soon after, the team behind OpenEBS&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openebs/openebs/issues/3701&#34;&gt; introduced&lt;/a&gt; numerous changes, paving the way for the project’s resubmission to the Sandbox. In October 2024, it was unarchived and became a Sandbox project again.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An overall architecture of OpenEBS in Kubernetes and in relation to other tooling is illustrated in this diagram:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXf5pEptmQ2fjTphReRTNDarWEcIcHInYD5EJGxIRPnZxb1R2ou_FpX5SCqutK1uoACZSkD-m2GipkxFnPlzHpGJoBEQV3CVYHQe7d7fk2_5gnW08Sa9HVjvQZ1Lhm78ZgjR2c5KwQ?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt=&#34;Stateful Workloads Graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;OpenEBS Control Plane manages the data engines and storage available on the K8s worker nodes, interacts with CSI and other tools to manage the lifecycle of volumes, make snapshots, perform resizes, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;OpenEBS Data Engines are used by Kubernetes stateful workloads and perform read and write operations on the underlying persistent storage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for the storage, OpenEBS supports two types:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Local storage. It’s limited to the node with the volume and comes with a minimal overhead. This type has several implementations: Hostpath, ZFS, LVM, Rawfile.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Replicated storage. It replicates data across multiple nodes (synchronously) and has the only implementation: Mayastor.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of these implementations, with the exception of Local PV Hostpath, are presented as CSI (Container Storage Interface) drivers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mayastor is written in Rust and, due to its complexity, is the most actively developed part of OpenEBS. It works only in the ReadWriteOnce access mode, supports filesystem and block volume modes, and the following file systems: ext4, btrfs, and xfs. It also allows volume resizing, backups, snapshots, and monitoring (Prometheus metrics are exposed). Mayastor features a kubectl plugin for viewing and managing its resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Afterword&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Again, we can see that most of the projects joining CNCF are 2-3 years old. The exceptions are OVN-Kubernetes (started in 2016), OpenEBS (the same 2016, but we already explained why this case is unique), and Cartography (2019). Almost half of the projects (6 out of 13) originate from the Asian companies/individuals (China, Korea, and Japan).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This time, AI/ML shines among the popular categories of the newly added projects, which is totally relevant as we see more such workloads in the Cloud Native space. Many networking-related tools are noticeable in this Sandbox batch, too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for the programming languages used, Go still dominates, followed by a small but steady presence of Rust, and one exception (Java). Licensing shows even greater consistency: 12 out of 13 projects chose Apache 2.0.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P.S. Other articles in this series&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.palark.com/cncf-sandbox-2023-h1/&#34;&gt;Part 1: 13 arrivals of 2023 H1&lt;/a&gt;: Inspektor Gadget, Headlamp, Kepler, SlimToolkit, SOPS, Clusternet, Eraser, PipeCD, Microcks, kpt, Xline, HwameiStor, and KubeClipper.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.palark.com/cncf-sandbox-2023-h2/&#34;&gt;Part 2: 12 arrivals of 2023 H2&lt;/a&gt;: Logging operator, K8sGPT, kcp, KubeStellar, Copa, Kanister, KCL, Easegress, Kuasar, krkn, kube-burner, and Spiderpool.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.palark.com/cncf-sandbox-2024-h1/&#34;&gt;Part 3: 14 arrivals of 2024 H1&lt;/a&gt;: Radius, Stacker, Score, Bank-Vaults, TrestleGRC, bpfman, Koordinator, KubeSlice, Atlantis, Kubean, Connect, Kairos, Kuadrant, and openGemini.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;最初发布在&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://blog.palark.com/cncf-sandbox-2024-h2/”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文涵盖了去年CNCF Sandbox接受的新开源项目的后半部分。 CNCF TOC（技术监督委员会）在8月，9月和10月进行的投票添加了它们。以下项目根据其正式类别列出，从包含更多项目的项目开始。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;安全与合规性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。批准&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://ratify.dev/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/notaryproject/ratify/ratify”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 250+ GH星，40+贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2021年8月13日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：Deis Labs（Microsoft于2017年收购）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/issues/96”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/133 href =“ https://ratify.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过批准，您可以通过验证针对特定策略的工件安全元数据来改善软件供应链安全。当在kubernetes中使用时，它利用看门人作为入院控制器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;批准设计基于一个遵循提供商模型的框架，并支持两种类型的提供商，即内部（内置）和外部（插件）。基本框架组件包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt;商店&lt;/em&gt;可以存储和分发OCI文物; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt;验证者&lt;/em&gt;负责根据提供的配置验证特定的人工制品类型; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt;执行者&lt;/em&gt;是“胶”，链接所有基于批准插件的组件，例如验证者，推荐商店和策略提供商。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于有插件提供商，因此可以轻松地集成自定义商店和验证器满足您的需求。批准将协调各种验证者，以使用您的策略获得最终的验证结果。然后，入院控制器可以在不同阶段依靠给定的结果来决定验证是否成功。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;批准具有ORAS作为商店的插件以及各种验证符：来自Sigstore的公证项目和cosign的符号，用于漏洞报告的验证器（包括Trivy或Grype生成的验证者）和Schema以及SBOM的Alpha插件。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 2。制图&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://cartography.dev/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;A href =“ https://github.com/cartography-cartography-cartcf/cartography&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 3400+ GH星，100+贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2019年3月2日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：lyft &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：python &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/58”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/135 href =“ https://cartography.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;制图是IT的工具，用于资产库存，重点是安全风险。基本上，它探索您现有的基础架构组件，并构建代表您的资产及其依赖项的地图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;制图涵盖了众多基础架构提供商，从Kubernetes和Cloud帐户（AWS，Azure，Digitalocean，GCP，Oracle Cloud）到GitHub，Pagerduty和AI供应商（Anthropic，OpenAI）。它支持与安全相关的提供商包括NIST CVE数据库，Trivy Security Scanner和CrowdStrike Falcon。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您使用的制图所需的只是配置数据源 - 即提供对您使用的服务的访问（例如，通过配置相关的API令牌） - 并运行CLI命令。完成后，您可以通过Web浏览器查看基础架构图。制图利用Neo4J数据库存储并显示数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfdl-dx1-rt523a8pxnjhckruhwozzybbabba2ksz45i_s2mmsumxrsnnnqkp gltfjbfi42r8zfldesgfogrswc9prr2tx_dciakoxds3ldc7pojdrvijrytjy_rx2iodhpaagvpklycia？ alt =“配置您的数据源的制图图形” revyrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;后者很重要，因为您可以执行强大的查询以获取有关您的资源的任何信息。这就是为什么该项目提供了一个用法教程，展示了您可能需要的几个典型查询，例如查找直接暴露于Internet的EC2实例，S3存储桶允许匿名访问或在所有GitHub存储库中使用哪些依赖关系。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;制图具有一个漂移检测模块，可帮助您记录数据更改。使用它，您可以指定一个neo4j查询以验证以定期运行并不时跟踪其结果的变化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;调度和编排&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 3。 hami &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://project-hami.io/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/project.com/project-hami/hami/hami”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;〜1800 GH星，70多个贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2021年9月8日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创建者：4paradigm &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/issues/97”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/132 href =“ https://hami.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个项目最初被称为K8S-VGPU-SCEDULER。今天，哈米代表&lt;strong&gt; h &lt;/strong&gt; eTer二烯&lt;strong&gt; a &lt;/strong&gt; i计算虚拟化&lt;strong&gt; mi &lt;/strong&gt; ddleware。它旨在简化和自动化用于Genai需求的设备（GPU，NPU和MLUS）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Hami通过共享在Kubernetes Pod中运行的各种并行任务的相同设备来提高资源效率。您可以选择特定类型的设备或针对混凝土设备。它还允许您控制分配的内存，在流多处理器上强制执行硬限制，并进行MIG调整（通过Dynamic-Mig的MIG-PART）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是哈米的高级架构：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxe4tmq4q4qr-znl1es7s1ft1iokdku_g0p2byh1iavlyc2byh1iavlyc2tef0xmgcpypc NNzDv_bxbHhhCIxoRtQjblq2jERF_-N_2S0xFXK3IGctbVJX2ilEcMkbGeoE2vFEDVXw4xnWP4jzN7lHA?key=3-FQaJkLZYHq_kM0W8Ai7Q&#34; alt =“ Hami高级体系结构的图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;突变Webhook检查是否有可用的资源来处理任务。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;调度程序将任务分配给节点和设备。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;设备插件按时间表将所需的设备映射到容器中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; HAMI核心监视容器中的资源使用情况并确保隔离。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该项目还具有一个可视化和管理资源，其用法和任务的Web UI。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，HAMI支持NVIDIA，CAMBRICON，HYGON，HUAWEI ASCEND，ILUVATAR，MTHREADS，METAX和ENFLAME的设备。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 4。 Kubernetes AI工具链操作员（KAITO）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kaito-project/kaito”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 600+ GH星，30多个贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2023年7月28日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：麻省理工学院&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创建者：Microsoft &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/106”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;A href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/298”&gt; href =“ https://kaito.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kaito很容易看到，Kaito是一家操作员，可以在Kubernetes中使用AI/ML工作负载（执行模型推断和调音工作负载）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于它起源于Azure Kubernetes Service（AKS）团队，因此该项目的重点是使用该云提供商的托管K8。但是，该文档还包括使用AWS EKS群集安装Kaito的说明。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kaito实现了基于容器的模型管理，该管理利用OpenAI兼容的服务器执行推理调用。该项目通过提供易于使用的内置配置和自动配置所需的GPU节点（在Azure中）来简化部署模型。对于推理运行时，它可与&lt;em&gt; vllm &lt;/em&gt;和&lt;em&gt;变形金刚&lt;/em&gt;从拥抱脸部使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一个整体kaito架构：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxermubjvaytac7bhvhsue_iyl3ahvxfdv7iptyg6xkbwo6xkbwo0pnaugph4 afbqzbagwqrzhlw94gc3zuudkpwfeezrnw0pm_uzsisop4w_3w_3w_3w_ogbrjicqqqmylacxe5yygx0y0oc1ina？ alt =“整体kaito架构的图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kaito的两个主要组件，即工作区控制器和节点配置器，分部在系统节点上。前者负责处理用户提供的自定义资源，创建用于节点自动提供的机器CRD，并为推理或调整创建所需的工作负载。后者使用机器CRD（来自Karpenter），并请求Azure Resource Manager将GPU节点添加到AKS群集中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了推理和微调功能外，Kaito还提供抹布（检索效果的一代），&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kaito-project/kaito/kaito/sissues/734”&gt; starting &lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://github.com/kaito-project/kaito/releases/tag/v0.5.0”&gt;最近的v0.5.0 &lt;/a&gt; repartion。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;服务网格&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 5。 kmesh &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kmesh.net/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kmesh-net/kmesh”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 600+ GH星，40+贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2022年10月8日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：华为&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO，C &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/108”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/132 href =“ https://hami.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kmesh是服务网格的高性能数据平面，旨在减少代理层的延迟开销并最大程度地减少资源消耗。为此，它利用EBPF实施流量编排，包括动态路由，授权和负载平衡。重要的是，最终用户应用程序不需要更改代码来受益于Kmesh带来的优化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kmesh用作其控制平面，可以以两种模式运行：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可提供完整体验的内核本地模式。它将L4和HTTP流量治理委托给内核，因此不需要通过代理层传递数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;双引擎模式，适用于那些喜欢增量过渡的人。它添加了管理L7流量的路点。对于此模式，需要在环境模式下运行ISTIO。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; kmesh在双引擎模式下运行。内核本地模式的流量相似，无路点&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了评估KMESH的性能和资源消耗，其作者提供&lt;a href =“ https://kmesh.net/docs/performanCE/“&gt;相关说明&lt;/a&gt;在项目的文档中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 6。 Sermant &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://sermant.io/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/sermant-io/sermant/sermant”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 1300+ GH星，〜30个贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2021年9月7日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：华为&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：java &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/issues/99”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/300” href =“ https://sermant.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Sermant是一个无替代的服务网，利用Java字节码增强来解决以微服务构建的大规模Java应用程序中的服务治理问题（基于Spring Cloud，Apache Dubbo等）。它提供了许多功能，例如动态配置，消息传递，心跳，服务注册，负载平衡，基于标签的路由，流量控制，分布式跟踪等等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其中一些功能是在框架级别实现的，而另一些则作为插件可用。项目的文档&lt;a href =“ https://sermant.io/en/document/plugin/”&gt; lists &lt;/a&gt;现有插件按类别分开：服务发现和实时配置；限制，降级和可维修性；应用程序流量路由；申请可观察性。还有一个用于创建新插件的开发人员指南。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;架构上，Sermant由三个主要组成部分形成：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdhsb-eyrab0rxkpbwoeil8wqn87utk40v23dggwsfmfmfmfmfmfmfmfgsfmfgsfgsf8nnswltttg Y0DNJ1ZYELXM8QKHZSMBCGC5ES9BOKXRHEUKY0LMXVGYM2N0FZQK6YSGWN-JHFQBLRFIDN9WR-XA4UZD？ alt =“由三个主组件形成的Sermant的图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt; javaagent &lt;/em&gt;启动了从服务治理中受益的申请； &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt;后端&lt;/em&gt;连接所有Javaagents并预处理数据; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt;动态配置中心&lt;/em&gt;动态更新Javaagents中的配置。该组件不是Sermant的一部分。暗示使用现有的开源解决方案，例如Zookeeper，ServiceComb Kie或NACOS。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多亏了Sermant中XDS协议的实现，与ISTIO服务网格的集成是可能的。在这种情况下，Sermant将直接与ISTIO的控制平面通信，并替换Envoy作为ISTIO的数据平面以进行服务治理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;服务代理&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 7。 loxilb &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.loxilb.io/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/loxilb-io/loxilb”&gt; githuB &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 〜1700 GH星，20+贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2022年7月1日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：Netlox &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/9”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/issues/139 href =“ https://loxilb.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; loxilb是Kubernetes的功能丰富的负载平衡器，旨在是基础架构 - 努力（即支持本地，公共和混合云环境），表演词和可编程。它主要专注于作为服务型负载平衡器运行，但也支持其他情况。该项目将EBPF作为其核心发动机。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; loxilb配备了基于GO的控制平面组件，基于EBPF的数据路径实现，基于GOBGP的集成路由堆栈，Kubernetes操作员（Kube-Loxilb）和Kubernetes Ingress Invress实现。这是使用loxilb的典型kubernetes群集的图：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcadrfcqb_-yvgo7serczux5bxlsoisrkepv2iwgqpmfcpmfc4i2djug_rud AK5TN6WXWMHTPC0AT46YJ-YBX-XEDGBDHFWT6UC54KFBITZTPOXGRG8NN_61KQ1FFIYLQLB37KKZVJ0T9G？ alt =“使用loxilb的典型kubernetes群集的图”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; loxilb不仅能够安装在各种基础架构中，而且还可以与任何Kubernetes分布和CNIS（包括法兰绒，Cilium和Calico）一起使用。它支持Kubernetes的NAT64和NAT66双堆栈以及广泛的协议：TCP，UDP，SCTP，QUIC等。其许多功能包括Kube-Proxy替换EBPF（k8的全群 - 网格），具有较高的可用性检测，并具有更高的端子，并具有更高的端子，并具有更大的端子，并具有更大的量表，并具有一定的范围。支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要开始使用loxilb，您可以从a &lt;a href =“ https://docs.loxilb.io/latest/#getting-ptarted-with-with-with-different-k8s-distribinest-tools-dorbortions-tools”&gt;指南&gt;各种指南&lt;/a&gt;根据您想在以下方式中运行：您想在：外部的：外部的crone proner中，ku in croment in croment in croper， kubernetes出口或独立（根本没有kubernetes）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云本机网络&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 8。 ovn-kubernetes &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://ovn-kubernetes.io/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;A href =“ https://github.com/ovn-kubernetes/ovn-kubernetes/ovn-kubernetes”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 900+ GH星，〜160个贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2016年8月15日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：红色帽子&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf沙盒：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/issues/111”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;A href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/302&gt;ding问题&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://ovnkubernetes.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OVN-KUBERNETES是用于实现OVN（开放虚拟网络）的Kubernetes群集的CNI（容器网络接口）插件，这是Open Vswitch顶部的抽象（Open Virtual Switch）。它旨在通过为企业和电信用例提供高级功能来增强K8S网络。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其中一些功能包括精细粒度出口流量控制，支持创建二级和本地网络（例如，用于多主教），用于混合Windows/Linux群集的混合网络（使用VXLAN隧道）以及将网络任务从CPU转换为NIC。它还通过保持建立的TCP连接持续存在，可以为库贝维特管理的虚拟机进行实时迁移。您可以在&lt;a href =“ https:///ovn-kubernetes.io/features/network-security-controls/admin-network-policy/”&gt; Project Project的文档&lt;/a&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ovn-kubernetes支持两种部署模式，具有不同的体系结构：默认的（集中控制平面）和互连（分布式控制平面）。后一个涉及通过OVN管理的基因隧道连接多个OVN部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认模式的体系结构涉及：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;控制平面：OVNKube-Master Pod（它观察K8S对象并将其转换为OVN逻辑实体），OVN NBDB数据库（存储这些逻辑实体），Northd（将实体转换为OVN逻辑流）和SBDB（存储Flowws）; &lt;/li&gt;; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;数据平面：ovnkube节点pod（它运行CNI可执行文件），OVN-CONTROLLER（将逻辑流从SDBD转换为OpenFlows）和OVS-Node Pod（OVS守护程序和数据库，虚拟开关）。&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxd1z5jf2qaibd5j1ohh-4peqzwsgqkyh8m5bdpuzf8cf8csqp6p6pi3ettqly Ayh8zyyycl7UQ_XSOX3C1UAADBHMW1GLUYII7UYFWFN6KNJL3IDQZRHX4LSVTRS3IEAEVRE1JNG1JNG1JNG1_ZMRMQ？ alt =“图形可视化ovnkube-master pod” referrerpolicy =“ no-refferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ovn-kubernetes是Red Hat的OpenShift容器平台中的默认CNI（对上个月发布的4.19版有效），并拥有NVIDIA作为另一个著名采用者。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可观察性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 9。 Perses &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://perses.dev/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/perses/perses/perses”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 1400多个GH星，50+贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2021年1月27日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：Amadeus IT组&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO，打字稿&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/sandbox/issues/93”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;A href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/134&gt; href =“ https：//perses.devstats.cncf.io/“&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; perses是一个可观察性可视化项目，它正在开发一个仪表板工具，其中包含更大的计划。它旨在提供标准化的仪表板规范，以改善各种可观察性工具的互操作性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以通过利用&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/perses/perses/perses-operator”&gt; perses operator &lt;/a&gt;来轻松地将仪表板作为kubernetes中的自定义资源部署为自定义资源。该项目还称自己为gitops友好，因为它具有在git中管理仪表板所需的一切：静态验证，在CI/CD管道中执行操作的CLI，CI/CD库和SDKS（在GO和CUE中）。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;哪些可观察性数据可以可视化？目前，它支持Prometheus指标和节奏痕迹。作者计划添加更多数据源，命名日志（尤其是在Opensearch和Loki中存储），作为其优先事项之一。支持Clickhouse作为可观察性后端是项目路线图中的另一个项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfbs2z64-djqcrhjewxybj2l_zaaz8brvyjtbzlwbggpppy0pxfdn69qzg sevei3kmzvid1d2lbo85ipr3sub0_v34by_wivoajqtinxna4_qukrbuoqlutm5zrlv5xa9y8fzxyq1yg？ alt =“ data persing图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Perses的设计使您可以将其用作独立工具，或将面板和仪表板嵌入其他UI（通过使用NPM软件包）。该项目遵循基于插件的体系结构，其核心插件在单独的&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/perses/pleses/plugins”&gt; github repo &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ https://perses.dev/perses.dev/perses/perses/ddocs/plugins/plugins/creation/creation/dugercunce &lt;/a&gt;上&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;应用程序定义和图像构建&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 10。 Shipwright &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://shipwright.io/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/shipwright-io-”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 700+ GH星，50+贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2020年2月6日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：红色帽子&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/issues/85”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;A href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/131 href =“ https://shipwrightcncf.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ShipWright是通过利用现有工具在Kubernetes上构建容器图像的框架。该项目意味着使用简单的YAML配置（通过CRD）描述了将使用哪些工具的应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基本上，与Shipwright一起，您需要：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;定义您要构建的内容：图像的来源（git存储库或oci伪影，dockerfile等），所需的卷，集装箱注册表才能按由此产生的图像，依此类推。您还可以启用对新生成图像的漏洞扫描。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;定义如何构建它，即将使用哪种工具。 Shipwright支持以下建筑商：Buildah，BuildKit（从Docker），BuildPacks，Kaniko，Ko和S2i（来自OpenShift的来源到图像）。每个后端都提供不同的功能和局限性。您可以通过为每个构建指定相关值（直接或通过kubernetes configmaps and Secrets）来控制构建过程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;运行构建过程。多亏了触发器，也可以是事件驱动的。值得注意的是，您可以对Github Webhooks的事件做出反应或观看Tekton Pipelines。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一切都发生在kubernetes中，因此，整个工作流程由a &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/shipwright-io/operator”&gt; kubernetes操作员&lt;/a&gt;。该项目还具有一个可以用作独立二进制或kubectl插件的CLI工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在可观察性方面，船赖特公开了几个普罗米修斯指标，例如总构建和建造持续时间 - 并支持&lt;em&gt; pprof &lt;/em&gt; prof &lt;/em&gt;分析模式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自动化和配置&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 11。 kusionstack &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kusionstack.io/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;A href =“ https://github.com/kusionstack”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 〜1500 GH星，30+贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2022年5月16日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创造者：蚂蚁群&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：GO &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/issues/83”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/candbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/295 href =“ https://kusionstack.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; KusionStack提供了各种专注于构建内部开发人员平台（IDP）的工具。它的核心是一个平台编排，称为&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kusionstack/kusion”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kusion &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。声明性和意图驱动的是，它围绕一个单个规范，在该规范中，开发人员定义了应用程序部署所需的工作量和所有依赖关系。 Kusion将完成其余的以确保应用程序运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种魔术将如何发生？您将需要平台工程师来创建所谓的Kusion模块。这些是项目的基本构建块，实施从开发人员那里抽象的实际基础架构，并由应用程序所需的数据库，网络服务等。每个模块都可以由一个或几个Kubernetes或Terraform资源组成。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcxuw8xbj0wkdrrrntqrxyqrxyqwydhecrgdst-lkklgrnsrysowwwysoww1oq51moj tjfpbnpyjqsy1lhkr5bxryqgi-knl_nfbvlez-b8govqjiljz4lzl3-ctip_hnp_hnp5bmjbsfanqng80j6sq？ alt =“ kusion模块Graphic“ referrerpolicy =” no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最初，只有通过CLI工具与Kusion进行交互，但是自最近的V0.14.0版本（2025年1月）以来，该项目引入了Kusion Server，其中包含开发人员门户和用于管理Kusion对象的静止API。此外，此Web UI可视化应用程序资源的拓扑。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其他值得注意的kusionstack工具是karpor和kuperator。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;搜索：功能强大的SQL风格查询，以快速从多群集设置中选择您需要的任何Kubernetes资源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; kubernetes资源的见解：展示现有问题的仪表板*和交互式拓扑视图。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; AI：基于Genai的现有问题的解释。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;*所有上述问题karpor当前显示依赖于&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; kubeadit &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;工具的输出。但是，作者&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kusionstack/karpor/issues/454”&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;正在考虑&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;添加其他工具（例如Trivy，Kubescape和Falco），以获取此功能，以获取此功能。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxffrhgibnv7bdx0acaifr4vxwvherldfy4hjtaqyf1hx5qhelrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrc AIF_BLZGLQOCAV5XCE6FAHONGFOAHEYPVIQG9FTHW4PZOHNIC8-Y0OSU-JAECER9I_PXNQT1KSDVPYAWQ？key = 3-FQAJKLZLZLZLZYHQ_KM0W8AI7Q“ alt =“ karpor仪表板图形” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kusionstack/kuperator”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kuperator &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;是一组工作负载和运营商“旨在弥合平台开发与kubernetes之间的间隙。”它们包括用于工作负载生命周期管理的控制器，将特定的配置注入符合某些条件的POD，在一批POD上执行单发操作任务等等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;容器运行时&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 12。 youki &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://youki-dev.github.io/youki/”&gt; website &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;A href =“ https：//github.com/youki-dev/youki-dev/youki/youki&gt; github”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 〜6800 GH星，〜130个贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2021年3月27日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创作者：Toru Komatsu（个人）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：Rust &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/issues/103”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/297 href =“ https://youki.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您是否曾经想过用Rust写的容器运行时？那正是尤基所在。它最初是一个爱好项目，探索集装箱运行时，最终陷入社区巨大的努力（请参阅上面的令人印象深刻的GitHub统计数据！）。正如作者所强调的那样，由于快速并且需要不多的记忆，Youki可以成为严格资源限制环境的良好候选人。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; youki是符合OCI的&lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;低级运行时，可直接用于创建，启动和运行容器。但是，将其与更高级别的运行时（例如Docker或Podman）相结合更加方便。关于Youki的其他一些事实：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;它可以在无根模式下工作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;目前，它仅在Linux上工作。在涉及虚拟化的情况下，可以在其他平台上使用它，并且有Vagrant的VM设置有现成的VagrantFiles。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;它支持WebAssembly，这意味着您可以使用WebAssembly模块构建容器映像，然后使用Youki运行此容器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云本机存储&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 13。 Openebs &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://openebs.io/”&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/openebs/openebs/openebs”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 〜9400 GH星，200+贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始提交：2016年8月1日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;许可证：Apache 2.0 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;原始所有者/创建者：Mayadata（2021年DataCore收购）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;语言：生锈，&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf sandbox：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/sandbox/issues/104”&gt; sandbox request &lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/cncf/cncf/cncf/sandbox/sandbox/sandbox/sissues/299 href =“ https://openebs.devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstats &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OpenEBS是Kubernetes工作负载的持续存储解决方案。它（重新）加入CNCF沙箱的故事是唯一的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;最初，OpenEB在2019年被接受为CNCF作为沙盒项目。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;然而，在2023年，由于缺乏活动，公开讨论了对该项目的归档 -  &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/toc/issues/1051”&gt;被培养&lt;/a&gt;。在2024年2月，它确实被存档了。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;不久之后，OpenEBS背后的团队&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/openebs/openebs/issues/3701”&gt;引入了&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;为该项目重新提交的沙箱铺平了许多更改。在2024年10月，它是未制成的，并再次成为沙箱项目。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此图中说明了Kubernetes中的OpenEBS的整体架构以及与其他工具的相关性：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxf5peptmq2fjtphrertndarwecichinyd5ejgxirpnzxxxb1r2 u_fpx5s cqutk1uoaczskd-m2gipkxfnplzhpgjobeqv3cvyhqe7d7d7d7fk2_5gnw08sa9hvjvqz1lhm78zgjr2c5k5Kwq？ alt =“状态工作负载图形” revyrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这里：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; OpenEBS控制平面管理K8上可用的数据引擎和存储空间S Worker节点，与CSI和其他工具进行交互，以管理卷的生命周期，制作快照，执行调整等等。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; kubernetes状态工作负载使用openebs数据引擎，并在基础持久存储上执行读写操作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;至于存储，OpenEBS支持两种类型：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;本地存储。它仅限于节点，并带有最小的开销。此类型具有多种实现：HostPath，ZFS，LVM，Rawfile。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;复制的存储。它可以通过多个节点复制数据（同步），并且具有唯一的实现：Mayastor。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除本地PV HostPath以外，所有这些实现均以CSI（容器存储接口）驱动程序的形式呈现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Mayastor用锈蚀书写，由于其复杂性，是Openebs最积极发展的一部分。它仅在ReadWriteOnce访问模式下工作，支持文件系统和块卷模式，以及以下文件系统：EXT4，BTRFS和XFS。它还允许调整大小，备份，快照和监视（暴露于普罗米修斯指标）。 Mayastor具有用于查看和管理其资源的Kubectl插件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;后字&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;再次，我们可以看到加入CNCF的大多数项目都有2  -  3年的历史。例外是OVN-KUBERNETES（始建于2016年），OpenEBS（同一2016年，但我们已经解释了这种情况为何独特）和制图（2019年）。几乎一半的项目（13个中的6个）来自亚洲公司/个人（中国，韩国和日本）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这次，AI/ML在新添加的项目的流行类别中闪耀，这完全相关，因为我们在云本机空间中看到了更多此类工作量。在此沙盒批处理中，许多与网络相关的工具也很明显。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;至于所使用的编程语言，GO仍然占主导地位，其次是生锈的小但稳定的存在，一个例外（Java）。许可显示更大的一致性：13个项目中有12个选择了Apache 2.0。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; p.s。本系列中的其他文章&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.palark.com/cncf-sandbox-2023-h1/&#34;&gt;Part 1: 13 arrivals of 2023 H1&lt;/a&gt;: Inspektor Gadget, Headlamp, Kepler, SlimToolkit, SOPS, Clusternet, Eraser, PipeCD, Microcks, kpt, Xline, HwameiStor, and Kubeclipper。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.palark.com/cncf-sandbox-2023-h2/&#34;&gt;Part 2: 12 arrivals of 2023 H2&lt;/a&gt;: Logging operator, K8sGPT, kcp, KubeStellar, Copa, Kanister, KCL, Easegress, Kuasar, krkn, kube-burner, and Spiderpool。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.palark.com/cncf-sandbox-2024-h1/&#34;&gt;Part 3: 14 arrivals of 2024 H1&lt;/a&gt;: Radius, Stacker, Score, Bank-Vaults, TrestleGRC, bpfman, Koordinator, KubeSlice, Atlantis, Kubean, Connect, Kairos, Kuadrant,和OpenGemini。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style =“高度：80px“ aria-hidded =“ true” class =“ wp-block-pacer is style-80-120”&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>