<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://rsshub.rssforever.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025: Day Three Keynote Recap】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025：第三天主题演讲回顾</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/07/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025-day-three-keynote-recap/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The last day of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 dawned bright and sunny again, with attendees streaming in to learn the latest about cutting edge topics including LLMs, 5G and 6G, and more. Here’s a snapshot of the keynotes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clayton Coleman, distinguished engineer at Google, and Jiaxin Shan, software engineer at Bytedance, presented &lt;strong&gt;LLM-Aware load balancing in Kubernetes: A new era of efficiency&lt;/strong&gt;. Their conclusion was load balancer are key, and that a lot of work can be automated out of GenAI serving using two basic principles: Model the cost of an incoming LLM request and decide how sending it to a backend will impact the latency of other requests, and build a realtime snapshot of each backend’s performance by continuously gathering metrics so it’s possible to capture the complex relationships between hardware, concurrency and client-visible latency. Their prediction: 2025 will be the year of production scaling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A panel of telecom experts including Faseela K from Ericsson Software Engineering, Tom Kivlin of Vodafone, Philippe Ensarguet of Orange, and Joel Studler of Swissccom spoke about &lt;strong&gt;Cloud native evolution in telecom: 5G, 6G, and beyond!&lt;/strong&gt; Their conclusion is that the industry needs a cultural shift and that tech companies need to adopt cloud native tooling in order to maximize productivity gains. “Everything we fix today reduces tech debt tomorrow.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Eddie Knight, OSPO lead at Sonatype and Michael Lieberman, CTO at Kusari, discussed &lt;strong&gt;Cutting through the fog: Clarifying CRA compliance&lt;/strong&gt; in cloud native. Their presentation explained the Cyber Resilience Act, EU legislation intended to protect consumers and businesses from cybersecurity threats in products with digital elements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ricardo Rocha, computing engineer at CERN and Katie Gamanji, senior field engineer at Apple, spoke about &lt;strong&gt;221B Cloud Native Street&lt;/strong&gt;, on behalf of the CNCF Technical Oversight Committee. Among other efforts, the TOC has kicked off the TAG reboot initiative, with the aim to scale the TAGs and prepare the community for the next decade of cloud native. And the TOC has also identified a few gaps that we believe will shape the future trends within our ecosystem, including multicluster management, cost management and sustainability, and tooling around infrastructure provisioning and secret management.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Carolina Lindqvist, system specialist at EPFL, spoke about &lt;strong&gt;Science at light speed: Cloud native infrastructure for astronomy workloads&lt;/strong&gt;. The Square Kilometre Array has three sites – one telescope in South Africa, one in Australia and a headquarters in the UK – 12 member states, and generates 600 petabytes of data a year! The project has a wide variety of science goals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to experience more of Day three of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025? &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-cloudnativecon-activity-7313952932893188096-gvBL?&#34;&gt;Watch the video!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe的最后一天再次亮起了明亮和阳光明媚，与会者正在播放有关最新的有关最新主题，包括LLMS，5G和6G等。这是主题演讲的快照。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Clayton Coleman，Google的杰出工程师和Bytedance的软件工程师Jiaxin Shan提出了Kubernetes中的&lt;strong&gt; llm-Awaine负载平衡：效率的新时代&lt;/strong&gt;。他们的结论是负载平衡器是关键，并且可以使用两个基本原则从Genai自动化大量工作：建模传入的LLM请求的成本，并确定如何将其发送到后端，将影响其他请求的延迟，并将每个后端的实时快照构建每个后端绩效的实时快照，从而可以通过不断地捕获相互限制的关系，以便彼此之间的相关性，以便彼此之间的相关性，以便彼此之间的相关性，并可以彼此之间的范围和界限。他们的预测：2025将是生产规模的年份。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;电信专家小组，包括爱立信软件工程的Faseela K，沃达丰的汤姆·基维林（Tom Kivlin），橙色的菲利普·埃恩盖特（Philippe of Orange）和瑞士科姆（Swissccom）的乔尔·斯图勒（Joel Studler）在电信中&lt;strong&gt;云云的本地进化：5G，6G，6G，6G，以及超越他们的结论都需要在文化上进行工业界的秩序，而这些工具是文化上的工具。 “我们今天修复的一切都会减少明天的技术债务。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Sonatype的OSPO领导者Eddie Knight和Kusari的CTO迈克尔·利伯曼（Michael Lieberman）讨论了&lt;strong&gt; cutter of fog：在云本地澄清CRA合规性&lt;/strong&gt;。他们的演讲解释了《网络弹性法》，欧盟立法旨在保护消费者和企业免受具有数字元素产品的网络安全威胁。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Ricardo Rocha是Cern的计算机工程师和Apple高级野外工程师Katie Gamanji，他代表CNCF技术监督委员会谈到了&lt;strong&gt; 221B Cloud Native Street &lt;/strote&gt;。除其他努力外，TOC还开始了标签重新启动倡议，目的是扩展标签并为社区做好准备，为接下来的十年云本地人做好准备。 TOC还确定了一些我们认为将塑造我们生态系统中未来趋势的空白，包括多群集管理，成本管理和可持续性，以及围绕基础设施提供和秘密管理的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;EPFL的系统专家Carolina Lindqvist在光速时谈到了&lt;strong&gt;科学：天文学工作负载的云本地基础设施&lt;/strong&gt;。平方公里的阵列有三个地点 - 南非的一个望远镜，一个位于澳大利亚的望远镜，一个在英国的总部 -  12个成员国，每年产生600毫无疑问的数据！该项目具有各种各样的科学目标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想体验更多的库贝康 + Cloudnativecon欧洲2025年的第三天吗？ &lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-cloudnativecon-activity-7313952932893188096-gvbl吗？”&gt;观看视频！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025: Day One Keynote Recap】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025：第一天的主题演讲回顾</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/02/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025-day-one-keynote-recap/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;On a bright sunny London day, attendees from all over the world flocked to the ExCel Arena for the first day of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 2025. Here’s a quick recap of the keynotes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The crowd was welcomed by Cloud Native Computing Foundation CTO and founder Chris Aniszczyk, who talked about the tenth anniversary of cloud native computing and walked everyone down memory lane. Chris updated the audience on a number of efforts – from Golden Kubestronauts to training efforts in Africa (a partnership with Andela) – and also talked about the beta release of GitJobs.dev, a way to find open source jobs. Then Vasu Chandrasekhara from SAP joined him to explain NeoNephos, a sovereign cloud-edge continuum for Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Christine Yen, CEO and cofounder of Honeycomb, presented a keynote on &lt;strong&gt;Observability in the age of LLMs&lt;/strong&gt;. Christine explained that writing software today feels more like magic than ever, and that while LLMs are like APIs, they complicate the traditional ways of doing things because they can be difficult to test, mock up and debug. The answer, she argued, was observability, because it helps embrace the unpredictability that LLMs bring. The trick is to bundle observability with evals so teams can capture the good and bad as it happens and create systems that evolve with the code. The good news? This isn’t a new skillset. A lot of this shift is already underway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vijay Samuel, principal MTS and architect at eBay, spoke about &lt;strong&gt;AI-enabled observability explainers – We actually did something with AI!&lt;/strong&gt; With 4600 microservices powering the eBay site, and 15PB of logs per day, Vijay explained how incidents impacted the team’s ability to provide the highest quality customer experience and that trying to deal with all this data manually is cumbersome. So his group started small experiments using LLMs as observability building blocks that could summarize and explain critical paths. They found simple flows they could automate and in the end leaned into LLMs’ strengths all the while realizing there were still things best done with code instead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Greg Kroah-Hartman, Linux Kernel Maintainer and Fellow with The Linux Foundation, spoke on &lt;strong&gt;Rust in the Linux Kernel: A new era for cloud native performance and security&lt;/strong&gt;. Greg walked the audience through the close relationship between Rust and Linux and shared some statistics, including the fact that Linux has 4,992 developers and 355+ employers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rob Koch, principal of Slalom Build and an American Sign Language user, shared his experience working toward machine recognition of sign language, in &lt;strong&gt;Empowering accessibility through Kubernetes: The future of real-time sign language interpretation&lt;/strong&gt;. Currently only two&amp;nbsp; or three companies in the world are working on this, Rob explained, and his company is using Kubeflow and Kubernetes to tackle the challenge. Kubeflow simplifies the deployment of machine learning models, ensuring smooth transitions from training to production.In the future, the company wants to prepare for recognizing other sign languages and seeing things from other viewpoints.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kasper Borg Nissen, developer relations engineer at Dash0, spoke on &lt;strong&gt;The observability platform engineering advantage: from zero code to monitoring as code&lt;/strong&gt;. His contention is that current systems are really inefficient when it comes to observability. “We don’t have a &lt;em&gt;metrics problem&lt;/em&gt;, or a &lt;em&gt;tracing problem&lt;/em&gt;. We have systems problems.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;And yet, many of us still treat these as separate entities. We have one browser tab for logs, another for metrics, and a third for tracing. We are relying on humans to correlate signals across them. It’s inefficient, it’s error-prone, and frankly, it’s not how modern observability should work.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He ended with a call to action to apply platform engineering principles to observability: “Applying platform engineering principles can transform observability from an afterthought into a seamless, scalable, and developer-friendly experience.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get more of Day One &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-activity-7313294603816689664-VZJR?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=member_android&amp;amp;rcm=ACoAAAZ5jugBqGBtxyEC7vpreMCIH8DipnVChMs&#34;&gt;in this video&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在阳光明媚的伦敦日，来自世界各地的与会者涌向Excel Arena，在Kubecon + Cloudnativecon 2025的第一天。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人群受到Cloud Native Computing Foundation CTO和创始人Chris Aniszczyk的欢迎，他们谈到了Cloud Native Computing的十周年，并将所有人带走了记忆巷。克里斯（Chris）对观众进行了许多努力的更新 - 从黄金kubestronauts到非洲的培训工作（与安德拉（Andela）的合作伙伴关系） - 还谈到了Gitjobs.dev的Beta版本，这是找到开源工作的一种方式。然后，来自SAP的Vasu Chandrasekhara与他一起解释了Neonephos，Neonephos是欧洲的主权云边缘连续体。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Honeycomb的首席执行官兼联合创始人Christine Yen在LLMS时代&lt;strong&gt;可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;时提出了一个主题演讲。克里斯汀（Christine）解释说，今天写软件比以往任何时候都更像是魔术，尽管LLM就像API，但它们会使传统的做事方式变得复杂，因为它们很难测试，模拟和调试。她认为，答案是可观察到的，因为它有助于接受LLMS带来的不可预测性。诀窍是用evals捆绑可观察性，以便团队可以在发生时捕获好和坏处，并创建随着代码发展的系统。好消息？这不是一个新技能。这种转变已经在进行中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;eBay的主要MTS和建筑师Vijay Samuel谈到了&lt;strong&gt; AI-AI-AI-A-AI-A-Absibal可观察性解释器 - 我们实际上是在AI！&lt;/strong&gt;的情况下做了一些事情！&lt;/strong&gt;，有4600个微服务为eBay网站提供动力，每天为15％的日志提供了15％的日志，Vijay解释了该团队的能力如何提供最高质量的客户经验，以实现最高质量的客户经验和所有这些数据。因此，他的小组使用LLM作为可观察性构建块开始了小型实验，可以总结并解释关键路径。他们发现他们可以自动化的简单流程，最终倾向于LLMS的优势，同时意识到仍然可以使用代码做得最好。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Greg Kroah-Hartman，Linux内核维护者和Linux Foundation的研究员在Linux内核中发表了&lt;strong&gt; Rust：云本地性能和安全性的新时代&lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt;。格雷格（Greg）通过Rust和Linux之间的密切关系，分享了一些统计数据，其中包括Linux拥有4,992个开发人员和355多名雇主。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;激流回旋构建的负责人和美国手语用户的主管Rob Koch分享了他致力于机器识别手语的经验，&lt;strong&gt;通过Kubernetes授权可访问性：实时手语解释的未来&lt;/strong&gt;。 Rob解释说，目前，世界上只有两三家公司正在为此做出努力，他的公司正在使用Kubeflow和Kubernetes来应对挑战。 kubeflow简化了部署者机器学习模型的T，确保从培训到生产的平稳过渡。该公司希望准备识别其他标志语言并从其他观点看到事物。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; DASH0开发人员关系工程师Kasper Borg Nissen在&lt;strong&gt;上发表了可观察性平台工程优势：从零代码到监视代码&lt;/strong&gt;。他的论点是，目前的系统在观察性方面确实效率低下。 “我们没有一个&lt;em&gt;衡量问题&lt;/em&gt;或&lt;em&gt;跟踪问题&lt;/em&gt;。我们有系统问题。&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;，但是，我们中的许多人仍将这些问题视为单独的实体。我们有一个浏览器访问日志，另一个用于指标，三分之一来跟踪。我们依靠人类的人，坦率地说明了它的误差。现代可观察性应该起作用。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他以采取行动的呼吁将平台工程原则应用于可观察性：“应用平台工程原则可以将可观察性从事后思考转变为无缝，可扩展和开发人员友好的体验。” &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;获得更多第一天&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-activity-7313294603816 689664-vzjr？utm_source = share＆utm_medium = member_android＆rcm = acoaaaaz5JUGBQGBTXYEC7VPREMCIH8DIPNVCHMS“&gt; IN&gt; IN这个视频&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Get to Know KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Co-Chair Faseela K.】了解Kubecon + Cloudnativecon联合主席Faseela K.</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/31/get-to-know-kubecon-cloudnativecon-co-chair-faseela-k/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Faseela Kundattil is one of those people who just seems to do a lot of things: Cloud Native Developer, project maintainer, CNCF Ambassador, LFX mentor, Technical Oversight Committee member, new mom, and now KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 Keynote speaker and co-chair. She even (co-)wrote the book on &lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2024/istio-phippy-book/&#34;&gt;Istio Service Mesh (for kids!)&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maybe cloud native is her super power? She certainly credits cloud native with giving her opportunities early in her career that she wouldn’t have had otherwise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I was just a few years into the industry but open source gave me a chance to contribute code upstream,” she says. “And the thing about open source was there were a lot of other companies who were collaborating with us on the same project.&amp;nbsp; So it was giving me some perspective about how we are able to work in a remote environment, but still collaborate with each other in a remote way. We were very efficient and all that learning came from open source ways of working.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even at a very early stage in her career, Faseela was able to travel and give talks. “It was good exposure for me,” she says. “I learned how to represent my company externally, but also to make sure everybody’s needs are met and ours are met too. Collaboration is something I really learned from open source.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her bottom line: “I do not think if you work in a single company, in a fully closed environment, you’ll get all this learning and collaboration and supporting each other kind of environment,” she explains. To get all that, it takes cloud native.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And it doesn’t hurt to have your family behind you either. “While cloud native may seem to be my superpower, I am really grateful to have a supportive family: my husband and my 10 year-old daughter who have extended all their support in the background taking care of our one year-old baby boy while I pay attention to my KubeCon responsibilities and&amp;nbsp; look like a super woman!”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How it all started&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Faseela, who is from India, started her career in Bangalore, spending nearly 11 years in the software networking industry. Her first role was at Ericsson as a Graduate Engineering Trainee after college and eventually she moved to Cisco as part of the platform engineering team. When Covid hit, she and her family decided to make the move to Europe and they settled in Aachen, Germany where she was able to return to Ericsson. The move made her happy, she says, because she was able to go back to working in open source. At Ericsson she’d worked on Linux Foundation projects including Open Daylight. “I really loved that. I missed those times because it was really that collaborative environment in open source,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her return to Ericsson gave her the chance to work on a CNCF project, Istio, and she’s been deep into open source for these last three years. “I started as a normal contributor first, but I was soon able to become a maintainer and then later a steering committee member,” she says. Faseela has also served as the event co-chair for both the IstioDays co-located with KubeCon in 2023 and has been a Program Committee member at several KubeCons. And of course her day job keeps her busy too: she is a key member driving the 5G transformation of Ericsson, designing Cloud Native Network Functions and bridging the gap between telco and open source.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most recently, she’s been elected to the CNCF’s Technical Oversight Committee (the TOC), which is the governing body that gives technical directions for all the CNCF projects. And she is a co-chair for the upcoming three KubeCon + CloudNativeCons, “something I’m really looking forward to.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New to KubeCon? Faseela’s best advice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No matter where you are on your cloud native journey, you’ll find a place for you at KubeCon, of that Faseela is certain. “It’s like the best event or the best platform where you can network and get to know other experts from the industry and understand how cloud computing works and how to contribute to open source.” Her suggestions for those new to KubeCon: Pick &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;the beginner tracks&lt;/a&gt;, dive into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;ContribFests&lt;/a&gt;, don’t skip the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;KubeCrawl&lt;/a&gt;, consider the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Peer Group Mentoring opportunities&lt;/a&gt;, attend the live demos, &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu2025.sched.com/event/1vTiQ/project-pavilion-tour&#34;&gt;explore the Project Pavillion&lt;/a&gt;, and just network in the hallways.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t miss Faseela’s talks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She and co-author Lin Sun will be &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;speaking about their book Izzy Saves the Birthday&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Faseela and several others will be delivering a keynote on &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Evolution in Telecom: 5G, 6G and Beyond!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And she will also be at &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Contribfest: A Beginner’s Guide to Contributing to Istio&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; faseela kundattil是似乎做很多事情的人之一：云本地开发人员，项目维护者，CNCF大使，LFX导师，技术监督委员会成员，新妈妈和现在的Kubecon + Cloubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025 Keynote Keynote Keynote Speaker and Co-inder和联合主教。她甚至（共同）在&lt;a href =“ https://istio.io/latest/blog/2024/istio-phippy-book/”&gt; istio服务网格（For Kids！）&lt;/a&gt;上写了这本书。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;也许云本地人是她的超级力量吗？她当然会认为云本地人在职业生涯的早期就给自己的机会归功于她本来没有的机会。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我已经进入该行业只有几年了，但是开源给了我在上游贡献代码的机会，”她说。 “关于开源的事情是，还有许多其他公司与我们合作在同一项目上。因此，这给了我一些观点，即我们如何在偏远的环境中工作，但仍然以远程方式与彼此进行合作。我们非常有效，所有学习都来自开放源代码的工作方式。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使在她职业生涯的早期阶段，Faseela也能够旅行并进行演讲。她说：“这对我来说是个好曝光。” “我学会了如何在外部代表我的公司，但也要确保满足每个人的需求，也满足了我们的需求。合作是我真正从开源中学到的东西。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她的底线：“我认为，如果您在一家公司中工作，在一个完全封闭的环境中，您将获得所有这些学习，协作并互相支持的环境，”她解释说。为了获得所有这些，它需要云原生。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，让您的家人在您身后也没有什么坏处。 “虽然Cloud Native似乎是我的超级大国，但我真的很高兴有一个支持家庭的家庭：我的丈夫和我10岁的女儿，他们在背景中扩大了所有的支持，而我照顾了我们一岁的男婴，而我关注了我的库贝肯责任，看起来像个超级女人！” &lt;/p&gt;！” &lt;/p&gt;！&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;一切都开始&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;来自印度的&lt;p&gt; Faseela在班加罗尔开始了她的职业生涯，在软件网络行业工作了近11年。她的第一个职位是大学毕业后在爱立信担任研究生工程学员，最终作为平台工程团队的一部分移居思科。当Covid命中时，她和她的家人决定搬到欧洲，他们定居在德国的Aachen，在那里她能够返回爱立信。她说，此举使她开心，因为她能够回到开源工作。在爱立信，她从事Linux基金会项目，包括开放日光。她解释说：“我真的很喜欢。我错过了那些时代，因为这确实是开源的协作环境。”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她返回爱立信给了她有机会从事CNCF项目ISTIO的工作，她已经深入了最近三年的来源。她说：“我首先是正常的贡献者，但我很快就可以成为一名维护者，然后成为指导委员会成员。” Faseela还曾在2023年与Kubecon共同列为ISTIODAYS的活动共同主席，并一直是多个Kubecons的计划委员会成员。当然，她的日常工作也让她忙碌：她是驱动爱立信的5G转型，设计云本地网络功能并弥合电信公司和开源之间的差距的关键成员。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近，她当选为CNCF技术监督委员会（TOC），该委员会是管理机构，为所有CNCF项目提供了技术指导。她是即将到来的三个Kubecon + Cloudnativecons的联合主席，“我真的很期待。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;新的库贝肯？ Faseela的最佳建议&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您在云本地旅程中，您都可以在库贝肯找到一个faseela的地方。 “这就像最好的活动或最好的平台，您可以在这里建立网络并了解来自行业的其他专家，并了解云计算的工作原理以及如何为开源做出贡献。”她对新手Kubecon的建议：挑选&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt;初学者跟踪&lt;/a&gt;，潜入&lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt; conforfests &lt;/a&gt;，不要跳过&lt;a &lt;a &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; kubecrawl &lt;/a&gt;，考虑&lt;a href =“小组指导机会&lt;/a&gt;，参加现场演示，&lt;a href =“ https://kccnceu2025.sched.com/event/1vtiq/project-project-pavilion-tour”&gt;探索Project Project Project of Project Project Pavillion &lt;/a&gt;，并且只是在走廊上进行网络。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;不要错过Faseela的谈话&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她和合着者林太阳将是&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt;谈论他们的书Iszzy save y i zzzy挽救了生日&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; faseela和其他几个人将在&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt;电信中的云原生进化：5G，6G和超越！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她也将在&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/progm/program/schedule/”&gt; converfest：贡献到istio的初学者指南。&lt;/a&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025: Day Two Keynote Recap】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025：第二天的主题演讲回顾</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/03/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025-day-two-keynote-recap/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Over 12,000 attendees streamed into the ExCel Arena for the second day of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025, enjoying yet another sunny day in London and primed to hear real world stories of cloud innovation. Here’s a quick recap of the day’s keynote speeches.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A four-person panel keynote – &lt;strong&gt;Mind the Gap: Bridging cloud native innovation with real world use&lt;/strong&gt; – took a deep dive into how cloud native has fundamentally changed the way some very large companies are doing business. Panelists from HSBC, Peptone, Spotify and Apple outlined the challenges they faced, and the successes they found with cloud native. A couple of examples:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From HSBC: “We’re currently servicing around 600 million discrete hits a day, with over 7000 services in production, with thousands still to migrate from the legacy platform, all running in only a dozen or so clusters. Our clusters are very stable, but change can still be a pain point. To mitigate those issues during upgrades, we run our clusters in a blue/green pair and rehydrate clusters from etcd backups, cutting traffic over only when we’re happy that everything in the upgraded cluster is stable.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FromSpotify: “There’s been tension in how we balance internal priorities with external ones. But ultimately, this is a virtuous cycle. If we hadn’t open sourced Backstage, we’d likely still be living with our previous, more complicated backend system. In five years, we’ve gone from basically just a thin framework for building an IDP, to a better Backstage than we could have built on our own. Now, we’ve taken that further, to create the best IDP for the future.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katie Gamanji, senior field engineer at Apple, talked about &lt;strong&gt;Open source in Apple’s private cloud compute&lt;/strong&gt;. At Apple, private cloud compute helps scale AI operations. Keeping privacy in mind, Apple ensures encryption is end to end. Swift libraries work with the community for open source. And gRPC and Swift teamed with private cloud compute are what enables it all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Top End User Award was given to Ant Group.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gabriel Quennesson, Michelin’s container as a service tech lead, and Arnaud Pons, container as a service product architect, spoke about &lt;strong&gt;Driving innovation at Michelin: How we scaled cloud &amp;amp; on-prem infrastructure while cutting costs&lt;/strong&gt;. The company was misaligned with its previous vendor’s strategy, while at the same time all of Michelin was embracing open source. And of course the team wanted to remain attractive to top tech talent. Switching to Kubernetes – and doing it themselves – brought platform costs down 44% and upgrade leadtime down 85% all while doubling their Kubernetes footprint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Discussing &lt;strong&gt;CNCF at 10: Navigating challenges, embracing opportunities&lt;/strong&gt; were Joseph Sandoval, principal product manager at Adobe, Liz Rice, chief open source officer from Isovalent at Cisco, and Katie Gamanji, senior field engineer with Apple. They walked the audience through the history of the last ten years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And Hans Kristian Flaatten, lead platform engineer NAV and Audun Fauchald Strand, principal software engineer, NAV, shared their &lt;strong&gt;Adventures of building platform as a service for the government&lt;/strong&gt;, which is a public PaaS in Norway with 81 member organizations that provides speed and agility to developers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want more KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025? &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-activity-7313607861245280258-lfNe?&#34;&gt;Watch the video!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;超过12,000名与会者在库贝肯 + Cloudnativecon欧洲2025年的第二天涌入Excel竞技场，在伦敦享受了又一个晴天，并听到了现实世界中有关云创新的故事。这是当天主题演讲的快速回顾。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个四人面板主题演讲 -  &lt;strong&gt;脑海中的差距：与现实世界使用&lt;/strong&gt;的桥接云国际创新 - 深入了解了云本地人如何从根本上改变了一些大型公司开展业务的方式。来自汇丰银行，peptone，Spotify和Apple的小组成员概述了他们面临的挑战，以及他们在Cloud Native中发现的成功。几个例子：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来自汇丰银行：“我们目前每天为6亿个离散命中率提供服务，生产的7000多个服务，成千上万的服务仍可以从遗产平台迁移，所有这些服务都只有十几个左右的群集。我们的插曲非常稳定。我们的cluts非常稳定，但变化仍然可以减轻我们的痛苦。只有当我们很高兴升级的集群中的所有内容都稳定时，才能减少交通。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“我们如何在内部优先级与外部优先级保持紧张。但是最终，这是一个良好的周期。如果我们没有开放式的后台，我们可能仍然与以前的，更复杂的后端体系相处。五年来，我们从基本上是一个伟大的框架来构建AN AN AN AN AN AN AN AN ETIC。现在，我们已经建立了一个伟大的ID。现在，我们已经建立了一个。未来。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;苹果的高级野外工程师凯蒂·甘曼吉（Katie Gamanji）在苹果的私人云计算中谈到了&lt;strong&gt;开源&lt;/strong&gt;。在Apple，Private Cloud Compute有助于扩展AI操作。牢记隐私，苹果确保加密是端到端的。 Swift图书馆与社区合作开源。 GRPC和Swift与私有云计算合作，这是所有功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终用户奖获得了蚂蚁组。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Gabriel Quennesson，米其林作为服务技术负责人的容器，而Arnaud Pons（作为服务产品架构师）的Arnaud Pons谈到了&lt;strong&gt;在米其林开车的创新：我们如何缩放云和本地基础架构，同时削减成本&lt;/strong&gt;。该公司与以前的供应商的策略不一致，与此同时，米其林全部都在接受开源。当然，团队希望对顶尖技术人才保持吸引力。切换到kubernetes并自己进行 - 使平台的成本下降了44％，并升级了85％的平台，同时使他们的kubernetes footprint加倍。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;讨论&lt;strong&gt; CNCF 10：面临挑战，拥抱机会&lt;/strong&gt;是约瑟夫·桑多尔（Joseph SandovalO苹果高级野外工程师Katie Gamanji。他们引导观众度过了过去十年的历史。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和汉斯·克里斯蒂安·弗拉昂（Hans Kristian Flaatten），首席平台工程师纳尔（Nav）和纳维尔（Nav）首席软件工程师的阿杜·福卡尔德（Audun Fauchald Strand）分享了他们的&lt;strong&gt;构建平台的冒险，作为政府的服务&lt;/strong&gt;，这是挪威的公共PAAS，与81个成员组织是挪威的公共PAA，为开发人员提供速度和敏捷性。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想要更多的kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025？ &lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-activity-7313607861245280258-lfne？&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【10 Questions to Help You Decide Whether to Hire an SRE or Managed KaaS】10个问题，以帮助您决定是雇用SRE还是托管KAAS</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/09/10-questions-to-help-you-decide-whether-to-hire-an-sre-or-managed-kaas/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Deciding between managing Kubernetes in-house or partnering with a managed service provider can be a difficult choice for organizations seeking to optimize their cloud infrastructure. Over the past several years, I’ve been part of the decision to hire talent in-house or use a managed service provider (not for Kubernetes management, of course—that’s where our team shines the brightest!).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most organizations make these types of decisions often, especially in areas such as payroll, graphic design, and accounting. Many factors go into the decision including our time and expertise to supervise the employee and the evolving needs of the business. When a skill is going to be a long term strategic asset to our business, I nearly always choose to hire an internal expert to join our team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Practical Guidelines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to choosing to hire a service provider or in-house talent to drive your business forward, lean on these practical guidelines:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Align with Core Competencies: For jobs that are central to your organization’s mission, developing internal expertise is nearly always the best choice. This approach ensures that the team handling these tasks is deeply integrated into your company’s culture and objectives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Leverage Established Solutions: Often, engineers pride themselves on building something new and better. For challenges that have already been effectively addressed by existing solutions, however, it is usually best to use existing solutions or experts. In other words, don’t expend resources unnecessarily to reinvent something. Instead, benefit from proven solutions or practices when possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scalability and Growth: While large enterprises, like Apple or Microsoft, might have the capacity to bring everything in-house, smaller organizations must examine which functions to outsource carefully. This approach enables you to focus on areas where you can achieve the most significant business impact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another aspect to consider is whether you’re choosing between a managed service provider or a short-term consultant or project-based consulting agreement. Managed service providers typically have a vested interest in the sustained success of their clients because they offer ongoing support and optimization as part of a long-term contract. In contrast, some consultants may focus on short-term projects without a commitment to your organization’s long-term outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Infrastructure Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Managing cloud infrastructure is a bit like a band using a recording studio. While the band’s unique music is their core product, the recording equipment and studio environment are essential tools that support the creation of the band’s music. However, mastering the intricacies of studio design or sound engineering could divert them from their primary focus—making music with their signature sound. Does every member of the band need to be a sound engineer to make good music? Definitely not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, organizations should concentrate on building and differentiating their core services and consider outsourcing complex infrastructure management to specialists. Building, deploying, and maintaining cloud infrastructure isn’t what makes most companies money. They need the infrastructure, but not the in-house skills to build and manage it. In short, to maximize the chance of success, organizations should internalize functions that are central to their core competencies and outsource tasks that (while important) do not define their unique value proposition.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As businesses adopt Kubernetes or increase their K8s footprint, a common question is whether it makes sense build an in-house team (perhaps starting with hiring a Site Reliability Engineer (SRE)) to manage Kubernetes or bring in a Managed Kubernetes-as-a-Service (KaaS) provider.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below are ten key questions to help guide your decision-making process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;em&gt;What is our core business focus, and does Kubernetes management augment it?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your primary business goal is building software products or delivering services, managing Kubernetes in-house might divert valuable resources from where they’re needed most. A managed service allows you to focus on your core business while experts handle Kubernetes operations. However, if infrastructure management is a strategic advantage (such as in a cloud monitoring SaaS company), having an SRE or an internal team might be worth the investment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;em&gt;Do we have (or can we attract) the right Kubernetes expertise?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes is complex, and hiring skilled professionals—like an SRE team—can be both challenging and expensive. If you already have DevOps engineers in-house who understand Kubernetes well, building an internal team might be fairly simple. On the other hand, if hiring or training your team on Kubernetes is a bottleneck, a managed Kubernetes provider can offer immediate expertise, reducing the learning curve and accelerating your deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. &lt;em&gt;How much control do we need over our Kubernetes environment?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your organization requires full control over networking, security, storage, and custom configurations, an in-house SRE team gives you the flexibility to fine-tune Kubernetes for your organization’s unique needs. A Managed Kubernetes-as-a-Service provider, on the other hand, may remove some of the fine-grained control from your team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;em&gt;What are our uptime, reliability, and performance requirements?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mission-critical applications require high availability and rapid disaster recovery capabilities. An experienced SRE can optimize performance, ensure redundancy, and set up incident response protocols tailored to your business, but particularly if you have a small SRE team, they’ll always be on call for infrastructure pages and they’ll be the go to person for everything infrastructure-related.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. &lt;em&gt;What are the true costs of hiring vs. outsourcing Kubernetes management?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An SRE’s salary can exceed $150K–$200K per year, not including benefits, tools, training, and additional operations support. Organizations should calculate the Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) for both approaches, considering:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Salaries, training, and hiring costs&lt;br&gt;Infrastructure and tool expenses&lt;br&gt;Downtime and operational inefficiencies&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;6. &lt;em&gt;How quickly do we need to deploy and scale Kubernetes?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your team needs to deploy Kubernetes rapidly, a managed service provider can deliver environments configured to align with Kubernetes best practices quickly, reducing the time to deployment considerably. In contrast, hiring an SRE and building an internal Kubernetes team requires time for recruitment, onboarding, and infrastructure setup. If speed is important, a managed service provider can accelerate your path to deploying production workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;7. &lt;em&gt;What level of security and compliance do we require?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Security is a top concern for Kubernetes environments because Kubernetes is not secure by default. If your organization operates in a regulated industry (finance, healthcare, and government to name just a few), compliance requirements may demand stricter control over configurations, access management, and logging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An in-house SRE team provides full control over security policies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;8. &lt;em&gt;How will we handle ongoing monitoring, incident response, and troubleshooting?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes requires continuous monitoring and proactive issue resolution. An in-house SRE team can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Customize observability tools (Prometheus, Grafana, and so on)&lt;br&gt;Create automated alerting systems&lt;br&gt;Implement self-healing mechanisms&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But in-house teams must also monitor, respond to, and resolve infrastructure alerts quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;9. &lt;em&gt;Are we planning for a multi-cloud or hybrid cloud strategy?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your organization intends to deploy Kubernetes across multiple cloud providers (AWS, GCP, and Azure) or in a hybrid-cloud setup, managing Kubernetes internally provides the flexibility to optimize workloads across different environments. That also means your internal team will need to know the details of each cloud service provider.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;10. &lt;em&gt;What is our long-term Kubernetes roadmap?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes is constantly maturing, requiring organizations to keep up with upgrades, security patches, and feature changes in K8s, related APIs, and add-ons. If your business requires long-term control and deep Kubernetes expertise, investing in an internal team makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, if Kubernetes is a means to an end rather than a strategic focus, outsourcing management to a trusted provider ensures you always have access to up-to-date infrastructure without needing to stay ahead of Kubernetes advancements yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which Path is Right for You?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If Kubernetes is mission-critical, requires deep customization, and your organization has the resources to build and retain an internal team, hiring an SRE may be the right choice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to focus on your applications and business growth while offloading Kubernetes complexities, a Managed Kubernetes-as-a-Service provider offers a faster, cost-effective, and scalable solution. The decision depends on your business goals, in-house expertise, and operational priorities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fairwinds.com/&#34;&gt;Fairwinds&lt;/a&gt; Managed Kubernetes-as-a-Service can accelerate your cloud adoption initiatives and help your team to get back to making great music (or building new apps and services, whichever is your passion).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在内部管理Kubernetes或与托管服务提供商合作之间，对于寻求优化其云基础架构的组织而言，这是一个困难的选择。在过去的几年中，我一直是在内部聘请人才或使用托管服务提供商的决定（当然不是用于Kubernetes Management，这是我们的团队最聪明的地方！）。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大多数组织经常做出这些类型的决定，尤其是在工资单，图形设计和会计等领域。决定的许多因素包括我们的时间和专业知识来监督员工和企业不断发展的需求。当技能成为我们业务的长期战略资产时，我几乎总是选择雇用内部专家加入我们的团队。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;实用准则&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;选择聘请服务提供商或内部人才以推动您的业务前进，请依靠这些实用准则：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与核心竞争力保持一致：对于您组织任务至关重要的工作，发展内部专业知识几乎总是最好的选择。这种方法确保处理这些任务的团队已深入融合到您公司的文化和目标中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;利用已建立的解决方案：通常，工程师以建造新事物更好而感到自豪。但是，对于现有解决方案已经有效解决的挑战，通常最好使用现有的解决方案或专家。换句话说，不要不必要地消耗资源来重塑某些东西。相反，在可能的情况下受益于经过验证的解决方案或实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可扩展性和增长：虽然像苹果或微软这样的大型企业可能有能力将所有东西带入内部，但较小的组织必须检查哪些功能要仔细外包。这种方法使您能够专注于可以实现最重要业务影响的领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要考虑的另一个方面是您是在托管服务提供商还是短期顾问或基于项目的咨询协议之间进行选择。托管服务提供商通常对客户的持续成功具有既得利益，因为他们提供了长期合同的一部分，提供持续的支持和优化。相比之下，一些顾问可能会专注于短期项目，而无需承诺您组织的长期成果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云基础架构管理&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;管理云基础架构有点像使用录音室的乐队。尽管乐队的独特音乐是他们的核心产品，但录音设备和工作室环境是支持乐队音乐创作的重要工具。但是，掌握工作室设计或声音工程的复杂性可能会将它们从主要重点转移到他们的主要焦点中 - 用他们的标志性声音来制作音乐。每一个成员E乐队需要成为声音工程师来制作好音乐吗？绝对不是。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同样，组织应集中精力建设和区分其核心服务，并考虑将复杂的基础设施管理外包给专家。建立，部署和维护云基础架构并不是大多数公司的钱。他们需要基础设施，但不需要内部技能来建立和管理它。简而言之，为了最大化成功的机会，组织应内部化对其核心能力和外包任务至关重要的功能，而这些任务（尽管很重要）并未定义其独特的价值主张。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着企业采用Kubernetes或增加其K8S足迹，一个普遍的问题是，建立一个内部团队是否有意义（也许是从雇用网站可靠性工程师（SRE）开始来管理Kubernetes或引入托管的Kubernetes-as-as-as-a-Service（KAAS）提供者。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是十个关键问题，可以帮助指导您的决策过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 1。 &lt;em&gt;我们的核心业务重点是什么？&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的主要业务目标是构建软件产品或提供服务，那么内部管理Kubernetes可能会将宝贵的资源从最需要的地方转移。托管服务使您可以专注于核心业务，而专家处理Kubernetes运营。但是，如果基础架构管理是一种战略优势（例如在云监控SaaS公司中），那么拥有SRE或内部团队可能值得投资。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2。 &lt;em&gt;我们是否有（或可以吸引）合适的Kubernetes专业知识？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes很复杂，雇用熟练的专业人士（例如SRE团队）既具有挑战性又昂贵。如果您的内部DevOps工程师对Kubernetes了解很好，那么建立一个内部团队可能相当简单。另一方面，如果您在Kubernetes上招聘或培训团队是瓶颈，那么托管的Kubernetes提供商可以立即提供专业知识，减少学习曲线并加速您的部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 3。 &lt;em&gt;我们需要多少控制Kubernetes环境？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的组织需要对网络，安全性，存储和自定义配置进行完全控制，则内部SRE团队可以灵活地为组织的独特需求进行微调Kubernetes。另一方面，托管的kubernetes-as-a-Service提供商可能会从您的团队中删除一些细粒度的控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 4。 &lt;em&gt;我们的正常运行时间，可靠性和性能要求是什么？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;关键任务应用需要高可用性和快速灾难恢复能力。经验丰富的SRE可以优化性能，确保冗余并设置为您的业务量身定制的事件响应协议，但尤其是如果您有一个小型SRE团队，他们总是会呼吁基础架构页面和您将成为所有与基础设施有关的人。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 5。 &lt;em&gt;雇用与外包Kubernetes管理的真正成本是多少？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; SRE的薪水每年的薪水可能超过$ 150万美元，不包括福利，工具，培训和其他运营支持。组织应计算两种方法的总拥有成本（TCO），考虑到：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;薪水，培训和招聘成本&lt;br&gt;基础设施和工具支出&lt;br&gt;停机时间和运营效率低下&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 6。 &lt;em&gt;我们需要多快地部署和扩展Kubernetes？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的团队需要快速部署Kubernetes，则托管服务提供商可以提供配置的环境，以迅速与Kubernetes的最佳实践保持一致，从而减少了大量部署的时间。相比之下，雇用SRE并建立内部Kubernetes团队需要时间进行招聘，入职和基础设施。如果速度很重要，则托管服务提供商可以加速您部署生产工作负载的道路。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 7。 &lt;em&gt;我们需要什么级别的安全性和合规性？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;安全性是Kubernetes环境的主要关注点，因为默认情况下Kubernetes并不安全。如果您的组织在受监管的行业中运营（金融，医疗保健和政府仅举几例），则合规性要求可能需要对配置，访问管理和伐木的更严格的控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;内部SRE团队提供对安全政策的完全控制。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 8。 &lt;em&gt;我们将如何处理正在进行的监视，事件响应和故障排除？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes需要持续监控和主动问题解决。内部SRE团队可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自定义可观察性工具（Prometheus，Grafana等）&lt;br&gt;创建自动警报系统&lt;br&gt;实施自我修复机制&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是内部团队还必须迅速监视，响应和解决基础架构警报。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 9。 &lt;em&gt;我们是否正在计划进行多云或混合云策略？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的组织打算在多个云提供商（AWS，GCP和Azure）或Hybrid-Cloud设置中部署Kubernetes，内部管理Kubernetes，可以灵活地在不同环境中优化工作负载。这也意味着您的内部团队将需要了解每个云服务提供商的详细信息。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 10。 &lt;em&gt;我们的长期Kubernetes路线图是什么？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes一直在成熟，要求组织跟上K8，相关API和附加组件中的升级，安全补丁和功能更改。如果您的业务需要长期控制和深入的Kubernetes专业知识，那么投资内部团队是有道理的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，如果Kubernetes是结束而不是战略重点的手段，则将管理外包给值得信赖的提供商确保您始终可以使用最新的基础架构t需要自己在Kubernetes的进步领先。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;哪种路径适合您？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果Kubernetes是关键任务，需要深入的自定义，并且您的组织有资源来建立和保留内部团队，那么雇用SRE可能是正确的选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您想在卸载Kubernetes复杂性的同时专注于应用程序和业务增长，则托管的Kubernetes-As-a-Service提供商提供了更快，具有成本效益和可扩展的解决方案。该决定取决于您的业务目标，内部专业知识和运营优先级。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ http://www.fairwinds.com/”&gt; fairwinds &lt;/a&gt;管理的kubernetes-as-as-a-service可以加速您的云采用计划，并帮助您的团队帮助您的团队重新制作出色的音乐（或建立出色的音乐和服务，或者是您的热情）。&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Components vs. Containers: Fight?】组件与容器：战斗？</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/09/components-vs-containers-fight/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;WebAssembly components offer a new way to deploy microservices and other applications in cloud native environments. This naturally raises the question: is the upstart component out to replace containers? Or is this one of those situations where the apparent rivals need to learn to work together?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a proper answer, we need to examine the similarities and differences between the two technologies, and then consider how we should understand their respective use-cases—both taken independently or working in tandem.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then we’ll explore how WebAssembly (Wasm) can extend the frontiers of container orchestration across multiple clouds, edges, and devices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But first: what is a WebAssembly component, and how does it differ from a container?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is a WebAssembly component?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WebAssembly is a highly efficient bytecode format that targets a virtual instruction set architecture. When you compile code from the language of your choice to a Wasm binary, you can run that slim binary anywhere you can install a WebAssembly runtime (essentially a tiny virtual machine).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WebAssembly components&lt;/strong&gt; add a standardized layer of specification over the core Wasm format that makes the binaries…&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interoperable&lt;/strong&gt;: Components can import and export functions from other components over language-agnostic interfaces—meaning that a component written in Rust can invoke a function in a component written in Go.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Composable&lt;/strong&gt;: Two or more components can be combined into a single component at build-time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introspectable&lt;/strong&gt;: When a component imports (that is, depends on) functions from another component, that dependency is defined in the binary itself and can be introspected by a system or operator.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;💡&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The WebAssembly Component Model was introduced with&lt;a href=&#34;https://wasi.dev/&#34;&gt; WebAssembly System Interface (WASI) 0.2&lt;/a&gt;. Check out this&lt;a href=&#34;http://wasmcloud.com/blog/wasi-preview-2-officially-launches/&#34;&gt; blog&lt;/a&gt; for a deeper dive, and Luke Wagner’s&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tAACYA1Mwv4&#34;&gt; WasmCon talk&lt;/a&gt; remains a perfect introduction to the concept.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Set alongside containers, a few major distinctions emerge right away:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portability&lt;/strong&gt;: A single component can run anywhere you have a WebAssembly runtime (like Wasmtime) that supports the component specification. You don’t need to build one component per OS per architecture. A single artifact runs everywhere.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Size&lt;/strong&gt;: WebAssembly binaries are small—typically ranging from kilobytes to megabytes—so it’s possible to bin pack more workloads on a given piece of hardware.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication&lt;/strong&gt;: In an orchestrated deployment, containers communicate over network boundaries, and those network communications are often a major source of expense at scale. In any Wasm system that supports components, closely coupled components can be composed together—and in wasmCloud, distributed components can communicate via dynamic runtime links.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc4DXuB__oPOAypFgD4gEP9DlCj57F8DVOwghu3KihrkUWKwOVBxUdtf4GCY6pXV8dNdqntEhgZ4BYbkwam-KyvyxBpwt8MLy_4h9ROII814lwaktMTg8u_yGa_79q2i8AOUO_9lw?key=gcY2NLbqwUvGy4pTEXLDXDeT&#34; alt=&#34;containers vs. components&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Containers versus components by the numbers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At a high level, perhaps the most important distinction is that &lt;strong&gt;components abstract the application logic alone&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even the slimmest distro-less base image includes a bare minimum of libraries that sit between the application and the kernel, and often container images contain much, much more in the way of libraries and utilities. This is great when you want to, say, spin up a standard developer environment in a devcontainer. That’s a use-case that is perfect for containers and doesn’t make sense for components today. Containers are perfect for portable, isolated, reproducible environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Components, by contrast, are the right level of abstraction for applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Epochs of abstraction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can think of the timeline of software deployment as epochs of progressive abstraction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcL9YnKs3m7XGk_5HCNeHreJaDbH9eVvt_g8kWLDQg-9j4aGuQL8MXYpyxvGYSGXz0ohz7Qt1hbUVCfiAxAIRqfIcM_SLzHSZ4KocqXf9rp9YKWIVfpHDhNIibsdgvvMf2ul_f_tg?key=gcY2NLbqwUvGy4pTEXLDXDeT&#34; alt=&#34;timeline of software deployment&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Epochs of abstraction&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started with tightly coupled, monolithic systems. Virtual machines decoupled operating systems from specific hardware, reducing reliance on data centers. Containers emerged as the next level of abstraction, and container orchestrators helped run applications more flexibly and efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The next layer of abstraction, WebAssembly components, sees applications as collections of interchangeable components, linked at runtime. When built with components, applications are tiny, portable, and polyglot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Compared to virtual machines, containers introduced an improvement in efficiency, but there are some significant limitations when it comes to orchestrating containers at-scale and on the edge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orchestrating efficiency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes made the great lift-and-shift to the cloud possible, and is essential for abstracting infrastructure, but &lt;strong&gt;isn’t great for running applications without a bunch of additional work&lt;/strong&gt;. The traditional approach to running containerized applications on Kubernetes faces some significant limitations:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edge deployments: &lt;/strong&gt;Running containers at the edge with Kubernetes is challenging, even with lightweight distributions. The tiniest container is a few MBs, so available resources are occupied simply getting Kubernetes to work.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resource efficiency and the price of the cold start problem: &lt;/strong&gt;Over 80% of container spend is on idle infrastructure (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.datadoghq.com/state-of-cloud-security/&#34;&gt;DataDog 2024 State of Cloud&lt;/a&gt;). Containerized applications need containers to run persistently to address spikes in traffic, and to meet standard latency expectations. As the statistics show, keeping ‘just in case’ instances running is expensive.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since components are able to start in milliseconds, they face no such challenges. The first—and likely most common—reason people want to run components is that they dramatically improve resource efficiency wherever there is a reliance on Kubernetes. With components, teams can write code in the language of their choice and run it anywhere, including in places where even containers are impractical.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If an organization is already using Kubernetes, it’s easy to run components on existing clusters with &lt;strong&gt;wasmCloud&lt;/strong&gt;, a WebAssembly orchestrator that runs distributed Wasm applications at scale, either standalone or on Kubernetes itself.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In fact, wasmCloud can help extend Kubernetes to tackle traditional challenge areas like multi-cloud and edges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WebAssembly + Kubernetes: Cloud native’s new tag team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In an early wasmCloud use case,&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2022/11/17/better-together-a-kubernetes-and-wasm-case-study/&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Adobe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; capitalized on wasmCloud to prove it could make its Kubernetes estate more efficient. The company has continued to expand its use of Wasm:&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/live/B1Q_Xx5i6Ek?feature=shared&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Engineers from Adobe and Akamai&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; work with wasmCloud to run WebAssembly across cloud services, Kubernetes clusters, and edges.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In industry, &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/fQdkNGZqYZA?feature=shared&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MachineMetrics&lt;/strong&gt; uses wasmCloud&lt;/a&gt; to move platform capabilities across edges and clouds with dynamic fault-tolerance. In telecoms, the&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/01/05/bringing-webassembly-to-telecoms-with-cncf-wasmcloud/&#34;&gt; WebAssembly Canvas TM Forum Catalyst Project&lt;/a&gt; has proved the value of &lt;strong&gt;replacing&lt;/strong&gt; Kubernetes with wasmCloud in managing its estate of open APIs, and is now reviewing how wasmCloud can work together with Kubernetes to drive efficiencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;wasmCloud hosts can run on a Kubernetes cluster or external to it: bare metal, VMs, IoT devices, or pretty much anywhere you want. Regardless of where hosts are running, they can be connected. Kubernetes handles infrastructure management by orchestrating wasmCloud hosts, while wasmCloud handles application-level operations with full support for component capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;💡&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to try running WebAssembly components on a local kind cluster? See &lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.com/docs/deployment/k8s/&#34;&gt;wasmCloud’s Kubernetes guide&lt;/a&gt; for simple instructions that should take about 5 minutes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come for the efficiency, stay for the flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This separation of concerns—containers and Kubernetes for infrastructure, components and wasmCloud for applications—means that WebAssembly runtime operations are unconstrained by container-centric frameworks and abstractions; wasmCloud can extend Kubernetes to provide new hybrid compute options and expand the frontiers of computing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is where Wasm’s paradigm-shifting superpowers come into play. There are serious cost savings to be had by using Wasm for applications, but by adopting wasmCloud, we avoid lock-in to proprietary systems, engineers can use their existing cloud native infrastructure, and we can build with the most powerful and singular features of the WebAssembly &lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.com/docs/concepts/components&#34;&gt;component model&lt;/a&gt;—composability and standards-based interoperability. When all is said and done,&amp;nbsp; containers and components aren’t rivals at all, but are instead a powerful, flexible team for combating infrastructure inefficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about running WebAssembly components, wasmCloud, and running Wasm on Kubernetes, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.wasmcloud.com/&#34;&gt;wasmCloud Slack&lt;/a&gt; or join a &lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.com/community/&#34;&gt;weekly wasmCloud community meeting&lt;/a&gt;. Hope to see you there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; WebAssembly组件提供了一种在云本机环境中部署微服务和其他应用程序的新方法。这自然提出了一个问题：替换容器的新贵组件是否耗尽？还是这是明显竞争对手需要学习一起工作的情况之一？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了做出适当的答案，我们需要检查两种技术之间的相似性和差异，然后考虑我们应该如何理解它们各自的用例（都独立拍摄或串联工作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，我们将探讨WebAssembly（WASM）如何将容器编排的前沿跨多个云，边缘和设备扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但首先：什么是WebAssembly组件，它与容器有何不同？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是WebAssembly组件？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; WebAssembly是一种高效的字节码格式，它针对虚拟指令集体系结构。当您将代码从您选择的语言中编译为WASM二进制文件时，您可以在可以安装WebAssembly运行时运行该纤细的二进制文件（本质上是微型虚拟机）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; WebAssembly组件&lt;/strong&gt;在核心WASM格式上添加标准化的规范层，该格式使二进制文件…&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可互操作&lt;/strong&gt;：组件可以从其他组件中导入和导出语言界面界面的函数，这意味着用Rust编写的组件可以在GO中写入的组件中调用一个函数。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;综合&lt;/strong&gt;：可以将两个或多个组件合并为一个组件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;内省&lt;/strong&gt;：当组件导入（即，取决于）来自另一个组件的函数时，该依赖性是在二进制本身中定义的，并且可以由系统或操作员进行内置。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;💡&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt; WebAssembly组件模型是用&lt;a href =“ https://wasi.dev/”&gt; WebAssembly System Interface（wasi）0.2 &lt;/a&gt;引入的。请查看此&lt;a href =“ http://wasmcloud.com/blog/wasi-preview-2-c--c--in-launches/”&gt; Blog &lt;/a&gt;进行更深入的潜水，Luke Wagner的&lt;a href =”概念。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与容器旁边设置，立即出现了一些主要区别：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可移植性&lt;/strong&gt;：单个组件可以在您拥有支持组件规范的WebAssembly运行时（例如WASMTIME）运行。您不需要每个OS每个OS构建一个组件。一个人工制品无处不在。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;尺寸&lt;/strong&gt;：Websembly二进制文件很小 - 从千数到兆字节的范围很小，因此可以在给定的硬件上包装更多的工作负载。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;交流&lt;/strong&gt;：在兽人中部署的部署，在网络边界上进行通信的容器，这些网络通信通常是大规模支出的主要来源。在支持组件的任何WASM系统中，都可以将密切耦合的组件组合在一起 - 在WasmCloud，分布式组件可以通过动态运行时链接进行通信。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxc4dxub__opoaypfgd4gep9dlcj57f8dvowghu3kihrkihrkihrkuwkwovbxudtf4 GCY6PXV8DNDQNTEHGZ4BYBKWAM-KYVYXBPWT8MLY_4H9ROII814LWAKTMTG8U_YGA_YGA_YGA_79Q2I8AOUO_9LW？ alt =“容器vs.组件” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;容器与数字的组件&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在高水平上，也许最重要的区别是&lt;strong&gt;组件仅抽象应用程序逻辑&lt;/strong&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使是最微小的无分布的基本图像，也包括坐在应用程序和内核之间的最少库，并且通常在库和实用程序的方式上包含更多的容器图像。当您想在Devcontainer中旋转标准开发人员环境时，这很棒。这是一个非常适合容器的用例，对于当今的组件却没有意义。容器非常适合便携式，隔离，可再现的环境。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;相比之下，&lt;p&gt;组件是应用程序的正确水平。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;抽象的时代&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以将软件部署的时间表视为渐进抽象的时代。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcl9ynks3m7xgk_5hcnehrejadbh9evvt_g8kwldqg-9j4j4aguql8mxypy xvgysgxz0ohz7qt1hbuvcfiaxairqficm_slzhsz4kocqxf9rp9rp9ykwivffphdhniibsdgvvvvvmf2ul_f_tg？ alt =“软件部署的时间表” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;抽象的时代&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们从紧密耦合的整体系统开始。虚拟机从特定硬件中解开操作系统，从而降低了对数据中心的依赖。容器作为下一个抽象级别出现，并且容器编排者帮助更灵活，更有效地运行应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下一层抽象，WebAssembly组件，将应用程序视为在运行时链接的可互换组件的集合。当使用组件构建时，应用程序很小，便携式和多面体。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与虚拟机相比，容器引入了提高效率的提高，但是在安排容器处于尺度和边缘方面存在一些显着限制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-tearing”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;精心策划效率&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes使云到云的巨大移动可能是可能的，对于抽象基础架构至关重要，但&lt;strong&gt;如果没有其他工作&lt;/strong&gt;，对于运行应用程序而言并不是很好。在Kubernetes上运行集装箱应用程序的传统方法面临一些重大局限性：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;边缘部署：&lt;/strong&gt;在带有kubernetes的边缘运行容器，即使使用轻巧的分布也很具有挑战性。最小的容器是几个MB，因此可用的资源被占用只是让Kubernetes工作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;资源效率和冷启动问题的价格：&lt;/strong&gt;超过80％的集装箱支出是在空闲基础架构上（&lt;a href =“ https://www.datadoghq.com/state-of-cloud-security/”&gt; datadog 2024云&lt;/a&gt;）。容器化的应用程序需要容器才能持续运行以解决流量中的峰值，并满足标准的延迟期望。正如统计数据所示，保持“以防万一”的情况很昂贵。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于组件能够以毫秒的速度开始，因此他们没有面临此类挑战。人们想要运行组件的第一个（也是最常见的季节）是，无论依赖Kubernetes，他们都会显着提高资源效率。借助组件，团队可以用自己选择的语言编写代码，并在任何地方运行它，包括在容器不切实际的地方。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果组织已经在使用Kubernetes，则可以很容易地使用&lt;strong&gt; WasmCloud &lt;/strong&gt;在现有群集上运行组件，这是一种websembly编排，可以按独立或Kubernetes本身运行分布式WASM应用程序。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;实际上，WasmCloud可以帮助扩展Kubernetes，以应对传统挑战领域，例如多云和边缘。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In an early wasmCloud use case,&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2022/11/17/better-together-a-kubernetes-and-wasm-case-study/&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Adobe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; capitalized on wasmCloud to prove it could make its Kubernetes estate more efficient. The company has continued to expand its use of Wasm:&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/live/B1Q_Xx5i6Ek?feature=shared&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Engineers from Adob​​e and Akamai&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; work with wasmCloud to run WebAssembly across cloud services, Kubernetes clusters, and edges. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在行业中，&lt;a href =“ https://youtu.be/fqdkngzqyza?feature=shared”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; MachineMetrics &lt;/strong&gt;使用WasmCloud &lt;/a&gt;用动态断层率将平台跨越边缘和云移动平台能力。在电信中，&lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/01/05/bringing-webassembly-to-telecoms-with-with-with-with-cncf-wasmcloud/&gt;管理其开放式API的财产，现在正在审查Wasmcloud如何与Kubernetes合作以提高效率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; wasmcloud hosTS可以在Kubernetes群集或外部运行：裸机，VM，IoT设备或几乎任何您想要的地方。无论主机在哪里运行，都可以连接。 Kubernetes通过协调WasmCloud主机来处理基础架构管理，而WasmCloud处理应用程序级操作，并全力支持组件功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;💡&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;是否想尝试在本地类型集群上运行WebAssembly组件？请参阅&lt;a href =“ https://wasmcloud.com/docs/deployment/k8s/”&gt; Wasmcloud的Kubernetes指南&lt;/a&gt;，请使用大约5分钟的简单说明。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;来提高效率，保持灵活性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种关注点的分离 - 用于基础架构，组件和wasmcloud应用程序的关键和kubernetes，webAssembly运行时操作不受以容器为中心的框架和抽象来限制的。 WasmCloud可以扩展Kubernetes来提供新的混合计算选项并扩展计算的前沿。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是Wasm的范式转移超级大国发挥作用的地方。通过使用WASM进行应用，可以节省大量成本，但是通过使用WasmCloud，我们避免锁定专有系统，工程师可以使用其现有的云本机基础架构，我们可以使用WebAssembly的最强大和最奇异的特征&lt;a href &lt;a href &lt;a href =“基于标准的互操作性。说完一切后，容器和组件根本不是竞争对手，而是一个强大，灵活的团队，用于打击基础设施效率低下。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关运行WebAssembly组件，WasmCloud和在Kubernetes上运行WASM的更多信息，请查看&lt;a href =“ https：//slack.wasmcloud.com/”&gt; wasmcloud slack &lt;/a&gt;或加入a &lt;a href =“希望在那里见到你！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubestronaut in Orbit: Iliyan Petkov】轨道上的kubestronaut：iliyan petkov</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/08/kubestronaut-in-orbit-iliyan-petkov/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1200&#34; height=&#34;630&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Kubestronaut - Illiyan Petkov&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-129184&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem.jpg 1200w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-300x158.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-1024x538.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-388x204.jpg 388w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-776x408.jpg 776w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-900x473.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-381x200.jpg 381w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-762x400.jpg 762w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-590x310.jpg 590w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Copy-of-Copy-of-Copy-of-Kubestronaut-willem-1180x620.jpg 1180w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get to know Iliyan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;His fascination with computers and electronics began early, sparked by his father and fueled by various games and sci-fi movies. Over the years, he developed a passion for open-source technologies, system administration, DevOps, programming, and sharing knowledge through teaching. This journey naturally led him to container technology and Kubernetes, becoming one of the first Kubestronauts in Bulgaria and Eastern Europe. In 2022, together with a close friend and fellow Kubestronaut, he founded a company driven by a shared vision of knowledge sharing, engineering excellence, and innovation. In addition to teaching classes on Kubernetes and various cloud technologies, he actively engages in project work and consulting, guiding organizations through their cloud native journeys. He believes in the power of community and regularly participates in meetups and conferences, both as an attendee and occasionally as a speaker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When did you get started with Kubernetes and/or cloud native? What was your first project?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While I had been working with containers for some time, I began experimenting with Kubernetes in 2019. My first major Kubernetes project came in 2020, when I led a small team tasked with building a large-scale internal cloud platform based on Kubernetes. This project presented numerous challenges related to scalability and reliability, but it was an invaluable learning experience that truly ignited my passion for Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the primary CNCF projects you work on or use today? What projects have you enjoyed the most in your career?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Depending on the specific use case and challenge, I frequently leverage multiple projects from the Kubernetes ecosystem. Beyond Kubernetes itself, I primarily use Cilium as my CNI solution, Harbor for container image registry management, and Prometheus paired with Grafana for comprehensive monitoring and alerting. I also regularly work with ExternalDNS, Cert-Manager, OPA, Helm, OpenEBS, and Longhorn. The project I enjoy the most is Kubernetes. It is vibrant and dynamic, constantly adapting to the latest trends and industry challenges, and it has an incredible community around it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How have the certs or CNCF helped you in your career?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I enjoy learning new technologies and taking exams, though not necessarily to advance my career. I often use the goal of passing a certification as an “excuse” to spend more time diving into a new project or gaining a deeper understanding of technology that interests me. In a way, I’ve come full circle—from taking Kubernetes-related exams to assisting with beta tests of new exams like KCNA and KCSA, and eventually volunteering to help develop new CNCF exams. I also appreciate the social aspect of certifications, as they allow me to meet like-minded people. Through the CNCF Kubestronaut program, we’ve built a small community that meets periodically in person. From a practical standpoint, preparing for and taking exams helps me stay current with the latest trends and enables me to support others in passing their certifications. Additionally, my certifications help build trust and confidence in my business partners, who rely on me to provide professional support for their projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are some other books/sites/courses you recommend for people who want to work with k8s?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Kubernetes documentation is excellent—huge kudos to all contributors and tech writers! Although I enjoy reading books, I rarely have the time to finish them cover to cover. Instead, I often watch YouTube recordings of talks from conferences like KubeCon, as well as video training on platforms such as Udemy. Early in my Kubernetes journey, the outstanding trainings by Mumshad Mannambeth for the CKA and CKAD, along with the excellent CKS course by Kim Wüstkamp (founder of killer.sh), which is now also freely available on YouTube, were incredibly helpful to me. I highly recommend attending conferences and local community meetups, as they provide great opportunities to connect with and learn from leading experts. Additionally, the CNCF Slack community has channels for certification-related discussions, CNCF projects, and initiatives where I have picked up many valuable tips and tricks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you do in your free time?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Outside of work, I enjoy training in Aikido, mountain biking, running, and exploring new places with my family. I also enjoy tinkering with electronics, home automation, and IoT, trying out new open-source projects, and furthering my curiosity in AI/ML.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What would you tell someone who is just starting their K8s certification journey? Any tips or tricks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I like to approach Kubernetes certifications with a positive mindset, viewing them as challenges to solve within a limited timeframe. Maintaining a positive attitude significantly reduces stress during the exam. Of course, failure is always a possibility, but I see it as a valuable learning opportunity to identify and address knowledge gaps before taking advantage of the free retake offered with Kubernetes exams. Good preparation before the exams is essential. I consistently stay updated with the latest exam curriculum, as the exams evolve alongside the technology. The CNCF’s official exam tips and tricks guide, along with its documentation, are invaluable resources. Additionally, numerous blog posts provide practical advice for optimizing productivity during the exam. The more you practice, the more confident you will become. Fortunately, setting up Kubernetes environments for practice is incredibly easy using Kind or Minikube on your local machine (or even a Raspberry Pi), or by leveraging cloud-based platforms like Killercoda and killer.sh, which provide realistic lab scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today the cloud native ecosystem is way more than Kubernetes. Do you plan to get other cloud native certifications from the CNCF?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Absolutely! This year, I plan to pursue certifications in Argo, Cilium, Istio, Kyverno, and OpenTelemetry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What else would you like to share in this feature?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want to express my gratitude to the CNCF community and everyone who has supported me along my journey. Sharing knowledge and helping one another is what makes this community truly special! Learning is not a one-time challenge, but an ongoing process. As the famous quote goes: “Stay hungry. Stay foolish.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 1200” height =“ 630” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/wploads/uploads/uploads/uploads/255/255/255/25/copy-copy-copy--copy-------- alt =“ kubestronaut-Illiyan Petkov” class =“ WP-Image-129184” Srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/2025/04/copy-opopy-opopy-of-copy-of-copy-of-copy-of-copy-of-copy-of-kubestronaut-willem.jpqudg gylem.jp120000w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-op-opopy-copy-op-copy-of-copy-opopy-of-copy-of--kubestronaut-willem-300x158.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-op-copy-copy-of-copy-of-copy-copy-opy-of-kubestronaut-willem-1024x538.jpg 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-op-copy-copy-op-copy-of-copy-copy-opy-of-kubestronaut-willem-768x403.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-opy-copy-copy-copy-of-copy-op-copy-op-copy-of--kubestronaut-willem-194x102.jpg 194w，194w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-op-copy-copy-op-copy-of-copy-copy-op-copy-of--kubestronaut-willem-388x204.jpg 388w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-op-copy-copy-of-copy-of-copy-copy-opy-of-kubestronaut-willem-776x408.jpg 776w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-op-copy-copy-op-copy-of-copy-opopy-op-copy-of--kubestronaut-willem-900x473.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-oppopy-of-copy-op-copy-of-copy-copy-opy-of-copy-of--kubestronaut-willem-381x200.jpg 381W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-opy-op-copy-op-copy-of-copy-of-copy-opy-of-qopy-of-kubestronaut-willem-762x400.jpg 762w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-op-copy-copy-op-copy-of-copy-copy-opy-of-copy-of-kubestronaut-willem-590x310.jpg 590w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/copy-oppopy-ob-copy-op-copy-of-copy-opopy-op-copy-of--kubestronaut-willem-1180x620.jpg 1180w 1180w“ simbo =” size =“ auto，（max-width：max-width：1200px）100vw，1200vw，120000px” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他对计算机和电子产品的着迷始于他的父亲，并受到各种游戏和科幻电影的推动。多年来，他对开源技术，系统管理，DevOps，编程以及通过教学共享知识产生了热情。这次旅程自然会使他进入集装箱技术和库伯纳泰，成为保加利亚和东欧的最早的库布斯特隆人之一。 2022年，他与一位密友和Kubestronaut同胞一起成立了一家公司，该公司由知识共享，卓越工程和创新的共同愿景驱动。除了教授有关Kubernetes和各种云技术的课程外，他还积极从事项目工作和咨询，并通过其云土著旅行指导组织。他相信社区的力量，并定期作为与会者和偶尔作为演讲者参加聚会和会议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您什么时候开始使用Kubernetes和/或Cloud Native？您的第一个项目是什么？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我使用集装箱工作了一段时间时，我于2019年开始尝试Kubernetes。我的第一个主要Kubernetes项目是在2020年，当时我领导了一个小TEAM的任务是建立基于Kubernetes的大规模内部云平台。该项目提出了许多与可伸缩性和可靠性有关的挑战，但这是一种无价的学习经历，真正激发了我对Kubernetes的热情。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您今天从事或使用的主要CNCF项目是什么？您在职业生涯中最喜欢哪些项目？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据特定用例和挑战，我经常利用Kubernetes生态系统的多个项目。除了Kubernetes本身之外，我主要使用Cilium作为CNI解决方案，用于容器图像注册表的Harbor以及Prometheus与Grafana配对，以进行全面的监控和警报。我还定期与外部DNS，CERT-MANAGER，OPA，HELM，OPENEBS和LONGHORN合作。我最喜欢的项目是Kubernetes。它充满活力和充满活力，不断地适应最新趋势和行业挑战，并且周围有一个令人难以置信的社区。&lt;/​​p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;证书或CNCF在您的职业生涯中如何帮助您？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我喜欢学习新技术并参加考试，尽管不一定是为了促进我的职业生涯。我经常以通过认证作为“借口”的目标，花更多的时间潜入一个新项目或对使我感兴趣的技术有更深入的了解。从某种意义上说，我从参加Kubernetes相关的考试到协助KCNA和KCSA等新考试的Beta测试，并最终自愿提供帮助开发新的CNCF考试的新考试。我也感谢认证的社会方面，因为它们使我能够结识志趣相投的人。通过CNCF Kubestronaut计划，我们建立了一个小型社区，该社区定期亲自开会。从实际的角度来看，准备和参加考试可以帮助我保持最新趋势，使我能够支持他人通过认证。此外，我的认证有助于建立对我的业务合作伙伴的信任和信心，他们依靠我为他们的项目提供专业支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您建议想要与K8合作的人推荐哪些其他书籍/网站/课程？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubernetes文档非常出色，这对所有贡献者和技术作家都很荣幸！尽管我喜欢阅读书籍，但我很少有时间完成掩护。取而代之的是，我经常观看诸如Kubecon之类的会议的YouTube录音以及Udemy等平台上的视频培训。在我的Kubernetes之旅的早期，Mumshad Mannambeth为CKA和CKAD提供的出色培训以及KimWüstkamp的出色CKS课程（Killer.sh的创始人）（现在在YouTube上也可以在YouTube上免费获得），对我非常有用。我强烈建议参加会议和当地社区聚会，因为它们提供了与之建立联系的绝佳机会D向领先的专家学习。此外，CNCF Slack社区还提供与认证有关的讨论，CNCF项目以及我挑选了许多宝贵的技巧和技巧的渠道。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您在空闲时间做什么？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在工作之外，我喜欢与家人一起在Aikido，山地自行车，跑步，跑步和探索新地方的培训。我也喜欢修补电子，家庭自动化和物联网，尝试新的开源项目，并在AI/ML中提高好奇心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您会告诉一个刚刚开始K8S认证旅程的人吗？有任何技巧或技巧吗？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我喜欢以积极的心态来对待Kubernetes认证，将其视为在有限的时间范围内解决的挑战。保持积极的态度会大大减轻考试期间的压力。当然，失败始终是一种可能性，但我认为这是一个宝贵的学习机会，可以在利用Kubernetes考试提供的免费retake之前识别和解决知识差距。考试前的良好准备是必不可少的。随着考试随着技术的发展，我一直在最新的考试课程中进行更新。 CNCF的官方考试技巧指南及其文档是宝贵的资源。此外，许多博客文章提供了实用建议，以优化考试期间的生产力。您练习的次数越多，您就会变得越有信心。幸运的是，在本地机器（甚至是覆盆子PI）上使用善良或Minikube设置Kubernetes练习非常容易，或者通过利用基于云的平台（例如Killercoda and Killer.sh）提供现实的实验室场景。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;如今，云本机生态系统比kubernetes更具。您是否打算从CNCF获得其他云本机认证？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;绝对！今年，我计划在Argo，Cilium，Istio，Kyverno和Opentelemetry中获得认证。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您还想在此功能中分享什么？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我想对CNCF社区以及在旅途中支持我的每个人表示感谢。分享知识并互相帮助的是使这个社区真正与众不同的原因！学习不是一次性的挑战，而是一个持续的过程。正如著名的名言所说：“保持饥饿。保持愚蠢。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Managing multi-line logs with Fluent Bit and Python】使用Fluent lit和Python管理多行日志</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/08/managing-multi-line-logs-with-fluent-bit-and-python/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In this blog you will learn about:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What makes multi-line logs challenging&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to configure a multi-line parser in Fluent Bit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Choosing the right parsing approach&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logs are essential for monitoring and debugging applications, but not all logs are created equal. While most logs follow a simple line-by-line format, others span multiple lines to improve readability. However, when mixed with other logs, these multi-line log entries can become challenging to parse and analyze. Important details can get lost in the noise without proper handling, making troubleshooting more time-consuming.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address this challenge, Fluent Bit allows the consolidation of multi-line logs into a single structured entry. In this post, we’ll explore the complexities of multi-line logging, why it matters, and how to configure &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.chronosphere.io/pipeline-data/plugins/source-plugins/fluent-bit?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt; to capture and manage these logs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Challenges with multi-line logs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why managing multi-line logs is challenging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unlike standard single-line &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/audit-log-definition-guide/&#34;&gt;log &lt;/a&gt;entries, multi-line logs such as stack traces span multiple lines, making them harder to process and analyze.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/your-introduction-to-log-collection/&#34;&gt;log&lt;/a&gt; processors treat each line separately, making debugging difficult, which causes critical information to become fragmented. This affects readability and makes troubleshooting harder since logs from various sources can mix, making it difficult to trace the full context of an error.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This fragmentation also makes it harder to filter, search, and correlate logs in monitoring tools. For example, in Elasticsearch, or any other logging platform, searching for a specific error message may return incomplete results because the full stack trace is split across multiple entries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example: Python stack trace logs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s an example of a typical Python exception log. When an exception occurs, Python outputs a detailed trace spanning multiple lines, showing where the error originated and how it propagated through the code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;2025-02-20 22:26:09,444 - ERROR - An error occurred:&#xA;Traceback (most recent call last):&#xA;  File &#34;/Users/final.py&#34;, line 25, in generate_errors&#xA;    5 / 0  # Intentional ZeroDivisionError&#xA;ZeroDivisionError: division by zero&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each line would be treated as a separate log entry without proper multi-line log handling. In the image below, you can see how each stack trace line appears as an individual log entry.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeHsGE0iSAQETd9lUQvCgEdjeong5o1eHD7ahho4aT1NV5hOYC31YOgkGDoD1NyKwJ8XKrpzjzZGqZcVxlun117XcCgNnTMPsuwErBKCez3rr1rssuRp25C1SVgrQcfDHDLwoWhwA?key=vEb2d48KyCGYVuiF_ixCwSJK&#34; alt=&#34;individual log entries&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address this, we need a way to group related lines into a single log entry. The solution? Fluent Bit &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/administration/configuring-fluent-bit/multiline-parsing&#34;&gt;Multi line Parser&lt;/a&gt; allows us to merge multi-line logs based on common patterns.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the next section, we’ll explore how to configure&lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt; Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt; to handle multi-line logs effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-line parsing in Fluent Bit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Parsing is the process of converting unstructured or raw text data into a structured format that is easier to process and analyze.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Fluent Bit, a multi-line parser is a component that processes log messages spread across multiple lines, concatenating them into a single log entry based on specific rules defined by regular expressions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, the parser uses state and regex rules to detect the start of a multi-line message and then continues to capture subsequent lines that are part of the same message.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are two ways to configure a multi-line parser:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Built-in Multi-line Parser:&lt;/strong&gt; Without any extra configuration,&lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit-academy/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt; Fluent Bit &lt;/a&gt;exposes certain pre-configured parsers (built-in) to solve specific multi-line parser cases like &lt;strong&gt;CRI, Python, Go, Docker, and Java&lt;/strong&gt;. Refer to this &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/fluent/fluent-bit/blob/master/conf/parsers.conf&#34;&gt;document&lt;/a&gt; to preview the built-in parser configuration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configurable Multi-line Parser:&lt;/strong&gt; In addition to the built-in parsers listed above, you can define your own multi-line parsers with your rules through the configuration files.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To know more about multi-line parsers, refer to this&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/administration/configuring-fluent-bit/multiline-parsing&#34;&gt; documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parsing multi-line logs: Input stage vs. filter stage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When working with multi-line log parsing in &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/fluent-bit-vs-fluentd/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt;, you have two primary options for where to handle the concatenation of related log lines: at the &lt;strong&gt;input stage&lt;/strong&gt; or the &lt;strong&gt;filter stage&lt;/strong&gt;. Each approach has distinct characteristics and performance implications. Let’s explore both.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc1bdDr41QtgW2yPWZ1mStb9w43sq2U-LJN5c4jwv3y19Uksk3QojDdfSnUhJTToeFEgDdPV8rKdjNbnf8gyHMsR4M0DjSwHH5qcFGI_Cg0ePZiB-p4DM3UV4jSXcbftHDh5xuK?key=vEb2d48KyCGYVuiF_ixCwSJK&#34; alt=&#34;architecture&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Input stage multi-line parsing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the input stage, multi-line parsing is applied immediately after the data is ingested—for example, when using the tail input plugin to read log files. Here, the parser’s rules are used to group log lines that belong to the same context into a single record before any further processing occurs. This method ensures that the log’s complete structure is preserved from the moment of ingestion, making it ideal for scenarios where downstream processing (e.g., filtering, routing, or output formatting) depends on having the full log entry intact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A key advantage of this approach is performance. Since concatenation happens as the log file is being read, it avoids the overhead of buffering and reprocessing later in the pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Filter stage multi-line parsing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, the &lt;strong&gt;multi-line filter&lt;/strong&gt; can be used to concatenate messages later in the pipeline. This filter is designed to reunite log lines that belong to a single context—like stack traces or multi-line application logs—but were split into separate records during ingestion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, this approach comes with some nuances:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance Consideration:&lt;/strong&gt; Concatenating logs at the filter stage is less efficient than at the input stage. The Fluent Bit documentation recommends using the tail plugin’s multi-line support for log files whenever possible, as it processes logs during ingestion rather than after.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buffering Behavior:&lt;/strong&gt; When the Buffer option is enabled, the filter holds messages until they’re fully concatenated or a timeout is reached. Without buffering, it processes one chunk at a time, which may not work well for inputs that send multi-line messages across separate chunks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pipeline Positioning:&lt;/strong&gt; The multi-line filter should be the first filter in your pipeline. Since it re-emits concatenated records to the pipeline’s head, any filters placed before it will process the logs twice—once before concatenation and once after. The filter ignores its own re-emitted records, but other filters won’t.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Single Filter Limitation:&lt;/strong&gt; You can’t configure multiple multi-line filters with overlapping tags, as this creates an infinite loop. Instead, use a single filter with a comma-separated list of parsers (e.g., multiline.parser = parser1,parser2).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choosing the right approach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use &lt;strong&gt;input stage parsing&lt;/strong&gt; (e.g., via tail) for log files or containerized logs where performance is critical, and the log structure is known at ingestion time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use &lt;strong&gt;filter stage parsing&lt;/strong&gt; when logs are ingested as separate records (e.g., via a network input) and need to be recombined later or when you need flexibility to apply parsing rules after initial processing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multi-line logs are helpful for debugging but can complicate analysis if not managed properly. Fluent Bit provides a robust solution by consolidating these logs into single, structured entries with its multi-line parser, whether used at the input or filter stage. By selecting the right approach—input for performance or filter for flexibility—you can streamline troubleshooting and ensure critical details remain intact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;This blog is the first in a two-part series. In the next installment we discuss in detail &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/multiline-builtin-parsers-fluent-bit/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;how to handle multi-line with built-in parsers in Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在此博客中，您将了解：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;是什么使多行日志具有挑战性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如何在Fluent位配置多行解析器&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;选择正确的解析方法&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;日志对于监视和调试应用程序至关重要，但并非所有日志都相等。尽管大多数日志都遵循简单的逐线格式，但其他日志却涵盖了多行以提高可读性。但是，当与其他日志混合时，这些多行日志条目可能会变得具有挑战性的解析和分析。重要的细节可能会在噪音中丢失而无需进行适当的处​​理，从而使故障排除更加耗时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了应对这一挑战，Fluent位允许将多线日志整合到单个结构化条目中。 In this post, we’ll explore the complexities of multi-line logging, why it matters, and how to configure &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.chronosphere.io/pipeline-data/plugins/source-plugins/fluent-bit?utm_source=CNCF&amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt; to capture and manage these日志。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;多行日志&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么管理多行日志&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与标准单行&lt;a href =“ https://chronosphere.io/lealen/audit-log-definition-guide/”&gt; log &lt;/a&gt;条目，多线日志（例如堆栈痕迹）跨越多行，使它们更难处理和分析。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多&lt;a href =“ https://chrronosphere.io/learn/your-indroduction-to-log-collection/”&gt; log &lt;/a&gt;处理器分别处理每条线，使调试变得困难，这会导致关键信息变得分散。这会影响可读性并使故障排除更加困难，因为来自各种来源的日志可能会混合，因此很难追踪错误的完整上下文。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种碎片也使在监视工具中过滤，搜索和关联日志变得更加困难。例如，在Elasticsearch或任何其他记录平台中，搜索特定错误消息可能会返回不完整的结果，因为完整的堆栈跟踪跨多个条目分开。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是典型的Python异常日志的示例。当发生异常时，Python输出了详细的跟踪跨越多行，显示了错误的起源以及如何通过代码传播。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; 2025-02-20 22：26：09,444-错误 - 发生错误：&#xA;Trackback（最近的最新电话）：&#xA;  文件“/users/final.py”，第25行，在generate_errors中&#xA;    5/0＃故意ZerodivisionError&#xA;ZerodivisionError：零部门&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每行将被视为单独的日志条目，而无需正确的多行日志处理。在下图中，您可以看到每个S大头钉跟踪线显示为单个日志条目。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxehsge0isaqetd9luqvcggedjeong5o1ehd7ahho4ho4ho4at1nv5hoyc31yogkg dod1nykwj8xkrpzjzzgqzcvxlun117xccgnntmpsuwerbkcez3rr1rssurp25c1svgrqcfdhdlwowhwa？ alt =“单个日志条目” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要解决这个问题，我们需要一种将相关行分组到单个日志条目中的方法。解决方案？流利的位&lt;a href =“ https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/administration/configuring-fluent-bit/multililine-parsing”&gt;多线解析器&lt;/a&gt;允许我们允许我们基于共同模式合并多线日志。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在下一节中，我们将探讨如何配置&lt;a href =“ https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit/?utm_source=cncf&amp;utm_medium = sponsordsponsord+content”&gt; fluent &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;流利位&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;的多行解析&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;解析是将非结构化或原始文本数据转换为易于处理和分析的结构化格式的过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Fluent位中，多行解析器是一个组件，该组件会处理分布在多行中的日志消息，将它们基于正则表达式定义的特定规则将它们连接到单个日志条目中。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，解析器使用状态和正则规则来检测多行消息的开始，然后继续捕获是同一消息的一部分的后续行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有两种配置多行解析器的方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Built-in Multi-line Parser:&lt;/strong&gt; Without any extra configuration,&lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit-academy/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt; Fluent Bit &lt;/a&gt;exposes certain pre-configured parsers (built-in) to solve specific multi-line parser &lt;strong&gt; CRI，Python，Go，Docker和Java等案例&lt;/strong&gt;。请参阅此&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/fluent/fluent/fluent-bit/blob/master/conf/conf/parsers.conf”&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;预览内置的parser配置。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可配置的多行解析器：&lt;/strong&gt;除了上面列出的内置解析器外，您还可以通过配置文件定义自己的多行解析器。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关多行解析器的更多信息，请参阅此&lt;a href =“ https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/manual/administration/configuring-fluent-bit/multiline-parsing-”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href =“ https://chronosphere.io/learn/learn/learn/learn/learn/learn/learn/learn/learn/learln/learln/learn/phluentd/?utm_source = cncf&amp;utm_medium = sponsored+content+content flogent for &lt;/a&gt;上，您可以在&lt;a的情况下，您可以在&lt;plogent上&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt;阶段&lt;/strong&gt;或&lt;strong&gt;过滤期&lt;/strong&gt;。每种方法都有不同的特征和性能的影响。让我们探索这两个。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxc1bddr41qtgw2 pypwz1mstb9w43sq2u-ljn5c4c4c4c4c4c4jwv3y19ukksk3qojddf snuhjttoefegddpv8rkdjnbnf8gyhmsr4m0djswh5qcfgi_cgi_cg0epzib-p4dm3uv4jsxcbfthdh5xuk？ alt =“架构” referrerpolicy =“ no-toferrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;输入阶段多行解析&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在输入阶段，摄入数据后立即应用多行解析（例如，使用尾部输入插件读取日志文件时。在这里，解析器的规则用于在进行任何进一步处理之前将属于同一上下文的日志线分组为单个记录。此方法可确保从摄入时刻保留日志的完整结构，使其非常适合下游处理（例如，过滤，路由或输出格式）的场景，取决于完整的日志输入完整。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种方法的关键优势是性能。由于在读取日志文件时会发生串联，因此避免了在管道中进行缓冲和重新处理的开销。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另外，&lt;strong&gt;多线过滤器&lt;/strong&gt;可用于稍后在管道中的串联消息。该过滤器旨在将属于单个上下文（例如堆栈轨迹或多行应用程序日志）重新整合日志线，但在摄入期间被分为单独的记录。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，这种方法带有一些细微差别：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;性能考虑：&lt;/strong&gt;在滤波阶段的串联日志的效率不如输入阶段。流利的位文档建议尽可能使用尾插件对日志文件的多行支持，因为它在摄入过程中而不是在摄入过程中进行日志。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;缓冲行为：&lt;/strong&gt;启用缓冲区选项时，过滤器将保留消息，直到完全串联或达到超时为止。没有缓冲，它一次处理一个块，这对于在单独块发送多行消息的输入中可能无法正常工作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;管道定位：&lt;/strong&gt;多行滤波器应该是管道中的第一个过滤器。由于它重新显示了将记录串联到管道的头部，因此将其放置在其之前的任何过滤器都将处理日志两次 - 在串联之前和之后一次。该过滤器忽略了自己的重新发射记录，但其他过滤器不会。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;单滤波器限制：&lt;/strong&gt;您无法配置带有重叠标签的多个多行滤波器，因为这会创建一个无限的循环。相反，请使用带有逗号分隔的解析器列表的单个过滤器（例如Multiline.Parser = Parser1，ParseR2）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;选择正确的方法&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用&lt;strong&gt;输入阶段解析&lt;/strong&gt;（例如，通过尾巴）用于日志文件或在摄入时间中已知的日志结构的日志结构。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用&lt;strong&gt;过滤阶段解析&lt;/strong&gt;当日志作为单独记录摄入时（例如，通过网络输入），需要以后或需要重新组合或需要灵活性来在初始处理后应用解析规则。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;结论&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多行日志有助于调试，但如果无法正确管理，可以使分析复杂化。 Fluent位通过将这些日志与其多行解析器（无论是在输入或过滤器阶段使用）合并为单个结构化条目，从而提供了强大的解决方案。通过选择正确的方法（用于性能或灵活性过滤的输入），您可以简化故障排除并确保关键细节保持完整。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;此博客是两部分系列中的第一个。在下一篇文章中，我们详细讨论&lt;a href =“ https://chronosphere.io/learn/multiline-builtin-parsers-fluent-bit/?utm_source = cncf&amp;utm_medium = sponsordium = sponsored+content+content”&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The End User TAB’s top talks at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025】最终用户选项卡在Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe的顶级谈判2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/31/the-end-user-tabs-top-talks-at-kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you are attending the upcoming KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 conference in London, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/people/end-user-technical-advisory-board/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF End User Technical Advisory Board (TAB)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; member recommendations for their top talk recommendations! 🙂&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ahmed Bebars:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the rich and captivating topics at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025, it is difficult to narrow down on just a few sessions for attendance. Nonetheless, I consider these two a “must”:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Metal To Apps: LinkedIn’s Kubernetes-based Compute Platform – Ahmet Alp Balkan &amp;amp; Ronak Nathani, LinkedIn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn must enable “bare-metal” servers to serve as a computing platform for applications; however, integration is key to flexibility. Insight from Ahmet Alp Balkan and Ronak Nathani on how challenges of tenant isolation, resilience, and developer usability are solved at such massive scales is crucial to understanding large-scale infrastructure transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lessons Learned From Architecting the Highest-scale Operational Systems in the World – Artur Bergman, Fastly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of the world’s largest systems contain a treasure trove of knowledge, and Artur Bergman manages them. His attention to detail with resilient and recovery-focused systems, specifically those intended to prevent cascading failures and enable rapid recovery, is important when building robust and scalable systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These sessions are unparalleled for those curious about how to build and manage large-scale, resilient infrastructures due to the immense focus and solutions straightforward challenges operating at scale deal with.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alolita Sharma:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of excellent talks at every KubeCon + CloudNativeCon conference. Some of the talks making it to my must-attend list this year include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Town Hall Panel Discussion: End User Technical Advisory Board (TAB) Town Hall&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? Come meet the CNCF’s end-user TAB! Learn about the TAB’s initiatives on reference architectures, project health and feedback. And use this opportunity to ask questions about areas where and how end-users can get involved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Project Lightning Talk: Perses Update – Augustin Husson, Maintainer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? Perses is a project that has the potential of changing the current open source observability landscape with the development of a new and unified UI framework that will present observability analysis dashboards and results out of the box. This talk will focus on project progress, features and roadmap which is key for end-users looking to have a cloud-native choice for observability user interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Keynote: AI Enabled Observability Explainers – We Actually Did Something With AI! – Vijay Samuel, Principal MTS, Architect, eBay&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? AI/ML continues to make deeper inroads in analyzing telemetry data and understanding systems at scale. eBay, an end-user building cloud-native observability solutions will be talking about how they have used AI algorithms to understand their telemetry metrics, traces and logs to create more predictable and accurate AI enabled observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: First Day Foresight: Anomaly Detection for Observability – Prashant Gupta &amp;amp; Kruthika Prasanna Simha, Apple&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? This end-user talk dives into the&amp;nbsp; benefits of using pre-trained ML models for day one anomaly detection. Using lightweight, unsupervised pre-trained models using cloud-native tools like Kubeflow for model fine-tuning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: An Exemplary Path: Leveraging EBPFs and OpenTelemetry To Auto-instrument for Exemplars – Charlie Le &amp;amp; Kruthika Prasanna Simha, Apple&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? Another interesting end-user talk takes a look at using exemplars effectively in an automated way by collecting eBPF data with OpenTelemetry and correlating application and kernel telemetry data to understand system performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: Designing a Common Query Language for Observability Data – Alolita Sharma, Apple; Pereira Braga, Google; Chris Larsen, Netflix&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unifying query languages is key in reducing toil for app developers and end users to query and analyze observability data. A common query language that can leverage all observability data such as metrics, traces, profiles, events, logs to facilitate correlation, support trend analytics and provide end-to-end observability for AI applications. End users from Netflix and Apple have been driving the Observability TAG QLS workgroup to define and finalize a semantic query language spec in 2025 and are recommending SQL as a basis with further experimentation on syntaxes. This talk will explore the trade-offs between simplicity, expressiveness, and performance. This query language convergence for end-to-end analytics could enhance reliability and operational efficiency for SREs and your app developers. This could be a win-win for all end-users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kenta Tada:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many excellent sessions at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025, addressing key challenges and innovations in cloud-native adoption. As organizations continue to scale their cloud infrastructure, efficient observability and extensibility are becoming critical for maintaining performance and reliability. I’d like to highlight two sessions that offer practical insights for end-user organizations on leveraging eBPF—one for enhancing userspace extensibility and another for gaining deep, network visibility without infrastructure modifications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: eBPF and Wasm: Unifying Userspace Extensions With Bpftime – Yusheng Zheng, eunomia-bpf&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As end-user organizations seek to extend and customize their cloud-native environments, both eBPF and Wasm offer compelling solutions—eBPF for kernel-level optimizations and Wasm for userspace sandboxing. However, both face challenges when userspace extensions need to interact deeply with host applications. This session by Yusheng Zheng introduces bpftime, a novel framework that extends eBPF’s capabilities into userspace without the overhead of Wasm’s sandboxing. If your organization is looking for a high-performance and secure way to extend applications using uprobe and XDP in a userspace eBPF runtime, don’t miss this session!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: Using eBPF for Non-invasive, Performant, Instant Network Monitoring – Mario Macías &amp;amp; Marc Tudurí, Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For end-user organizations, gaining network visibility without disrupting existing infrastructure is a major challenge. This session by Mario Macías and Marc Tudurí from Grafana showcases how eBPF enables lightweight, non-invasive network monitoring across layers L3 to L7 without requiring infrastructure modifications. Their approach integrates low-level network telemetry with Kubernetes metadata, providing actionable insights into service communication and traffic patterns. If your organization is looking to enhance observability while minimizing overhead, this session is highly recommended!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ricardo Rocha:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KubeCon +CloudNativeCon keeps delivering, in size and in quality. The London event will again keep a strong focus on end users, with a large number of sessions reporting experiences and best practices for a variety of use cases. These are usually my favorite sessions, together with those where community members from different vendors and organizations got together to tackle very hard problems. Hard to pick but here goes one example from each of these two categories.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session: Kubernetes WG Device Management – GPUs, TPUs, NICs and More With DRA – Kevin Klues, NVIDIA &amp;amp; Patrick Ohly, Intel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the hype and demand still strong, the usage of accelerators for AI and other workloads keeps growing. But looking at the longer term, the success of these new ways of computing at scale will require more efficient, sustainable use of these expensive resources. The DRA effort has shown how our community can gather and work together to deliver now the features that will help us succeed in the future. This kubecon includes several other talks about Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA), including some from my organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session: The Bricks That Make Us – How the LEGO Group Avoids 50 Mediocre Kubernetes Implementations – Thomas Øther Rasmussen &amp;amp; Paul Farver, The LEGO Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Being a huge LEGO fan I’m far from being alone in our community. Hearing about the challenges faced by the LEGO group scaling out platforms and teams makes for a very interesting and entertaining session, with lessons to be learned by end users from all domains. With great speakers as well, this will be a session not to be missed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re not registered yet, there’s still plenty of time to catch these sessions – and many more – in person. Also, come say Hi and meet us &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;at the TAB session on Friday April 4 2025&lt;/a&gt;. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;If you are attending the upcoming KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 conference in London, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/people/end-user-technical-advisory-board/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF End User Technical Advisory Board (TAB)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; member recommendations for their top talk recommendations! 🙂&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;艾哈迈德·贝巴尔（Ahmed Bebars）：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在2025年库贝康 + Cloudnativecon欧洲的富裕和迷人的话题中，很难只参加几次会议才能参加。尽管如此，我认为这两个是“必须”：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; LinkedIn必须启用“裸机”服务器作为应用程序的计算平台；但是，集成是灵活性的关键。艾哈迈德·阿尔普·巴尔干（Ahmet Alp Balkan）和罗纳克·纳撒尼（Ronak Nathani）的洞察力对租户隔离，弹性和开发人员的可用性的挑战如何在如此庞大的规模上解决对于理解大规模的基础设施转换至关重要。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;从架构中汲取的经验教训，从世界上汲取的最高规模的操作系统 -  Artur Bergman  -  Artur Bergman，快速&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/prally&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;世界上一些最大的系统包含知识的宝库，Artur Bergman对其进行了管理。在建立强大而可扩展的系统时，他对以弹性和以恢复为中心的系统的关注非常重要。&lt;/p&gt;，很重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于那些对如何建立和管理大规模弹性基础设施的人来说，这些会议是无与伦比的，这是由于巨大的重点和解决方案在大规模上运行的直接挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Alolita Sharma：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在每次Kubecon + Cloudnativecon会议上都有许多出色的演讲。一些会谈将其列入我今年的必不可少的列表包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？快来遇到CNCF的最终用户标签！了解有关参考架构，项目健康和反馈的标签计划。并利用这个机会来询问有关最终用户在哪里以及如何参与的领域的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;项目闪电谈话：perses更新 - 奥古斯丁·侯赛因（Augustin Husses），维护者&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/prong&gt; &lt;/p &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？ Perses是一个具有更改当前开源可观察性的项目随着新的统一UI框架的开发，景观将展示可观察性分析仪表板和结果。这次演讲将重点介绍项目进度，功能和路线图，这对于希望有云代表选择用户界面的最终用户是关键。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;emt&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; keynote：ai启用可观察力的解释器 - 实际上是用AI做的！ -  Vijay Samuel，主要MTS，建筑师，eBay &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？ AI/ML继续在分析遥测数据和大规模理解系统方面更加深入。 eBay，最终用户建筑物云本地可观察性解决方案将讨论他们如何使用AI算法来了解其遥测指标，痕迹和日志以创建更可预测和准确的AI启用AI的可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; sessign：第一天的预见：观察到可观察性 -  prashant gupta＆kruthika＆kruthika＆kruthika＆kruthika prasika prasha prasha simha，apple sim &lt;/em em&gt; &lt;/&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？该最终用户谈话深入了解第一天的异常检测中使用预训练的ML模型的好处。使用轻巧的，无监督的预训练模型，使用云原生工具（例如KubeFlow）进行微调。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: An Exemplary Path: Leveraging EBPFs and OpenTelemetry To Auto-instrument for Exemplars – Charlie Le &amp; Kruthika Prasanna Simha, Apple &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？另一个有趣的最终用户谈话通过使用OpenTelemetry和将应用程序和内核遥测数据收集EBPF数据来有效地使用示例来了解系统性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; session：设计一种常见的Query语言，用于过时性数据 -  Alolita Sharma，Apple，Apple，Apple; Pereira Braga，Google；克里斯·拉尔森（Chris Larsen），netflix &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;统一查询语言是减少应用程序开发人员的辛劳和最终用户查询和分析可观察性数据的关键。一种通用的查询语言，可以利用所有可观察性数据，例如指标，迹线，配置文件，事件，日志来促进相关性，支持趋势分析并为AI应用程序提供端到端可观察性。 Netflix和Apple的最终用户一直在推动可观察性标签QLS工作组，以定义和最终确定2025年的语义查询语言规范，并建议SQL作为语法进一步实验。这次演讲将探讨简单，表现力和性能之间的权衡。端到端分析的这种查询语言融合可以提高可靠性和运行SRES和您的应用程序开发人员的效率。对于所有最终用户来说，这可能是双赢的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;肯塔·塔达（Kenta Tada）：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2025年的库贝肯 + Cloudnativecon欧洲有许多出色的会议，以应对云原始采用的主要挑战和创新。随着组织继续扩展其云基础架构，有效的可观察性和可扩展性对于维持性能和可靠性至关重要。我想强调两个会议，为最终用户组织提供实用的见解，以利用EBPF，可提高用户空间的扩展性，而另一项可在没有基础架构修改的情况下获得深度，网络可见性。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; session：ebpf和wasm：ebpf and wasm：bpftime – yusheng zheng zheng zheng，eunhom ppf &lt;/emunom pff &lt;/em em pff &lt;/em em&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着最终用户组织寻求扩展和自定义其云本地环境，EBPF和WASM提供了引人注目的解决方案 - 用于内核级优化的EBPF，以及用于用户空间沙盒的WASM。但是，当用户空间扩展需要与主机应用程序进行深入互动时，这两者都面临挑战。 Yusheng Zheng的这次会议介绍了Bpftime，这是一个新颖的框架，将EBPF的功能扩展到了Userspace，而没有WASM的沙盒开销。如果您的组织正在寻找一种高性能和安全的方法，以在用户空间EBPF运行时使用Uprobe和XDP扩展应用程序，请不要错过此会话！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: Using eBPF for Non-invasive, Performant, Instant Network Monitoring – Mario Macías &amp; Marc Tudurí, Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于最终用户组织而言，在不中断现有基础设施的情况下获得网络可见性是一个主要挑战。 MarioMacías和MarcTudurí的这次会议展示了EBPF如何在不需要基础架构修改的情况下，在L3至L7层之间实现了轻巧的非侵入性网络监视。他们的方法将低级网络遥测与Kubernetes元数据集成在一起，从而提供了对服务通信和流量模式的可行见解。如果您的组织希望在最小化开销时提高可观察性，则强烈建议您进行此会议！&lt;/p&gt;！&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Ricardo Rocha：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubecon +CloudNativeCon保持尺寸和质量。伦敦活动将再次重点关注最终用户，并为各种用例提供​​大量的会议报告经验和最佳实践。这些通常是我最喜欢的会议，以及来自不同供应商和组织的社区成员聚在一起解决非常困难的问题的会议。很难选择，但这里有一个例子从这两个类别中的每个类别中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; session：kubernetes wg设备管理 -  gpus，tpus，tpus，tpus，nics，nics及其更多 -  kevin kevin kevin klues＆kevin klues＆patrick＆patrick＆patrick，英特尔&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着炒作和需求仍然强劲，加速器对AI和其他工作量的使用不断增长。但是，从长远来看，这些新的计算方式的成功将需要对这些昂贵的资源进行更有效，可持续的使用。 DRA的努力表明，我们的社区如何聚集和共同努力，以提供帮助我们将来成功的功能。这个库贝孔还包括有关动态资源分配（DRA）的其他几次讨论，其中包括我的组织中的一些。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; sessign&gt; &lt;strong&gt; session：使我们 - 乐高乐团如何避免50个中高级库伯尼特的实施 - &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为一个巨大的乐高粉丝，我并不是一个人在社区中。听到乐高集团扩大平台和团队所面临的挑战，这是一个非常有趣且有趣的会议，最终用户可以从所有域中吸取教训。凭借出色的演讲者，这将是不容错过的会议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您尚未注册，仍然有足够的时间亲自捕捉这些会议以及更多的会议。另外，快来打个招呼并与我们见面&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&gt;在2025年4月4日星期五的表会议上。在那里见！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes hardening made easy: Running CIS Benchmarks with kube-bench】kubernetes硬化变得容易：用kube板凳运行顺式基准测试</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/08/kubernetes-hardening-made-easy-running-cis-benchmarks-with-kube-bench/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today’s world, where security risks and breaches are growing daily, it is crucial to maintain our applications and infrastructure’s compliance with security standards and that is where CIS benchmarks from CIS (Center for Internet Security) comes in. And with kube-bench, running these checks becomes straightforward, helping you strengthen your Kubernetes clusters with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CIS Benchmarks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; Here is the mission statement from CIS’s website.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to make the connected world a safer place by developing, validating, and promoting timely best practice solutions that help people, businesses, and governments protect themselves against pervasive cyber threats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt; Ref. https://www.cisecurity.org/ for more details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It basically helps us to jot down:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What best practices/guidelines to use?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which tools are available to assist us in scanning our application or infrastructure?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Making sure the best practices are updated in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The benchmarks are basically available for multiple platforms including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All the public cloud providers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Softwares&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;DevSecOps tools&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mobile devices&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Operating Systems&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;and much more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can find their extensive list here: https://learn.cisecurity.org/benchmarks&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CIS Benchmarks: Download PDF for your platform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For downloading the PDF files you just need to provide some general details about yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeeWJQxxCFz1NqXYEANUuXEi7dxUvpHZ1w43fPW2NC2-kJ646egZYO_HheHyizoyKqmz0ljog60mUwd3ozAlUmXfiCNULTruPqnlmCRi6CiRSG00g4910fZ4NwgVDDTjplF3ot1OQ?key=vQuF7QUoFTWlBXZL5X937VZe&#34; alt=&#34;the PDF download screen&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once done, press “Submit” and you will receive an email with the link from where you can download all kinds of benchmarks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It looks something like this:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc-QHJTvNcTcKuXNAulAm_BJgn-teOKivnoN4mvP-YkZWnuGuxoBsRsRgVLPLfeaaR09cdqxhneoA1TDiUHEypnbmvZ2oyn8rN8Y5oMvo2x9oB2y7I3yZUjD0mAQMPE8-W0SXHW4g?key=vQuF7QUoFTWlBXZL5X937VZe&#34; alt=&#34;Where to download benchmarks&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upon pressing “Access PDFs” you will be routed to their extensive list of benchmarks which looks something like this:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfo5Vud_7F9nXpiMloldBJx4iGcf-G2-HKLDvM8ZoskQu7HM3Sbrs6uFseijxX3FKq_q26zuVMQpAgv8HQfPRmBfAOSC7zgAjsJqUclmMJZD1cZCLaQwdnTtZ7e1B8eeOlBlJ_BYA?key=vQuF7QUoFTWlBXZL5X937VZe&#34; alt=&#34;What happens when you access PDFs&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can choose whatever you want to, but since we are interested in Kubernetes as of now, we will scroll down to the Kubernetes section.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfwoO2c3JTQjw7CMqnckKNPaWu8CEqlQtaRhgWSWjp66F5STH-bGdCPgXgXBYpQOBI4qg8wFqZae2H7HS_b2-xTLjvmddLiflnTi6sRZfxALXW5XziY2sfxtU2tAHNpJEIV0tsulQ?key=vQuF7QUoFTWlBXZL5X937VZe&#34; alt=&#34;The Kubernetes section&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the good part here is, this is not limited to vanilla Kubernetes, we can even download benchmarks for all the Kubernetes flavours like EKS from AWS, AKS from Azure, GKE from Google, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you download a specific PDF, you will see it contains a great amount of details including recommendations, problem statement, impact, remediation, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, if you have observed the PDF contains thousands of recommendations and going thru them and applying them one by one is a time-consuming task and just imagine you have 100s of clusters. Though I would recommend you to at-least go thru it once and get an idea of what all details it contains and how we can make use of it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To make our lives easier there are a couple of tools which can help us to automate this process and help us to identify where we are lacking. So that we can fix them quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CIS Benchmarks: Tools&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are a couple of tools which are managed by CIS itself like CIS-CAT Lite/CIS-CAT Pro/etc. CIS-CAT Lite is a free version and it supports a limited number of options excluding Kubernetes. CIS-CAT Pro is the one which supports Kubernetes but it is just available for CIS SecureSuite Members.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ref. https://www.cisecurity.org/cybersecurity-tools for more details about the tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s talk about the good part, the community has given us a couple of open source tools which do the same 😉 the most used one is kube-bench (from Aqua Security).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HOWTO: kube-bench&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;kube-bench is a tool that checks whether Kubernetes is deployed securely by running the checks documented in the CIS Kubernetes Benchmark.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are multiple ways to run kube-bench&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install it via a package manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Download the latest package based on your OS from github releases page and install it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ref: https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/releases&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Since, I am using Ubuntu, I will use dpkg to get this package installed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ wget https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/releases/download/v0.10.2/kube-bench_0.10.2_linux_amd64.deb&#xA;$ sudo dpkg -i kube-bench_0.10.2_linux_amd64.deb&#xA;Selecting previously unselected package kube-bench.&#xA;(Reading database ... 41333 files and directories currently installed.)&#xA;Preparing to unpack kube-bench_0.10.2_linux_amd64.deb ...&#xA;Unpacking kube-bench (0.10.2) ...&#xA;Setting up kube-bench (0.10.2) ...&#xA;$ kube-bench version&#xA;0.10.2&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Run as a job in the Kubernetes Cluster&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Get the job.yaml from the same github link and deploy it on your cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ref: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/blob/main/job.yaml&#34;&gt;https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/blob/main/job.yaml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Based on your platforms there are multiple job*.yaml files available like for EKS, AKS, GKE, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/main/job.yaml&#xA;job.batch/kube-bench created&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ k get pods&#xA;NAME               READY   STATUS      RESTARTS   AGE&#xA;kube-bench-n22k9   0/1     Completed   0          96s&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ k logs kube-bench-n22k9 | head -n 20&#xA;[INFO] 1 Control Plane Security Configuration&#xA;[INFO] 1.1 Control Plane Node Configuration Files&#xA;[PASS] 1.1.1 Ensure that the API server pod specification file permissions are set to 600 or more restrictive (Automated)&#xA;[PASS] 1.1.2 Ensure that the API server pod specification file ownership is set to root:root (Automated)&#xA;[PASS] 1.1.3 Ensure that the controller manager pod specification file permissions are set to 600 or more restrictive (Automated)&#xA;[PASS] 1.1.4 Ensure that the controller manager pod specification file ownership is set to root:root (Automated)&#xA;[PASS] 1.1.5 Ensure that the scheduler pod specification file permissions are set to 600 or more restrictive (Automated)&#xA;[PASS] 1.1.6 Ensure that the scheduler pod specification file ownership is set to root:root (Automated)&#xA;&#xA;OUTPUT TRIMMED&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ k logs kube-bench-n22k9 | tail -n 20&#xA;OUTPUT TRIMMED&#xA;&#xA;5.7.3 Follow the Kubernetes documentation and apply SecurityContexts to your Pods. For a&#xA;suggested list of SecurityContexts, you may refer to the CIS Security Benchmark for Docker&#xA;Containers.&#xA;&#xA;5.7.4 Ensure that namespaces are created to allow for appropriate segregation of Kubernetes&#xA;resources and that all new resources are created in a specific namespace.&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;== Summary policies ==&#xA;0 checks PASS&#xA;6 checks FAIL&#xA;29 checks WARN&#xA;0 checks INFO&#xA;&#xA;== Summary total ==&#xA;57 checks PASS&#xA;19 checks FAIL&#xA;54 checks WARN&#xA;0 checks INFO&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Just check the logs of the pod for all the recommendations. These logs contain multiple sections for different-different Kubernetes components like Controlplane, ETCD, Worker nodes, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;At the end of each section you can see statistics about the checks and at the end of the logs you will see a quick summary about the total (as mentioned above).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;== Summary node ==&#xA;14 checks PASS&#xA;2 checks FAIL&#xA;8 checks WARN&#xA;0 checks INFO&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Run as a docker container&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;docker run --rm --net host --pid host --user 0 \&#xA;  -v /etc:/etc:ro \&#xA;  -v /var:/var:ro \&#xA;  -v /usr/bin:/usr/bin:ro \&#xA;  -v /usr/lib:/usr/lib:ro \&#xA;  aquasec/kube-bench:latest --benchmark cis-1.24&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can change the version based on your requirement, 1.24 is the latest one.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;More details about the versions can be found here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/tree/main/cfg&#34;&gt;https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/tree/main/cfg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For this as well, just check the logs of the container and you will find the same results as we described in the earlier section.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is how the remediation steps look like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;== Remediations master ==&#xA;1.1.9 Run the below command (based on the file location on your system) on the control plane node.&#xA;For example, chmod 600 &amp;lt;path/to/cni/files&amp;gt;&#xA;&#xA;1.1.11 On the etcd server node, get the etcd data directory, passed as an argument --data-dir,&#xA;from the command &#39;ps -ef | grep etcd&#39;.&#xA;Run the below command (based on the etcd data directory found above). For example,&#xA;chmod 700 /var/lib/etcd&#xA;&#xA;1.1.12 On the etcd server node, get the etcd data directory, passed as an argument --data-dir,&#xA;from the command &#39;ps -ef | grep etcd&#39;.&#xA;Run the below command (based on the etcd data directory found above).&#xA;For example, chown etcd:etcd /var/lib/etcd&#xA;&#xA;1.1.19 Run the below command (based on the file location on your system) on the control plane node.&#xA;For example,&#xA;chown -R root:root /etc/kubernetes/pki/&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;References:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;– https://www.cisecurity.org/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;– https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feel free to add your thoughts and experiences, Happy Learning! 🙂&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;URL: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dev.to/aws-builders/kubernetes-hardening-made-easy-running-cis-benchmarks-with-kube-bench-38ne&#34;&gt;Kubernetes hardening made easy: Running CIS Benchmarks with kube-bench – DEV Community&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的世界中，安全风险和违规每天都在增长，维持我们的应用程序和基础设施遵守安全标准至关重要，这就是CIS（互联网安全中心）的顺式基准（CIS基准）进入的地方。借助Kube-Bench，使用Kube-Bench，运行这些检查，可以使您的Kubernetes Clusters Clusters Clusters corfure clusters。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;顺式基准&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p &gt;&gt;这是CIS网站的任务声明。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的使命是通过开发，验证和促进及时的最佳实践解决方案来帮助人们，企业和政府保护自己免受普遍的网络威胁。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p &gt;&gt;参考。 https://www.cisecurity.org/有关更多详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它基本上可以帮助我们记下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用哪些最佳实践/准则？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;有哪些工具可以帮助我们扫描应用程序或基础架构？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;确保最佳实践及时更新。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基本上可用于多个平台，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;所有公共云提供商。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;软件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; DevSecops工具&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;移动设备&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;操作系统&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;等等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在此处找到他们的广泛列表：https：//learn.cisecurity.org/benchmarks &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;顺式基准：为您的平台下载PDF &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用于下载PDF文件，您只需要提供有关您自己的一些一般详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxeewjqxxcxcfzfz1nqxyeanuuxei7dxuvphz1w43fppw2nc2nc2nc2-kj64646egzyo_hh ehyizoykqmz0ljog60muwd3ozalumxficnultrupqnlmcri6cirsg00g4910fz4nwgvddtjplf3ot1oq？ alt =“ pdf下载屏幕” revyrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成后，按“提交”，您将收到带有链接的电子邮件，您可以下载各种基准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;看起来像这样：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxc-qhjtvnctckuxnaulam_bjgn-teokivnon4mvp-ykzwnuguxobsrsrsrg vlplfeaar09cdqxhneoa1tdiuheypnbmvz2oyn8rn8y5omvo2x9ob2y7i3yzujd0maqmpe8-w0sxhw4g？ alt =“在哪里下载基准” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;按下“访问PDF”时，您将被路由到其广泛的基准列表，看起来像这样：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfo5vud_7f9nxpimloldbjx4igcf-g2-g2-hkldvm8zoskqu7hm3sbrs6sufs EIJXX3FKQ_Q26ZUVMQPAGV8HQFPRMBFAOSC7ZGAJSJQUCLMMJZD1CZCLAQWDNTTTZ7E1B8EEOLBLJ_BYA？ alt =“访问时会发生什么pdfs“ referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以选择您想要的任何东西，但是由于我们现在对Kubernetes感兴趣，因此我们将滚动到Kubernetes部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfwoo2c3jtqjw7cmqncknckknpawu8ceqlqlqtarhgwswsjp666f5sth bgdcpgx GXBYPQOBI4QG8WFQZAE2H7HS_B2-XTLJVMDDDLIFLNTI6SRZFXALXW5XZIY2SFXTU2TAHNPJEIV0TSULQ？ alt =“ kubernetes部分” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，这里的好部分是，这不仅限于Vanilla Kubernetes，我们甚至可以为所有Kubernetes口味下载基准，例如AWS，Aks aks aks aks aks akes akes from Azure，Game，Google的GKE等。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下载特定的PDF后，您会看到它包含大量详细信息，包括建议，问题声明，影响，补救等等。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，如果您观察到PDF包含成千上万的建议，并通过它们进行一一应用是一项耗时的任务，然后想象一下您有100个集群。虽然我建议您至少一次，并了解它包含的所有细节以及我们如何使用它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了使我们的生活更轻松，有几个工具可以帮助我们自动化此过程并帮助我们确定缺乏的位置。这样我们就可以快速修复它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;顺式基准：工具&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有几个工具由CIS本身管理，例如CIS-CAT LITE/CIS-CAT PRO/等。 CIS-CAT LITE是一个免费版本，它支持不包括Kubernetes的数量有限的选项。 CIS-CAT Pro是支持Kubernetes的Pro，但它仅适用于CIS Seecuresuite成员。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;参考。 https://www.cisecurity.org/cybersecurity-tools有关工具的更多详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，让我们谈谈良好的部分，社区给了我们几个开源工具，这些工具可以执行相同的操作。最常用的工具是Kube-Bench（来自Aqua Security）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; howto：kube-bench &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kube-Bench是一种工具，可以通过运行CIS Kubernetes基准中记录的支票来检查Kubernetes是否安全部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;有多种运行Kube Bench的方法&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;通过软件包管理器安装&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;从GitHub发布页面下载最新软件包并安装它。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;参考：https：//github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/releases &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;由于我正在使用Ubuntu，我将使用DPKG安装此软件包。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ wget https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/kube-bench/releases/download/download/v0.2/kube-bench_0.10.10.2_10.2_1.2_1.2_linux_amd64.deb&#xA;$ sudo dpkg -i kube -bench_0.10.2_linux_amd64.deb&#xA;选择先前未选择的软件包kube ben。&#xA;（读取数据库... 41333当前已安装的文件和目录。）&#xA;pre削减包装kube-bench_0.10.2_linux_amd64.deb ...&#xA;解开Kube Bench（0.10.2）...&#xA;设置Kube Bench（0.10.2）...&#xA;$ kube-Bench版本&#xA;0.10.2&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在kubernetes群集中作为工作&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;从同一github链接中获取工作。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; ref：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/blob/main/job.yaml”&gt; https://github.com/aquasecurity/aquasecurity/kube-bube/kube-bube/kube-bench/blob/main/main/job.yaml/job.yaml/job.yaml &lt;/a-a-yaml &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;基于您的平台，有多个作业*.YAML文件，例如EK，AK，GKE等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ kubectl应用-f https：//raw.githubusercontent.com/aquasecurity/aquasecurity/kube-bench/main/main/job.yaml&#xA;job.批次/kube-bench创建了&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ k获取吊舱&#xA;名称准备状态重新开始年龄&#xA;Kube-Bench-N22K9 0/1完成0 96S&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ k logs kube-bench-n22k9 |头-N 20&#xA;[INFO] 1控制平面安全配置&#xA;[信息] 1.1控制平面节点配置文件&#xA;[通过] 1.1.1确保API服务器POD规范文件权限设置为600或更多限制性（自动化）&#xA;[通过] 1.1.2确保将API服务器POD规范文件所有权设置为root：root（自动化）&#xA;[通过] 1.1.3确保控制器管理器POD规范文件权限设置为600或更多限制性（自动化）&#xA;[通过] 1.1.4确保控制器管理器POD规范文件所有权设置为root：root（自动化）&#xA;[通过] 1.1.5确保调度程序POD规范文件权限设置为600或更多限制性（自动化）&#xA;[通过] 1.1.6确保调度程序POD规范文件所有权设置为root：root（自动化）&#xA;&#xA;输出修剪&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ k logs kube-bench-n22k9 |尾巴-n 20&#xA;输出修剪&#xA;&#xA;5.7.3遵循Kubernetes文档，并将SecurityContexts应用于您的吊舱。对于&#xA;建议的SecurityContext列表，您可以参考Docker的CIS安全基准&#xA;容器。&#xA;&#xA;5.7.4确保创建命名空间以允许kubernetes的适当分离&#xA;资源和所有新资源都是在特定名称空间中创建的。&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ==摘要策略==&#xA;0检查通行证&#xA;6个检查失败&#xA;29检查警告&#xA;0检查信息&#xA;&#xA;==摘要总计==&#xA;57支票通行证&#xA;19支票失败&#xA;54检查警告&#xA;0检查信息&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;只需检查所有建议的吊舱日志即可。这些日志包含多个不同的部分，用于不同不同的kubernetes组件，例如Control Plane，ETCD，Worker节点等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在每个部分的末尾，您可以看到有关检查的统计信息，在日志结束时，您将看到有关总数的快速摘要（如上所述）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-b锁定代码“&gt; &lt;code class =”&gt; ==摘要node ==&#xA;14个检查通行证&#xA;2个检查失败&#xA;8检查警告&#xA;0检查信息&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;作为Docker容器&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;运行&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; docker run -rm-net主机 -  pid host -pid host -user 0 \&#xA;  -v /etc： /etc：ro \&#xA;  -v /var： /var：ro \&#xA;  -v/usr/bin：/usr/bin：ro \&#xA;  -v/usr/lib：/usr/lib：ro \&#xA;  Aquasec/Kube-Bench：最新 - 基准测试CIS-1.24&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;br&gt;您可以根据要求更改版本，1.24是最新的。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;有关该版本的更多详细信息，请参见：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench/kench/tree/main/main/main/main/cfg”&gt; https://github.com/aquasecurity/aquasecurity/kube-bench/kube-bench/kube-bench/kube-bench/tree/tree/main/main/main/main/main/main/main/main/main/main/cfg &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;也为此，只需检查容器的日志，您就会找到与我们在前一节中描述的相同的结果。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是补救步骤的样子：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ==修复master ==&#xA;1.1.9在控制平面节点上运行以下命令（基于系统上的文件位置）。&#xA;例如，CHMOD 600 &lt;PATH/TO/CNI/FILES&gt;&#xA;&#xA;1.1.11在ETCD服务器节点上，获取ETCD数据目录，作为参数传递 -  data-dir，&#xA;从命令的ps -ef | grep etctd&#39;。&#xA;运行以下命令（基于上面找到的ETCD数据目录）。例如，&#xA;CHMOD 700/var/lib/etcd&#xA;&#xA;1.1.12在ETCD服务器节点上，获取ETCD数据目录，作为参数传递 -  data-dir，&#xA;从命令的ps -ef | grep etctd&#39;。&#xA;运行以下命令（基于上面找到的ETCD数据目录）。&#xA;例如，chown etct：etcd/var/lib/etcd&#xA;&#xA;1.1.19在控制平面节点上运行以下命令（基于系统上的文件位置）。&#xA;例如，&#xA;chown -r root：root/etc/kubernetes/pki/&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;参考：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  https://www.cisecurity.org/ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随意添加您的想法和经验，学习快乐！ 🙂&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; url：&lt;a href =“ https://dev.to/aws-builders/kubernetes-hardening-made-made-made-r---------------------&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>