<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://rsshub.rssforever.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025: Day One Keynote Recap】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025：第一天的主题演讲回顾</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/02/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025-day-one-keynote-recap/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;On a bright sunny London day, attendees from all over the world flocked to the ExCel Arena for the first day of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 2025. Here’s a quick recap of the keynotes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The crowd was welcomed by Cloud Native Computing Foundation CTO and founder Chris Aniszczyk, who talked about the tenth anniversary of cloud native computing and walked everyone down memory lane. Chris updated the audience on a number of efforts – from Golden Kubestronauts to training efforts in Africa (a partnership with Andela) – and also talked about the beta release of GitJobs.dev, a way to find open source jobs. Then Vasu Chandrasekhara from SAP joined him to explain NeoNephos, a sovereign cloud-edge continuum for Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Christine Yen, CEO and cofounder of Honeycomb, presented a keynote on &lt;strong&gt;Observability in the age of LLMs&lt;/strong&gt;. Christine explained that writing software today feels more like magic than ever, and that while LLMs are like APIs, they complicate the traditional ways of doing things because they can be difficult to test, mock up and debug. The answer, she argued, was observability, because it helps embrace the unpredictability that LLMs bring. The trick is to bundle observability with evals so teams can capture the good and bad as it happens and create systems that evolve with the code. The good news? This isn’t a new skillset. A lot of this shift is already underway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vijay Samuel, principal MTS and architect at eBay, spoke about &lt;strong&gt;AI-enabled observability explainers – We actually did something with AI!&lt;/strong&gt; With 4600 microservices powering the eBay site, and 15PB of logs per day, Vijay explained how incidents impacted the team’s ability to provide the highest quality customer experience and that trying to deal with all this data manually is cumbersome. So his group started small experiments using LLMs as observability building blocks that could summarize and explain critical paths. They found simple flows they could automate and in the end leaned into LLMs’ strengths all the while realizing there were still things best done with code instead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Greg Kroah-Hartman, Linux Kernel Maintainer and Fellow with The Linux Foundation, spoke on &lt;strong&gt;Rust in the Linux Kernel: A new era for cloud native performance and security&lt;/strong&gt;. Greg walked the audience through the close relationship between Rust and Linux and shared some statistics, including the fact that Linux has 4,992 developers and 355+ employers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rob Koch, principal of Slalom Build and an American Sign Language user, shared his experience working toward machine recognition of sign language, in &lt;strong&gt;Empowering accessibility through Kubernetes: The future of real-time sign language interpretation&lt;/strong&gt;. Currently only two&amp;nbsp; or three companies in the world are working on this, Rob explained, and his company is using Kubeflow and Kubernetes to tackle the challenge. Kubeflow simplifies the deployment of machine learning models, ensuring smooth transitions from training to production.In the future, the company wants to prepare for recognizing other sign languages and seeing things from other viewpoints.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kasper Borg Nissen, developer relations engineer at Dash0, spoke on &lt;strong&gt;The observability platform engineering advantage: from zero code to monitoring as code&lt;/strong&gt;. His contention is that current systems are really inefficient when it comes to observability. “We don’t have a &lt;em&gt;metrics problem&lt;/em&gt;, or a &lt;em&gt;tracing problem&lt;/em&gt;. We have systems problems.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;And yet, many of us still treat these as separate entities. We have one browser tab for logs, another for metrics, and a third for tracing. We are relying on humans to correlate signals across them. It’s inefficient, it’s error-prone, and frankly, it’s not how modern observability should work.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He ended with a call to action to apply platform engineering principles to observability: “Applying platform engineering principles can transform observability from an afterthought into a seamless, scalable, and developer-friendly experience.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get more of Day One &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-activity-7313294603816689664-VZJR?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=member_android&amp;amp;rcm=ACoAAAZ5jugBqGBtxyEC7vpreMCIH8DipnVChMs&#34;&gt;in this video&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在阳光明媚的伦敦日，来自世界各地的与会者涌向Excel Arena，在Kubecon + Cloudnativecon 2025的第一天。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人群受到Cloud Native Computing Foundation CTO和创始人Chris Aniszczyk的欢迎，他们谈到了Cloud Native Computing的十周年，并将所有人带走了记忆巷。克里斯（Chris）对观众进行了许多努力的更新 - 从黄金kubestronauts到非洲的培训工作（与安德拉（Andela）的合作伙伴关系） - 还谈到了Gitjobs.dev的Beta版本，这是找到开源工作的一种方式。然后，来自SAP的Vasu Chandrasekhara与他一起解释了Neonephos，Neonephos是欧洲的主权云边缘连续体。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Honeycomb的首席执行官兼联合创始人Christine Yen在LLMS时代&lt;strong&gt;可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;时提出了一个主题演讲。克里斯汀（Christine）解释说，今天写软件比以往任何时候都更像是魔术，尽管LLM就像API，但它们会使传统的做事方式变得复杂，因为它们很难测试，模拟和调试。她认为，答案是可观察到的，因为它有助于接受LLMS带来的不可预测性。诀窍是用evals捆绑可观察性，以便团队可以在发生时捕获好和坏处，并创建随着代码发展的系统。好消息？这不是一个新技能。这种转变已经在进行中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;eBay的主要MTS和建筑师Vijay Samuel谈到了&lt;strong&gt; AI-AI-AI-A-AI-A-Absibal可观察性解释器 - 我们实际上是在AI！&lt;/strong&gt;的情况下做了一些事情！&lt;/strong&gt;，有4600个微服务为eBay网站提供动力，每天为15％的日志提供了15％的日志，Vijay解释了该团队的能力如何提供最高质量的客户经验，以实现最高质量的客户经验和所有这些数据。因此，他的小组使用LLM作为可观察性构建块开始了小型实验，可以总结并解释关键路径。他们发现他们可以自动化的简单流程，最终倾向于LLMS的优势，同时意识到仍然可以使用代码做得最好。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Greg Kroah-Hartman，Linux内核维护者和Linux Foundation的研究员在Linux内核中发表了&lt;strong&gt; Rust：云本地性能和安全性的新时代&lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt;。格雷格（Greg）通过Rust和Linux之间的密切关系，分享了一些统计数据，其中包括Linux拥有4,992个开发人员和355多名雇主。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;激流回旋构建的负责人和美国手语用户的主管Rob Koch分享了他致力于机器识别手语的经验，&lt;strong&gt;通过Kubernetes授权可访问性：实时手语解释的未来&lt;/strong&gt;。 Rob解释说，目前，世界上只有两三家公司正在为此做出努力，他的公司正在使用Kubeflow和Kubernetes来应对挑战。 kubeflow简化了部署者机器学习模型的T，确保从培训到生产的平稳过渡。该公司希望准备识别其他标志语言并从其他观点看到事物。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; DASH0开发人员关系工程师Kasper Borg Nissen在&lt;strong&gt;上发表了可观察性平台工程优势：从零代码到监视代码&lt;/strong&gt;。他的论点是，目前的系统在观察性方面确实效率低下。 “我们没有一个&lt;em&gt;衡量问题&lt;/em&gt;或&lt;em&gt;跟踪问题&lt;/em&gt;。我们有系统问题。&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;，但是，我们中的许多人仍将这些问题视为单独的实体。我们有一个浏览器访问日志，另一个用于指标，三分之一来跟踪。我们依靠人类的人，坦率地说明了它的误差。现代可观察性应该起作用。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他以采取行动的呼吁将平台工程原则应用于可观察性：“应用平台工程原则可以将可观察性从事后思考转变为无缝，可扩展和开发人员友好的体验。” &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;获得更多第一天&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-activity-7313294603816 689664-vzjr？utm_source = share＆utm_medium = member_android＆rcm = acoaaaaz5JUGBQGBTXYEC7VPREMCIH8DIPNVCHMS“&gt; IN&gt; IN这个视频&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025: Day Two Keynote Recap】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025：第二天的主题演讲回顾</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/03/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025-day-two-keynote-recap/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Over 12,000 attendees streamed into the ExCel Arena for the second day of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025, enjoying yet another sunny day in London and primed to hear real world stories of cloud innovation. Here’s a quick recap of the day’s keynote speeches.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A four-person panel keynote – &lt;strong&gt;Mind the Gap: Bridging cloud native innovation with real world use&lt;/strong&gt; – took a deep dive into how cloud native has fundamentally changed the way some very large companies are doing business. Panelists from HSBC, Peptone, Spotify and Apple outlined the challenges they faced, and the successes they found with cloud native. A couple of examples:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From HSBC: “We’re currently servicing around 600 million discrete hits a day, with over 7000 services in production, with thousands still to migrate from the legacy platform, all running in only a dozen or so clusters. Our clusters are very stable, but change can still be a pain point. To mitigate those issues during upgrades, we run our clusters in a blue/green pair and rehydrate clusters from etcd backups, cutting traffic over only when we’re happy that everything in the upgraded cluster is stable.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FromSpotify: “There’s been tension in how we balance internal priorities with external ones. But ultimately, this is a virtuous cycle. If we hadn’t open sourced Backstage, we’d likely still be living with our previous, more complicated backend system. In five years, we’ve gone from basically just a thin framework for building an IDP, to a better Backstage than we could have built on our own. Now, we’ve taken that further, to create the best IDP for the future.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Katie Gamanji, senior field engineer at Apple, talked about &lt;strong&gt;Open source in Apple’s private cloud compute&lt;/strong&gt;. At Apple, private cloud compute helps scale AI operations. Keeping privacy in mind, Apple ensures encryption is end to end. Swift libraries work with the community for open source. And gRPC and Swift teamed with private cloud compute are what enables it all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Top End User Award was given to Ant Group.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gabriel Quennesson, Michelin’s container as a service tech lead, and Arnaud Pons, container as a service product architect, spoke about &lt;strong&gt;Driving innovation at Michelin: How we scaled cloud &amp;amp; on-prem infrastructure while cutting costs&lt;/strong&gt;. The company was misaligned with its previous vendor’s strategy, while at the same time all of Michelin was embracing open source. And of course the team wanted to remain attractive to top tech talent. Switching to Kubernetes – and doing it themselves – brought platform costs down 44% and upgrade leadtime down 85% all while doubling their Kubernetes footprint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Discussing &lt;strong&gt;CNCF at 10: Navigating challenges, embracing opportunities&lt;/strong&gt; were Joseph Sandoval, principal product manager at Adobe, Liz Rice, chief open source officer from Isovalent at Cisco, and Katie Gamanji, senior field engineer with Apple. They walked the audience through the history of the last ten years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And Hans Kristian Flaatten, lead platform engineer NAV and Audun Fauchald Strand, principal software engineer, NAV, shared their &lt;strong&gt;Adventures of building platform as a service for the government&lt;/strong&gt;, which is a public PaaS in Norway with 81 member organizations that provides speed and agility to developers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want more KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025? &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-activity-7313607861245280258-lfNe?&#34;&gt;Watch the video!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;超过12,000名与会者在库贝肯 + Cloudnativecon欧洲2025年的第二天涌入Excel竞技场，在伦敦享受了又一个晴天，并听到了现实世界中有关云创新的故事。这是当天主题演讲的快速回顾。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个四人面板主题演讲 -  &lt;strong&gt;脑海中的差距：与现实世界使用&lt;/strong&gt;的桥接云国际创新 - 深入了解了云本地人如何从根本上改变了一些大型公司开展业务的方式。来自汇丰银行，peptone，Spotify和Apple的小组成员概述了他们面临的挑战，以及他们在Cloud Native中发现的成功。几个例子：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来自汇丰银行：“我们目前每天为6亿个离散命中率提供服务，生产的7000多个服务，成千上万的服务仍可从遗产平台迁移，所有这些服务都只有十几个左右的群集。我们的插图非常稳定。我们的clust非常稳定，但变化仍然可以减轻我们的痛苦。只有当我们很高兴升级的集群中的所有内容都稳定时，才能减少交通。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“我们如何在内部优先级与外部优先级保持紧张。但是最终，这是一个良好的周期。如果我们没有开放式的后台，我们可能仍然与以前的，更复杂的后端体系相处。五年来，我们从基本上是一个伟大的框架来构建AN AN AN AN AN AN AN AN ETIC。现在，我们已经建立了一个伟大的ID。现在，我们已经建立了一个。未来。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;苹果的高级野外工程师凯蒂·甘曼吉（Katie Gamanji）在苹果的私人云计算中谈到了&lt;strong&gt;开源&lt;/strong&gt;。在Apple，Private Cloud Compute有助于扩展AI操作。牢记隐私，苹果确保加密是端到端的。 Swift libraries work with the community for open source. GRPC和Swift与私有云计算合作，这是所有功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终用户奖获得了蚂蚁组。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Gabriel Quennesson，米其林作为服务技术负责人的容器，而Arnaud Pons（作为服务产品架构师）的Arnaud Pons谈到了&lt;strong&gt;在米其林开车的创新：我们如何缩放云和本地基础架构，同时削减成本&lt;/strong&gt;。该公司与以前的供应商的策略不一致，与此同时，米其林全部都在接受开源。当然，团队希望对顶尖技术人才保持吸引力。切换到kubernetes并自己进行 - 使平台的成本下降了44％，并升级了85％的平台，同时使他们的kubernetes footprint加倍。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;讨论&lt;strong&gt; CNCF 10：面临挑战，拥抱机会&lt;/strong&gt;是约瑟夫·桑多尔（Joseph SandovalO苹果高级野外工程师Katie Gamanji。他们引导观众度过了过去十年的历史。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和汉斯·克里斯蒂安·弗拉昂（Hans Kristian Flaatten），首席平台工程师纳尔（Nav）和纳维尔（Nav）首席软件工程师的阿杜·福卡尔德（Audun Fauchald Strand）分享了他们的&lt;strong&gt;构建平台的冒险，作为政府的服务&lt;/strong&gt;，这是挪威的公共PAAS，与81个成员组织是挪威的公共PAA，为开发人员提供速度和敏捷性。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想要更多的kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025？ &lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/posts/cloud-native-computing-foundation_kubecon-activity-7313607861245280258-lfne？&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Karmada Launches Adopter Group】Karmada推出采用者组</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/26/karmada-launches-adopter-group/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Karmada is thrilled to announce the launch of the Adopter Group program. This program aims to create a dynamic platform where adopters can connect, collaborate, and share information efficiently. By fostering an environment of shared experiences and mutual support, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/community/tree/main/adopter-group&#34;&gt;Karmada Adopter Group&lt;/a&gt; hopes to build a crucial link between adopters and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada&#34;&gt;Karmada community&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeUfvaW6ONyXuQOL84s7JvWisoenqIZFsgBaf2zZIrUE_oP5QXOldG7NrPCoUNKiJrz50IXQCfwSXAULoeuVleLo35J_nG3kvVENe0oiLwjs2Q98Z5Xb3VXLx4rS1lRyDmB1LX9Ew?key=acY2KhDpIrkDoVqIPA5GV8Am&#34; alt=&#34;Karmada Adopter Group graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an open-source multi-cloud and multi-cluster container orchestration engine, &lt;a href=&#34;https://karmada.io/&#34;&gt;Karmada&lt;/a&gt; has grown rapidly since its open-source in 2021 and became a CNCF Incubating Project in December 2023, with contributors span over 20+ countries and regions worldwide. Karmada has already been successfully deployed in production environments across dozens of large enterprises, serving as a key technological foundation for managing both general and heterogeneous computing resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the strong support from a large number of adopters, Karmada continuously improved and optimized through valuable feedback. This support includes, but is not limited to, detailed usage feedback, issue resolutions, and rich practical experience sharing, significantly contributing to the project’s maturity and stability. The close collaboration among community members enables Karmada to quickly address challenges in applications and continuously enhance the user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To further promote communication and collaboration, Karmada adopters can now&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/community/issues/new?template=adopter-group-application.yaml&#34;&gt; join the&amp;nbsp; group&lt;/a&gt; to connect with global developers and jointly explore multi-cluster technologies. This not only facilitates technical exchanges and best practice sharing but also provides a solid foundation for continuous innovation and development. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced user, you can find the information and assistance you need here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;About Karmada Adopter Group&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Karmada Adopter Group has a dedicated Google mailing group and GitHub Org team, with important announcements, updates, and information sharing for the members. The main functions include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge Sharing&lt;/strong&gt;: Facilitating the exchange of experiences, challenges, and solutions among Karmada adopters.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promoting Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;: Providing a platform for adopters to work together, share ideas, and solve common problems.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Support&lt;/strong&gt;: Offering resources, tutorials, and guidance to help adopters effectively utilize Karmada.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feedback Collection&lt;/strong&gt;: Listening to user feedback to guide Karmada’s future development.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Events&lt;/strong&gt;: Enhancing community engagement through regular meetups, webinars, and other activities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By joining the Karmada Adopter Group, you can connect with peers facing similar challenges, seeking solutions and development that are more suitable for you. Including:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Technical Support:&lt;/strong&gt; Including solution evaluation, daily operations, issue troubleshooting, version upgrades, and more.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increased Visibility:&lt;/strong&gt; More global exposure for your company and team&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building Technical Influence:&lt;/strong&gt; Opportunities to co-create technical presentations at events like KubeCon and other online/offline conferences.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Staying Informed: &lt;/strong&gt;Timely updates on critical features, bug fixes, and security risks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Top Talent Recruitment&lt;/strong&gt;: Leverage community channels for global talent recruitment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expanding Business Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: Establish potential business connections and collaborations with other members.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Join Karmada Adopter Group&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any company using Karmada&lt;strong&gt; in production environments&lt;/strong&gt; can apply to join the Group. Whether you are an end-user or a vendor, your participation is welcome.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;End-adopters&lt;/strong&gt;: Companies or organizations that use Karmada for multi-cloud or multi-cluster management within their internal IT infrastructure.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vendors:&lt;/strong&gt; Companies that integrate Karmada into their products or services to offer to other enterprises or organizations.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, there are no strict requirements for community contributions to join the Group. However, we encourage members to actively participate in community activities and share experiences and insights. Please note that future requirements may include contributions such as code submissions, documentation, issue resolutions, or use case sharing to maintain membership.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Visit the Karmada Adopter Group application form and submit an issue to start your newcloud-native&amp;nbsp; journey.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application Entry&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[1] Karmada Adopter Group Application Form: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/community/issues/new?template=adopter-group-application.yaml&#34;&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/community/issues/new?template=adopter-group-application.yaml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[2] For more details, visit:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/community/tree/main/adopter-group&#34;&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/community/tree/main/adopter-group&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Karmada Adopter Group welcomes your participation! For more information, please contact:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintainer Mailing List&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:cncf-karmada-maintainers@lists.cncf.io&#34;&gt;cncf-karmada-maintainers@lists.cncf.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;About Karmada&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Karmada is the first CNCF multi-cloud and multi-cluster container orchestration project (Incubating), designed to help manage multi-cloud clusters as easily as managing a single cluster. It seamlessly integrates multi-cloud solutions into the cloud-native ecosystem. Karmada contributors are worldwide from over 100 companies, spanning more than 20 countries and regions. Karmada is already in production use at organizations such as Huawei Cloud, DaoCloud, Xingye Digital Finance, China Mobile, China Unicom, Ctrip, 360 Group, Sina, and ZTO Express, providing smooth cloud-native transition solutions.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://karmada.io/&#34;&gt;https://karmada.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitHub: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada&#34;&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Slack Channel: &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;https://slack.cncf.io/&lt;/a&gt; (#karmada)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Karmada很高兴宣布采用组计划的启动。该计划旨在创建一个动态平台，采用者可以在其中有效连接，协作和共享信息。通过培养共同的经验和相互支持的环境，&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/karmada-io/community/community/community/main/main/main/adopter-group”&gt; karmada采用者&lt;/a&gt;希望在收养者和&lt;a a href =“ href =” href =“ href =” href =“ href =” href =“ href =” href =“/社区&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxeufvaw6onyxuqol84s7jvwisoenqizfsgbafsgbaf2zzirue_op5qxoldg7nr pcounkijrz50ixqcfwsxauloeuvlelo35J_NG3KVENE0OILWJS2Q98Z5XB3VXLXLX4RRS1LRYDMB1LX9EW？ alt =“ karmada采用者组图形” revyrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为一种开源多云和多簇容器编排引擎，&lt;a href =“ https:///karmada.io/”&gt; karmada &lt;/a&gt;自2021年开放式启动以来，它已经迅速发展，并成为2023年12月的CNCF培养项目，并与2023年12月的CNCF孵化，与2023年12月相比，跨越了20多个国家/地区。 Karmada已经成功地部署在数十家大型企业的生产环境中，是管理一般和异构计算资源的关键技术基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;得益于大量采用者的大力支持，Karmada通过有价值的反馈不断改进和优化。这种支持包括但不限于详细的使用反馈，发行决议和丰富的实践经验共享，这极大地促进了该项目的成熟度和稳定性。社区成员之间的密切合作使Karmada能够快速应对应用程序中的挑战并不断增强用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To further promote communication and collaboration, Karmada adopters can now&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/community/issues/new?template=adopter-group-application.yaml&#34;&gt; join the  group&lt;/a&gt; to connect with global developers and jointly explore multi-cluster technologies.这不仅有助于技术交流和最佳实践共享，而且为持续创新和发展奠定了坚实的基础。无论您是初学者还是经验丰富的用户，您都可以在此处找到所需的信息和帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H1 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;关于Karmada采用者组&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Karmada采用者组有一个专门的Google邮件组和GitHub组织团队，并为会员提供了重要的公告，更新和信息共享。主要功能包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;知识共享&lt;/strong&gt;：促进卡玛达采用者之间的经验，挑战和解决方案的交换。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;促进协作&lt;/strong&gt;：为采用者提供一个共同努力，分享想法和解决共同概率的平台柠檬。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;用户支持&lt;/strong&gt;：提供资源，教程和指导，以帮助采用者有效利用Karmada。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;反馈收集&lt;/strong&gt;：聆听用户反馈以指导Karmada的未来发展。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;社区活动&lt;/strong&gt;：通过常规聚会，网络研讨会和其他活动来增强社区参与。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;加入Karmada采用者小组，您可以与面临类似挑战的同行联系，寻求更适合您的解决方案和开发。包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;社区技术支持：&lt;/strong&gt;包括解决方案评估，日常操作，问题故障排除，版本升级等。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提高了可见性：&lt;/strong&gt;您的公司和团队的全球敞口&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;建立技术影响力：&lt;/strong&gt;在Kubecon和其他在线/离线会议等活动中共同创建技术演示的机会。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;保持知识：&lt;/strong&gt;及时更新关键功能，错误修复和安全风险&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;顶级人才招聘&lt;/strong&gt;：利用社区渠道进行全球人才招聘。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;扩大商机&lt;/strong&gt;：与其他成员建立潜在的业务联系和合作。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;加入Karmada采用者组&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在生产环境中使用Karmada &lt;strong&gt;的任何公司&lt;/strong&gt;都可以适用以加入小组。无论您是最终用户还是供应商，都欢迎您的参与。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;最终式式&lt;/strong&gt;：在其内部IT基础架构中使用Karmada用于多云或多群集管理的公司或组织。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;供应商：&lt;/strong&gt;将Karmada集成到其产品或服务中以向其他企业或组织提供的公司。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，没有严格的社区捐款要求加入该小组。但是，我们鼓励成员积极参与社区活动并分享经验和见解。请注意，未来的要求可能包括诸如代码提交，文档，发行决议或用例共享以维护会员资格之类的贡献。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;访问Karmada采用者组申请表，并提交一个问题以开始您的新云机构旅程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;应用程序条目&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; [1] Karmada采用者组申请表：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/karmada-io/community/issues/new?template= adopter-group-application.yaml”&gt; https：//github.com/karmada-io/karmada-io/community/community/sissues/new?template?template?template= adopter = adopter = adopter = adoptergroup-papplication.yammllapple.yamam &lt;/yamam &lt;//&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;P&gt; [2]有关更多详细信息，请访问：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/karmada-io/community/tree/main/main/adopter-group”&gt; https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada-io/community/community/tree/main/main/main/adopter-group-group-group-group-group-group &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Karmada采用者小组欢迎您的参与！有关更多信息，请联系：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;维护器邮件列表&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;a href =“ mailto：cncf-karmada-maintainers@lists.cncf.io”&gt; cncf-karmada-maintainers@lists.cncf.io &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H1 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;关于Karmada &lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Karmada是第一个CNCF多云和多群集容器编排项目（孵化），旨在帮助管理多云簇，就像管理单个群集一样。它无缝将多云解决方案集成到云本地生态系统中。 Karmada贡献者来自全球100多家公司，涵盖了20多个国家和地区。 Karmada已经在华为云，Daocloud，Xingye Digital Finance，中国移动，中国Unicom，Ctrip，360 Group，Sina和Zto Express等组织中使用了生产使用。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;网站：&lt;a href =“ https://karmada.io/”&gt; https://karmada.io/ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; github：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada”&gt; https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; slack频道：&lt;a href =“ https://slack.cncf.io/”&gt; https://slack.cncf.io/ &lt;/a&gt;（#karmada）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cedar: A New Approach to Policy Management for Kubernetes】雪松：Kubernetes政策管理的新方法</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/28/cedar-a-new-approach-to-policy-management-for-kubernetes/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The challenges organizations face when managing access control and authorization in cloud-native environments continue to grow in complexity. Organizations scaling their Kubernetes deployments, for example, work to balance their security requirements, operational flexibility, and policy manageability. &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/prescriptive-guidance/latest/saas-multitenant-api-access-authorization/cedar.html&#34;&gt;Cedar&lt;/a&gt;, an open-source policy language and evaluation engine, offers a fresh perspective for addressing these challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Cedar?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cedar is a policy language designed for modern authorization needs. Though traditional &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/reference/access-authn-authz/rbac/&#34;&gt;role-based access control&lt;/a&gt; (RBAC) serves as a foundation for many organizations and applications, Cedar extends beyond simple role assignments to provide more nuanced and powerful policy controls.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cedar is both human-readable and machine-analyzable. Its policy structure supports quick retrieval, real-time evaluation with bounded latency, and suitability for large-scale deployments. Automated reasoning tools use Cedar to analyze and optimize policies, helping administrators prove their security model behaves as intended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cedar for Kubernetes: Bridging the Gap&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, Kubernetes administrators have had to manage different policy frameworks and tools for different types of controls—one set of tools for authorization, another for admission control, and possibly others for additional security requirements. Numerous other challenges stem from Kubernetes RBAC’s existing limitations: RBAC is allow-only and does not support denials, it does not support attribute-based access or conditions, and it does not support any form of glob matching for selection.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cedar’s integration with Kubernetes overcomes these challenges. Administrators can write both authorization and admission policies by using the same language and framework. This significantly reduces cognitive overhead and the risk of security gaps that can occur when managing multiple policy systems. Additionally, Cedar supports rich condition operators that allow fine-grained permissions on specific resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cedar for Kubernetes uses a combination of pluggable authorization and admission validation webhooks to enforce access controls within a cluster.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As shown in the following diagram, Cedar can be used to validate multiple extension points in the Kubernetes API, where traditionally separate policy formats are used with authorization and admission validation to enforce access controls in Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXea8yOT-ok9g_ix2eXS2VF0hVl92yPYWva_d4KczV0zcq0odE1o1YyRNdxUbLshSI52xGCGAk-qg12Dj5WMeeJIb8s-hI-js7ns918rJ1p87IKp9ZSB1Uh5-Ml47lKSqzycJaiKizF0GHj5BRFqd00?key=DC-GUc3VWfaF0eM7OnAsVH_Q&#34; alt=&#34;How to use Cedar to validate multiple extension points&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Features and Benefits of Cedar for Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cedar for Kubernetes provides these key features and benefits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Label-based access controls and attribute-based rules that allow policy authors to construct policies that enforce new boundaries in a Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Custom resource definitions (CRDs) for storing Cedar policies directly in Kubernetes clusters. Users can use CRDs to define permissions as Kubernetes resources in a cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Compatibility with existing RBAC configurations through a converter. Users can easily migrate and customize existing policies without manual effort.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support for Kubernetes impersonation authorization so that users can easily author correct impersonation policies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automatic schema generation for Kubernetes built-in types and CRDs so that user-authored policies can be validated for correctness.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Unified policy management for both authorization and admission controls to reduce cognitive load on policy authors.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cedar for Kubernetes excels in its ability to maintain compatibility with existing RBAC configurations while providing sophisticated policy controls. This means organizations can gradually adopt Cedar without disrupting their current security posture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-World Applications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consider the common scenario of ensuring that all pods in a Kubernetes cluster have billing and owner labels set. With traditional policy frameworks, this might require separate tools and languages for enforcement. With Cedar, administrators can express both the permission to list, and create pods and the requirements for labels in the same policy file, making it easier for them to review and maintain security controls.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another common authorization need is to enable a security or observability pod the ability to list or modify other pods that are assigned to the same node. This is not possible today with Kubernetes RBAC, and operators often resort to granting an application more permissions than required, including permissions that can affect pods on other nodes. Cedar makes expressing this kind of attribute-based access simple and concise, enabling administrators to enforce tightly constrained least-privilege permissions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking Forward&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The cloud-native ecosystem continues to evolve, and with it, approaches to security and policy management must adapt. Cedar represents a step forward in this evolution, offering a new approach to policy management that aligns well with the cloud-native principles of scalability and automation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Organizations interested in exploring Cedar with Kubernetes can begin by using tools such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://kind.sigs.k8s.io/&#34;&gt;kind&lt;/a&gt; in development environments. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/awslabs/cedar-access-control-for-k8s&#34;&gt;Cedar for Kubernetes project&lt;/a&gt; is open source and welcomes community involvement. This means you can try Cedar for free without any cloud dependencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As Kubernetes deployments grow in complexity, the need for more sophisticated yet manageable policy controls is increasingly important. Cedar’s approach to policy management—combining human-readable policies with machine-analyzable capabilities—represents a promising direction for the future of cloud-native security.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cedar for Kubernetes’ integration and unification of authorization and admission controls under a single policy language addresses a need in Kubernetes security management. Though this integration continues to mature, Cedar’s core principles of unification, analyzability, and scalability align well with the challenges facing modern cloud-native deployments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cedar offers a path toward sophisticated, maintainable, and verifiable policy management for organizations looking to evolve their Kubernetes security strategies. As the Cedar for Kubernetes project continues to develop and gather community feedback, it has the potential to significantly improve how we approach authorization and policy management in cloud-native environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To read more about Cedar for Kubernetes, try it out locally, or contribute to it, see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/awslabs/cedar-access-control-for-k8s&#34;&gt;Cedar for Kubernetes GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are attending &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/register/&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025&lt;/a&gt;, then meet with us at the AWS Booth &lt;strong&gt;S300 to see demos on AWS open source projects.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在管理云本地环境中管理访问控制和授权时，组织面临的挑战继续在复杂性中增长。例如，组织扩展其Kubernetes部署，以平衡其安全要求，操作灵活性和策略可管理性。 &lt;a href =“ https://docs.aws.amazon.com/prescriptive-guidance/latest/saas-multitenant-api-api-apcess-authorization/cedar.html”&gt; scedar &lt;/a&gt;，一种开放式政策语言和评估引擎，为这些挑战提供了新的挑战。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是雪松？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;雪松是一种为现代授权需求而设计的政策语言。虽然传统&lt;a href =“ https://kubernetes.io/docs/reference/access-authn-authz/rbac/”&gt;基于角色的访问控制&lt;/a&gt;（RBAC）为许多组织和应用程序提供了许多简单的角色，但超越了更简单的角色分配，提供了更加努力和强大的策略控制和强大的策略控制。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cedar is both human-readable and machine-analyzable.其政策结构支持快速检索，实时评估，并具有有限的延迟，并适合大规模部署。自动推理工具使用Cedar来分析和优化策略，帮助管理员证明其安全模型的行为。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kubernetes的雪松：桥接间隙&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统上，Kubernetes管理员不得不为不同类型的控件管理不同的政策框架和工具 - 一组授权工具，另一个用于录取控制的工具，以及其他可能的其他安全要求。 Kubernetes RBAC的现有局限性造成的许多其他挑战：RBAC是仅允许的，不支持拒绝，它不支持基于属性的访问或条件，并且不支持任何形式的Glob selection选择。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Cedar与Kubernetes的集成克服了这些挑战。管理员可以使用相同的语言和框架来编写授权和入学策略。这大大降低了认知开销和管理多个策略系统时可能发生的安全差距的风险。此外，雪松还支持允许在特定资源上获得细粒度权限的丰富条件运算符。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; kubernetes的雪松使用了可插入授权和录取验证webhooks的组合来在集群中执行访问控制。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如下图所示，CEDAR可用于验证Kubernetes API中的多个扩展点，传统上单独的策略格式用于授权和录取验证以在Kubernetes中执行访问控制。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxea8yot-ok9g_ix2exs2vf0hvl92ypywva_d4kczv0zcqqqq0ode1o 1YyRNdxUbLshSI52xGCGAk-qg12Dj5WMeeJIb8s-hI-js7ns918rJ1p87IKp9ZSB1Uh5-Ml47lKSqzycJaiKizF0GHj5BRFqd00?key=Dc-guc3vwfaf0em7onasvh_q“ alt =”如何使用雪松验证多个扩展点“ referrerpolicy =” no-referrer&#39;&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Cedar对Kubernetes的关键特征和好处&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes的雪松提供了这些关键特征和好处：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;基于标签的访问控件和基于属性的规则，允许策略作者构建在Kubernetes群集中实施新边界的策略。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;直接在Kubernetes群集中存储雪松策略的自定义资源定义（CRD）。用户可以使用CRD来定义群集中的Kubernetes资源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过转换器与现有的RBAC配置的兼容性。用户可以在不手动努力的情况下轻松迁移和自定义现有政策。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持Kubernetes冒充授权，以便用户可以轻松地制定正确的模仿政策。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; kubernetes内置类型和CRD的自动架构生成，以便可以验证用户实现的策略以实现正确性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;授权和录取控制的统一政策管理，以减少政策作者的认知负担。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Kubernetes的&lt;p&gt;雪松在提供复杂的策略控制的同时保持与现有RBAC配置的兼容性的能力。这意味着组织可以逐渐采用Cedar而不会破坏其当前的安全姿势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;现实世界应用&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;考虑确保Kubernetes群集中的所有POD都设置计费和所有者标签的常见情况。借助传统的政策框架，这可能需要单独的工具和语言来执行。使用Cedar，管理员可以同时表达列出的权限，并创建POD和对同一策略文件中标签的要求，从而使他们更容易审核和维护安全控件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一个常见的授权需要是启用安全性或可观察性POD列出或修改分配给同一节点的其他POD的功能。 Kubernetes RBAC今天不可能做到这一点，并且运营商经常诉诸于申请的权限超过所要求的权限，包括可能影响其他节点的POD的许可。雪松使表达这种基于属性的访问简单简洁，使管理员能够执行紧密约束的最小特权权限。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;展望&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云本地生态系统继续发展，并且必须适应安全和政策管理的方法。雪松代表了这一进化中向前迈的一步，提供了一种新的政策管理方法，与可扩展性和自动化的云本地原理保持一致。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;有兴趣使用Kubernetes探索雪松的组织可以开始使用诸如&lt;a href =“ https:///kind.sigs.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.ios.k8s.k8s.ios.ios.k8s.k8s.k8s.ios.ios.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.k8s.ios.ios.ios.io.io &lt;/&gt; &lt;/&gt;环境。 &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/awslabs/cedar-access-control-for-k8s”&gt; kubernetes项目的雪松&lt;/a&gt;是开源的，欢迎社区参与。这意味着您可以免费尝试Cedar而无需任何云依赖。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;结论&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着Kubernetes部署的复杂性增长，对更复杂但可管理的政策控制的需求越来越重要。 Cedar的政策管理方法 - 将人类可读的政策与机器分析的能力结合起来 - 代表了云本地安全的未来的有前途的方向。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; cedar kubernetes的集成以及在单个政策语言下对Kubernetes Security Security Security Security Security Security Security Security Security Management of Kubernetes的整合和统一的授权和录取控制。尽管这种集成继续变得成熟，但Cedar的统一，分析性和可伸缩性的核心原则与现代云本地部署所面临的挑战非常吻合。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; Cedar为希望发展其Kubernetes安全策略的组织提供了一条通往先进，可维护和可验证的政策管理的途径。随着Kubernetes项目的Cedar继续发展和收集社区反馈，它有可能显着提高我们在云本地环境中处理授权和政策管理的方式。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;添加有关Kubernetes的Cedar的更多信息，在本地尝试或为其做出贡献，请参阅&lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/awslabs/cedar-access-control-for-k8s”&gt; kubernetes github存储库的雪松&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您要参加&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/register/”&gt; kubecon + kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025 &lt;/a&gt;然后，请与我们在AWS Booth &lt;strong&gt; S300与我们见面，请参见&lt;strong&gt; S300，请参见&lt;/aws Projects。&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Istio: The Highest-Performance Solution for Network Security】ISTIO：网络安全性最高绩效解决方案</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/27/istio-the-highest-performance-solution-for-network-security/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ambient mode provides more encrypted throughput than any other project in the Kubernetes ecosystem.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Encryption in transit is a baseline requirement for almost all Kubernetes environments today, and forms the foundation of a zero-trust security posture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the challenge with security is that it doesn’t come without a cost: it often involves a trade-off between complexity, user experience, and performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While most Cloud Native users will know of Istio as a service mesh, providing advanced HTTP functionality, it can also serve the role of providing a foundational network security layer. When we set out to build&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/docs/overview/dataplane-modes/#ambient-mode&#34;&gt; Istio’s ambient mode&lt;/a&gt;, these two layers were explicitly split. One of our primary objectives was to be able to offer security (and a long list of&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/docs/concepts/&#34;&gt; other features&lt;/a&gt;!) without compromise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With ambient mode, &lt;strong&gt;Istio is now the highest-bandwidth way to achieve a secure zero-trust network in Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lets look at some results before we dive into the how and why.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Putting it to the test&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To test performance, we utilized a standard network benchmarking tool,&lt;a href=&#34;https://iperf.fr/&#34;&gt; iperf&lt;/a&gt;, to measure the bandwidth of TCP traffic flowing through various popular Kubernetes network security solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc-v_dSOIT9zW97G_risTf2DclyVqq3qqa4zefRh6ZcFO4nH_mh1BOxOI46NGVWFRHyCGBOscUhqov-jice_bhpeZFuqNSUmSSKjfQPPbyQ2GUKejaE0533yhFBqHPEPXicgJIp?key=ECT8cSHbDu5C0PpuOldgOcds&#34; alt=&#34;TCP Throughput (higher is better)&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The results speak for themselves: Istio decisively leads the pack as the highest-performing network security solution. Even more impressive is that this gap continues to grow with each Istio release:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfiCt-ecaGG5xfTOXG20us3zJ1meEm7D9mypTPL1GKLzP7ST44W3E7vmC3sRsap_oaqoXIsJ20rPATRkCOMbSOIq50kFwgQTeRyZK3CaKNdEIaqMkFNt1fCUgHgNcuRMjTHNdvyvQ?key=ECT8cSHbDu5C0PpuOldgOcds&#34; alt=&#34;Ztunnel Performance by version&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio’s performance is driven by&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel&#34;&gt; ztunnel&lt;/a&gt;, a purpose built data plane that is light, fast, and secure. Over the last 4 releases, the performance of Ztunnel has improved by 75%!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Testing Details&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Implementations under test:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Istio: version 1.26 (prerelease), default settings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://linkerd.io/&#34;&gt;Linkerd&lt;/a&gt;: version edge-25.2.2, default settings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cilium.io/&#34;&gt;Cilium&lt;/a&gt;: version v1.16.6 with kubeProxyReplacement=true&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;WireGuard uses encryption.type=wireguard&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IPsec uses encryption.type=ipsec with the GCM-128-AES algorithm&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Additionally, both modes were tested with all of the recommendations in&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.cilium.io/en/stable/operations/performance/tuning/&#34;&gt; Cilium’s tuning guide&lt;/a&gt; (including netkit, native routing mode, BIGTCP (for WireGuard; IPsec is incompatible), BPF masquerade, and BBR bandwidth manager). However, the results were the same with and without these settings applied, so only one result is reported.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tigera.io/project-calico/&#34;&gt;Calico&lt;/a&gt;: version v3.29.2 with calicoNetwork.linuxDataplane=BPF and wireguardEnabled=true&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kindnet.es/&#34;&gt;Kindnet&lt;/a&gt;: version v1.8.5 with –ipsec-overlay=true.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some implementations only encrypt traffic cross-node, so are excluded from the same-node tests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tests were run on a single iperf connection (iperf3 -c iperf-server), averaging the result of 3 consecutive runs. The tests run on 16 core x86 machines running Linux 6.13. For various reasons, no implementation makes use of more than 1-2 cores when handling a single connection, so the core count is not a bottleneck.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: many of these implementations support HTTP control. This test does not exercise this functionality in any implementation.&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-vs-cilium/&#34;&gt; Previous posts&lt;/a&gt; have focused on this area of Istio.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Outpacing the Kernel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A very common perception in networking performance is that doing everything in the kernel, either natively or by using eBPF extensions, is the optimal way to achieve high performance. However, these results show the opposite effect: the user-space implementations – Linkerd and Istio – substantially outperform the kernel implementations. What gives?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One major factor is the speed of innovation. Performance is not static, and there is a constant progression of micro-optimizations, innovations, and adaptations to hardware improvements. The kernel serves a large number of use cases, and must evolve deliberately. Even when improvements are made, they can take many years to filter through to real world environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, user-space implementations are able to rapidly change and adapt to their specific targeted use cases, and run on any kernel version. Ztunnel is a great example of this effect in action, with substantial performance improvements coming in each quarterly release. A few of the most impactful changes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Migrating to rustls, a high performance TLS library focusing on safety (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/820&#34;&gt;#820&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reducing data copying on outbound traffic (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1012&#34;&gt;#1012&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dynamically tuning buffer sizes of active connections (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1024&#34;&gt;#1024&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Optimizing memory copies (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1169&#34;&gt;#1169&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Moving the cryptography library to AWS-LC, a high-performance cryptography library optimized for modern hardware (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1466&#34;&gt;#1466&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some other factors include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;WireGuard and Linkerd use the ChaCha20-Poly1305 encryption algorithm, while Istio uses AES-GCM. The latter is highly optimized on modern hardware.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;WireGuard and IPsec operate on individual packets (typically at most 1500 bytes, bound by the network MTU) while TLS operates on records of up to 16KB.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try ambient mode today&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking to enhance your cluster’s security without compromising on complexity or performance, now is the perfect time to try Istio’s ambient mode!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Follow the&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/getting-started/&#34;&gt; getting started guide&lt;/a&gt; to learn how easy it is to install and enable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can engage with the developers in the #ambient channel on&lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.istio.io/&#34;&gt; the Istio Slack&lt;/a&gt;, or use the&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/istio/discussions&#34;&gt; discussion forum on GitHub&lt;/a&gt; for any questions you may have.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;环境模式比Kubernetes生态系统中的任何其他项目提供了更多的加密吞吐量。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在运输中的加密是当今几乎所有kubernetes环境的基线要求，并构成了零值安全姿势的基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，安全性的挑战不是没有成本：它通常涉及复杂性，用户体验和性能之间的权衡。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然大多数云本地用户都会将ISTIO称为服务网格，并提供高级HTTP功能，但它也可以发挥提供基础网络安全层的作用。当我们着手构建&lt;a href =“ https://istio.io.io/latest/docs/overview/dataplane-modes/#ambient-mode”&gt; istio的环境模式&lt;/a&gt;，这两个层是明确拆分的。我们的主要目标之一是能够提供安全性（&lt;a href =“ https://istio.io.io/latest/docs/concepts/”&gt;其他功能&lt;/a&gt;！），而没有折衷。&lt;/p&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用环境模式，&lt;strong&gt; iStio现在是在Kubernetes中获得安全零值网络的最高带宽&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们在深入研究如何和原因之前先查看一些结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;将其放入测试&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要测试性能，我们使用了标准网络基准测试工具，&lt;a href =“ https://iperf.fr/”&gt; iperf &lt;/a&gt;，测量通过各种流行的Kubernetes网络安全解决方案流过的TCP流量的带宽。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxc-v_dsoit9zw97g_ristf2dclistf2dcqlyvqq q q q q q q q q q q q q q q q qqa4zefrh6zcfo4zecfo4nh_mh_mh1boxo i46ngvwfrhycgboscuhqov-jice_bhpezfuqnsumssskjfqppbbyq2gukejae0533yhfbqhpepepepticgjip？ alt =“ tcp吞吐量（更高）” reverrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结果自我说明：iStio果断地将该包作为表现最高的网络安全解决方案。更令人印象深刻的是，随着每个ISTIO的发布，此差距继续增长：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfict-ecagg5xftoxg20us3zj1meem7d9myptpl1gklzp7st444ww3e7vmc 3SRSAP_OAQOXISJ20RPATRKCOMBSOIQ50KFWGQTOREZK3CAKNDEIAQMKFNT1FCUGHGNCURMJTHNDVYVQ？ alt =“ ztunnel by by版本”“ reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; iStio的性能由&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/ztunnel”&gt; Ztunnel &lt;/a&gt;，一款专业的数据平面，轻巧，快速且安全。在过去的4个发行版中，Ztunnel的性能提高了75％！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;测试详细信息&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正在测试的实现：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; istio：版本1.26（预发行），默认设置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://linkerd.io/”&gt; linkerd &lt;/a&gt;：版本edge-25.2.2，默认设置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://cilium.io/”&gt; cilium &lt;/a&gt;：版本V1.16。6与kubeproxyplacement = true&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Wineguard使用gentryption.type = wireguard &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; iPSEC使用gentraption.type = ipsec与GCM-128-AES算法&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;此外，两种模式均在&lt;a href =“ https://docs.cilium.io/en/stable/performancation/performance/performance/tuning/”&gt; Cilium的调谐指南&lt;/a&gt;（包括NetKit，NetKit，NetKit，for bigbriber; ips insguard； 经理）。但是，在应用和没有这些设置的情况下，结果是相同的，因此仅报告一个结果。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.tigera.io/project-calico/”&gt; calico &lt;/a&gt;：版本v3.29.2 with caliconetwork.linuxdataplane = bpf and vireguardenable&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kindnet.es/”&gt; kindnet &lt;/a&gt;：版本v1.8.5 with –ipsec-overlay = true。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;某些实现仅加密流量交叉节点，因此从同一节点测试中排除了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;测试是在单个IPERF连接（IPERF3 -C IPERF -SERVER）上进行的，平均连续3次运行的结果。测试在运行Linux 6.13的16台Core X86机器上进行。由于各种原因，在处理单个连接时，没有实施不使用1-2个以上的内核，因此核心计数不是瓶颈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意：许多这些实现都支持HTTP控制。该测试不会在任何实现中行使此功能。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;超过内核&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;网络性能的一种非常普遍的看法是，在本质上或通过使用EBPF扩展，在内核中进行所有操作是实现高性能的最佳方法。但是，这些结果显示了相反的效果：用户空间实现（Linkerd和Istio）大大优于内核实现。什么给了？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个主要因素是创新速度。性能不是静态的，并且对硬件改进的微观选择，创新和适应性不断发展。内核提供大量用例，必须故意发展。即使进行了改进，它们也可能需要很多年才能过滤到现实世界环境。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;相比之下，用户空间实现能够快速更改并适应其特定的目标用例，并在任何内核版本上运行。 Ztunnel是这种行动中这种效果的一个很好的例子，每个季度发布中都有大量的性能提高。一些最有影响力的变化：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;迁移到Rustls，高性能TLS图书馆专注于安全（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/istio/ztunnel/pull/820”&gt;＃820 &lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;减少对出站流量复制的数据（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1012”&gt;＃1012 &lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/l我&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;活动连接的动态调整缓冲尺寸（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1024”&gt;＃1024 &lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;优化内存副本（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1169”&gt;＃1169 &lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将加密库库移至AWS-LC，这是一个针对现代硬件优化的高性能加密库（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/istio/ztunnel/pull/pull/1466”&gt;＃1466 &lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/li&gt;）。&lt;/li&gt;）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其他一些因素包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Wineguard和Linkerd使用CHACHA20-POLY1305加密算法，而ISTIO使用AES-GCM。后者对现代硬件进行了高度优化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Wireguard和Ipsec在单个数据包上运行（通常在最多1500个字节，由网络MTU绑定），而TLS则在最多16KB的记录上运行。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;今天尝试环境模式&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您希望在不妥协复杂性或性能的情况下增强集群的安全性，那么现在是尝试ISTIO环境模式的最佳时机！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;按照&lt;a href =“ https://istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/getting-started/”&gt;入门指南&lt;/a&gt;了解安装和启用的容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在&lt;a href =“ https://slack.istio.io/”上与#Ambient频道中的开发人员互动。&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Get to Know KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Co-Chair Faseela K.】了解Kubecon + Cloudnativecon联合主席Faseela K.</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/31/get-to-know-kubecon-cloudnativecon-co-chair-faseela-k/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Faseela Kundattil is one of those people who just seems to do a lot of things: Cloud Native Developer, project maintainer, CNCF Ambassador, LFX mentor, Technical Oversight Committee member, new mom, and now KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 Keynote speaker and co-chair. She even (co-)wrote the book on &lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2024/istio-phippy-book/&#34;&gt;Istio Service Mesh (for kids!)&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maybe cloud native is her super power? She certainly credits cloud native with giving her opportunities early in her career that she wouldn’t have had otherwise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I was just a few years into the industry but open source gave me a chance to contribute code upstream,” she says. “And the thing about open source was there were a lot of other companies who were collaborating with us on the same project.&amp;nbsp; So it was giving me some perspective about how we are able to work in a remote environment, but still collaborate with each other in a remote way. We were very efficient and all that learning came from open source ways of working.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even at a very early stage in her career, Faseela was able to travel and give talks. “It was good exposure for me,” she says. “I learned how to represent my company externally, but also to make sure everybody’s needs are met and ours are met too. Collaboration is something I really learned from open source.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her bottom line: “I do not think if you work in a single company, in a fully closed environment, you’ll get all this learning and collaboration and supporting each other kind of environment,” she explains. To get all that, it takes cloud native.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And it doesn’t hurt to have your family behind you either. “While cloud native may seem to be my superpower, I am really grateful to have a supportive family: my husband and my 10 year-old daughter who have extended all their support in the background taking care of our one year-old baby boy while I pay attention to my KubeCon responsibilities and&amp;nbsp; look like a super woman!”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How it all started&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Faseela, who is from India, started her career in Bangalore, spending nearly 11 years in the software networking industry. Her first role was at Ericsson as a Graduate Engineering Trainee after college and eventually she moved to Cisco as part of the platform engineering team. When Covid hit, she and her family decided to make the move to Europe and they settled in Aachen, Germany where she was able to return to Ericsson. The move made her happy, she says, because she was able to go back to working in open source. At Ericsson she’d worked on Linux Foundation projects including Open Daylight. “I really loved that. I missed those times because it was really that collaborative environment in open source,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Her return to Ericsson gave her the chance to work on a CNCF project, Istio, and she’s been deep into open source for these last three years. “I started as a normal contributor first, but I was soon able to become a maintainer and then later a steering committee member,” she says. Faseela has also served as the event co-chair for both the IstioDays co-located with KubeCon in 2023 and has been a Program Committee member at several KubeCons. And of course her day job keeps her busy too: she is a key member driving the 5G transformation of Ericsson, designing Cloud Native Network Functions and bridging the gap between telco and open source.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most recently, she’s been elected to the CNCF’s Technical Oversight Committee (the TOC), which is the governing body that gives technical directions for all the CNCF projects. And she is a co-chair for the upcoming three KubeCon + CloudNativeCons, “something I’m really looking forward to.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New to KubeCon? Faseela’s best advice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No matter where you are on your cloud native journey, you’ll find a place for you at KubeCon, of that Faseela is certain. “It’s like the best event or the best platform where you can network and get to know other experts from the industry and understand how cloud computing works and how to contribute to open source.” Her suggestions for those new to KubeCon: Pick &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;the beginner tracks&lt;/a&gt;, dive into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;ContribFests&lt;/a&gt;, don’t skip the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;KubeCrawl&lt;/a&gt;, consider the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Peer Group Mentoring opportunities&lt;/a&gt;, attend the live demos, &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu2025.sched.com/event/1vTiQ/project-pavilion-tour&#34;&gt;explore the Project Pavillion&lt;/a&gt;, and just network in the hallways.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t miss Faseela’s talks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She and co-author Lin Sun will be &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;speaking about their book Izzy Saves the Birthday&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Faseela and several others will be delivering a keynote on &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Evolution in Telecom: 5G, 6G and Beyond!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And she will also be at &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Contribfest: A Beginner’s Guide to Contributing to Istio&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; faseela kundattil是似乎做很多事情的人之一：云本地开发人员，项目维护者，CNCF大使，LFX导师，技术监督委员会成员，新妈妈和现在的Kubecon + Cloubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025 Keynote Keynote Keynote Speaker and Co-inder和联合主教。她甚至（共同）在&lt;a href =“ https://istio.io/latest/blog/2024/istio-phippy-book/”&gt; istio服务网格（For Kids！）&lt;/a&gt;上写了这本书。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;也许云本地人是她的超级力量吗？她当然会认为云本地人在职业生涯的早期就给自己的机会归功于她本来没有的机会。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我已经进入该行业只有几年了，但是开源给了我在上游贡献代码的机会，”她说。 “关于开源的事情是，还有许多其他公司与我们合作在同一项目上。因此，这给了我一些观点，即我们如何在偏远的环境中工作，但仍然以远程方式与彼此进行合作。我们非常有效，所有学习都来自开放源代码的工作方式。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使在她职业生涯的早期阶段，Faseela也能够旅行并进行演讲。她说：“这对我来说是个好曝光。” “我学会了如何在外部代表我的公司，但也要确保满足每个人的需求，也满足了我们的需求。合作是我真正从开源中学到的东西。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她的底线：“我认为，如果您在一家公司中工作，在一个完全封闭的环境中，您将获得所有这些学习，协作并互相支持的环境，”她解释说。为了获得所有这些，它需要云原生。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，让您的家人在您身后也没有什么坏处。 “虽然Cloud Native似乎是我的超级大国，但我真的很高兴有一个支持家庭的家庭：我的丈夫和我10岁的女儿，他们在背景中扩大了所有的支持，而我照顾了我们一岁的男婴，而我关注了我的库贝肯责任，看起来像个超级女人！” &lt;/p&gt;！” &lt;/p&gt;！&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;一切都开始&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;来自印度的&lt;p&gt; Faseela在班加罗尔开始了她的职业生涯，在软件网络行业工作了近11年。她的第一个职位是大学毕业后在爱立信担任研究生工程学员，最终作为平台工程团队的一部分移居思科。当Covid命中时，她和她的家人决定搬到欧洲，他们定居在德国的Aachen，在那里她能够返回爱立信。她说，此举使她开心，因为她能够回到开源工作。在爱立信，她从事Linux基金会项目，包括开放日光。她解释说：“我真的很喜欢。我错过了那些时代，因为这确实是开源的协作环境。”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她返回爱立信给了她有机会从事CNCF项目ISTIO的工作，她已经深入了最近三年的来源。她说：“我首先是正常的贡献者，但我很快就可以成为一名维护者，然后成为指导委员会成员。” Faseela还曾在2023年与Kubecon共同列为ISTIODAYS的活动共同主席，并一直是多个Kubecons的计划委员会成员。当然，她的日常工作也让她忙碌：她是驱动爱立信的5G转型，设计云本地网络功能并弥合电信公司和开源之间的差距的关键成员。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近，她当选为CNCF技术监督委员会（TOC），该委员会是管理机构，为所有CNCF项目提供了技术指导。她是即将到来的三个Kubecon + Cloudnativecons的联合主席，“我真的很期待。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;新的库贝肯？ Faseela的最佳建议&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您在云本地旅程中，您都可以在库贝肯找到一个faseela的地方。 “这就像最好的活动或最好的平台，您可以在这里建立网络并了解来自行业的其他专家，并了解云计算的工作原理以及如何为开源做出贡献。”她对新手Kubecon的建议：挑选&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt;初学者跟踪&lt;/a&gt;，潜入&lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt; conforfests &lt;/a&gt;，不要跳过&lt;a &lt;a &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; kubecrawl &lt;/a&gt;，考虑&lt;a href =“小组指导机会&lt;/a&gt;，参加现场演示，&lt;a href =“ https://kccnceu2025.sched.com/event/1vtiq/project-project-pavilion-tour”&gt;探索Project Project Project of Project Project Pavillion &lt;/a&gt;，并且只是在走廊上进行网络。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;不要错过Faseela的谈话&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她和合着者林太阳将是&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt;谈论他们的书Iszzy save y i zzzy挽救了生日&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; faseela和其他几个人将在&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt;电信中的云原生进化：5G，6G和超越！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她也将在&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/progm/program/schedule/”&gt; converfest：贡献到istio的初学者指南。&lt;/a&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Secure Kubernetes Edge Images with Kairos and k0s】用kairos和k0s构建安全的kubernetes边缘图像</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/25/building-secure-kubernetes-edge-images-with-kairos-and-k0s/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why combining these CNCF projects simplifies Kubernetes deployment at the edge.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge computing is rapidly changing the landscape of application deployment, demanding solutions that are lightweight, secure, and easily managed, particularly when it comes to Kubernetes distributions. Two projects under the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) umbrella, Kairos and k0s, present a compelling solution for constructing secure and immutable Kubernetes edge images. With the recent integration of k0s into Kairos, we aim to address these challenges more effectively. In this post, we’ll explore why this integration is significant and how it enhances edge deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For cloud-native professionals working with Kubernetes at the edge, balancing security, manageability, and performance remains a key challenge. This post explores how the integration of k0s and Kairos provides a streamlined approach to deploying secure, immutable Kubernetes edge images with minimal operational overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why k0s?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://k0sproject.io/&#34;&gt;k0s&lt;/a&gt; is a Kubernetes distribution that stands out for its lightweight nature and single-binary design, prioritizing simplicity. It achieves this by eliminating unnecessary dependencies while preserving full compatibility with Kubernetes. Key benefits of k0s include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No host OS dependencies – This characteristic allows k0s to run virtually anywhere, making it exceptionally well-suited for diverse edge scenarios where hardware and operating system standardization might be challenging.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lightweight and modular – The compact and modular nature of k0s makes it a perfect fit for constrained edge environments where resources like memory and storage might be limited.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Built-in security – By minimizing the number of moving parts, k0s inherently reduces the attack surface, enhancing security in edge deployments where vulnerabilities can be exploited.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While k0s is designed to be lightweight and modular, many traditional OSes introduce complexity and inconsistencies that can hinder edge deployments. Kairos provides an immutable, secure, and declarative foundation that complements k0s, ensuring a reliable platform for Kubernetes at the edge&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why Kairos?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Kubernetes distributions like k0s are designed for efficiency and portability, the underlying operating system can still introduce complexity, drift, and security risks—especially in edge environments. Kairos addresses this by transforming existing Linux distributions into immutable, secure, and declaratively managed OS images that are optimized for cloud-native infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Key capabilities include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Immutability&lt;/strong&gt; – Traditional configuration management tools help maintain consistency across a fleet, but they can’t entirely prevent drift or the emergence of “snowflake” machines. With immutability, the OS state remains unchanged between updates, ensuring a predictable and secure runtime environment while reducing the attack surface.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trusted Boot&lt;/strong&gt; – Kairos integrates Secure Boot and Unified System Images, ensuring that only signed and verified system components can execute. By leveraging hardware security features like Trusted Platform Modules (TPM), Kairos protects the boot process against tampering and enforces cryptographic validation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Declarative Configuration&lt;/strong&gt; – Kairos simplifies edge deployments with a &lt;strong&gt;cloud-init-like configuration model&lt;/strong&gt;, allowing teams to manage infrastructure in the same declarative way as cloud workloads.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vendor Agnostic&lt;/strong&gt; – Unlike traditional edge OS solutions that lock you into a specific Linux distribution, Kairos supports a wide range of existing distributions, including Ubuntu, openSUSE, Fedora, and Alpine, enabling organizations to use familiar tools and workflows.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By integrating with Kubernetes distributions like k0s, Kairos extends its immutability and security guarantees to the entire stack, making edge deployments &lt;strong&gt;more resilient, maintainable, and secure&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Power of k0s + Kairos&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By integrating Kairos with k0s, we create a Kubernetes edge stack that is not only lightweight and modular but also &lt;strong&gt;secure, immutable, and operationally simple&lt;/strong&gt;. This combination brings several advantages:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimal Footprint&lt;/strong&gt; – The single-binary design of k0s and the immutable infrastructure of Kairos drastically reduce system complexity, making edge nodes efficient and predictable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated, Declarative Deployment&lt;/strong&gt; – Kairos allows users to define their entire system—including OS and Kubernetes configuration—declaratively, ensuring that edge clusters can be deployed and updated with minimal manual intervention.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resilient &amp;amp; Self-Healing&lt;/strong&gt; – With an immutable OS and Kubernetes distribution, unexpected configuration drift is eliminated, reducing maintenance overhead and increasing reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;End-to-End Security&lt;/strong&gt; – By leveraging Secure Boot and trusted system images, the stack enforces cryptographic validation at every stage, from boot to runtime, making it highly resistant to tampering.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud-Native Consistency&lt;/strong&gt; – The combination of Kairos and k0s aligns with cloud-native operational models, enabling teams to manage Kubernetes at the edge using familiar GitOps and infrastructure-as-code practices.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With these capabilities, &lt;strong&gt;k0s and Kairos together form an ideal foundation for building, deploying, and managing Kubernetes clusters in edge environments where security, reliability, and simplicity are critical.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The integration of k0s and Kairos delivers a CNCF-backed stack that transforms the concept of &lt;strong&gt;secure, automated, and lightweight Kubernetes edge deployments into a tangible reality&lt;/strong&gt;. By seamlessly incorporating k0s into Kairos, we are making &lt;strong&gt;trusted, immutable, and remote-attestable Kubernetes clusters&lt;/strong&gt; readily accessible to the edge, paving the way for a new era of edge computing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get started, check out&lt;a href=&#34;https://kairos.io/&#34;&gt; Kairos&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;a href=&#34;https://k0sproject.io/&#34;&gt; k0s&lt;/a&gt; documentation. If you’re interested in seeing this integration in action, try deploying a secure Kubernetes edge node with Kairos and k0s today!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;为什么组合这些CNCF项目简化了边缘的Kubernetes部署。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;边缘计算正在迅速改变应用程序部署的景观，要求轻巧，安全且易于管理的解决方案，尤其是在Kubernetes发行版方面。云本机计算基础（CNCF）雨伞和K0的两个项目提出了一种令人信服的解决方案，用于构建安全且不可分割的Kubernetes边缘图像。随着K0的最新整合到Kairos，我们旨在更有效地解决这些挑战。在这篇文章中，我们将探讨为什么这种集成很重要以及如何增强边缘部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于与Kubernetes一起工作的云土机专业人员，平衡安全性，可管理性和性能仍然是一个关键挑战。这篇文章探讨了K0S和KAIROS的集成如何提供一种简化的方法，用于部署安全，不可变的Kubernetes边缘图像，并以最小的操作开销。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;为什么要K0S？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://k0sproject.io/”&gt; k0s &lt;/a&gt;是一个kubernetes分布，以其轻巧的性质和单二进制设计而脱颖而出，优先考虑简单性。它通过消除不必要的依赖性，同时保留与Kubernetes的完全兼容性来实现这一目标。 K0的主要好处包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;没有主机操作系统依赖性 - 此特征使K0几乎可以在任何地方运行，这非常适合用于多样化的边缘方案，而硬件和操作系统标准化可能具有挑战性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;轻巧和模块化 -  K0的紧凑和模块化性质使其非常适合受限的边缘环境，在内存和存储等资源可能受到限制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;内置安全性 - 通过最大程度地减少运动部件的数量，K0固有地降低了攻击表面，增强了可以利用漏洞的边缘部署的安全性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然K0S被设计为轻量级和模块化，但许多传统的OS会引入复杂性和不一致性，从而阻碍边缘部署。 Kairos提供了一个不变，安全且声明的基础，可以补充K0，确保了Edge的Kubernetes的可靠平台&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;为什么kairos？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然像K0S这样的Kubernetes分布是为了效率和可移植性而设计的，但基础操作系统仍然可以引入复杂性，漂移和安全风险，尤其是在边缘环境中。 Kairos通过将现有Linux分布转换为对云本地基础结构进行优化的不可变，安全和声明管理的OS图像来解决这一问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;关键功能包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;不变性&lt;/strong&gt;  - 传统的配置管理工具有助于保持机队的一致性，但它们可以”t完全防止漂移或“雪花”机器的出现。有了不变性，OS状态在更新之间保持不变，确保了可预测且安全的运行时环境，同时降低了攻击表面。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;值得信赖的引导&lt;/strong&gt;  -  Kairos集成了安全的启动和统一的系统图像，以确保仅签名和验证的系统组件才能执行。通过利用可信平台模块（TPM）之类的硬件安全功能，Kairos可以保护启动过程免受篡改并执行加密验证。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;声明配置&lt;/strong&gt;  -  Kairos使用&lt;strong&gt; cloud-init-init-int-Inig-like配置模型简化了边缘部署&lt;/strong&gt;，使团队能够以与云工作负载相同的声明方式管理基础架构。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;供应商不可知论&lt;/strong&gt;  - 与传统的边缘OS解决方案不同，您将您锁定在特定的Linux分布中，Kairos支持了广泛的现有分布，包括Ubuntu，Opensuse，Fedora，Fedora和Alpine，使组织能够使用熟悉的工具和工作库。&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过与Kubernetes分发集成，Kairos将其不可分割性和安全保证扩展到整个堆栈，使Edge部署&lt;strong&gt;更具弹性，可维护和安全&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; k0s + kairos &lt;/h2&gt;的力量&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过将kairos与K0集成在一起，我们创建了一个Kubernetes Edge堆栈，它不仅是轻巧和模块化的，而且还&lt;strong&gt;安全，不可变和操作简单&lt;/strong&gt;。这种组合带来了几个优点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;最小足迹&lt;/strong&gt;  -  K0S的单二元设计和Kairos的不变基础设施大大降低了系统的复杂性，从而使边缘节点有效且可预测。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自动化，声明性部署&lt;/strong&gt;  -  kairos允许用户定义其整个系统（包括OS和Kubernetes配置），以确保可以通过最小的手动干预来部署Edge簇。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;有弹性和自我修复&lt;/strong&gt;  - 随着不变的OS和Kubernetes分配，消除了意外的配置漂移，从而减少了维护开销并提高了可靠性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;端到端安全性&lt;/strong&gt;  - 通过利用安全的启动和受信任的系统图像，堆栈在每个阶段（从启动到运行时）执行加密验证，使其非常抵抗篡改。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云本地的一致性&lt;/strong&gt;  -  Kairos和K0s与云本地操作模型保持一致，使团队能够使用熟悉的Gitops和基础架构 -  As-As-Code实践来管理边缘的Kubernetes。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用这些功能，&lt;strong&gt; k0和kairos共同构成了在Edge Envi中建造，部署和管理Kubernetes群集的理想基础安全性，可靠性和简单性至关重要的措施。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;结论&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; K0S和Kairos的集成提供了CNCF支持的堆栈，该堆栈将&lt;strong&gt;安全，自动化和轻量级的Kubernetes Edge部署的概念转变为有形的现实&lt;/strong&gt;。通过将K0无缝纳入kairos，我们正在使&lt;strong&gt;可信赖，不可能且遥不可及的Kubernetes群集&lt;/strong&gt;很容易到达边缘，为Edge Computing的新时代铺平了道路。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要入门，请查看&lt;a href =“ https://kairos.io/”&gt; kairos &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ https://k0sproject.io/”&gt; k0s &lt;/a&gt;文档。如果您有兴趣看到此集成在行动中，请尝试使用Kairos和K0S部署安全的Kubernetes Edge节点！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The End User TAB’s top talks at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025】最终用户选项卡在Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe的顶级谈判2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/31/the-end-user-tabs-top-talks-at-kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you are attending the upcoming KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 conference in London, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/people/end-user-technical-advisory-board/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF End User Technical Advisory Board (TAB)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; member recommendations for their top talk recommendations! 🙂&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ahmed Bebars:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the rich and captivating topics at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025, it is difficult to narrow down on just a few sessions for attendance. Nonetheless, I consider these two a “must”:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Metal To Apps: LinkedIn’s Kubernetes-based Compute Platform – Ahmet Alp Balkan &amp;amp; Ronak Nathani, LinkedIn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn must enable “bare-metal” servers to serve as a computing platform for applications; however, integration is key to flexibility. Insight from Ahmet Alp Balkan and Ronak Nathani on how challenges of tenant isolation, resilience, and developer usability are solved at such massive scales is crucial to understanding large-scale infrastructure transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lessons Learned From Architecting the Highest-scale Operational Systems in the World – Artur Bergman, Fastly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of the world’s largest systems contain a treasure trove of knowledge, and Artur Bergman manages them. His attention to detail with resilient and recovery-focused systems, specifically those intended to prevent cascading failures and enable rapid recovery, is important when building robust and scalable systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These sessions are unparalleled for those curious about how to build and manage large-scale, resilient infrastructures due to the immense focus and solutions straightforward challenges operating at scale deal with.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alolita Sharma:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are a lot of excellent talks at every KubeCon + CloudNativeCon conference. Some of the talks making it to my must-attend list this year include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Town Hall Panel Discussion: End User Technical Advisory Board (TAB) Town Hall&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? Come meet the CNCF’s end-user TAB! Learn about the TAB’s initiatives on reference architectures, project health and feedback. And use this opportunity to ask questions about areas where and how end-users can get involved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Project Lightning Talk: Perses Update – Augustin Husson, Maintainer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? Perses is a project that has the potential of changing the current open source observability landscape with the development of a new and unified UI framework that will present observability analysis dashboards and results out of the box. This talk will focus on project progress, features and roadmap which is key for end-users looking to have a cloud-native choice for observability user interfaces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Keynote: AI Enabled Observability Explainers – We Actually Did Something With AI! – Vijay Samuel, Principal MTS, Architect, eBay&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? AI/ML continues to make deeper inroads in analyzing telemetry data and understanding systems at scale. eBay, an end-user building cloud-native observability solutions will be talking about how they have used AI algorithms to understand their telemetry metrics, traces and logs to create more predictable and accurate AI enabled observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: First Day Foresight: Anomaly Detection for Observability – Prashant Gupta &amp;amp; Kruthika Prasanna Simha, Apple&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? This end-user talk dives into the&amp;nbsp; benefits of using pre-trained ML models for day one anomaly detection. Using lightweight, unsupervised pre-trained models using cloud-native tools like Kubeflow for model fine-tuning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: An Exemplary Path: Leveraging EBPFs and OpenTelemetry To Auto-instrument for Exemplars – Charlie Le &amp;amp; Kruthika Prasanna Simha, Apple&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? Another interesting end-user talk takes a look at using exemplars effectively in an automated way by collecting eBPF data with OpenTelemetry and correlating application and kernel telemetry data to understand system performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: Designing a Common Query Language for Observability Data – Alolita Sharma, Apple; Pereira Braga, Google; Chris Larsen, Netflix&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unifying query languages is key in reducing toil for app developers and end users to query and analyze observability data. A common query language that can leverage all observability data such as metrics, traces, profiles, events, logs to facilitate correlation, support trend analytics and provide end-to-end observability for AI applications. End users from Netflix and Apple have been driving the Observability TAG QLS workgroup to define and finalize a semantic query language spec in 2025 and are recommending SQL as a basis with further experimentation on syntaxes. This talk will explore the trade-offs between simplicity, expressiveness, and performance. This query language convergence for end-to-end analytics could enhance reliability and operational efficiency for SREs and your app developers. This could be a win-win for all end-users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kenta Tada:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are many excellent sessions at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025, addressing key challenges and innovations in cloud-native adoption. As organizations continue to scale their cloud infrastructure, efficient observability and extensibility are becoming critical for maintaining performance and reliability. I’d like to highlight two sessions that offer practical insights for end-user organizations on leveraging eBPF—one for enhancing userspace extensibility and another for gaining deep, network visibility without infrastructure modifications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: eBPF and Wasm: Unifying Userspace Extensions With Bpftime – Yusheng Zheng, eunomia-bpf&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As end-user organizations seek to extend and customize their cloud-native environments, both eBPF and Wasm offer compelling solutions—eBPF for kernel-level optimizations and Wasm for userspace sandboxing. However, both face challenges when userspace extensions need to interact deeply with host applications. This session by Yusheng Zheng introduces bpftime, a novel framework that extends eBPF’s capabilities into userspace without the overhead of Wasm’s sandboxing. If your organization is looking for a high-performance and secure way to extend applications using uprobe and XDP in a userspace eBPF runtime, don’t miss this session!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: Using eBPF for Non-invasive, Performant, Instant Network Monitoring – Mario Macías &amp;amp; Marc Tudurí, Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For end-user organizations, gaining network visibility without disrupting existing infrastructure is a major challenge. This session by Mario Macías and Marc Tudurí from Grafana showcases how eBPF enables lightweight, non-invasive network monitoring across layers L3 to L7 without requiring infrastructure modifications. Their approach integrates low-level network telemetry with Kubernetes metadata, providing actionable insights into service communication and traffic patterns. If your organization is looking to enhance observability while minimizing overhead, this session is highly recommended!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ricardo Rocha:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KubeCon +CloudNativeCon keeps delivering, in size and in quality. The London event will again keep a strong focus on end users, with a large number of sessions reporting experiences and best practices for a variety of use cases. These are usually my favorite sessions, together with those where community members from different vendors and organizations got together to tackle very hard problems. Hard to pick but here goes one example from each of these two categories.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session: Kubernetes WG Device Management – GPUs, TPUs, NICs and More With DRA – Kevin Klues, NVIDIA &amp;amp; Patrick Ohly, Intel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the hype and demand still strong, the usage of accelerators for AI and other workloads keeps growing. But looking at the longer term, the success of these new ways of computing at scale will require more efficient, sustainable use of these expensive resources. The DRA effort has shown how our community can gather and work together to deliver now the features that will help us succeed in the future. This kubecon includes several other talks about Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA), including some from my organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session: The Bricks That Make Us – How the LEGO Group Avoids 50 Mediocre Kubernetes Implementations – Thomas Øther Rasmussen &amp;amp; Paul Farver, The LEGO Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why I’m Interested:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Being a huge LEGO fan I’m far from being alone in our community. Hearing about the challenges faced by the LEGO group scaling out platforms and teams makes for a very interesting and entertaining session, with lessons to be learned by end users from all domains. With great speakers as well, this will be a session not to be missed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re not registered yet, there’s still plenty of time to catch these sessions – and many more – in person. Also, come say Hi and meet us &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;at the TAB session on Friday April 4 2025&lt;/a&gt;. See you there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;If you are attending the upcoming KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 conference in London, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/people/end-user-technical-advisory-board/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF End User Technical Advisory Board (TAB)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; member recommendations for their top talk recommendations! 🙂&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;艾哈迈德·贝巴尔（Ahmed Bebars）：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在2025年库贝康 + Cloudnativecon欧洲的富裕和迷人的话题中，很难只参加几次会议才能参加。尽管如此，我认为这两个是“必须”：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; LinkedIn必须启用“裸机”服务器作为应用程序的计算平台；但是，集成是灵活性的关键。艾哈迈德·阿尔普·巴尔干（Ahmet Alp Balkan）和罗纳克·纳撒尼（Ronak Nathani）的洞察力对租户隔离，弹性和开发人员的可用性的挑战如何在如此庞大的规模上解决对于理解大规模的基础设施转换至关重要。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;从架构中汲取的经验教训，从世界上汲取的最高规模的操作系统 -  Artur Bergman  -  Artur Bergman，快速&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/prally&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;世界上一些最大的系统包含知识的宝库，Artur Bergman对其进行了管理。在建立强大而可扩展的系统时，他对以弹性和以恢复为中心的系统的关注非常重要。&lt;/p&gt;，很重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于那些对如何建立和管理大规模弹性基础设施的人来说，这些会议是无与伦比的，这是由于巨大的重点和解决方案在大规模上运行的直接挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Alolita Sharma：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在每次Kubecon + Cloudnativecon会议上都有许多出色的演讲。一些会谈将其列入我今年的必不可少的列表包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？快来遇到CNCF的最终用户标签！了解有关参考架构，项目健康和反馈的标签计划。并利用这个机会来询问有关最终用户在哪里以及如何参与的领域的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;项目闪电谈话：perses更新 - 奥古斯丁·侯赛因（Augustin Husses），维护者&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/prong&gt; &lt;/p &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？ Perses是一个具有更改当前开源可观察性的项目随着新的统一UI框架的开发，景观将展示可观察性分析仪表板和结果。这次演讲将重点介绍项目进度，功能和路线图，这对于希望有云代表选择用户界面的最终用户是关键。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;emt&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; keynote：ai启用可观察力的解释器 - 实际上是用AI做的！ -  Vijay Samuel，主要MTS，建筑师，eBay &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？ AI/ML继续在分析遥测数据和大规模理解系统方面更加深入。 eBay，最终用户建筑物云本地可观察性解决方案将讨论他们如何使用AI算法来了解其遥测指标，痕迹和日志以创建更可预测和准确的AI启用AI的可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; sessign：第一天的预见：观察到可观察性 -  prashant gupta＆kruthika＆kruthika＆kruthika＆kruthika prasika prasha prasha simha，apple sim &lt;/em em&gt; &lt;/&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？该最终用户谈话深入了解第一天的异常检测中使用预训练的ML模型的好处。使用轻巧的，无监督的预训练模型，使用云原生工具（例如KubeFlow）进行微调。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: An Exemplary Path: Leveraging EBPFs and OpenTelemetry To Auto-instrument for Exemplars – Charlie Le &amp; Kruthika Prasanna Simha, Apple &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么？另一个有趣的最终用户谈话通过使用OpenTelemetry和将应用程序和内核遥测数据收集EBPF数据来有效地使用示例来了解系统性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; session：设计一种常见的Query语言，用于过时性数据 -  Alolita Sharma，Apple，Apple，Apple; Pereira Braga，Google；克里斯·拉尔森（Chris Larsen），netflix &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;统一查询语言是减少应用程序开发人员的辛劳和最终用户查询和分析可观察性数据的关键。一种通用的查询语言，可以利用所有可观察性数据，例如指标，迹线，配置文件，事件，日志来促进相关性，支持趋势分析并为AI应用程序提供端到端可观察性。 Netflix和Apple的最终用户一直在推动可观察性标签QLS工作组，以定义和最终确定2025年的语义查询语言规范，并建议SQL作为语法进一步实验。这次演讲将探讨简单，表现力和性能之间的权衡。端到端分析的这种查询语言融合可以提高可靠性和运行SRES和您的应用程序开发人员的效率。对于所有最终用户来说，这可能是双赢的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;肯塔·塔达（Kenta Tada）：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2025年的库贝肯 + Cloudnativecon欧洲有许多出色的会议，以应对云原始采用的主要挑战和创新。随着组织继续扩展其云基础架构，有效的可观察性和可扩展性对于维持性能和可靠性至关重要。我想强调两个会议，为最终用户组织提供实用的见解，以利用EBPF，可提高用户空间的扩展性，而另一项可在没有基础架构修改的情况下获得深度，网络可见性。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; session：ebpf和wasm：ebpf and wasm：bpftime – yusheng zheng zheng zheng，eunhom ppf &lt;/emunom pff &lt;/em em pff &lt;/em em&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着最终用户组织寻求扩展和自定义其云本地环境，EBPF和WASM提供了引人注目的解决方案 - 用于内核级优化的EBPF，以及用于用户空间沙盒的WASM。但是，当用户空间扩展需要与主机应用程序进行深入互动时，这两者都面临挑战。 Yusheng Zheng的这次会议介绍了Bpftime，这是一个新颖的框架，将EBPF的功能扩展到了Userspace，而没有WASM的沙盒开销。如果您的组织正在寻找一种高性能和安全的方法，以在用户空间EBPF运行时使用Uprobe和XDP扩展应用程序，请不要错过此会话！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Session: Using eBPF for Non-invasive, Performant, Instant Network Monitoring – Mario Macías &amp; Marc Tudurí, Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于最终用户组织而言，在不中断现有基础设施的情况下获得网络可见性是一个主要挑战。 MarioMacías和MarcTudurí的这次会议展示了EBPF如何在不需要基础架构修改的情况下，在L3至L7层之间实现了轻巧的非侵入性网络监视。他们的方法将低级网络遥测与Kubernetes元数据集成在一起，从而提供了对服务通信和流量模式的可行见解。如果您的组织希望在最小化开销时提高可观察性，则强烈建议您进行此会议！&lt;/p&gt;！&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Ricardo Rocha：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubecon +CloudNativeCon保持尺寸和质量。伦敦活动将再次重点关注最终用户，并为各种用例提供​​大量的会议报告经验和最佳实践。这些通常是我最喜欢的会议，以及来自不同供应商和组织的社区成员聚在一起解决非常困难的问题的会议。很难选择，但这里有一个例子从这两个类别中的每个类别中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; session：kubernetes wg设备管理 -  gpus，tpus，tpus，tpus，nics，nics及其更多 -  kevin kevin kevin klues＆kevin klues＆patrick＆patrick＆patrick，英特尔&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着炒作和需求仍然强劲，加速器对AI和其他工作量的使用不断增长。但是，从长远来看，这些新的计算方式的成功将需要对这些昂贵的资源进行更有效，可持续的使用。 DRA的努力表明，我们的社区如何聚集和共同努力，以提供帮助我们将来成功的功能。这个库贝孔还包括有关动态资源分配（DRA）的其他几次讨论，其中包括我的组织中的一些。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/program/schedule/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; sessign&gt; &lt;strong&gt; session：使我们 - 乐高乐团如何避免50个中高级库伯尼特的实施 - &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么我有兴趣：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Being a huge LEGO fan I’m far from being alone in our community.听到乐高集团扩大平台和团队所面临的挑战，这是一个非常有趣且有趣的会议，最终用户可以从所有域中吸取教训。凭借出色的演讲者，这将是不容错过的会议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您尚未注册，仍然有足够的时间亲自捕捉这些会议以及更多的会议。另外，快来打个招呼并与我们见面&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/schedule/&gt;在2025年4月4日星期五的表会议上。在那里见！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Two New Cloud Native Heroes Challenges】宣布两个新的云土著英雄挑战</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/31/announcing-two-new-cloud-native-heroes-challenges/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Help us defeat a patent troll claiming methods for “manipulation of complex hierarchical data” and “analysis of hierarchical data” were invented in 2005&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to launch 2 additional &lt;a href=&#34;http://cncf.io/heroes&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Heroes Challenge&lt;/a&gt; contests in which you can earn swag, a ticket to attend a KubeCon+CloudNativeCon, and/or a US $3,000 cash prize by helping defend our ecosystem from patent trolls.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking information to invalidate claims of 2 different US patents asserted by patent troll Lower48 IP, LLC against Shopify. Each patent is featured in a separate contest with its own prizes. You can enter either contest without entering the other, but if you do enter both contests, you’ll have 2 chances to win!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Keep reading to learn about these contests and how you can enter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First Contest &amp;amp; Challenged Patent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first challenged patent (US-7681177-B2) relates to a method and system for transforming data between hierarchical structures, notably trees and symbol strings, aiming to simplify manipulation of complex hierarchical data. We’re seeking prior art to invalidate Claim 1 of this patent, which reads as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;1. A method comprising:executing instructions by a processor to:transform one or more electrical digital signals representing one or more trees to one or more electrical digital signals representing one or more corresponding symbol strings according to an association of trees and symbol strings comprising up to two or more grouping symbol types, said one or more symbol strings being associated with one or more corresponding numerals according to an association of symbol strings and numerals; andmanipulate said one or more signals representing said one or more symbol strings to provide one or more electrical digital signals representing a resulting symbol string corresponding with a resulting numeral according to said association of symbol strings and numerals,wherein said resulting numeral is representative of an arithmetic operation on said one or more corresponding numerals.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This patent has a priority date of February 27, 2005. For more information, see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://patroll.unifiedpatents.com/contests/nejqD8M975WrKxFTY&#34;&gt;’77 contest entry page&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://portal.unifiedpatents.com/patents/patent/US-7681177-B2&#34;&gt;’77 patent information&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second Contest and Challenged Patent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second challenged patent (US-11100070-B2) focuses on methods and systems for manipulating and analyzing hierarchical data, particularly through transformations into tree structures. We’re seeking prior art to invalidate Claim 1 of this patent. The full text of Claim 1 is below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;1. A method of querying a database, or a portion thereof, comprising:accessing instructions from one or more physical memory devices for execution by one or more processors;executing the instructions accessed from the one or more physical memory devices by the one or more processors;storing, in at least one of the physical memory devices, signal values, including numerical signal values, resulting from having executed the accessed instructions on the one or more processors, wherein the one or more physical memory devices also store the database, or the portion thereof;wherein the accessed instructions to transform the database, or the portion thereof, to the form of a hierarchically structured tree via one or more numerical signal values corresponding to content within the database, or the portion thereof;wherein the executing the transformation instructions comprises:generating the hierarchically structured tree via the one or more numerical signal values, the hierarchically structured tree comprising electronic content including binary digital signals and/or states; andwherein the executing the transformation instructions comprises:presenting a query to the database, or the portion thereof, via at least one numerical signal value to fetch the content within the database, or the portion thereof.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This patent has a priority date of April 28, 2005. For more information, see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://patroll.unifiedpatents.com/contests/FupbzXSAj9HHcfWvv&#34;&gt;’70 contest entry page&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://portal.unifiedpatents.com/patents/patent/US-11100070-B2&#34;&gt;’70 patent information&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Call for Prior Art&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/heroes/#what-is-prior-art&#34;&gt;“Prior art”&lt;/a&gt; is a legal term that refers to technical know-how that predated the patent application. Prior art can be used to invalidate or weaken a troll’s patent by demonstrating that the patented invention already existed and wasn’t “new” when the application for a patent was filed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are aware of any publicly available materials demonstrating that know-how regarding all of the elements of the invention described above already existed &lt;strong&gt;prior to September 26, 2017 &lt;/strong&gt;(the priority date of the challenged patent), please submit that evidence as “prior art” in this contest. However, please note that materials already listed in the “known references” tab of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://patroll.unifiedpatents.com/contests/mJ5QT4wkDCCjhy9xb&#34;&gt;Contest Description&lt;/a&gt; do not qualify and cannot be submitted in this contest.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Examples of materials that can be provided as prior art include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open source documentation, including release notes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Articles, books, and other publications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Written records of presentations at tech conferences&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Product manuals or descriptions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Standards and specification documents&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Any other publicly available documentation (in English) that existed prior to the challenged patent priority date&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Other patents with a priority date earlier than the priority date for the challenged patents&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instructions for Participating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please see our &lt;a href=&#34;http://cncf.io/heroes/participation-instructions&#34;&gt;Participation Instructions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://cncf.io/heroes&#34;&gt;the Heroes Challenge program page&lt;/a&gt; for more information and step-by-step instructions for entering &lt;a href=&#34;https://patroll.unifiedpatents.com/contests/mJ5QT4wkDCCjhy9xb&#34;&gt;this contest&lt;/a&gt;. Remember, a variety of prizes are available, and all entrants will receive a free Cloud Native Hero t-shirt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have questions or would like to request a 1:1 help session where a member of our Heroes Challenge team walks you through any aspect of the contest entry process, please message us at the CNCF slack channel &lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud-native.slack.com/archives/C07UZJRHZPY&#34;&gt;#heroes-challenge&lt;/a&gt; or at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:heroes@cncf.io&#34;&gt;heroes@cncf.io&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Know of Prior Art but don’t want to enter the Contest?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you would like to inform us of prior art without entering the contest, please email us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:heroes@cncf.io&#34;&gt;heroes@cncf.io&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Our Co-Host for the Cloud Native Heroes Challenge&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF is co-hosting this program with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.unifiedpatents.com/&#34;&gt;Unified Patents&lt;/a&gt;, the Linux Foundation’s partner in patent troll deterrence since 2019. Unified Patents is the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; organization that uses offensive community-driven strategies to deter patent trolls.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other relevant posts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/01/22/meet-the-winners-of-our-first-cloud-native-heroes-challenge/&#34;&gt;Learn from the Winners of our first Cloud Native Heroes Challenge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/12/announcing-the-cloud-native-heroes-challenge/&#34;&gt;Announcing the Cloud Native Heroes Challenge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/09/16/cncf-and-the-linux-foundation-partner-with-unified-patents-on-a-community-driven-approach-to-safeguard-open-source-innovation-from-patent-trolls/&#34;&gt;CNCF Partners with Unified Patents on a Community-Driven Approach to Safeguard Open Source from Patent Trolls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;在2005年发明了一种“操纵复杂层次数据”和“分析层次数据”的专利巨魔要求的方法。&lt;/em&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴启动2个额外的&lt;a href =“ http://cncf.io/heroes”&gt;云土著英雄挑战赛&lt;/a&gt;您可以在其中赢得赃物的票，参加Kubecon+Cloudnativecon的票，以及/或我们的3,000美元现金奖，通过为我们的EcoSosystem提供3,000美元的现金奖，以防御我们的EcoSystem，以防御我们的EcoSystem。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在寻求信息，以使专利巨魔Lower48 IP，LLC对Shopify的2种不同美国专利的索赔无效。每项专利都有自己的奖品的单独竞赛。您可以在不输入对方的情况下参加比赛，但是如果您确实输入了两个比赛，那么您将有2个机会赢得比赛！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;继续阅读以了解这些比赛以及如何输入。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;首次竞赛和挑战专利&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第一个挑战的专利（US-7681177-B2）与一种方法和系统有关，用于在层次结构（尤其是树木和符号字符串）之间转换数据，旨在简化对复杂层次数据的操纵。我们正在寻求先前的艺术，以使本专利的权利要求1无效，该专利的读物如下：&lt;/p&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-table”&gt; &lt;table class =“已经固定的layout”&gt; &lt;tbody&gt; &lt;try&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; 1。 A method comprising:executing instructions by a processor to:transform one or more electrical digital signals representing one or more trees to one or more electrical digital signals representing one or more corresponding symbol strings according to an association of trees and symbol strings comprising up to two or more grouping symbol types, said one or more symbol strings being associated with one or more corresponding numerals according to an association of symbol strings and numerals; Andmanipulate表示，代表一个或多个信号表示一个或多个符号字符串，以提供一个或多个电气数字信号，代表由此产生的符号字符串，根据符号和数字的上述数字相对应，其中所述的数字代表一个或多个相应的数字上的算法操作。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该专利的优先日期为2005年2月27日。有关更多信息，请参见&lt;a href =“ https://patroll.unifiedpatents.com/contests/contests/nejqd8m975wrkxfty” href =“ https://portal.unifiedpatents.com/patents/patent/us-7681177-b2”&gt; ’77专利信息&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第二次比赛和挑战专利&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第二项受到挑战的专利（US-11100070-B2）着重于操纵和分析层次数据的方法和系统，尤其是通过转换为树结构。我们正在寻求先前的艺术，以使本专利的权利要求1无效。权利要求1的全文如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-table”&gt; &lt;table class =“固定layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;1. A method of querying a database, or a portion thereof, comprising:accessing instructions from one or more physical memory devices for execution by one or more processors;executing the instructions accessed from the one or more physical memory devices by the one or more processors;storing, in at least one of the physical memory devices, signal values, including numerical signal values, resulting from having executed the在一个或多个处理器上访问的指令，其中一个或多个物理内存设备还存储数据库或其部分；其中访问的指令将数据库或其部分转换为层次结构的树的形式，通过一个或多个数值信号值与数据库中的内容相对应的内容，或者在contrient contrestion contrestion commistion commistion commistion commistion;通过一个或多个数值信号值结构化树，层次结构化的树包含电子内容，包括二进制数字信号和/或状态；在执行转换指令的何处包括：通过至少一个数值信号值向数据库或其部分提出查询，以获取数据库中的内容或其部分。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该专利的优先日期为2005年4月28日。有关更多信息，请参见&lt;a a href =“ https://patroll.unifiedpatents.com/contests/fupbzxsaj9hhchcfwvv”&gt; ’70竞赛入门页面&lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://portal.unifiedpatents.com/patents/patent/us-1100070-b2”&gt; ’70专利信息&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;呼吁先验艺术&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/heroes/#what-what-is-prior-art”&gt;“先前的艺术” &lt;/a&gt;是一个法律术语，是指早于专利申请的技术知识。可以通过证明已有专利的发明已经存在，并且在提交专利的申请时并不是“新的”，可以使用先前的艺术来使巨魔的专利无效或削弱巨魔的专利。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您知道任何公开可用的材料，证明了有关上述本发明的所有要素的知识，那么在2017年9月26日之前已经存在&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;（挑战专利的优先日期），请将证据作为本竞赛中的“先前艺术”。但是，请注意，&lt;a href =“ https://patroll.unifiedpatents.com/contests/mj5qt4wkdccjhy9xb” &lt;a href =“已知参考”选项卡中已列出的材料&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可以提供的材料的示例包括：&lt;/p&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;开源文档，包括发行笔记&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;文章，书籍和其他出版物&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在技术会议上的演示文稿的书面记录&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;产品手册或描述&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;标准和规范文档&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在受到挑战专利优先日期之前存在的任何其他公开可用的文档（英文）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;其他优先级的专利早于挑战专利的优先日期&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;参与的说明&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请参阅我们的&lt;a href =“ http://cncf.io/heroes/participatipation-instructions”&gt;参与指令&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ http://cncf.io/heroes”&gt;英雄挑战计划页面&lt;/a&gt;以获取更多信息和Stepby-Step clangions &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/ href =“ https://patroll.unifiedpatents.com/contests/mj5qt4wkdccjhy9xb”&gt;这场比赛&lt;/a&gt;。请记住，有各种各样的奖品，所有参赛者都会收到一件免费的云本地英雄T恤。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have questions or would like to request a 1:1 help session where a member of our Heroes Challenge team walks you through any aspect of the contest entry process, please message us at the CNCF slack channel &lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud-native.slack.com/archives/C07UZJRHZPY&#34;&gt;#heroes-challenge&lt;/a&gt; or at &lt;a href =“ mailto：heroes@cncf.io”&gt; heroes@cncf.io &lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;知道先前的艺术，但不想参加比赛？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您想在没有参加比赛的情况下向我们通知我们先前的艺术，请给我们发送电子邮件&lt;a href =“ mailto：heroes@cncf.io”&gt; herioes@cncf.io &lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;关于我们为云土著英雄挑战的共同主持人&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; cncf正在与&lt;a href =“ https://www.unifiedpatents.com/”&gt; Unified Putents &lt;/a&gt;，Linux基金会自2019年以来在专利巨魔威特伦斯的合作伙伴。统一专利是&lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;其他相关文章&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/2025/22/meet-the-winners-of-rour-------------------------------------------------------&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/2024/11/11/11/announcing-the-cloud-native-native-native-native-native-heroes-challenge/”&gt;宣布云原住民英雄挑战&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/2024/09/16/cncf----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- &lt;a href =&#39;href =&#39;href =&#39;在社区驱动的方法上，以保护开源巨魔&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reimagining Log Management Tools and Software: The Impact of AI and GenAI】重新构想日志管理工具和软件：AI和Genai的影响</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/03/24/reimagining-log-management-tools-and-software-the-impact-of-ai-and-genai/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Today’s distributed, cloud-native systems generate logs at a high rate, making it increasingly difficult to derive actionable insights. &lt;strong&gt;AI&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Generative AI (GenAI)&lt;/strong&gt; technologies—particularly large language models (LLMs)— are transforming log management tools by enabling teams to sift through this data, identify anomalies, and deliver real-time, context-rich intelligence to streamline troubleshooting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By applying &lt;strong&gt;transformer-based architectures&lt;/strong&gt;–which rely on specialized processes called &lt;em&gt;attention mechanisms&lt;/em&gt; to highlight the most meaningful parts of your log data—these models excel at parsing unstructured text (like log messages), understanding context, and even generating human-readable summaries or explanations of potential issues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we explore how AI-driven approaches are transforming log management tools into “intelligent assistants” for faster, more proactive incident resolution. We will look at how &lt;strong&gt;GenAI&lt;/strong&gt; techniques leverage attention mechanisms and language modeling to handle not just the detection of anomalies, but also the interpretation of logs and user queries, ultimately bridging the gap between raw machine data and actionable insights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Evolution of AI in Log Management Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Historically, traditional log management tools and methods relied on manual searches, static alerts, or rigid rule-based systems to spot anomalies. These methods can overwhelm teams with unhelpful alerts or require time-consuming deep dives just to pinpoint the root cause of a single issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;How AI Transforms Log Management Tools&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern, AI-driven log management tools represent a significant advancement forward in how logs are aggregated, analyzed, and interpreted:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manual queries vs. Automated Intelligence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traditional:&lt;/strong&gt; Engineers rely on manual searches and predefined dashboards, often missing hidden issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI/GenAI:&lt;/strong&gt; Continuous background analysis interprets logs contextually, surfacing relevant data without guesswork.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Static rules vs. Adaptive Detection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traditional:&lt;/strong&gt; Fixed thresholds risk both false alarms and missed anomalies as systems evolve.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI/GenAI:&lt;/strong&gt; Models learn “normal” behavior from historical data, dynamically adjusting to workload changes and reducing noise.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Surface-Level Alerts vs. Contextual summaries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traditional:&lt;/strong&gt; Alerts often come in the form of a minimal message—perhaps just an error code or a threshold breach. To understand the bigger picture, you have to dig through multiple logs, systems, or dashboards on your own.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI/GenAI:&lt;/strong&gt; Language models generate concise, human-readable explanations of errors, speeding up analysis.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Query-based investigations vs. Conversational interactions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traditional:&lt;/strong&gt; Complex syntax and filters create a steep learning curve and consume time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI/GenAI:&lt;/strong&gt; Natural language questions, teams can simply ask &lt;em&gt;“Why did we see so many 500 errors at 10:00 AM?”&amp;nbsp; &lt;/em&gt;The system then provides direct, context-rich answers, making collaboration easier and speeding up investigations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reactive troubleshooting vs. Intelligent Root Cause Analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traditional: &lt;/strong&gt;Post-incident, teams manually track issues across services, dependencies, deployments and error logs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI/GenAI:&lt;/strong&gt; Automatic correlation across systems highlights likely sources of errors, often before human intervention.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Known threats vs. Proactive anomaly detection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traditional:&lt;/strong&gt; Alerts largely focus on known issues or threshold breaches, leaving novel problems undetected until too late.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI/GenAI: &lt;/strong&gt;Advanced models identify subtle shifts or exceptions in log patterns, catching emerging threats early and preventing major incidents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Log Management Matters for Observability and How AI/GenAI Elevates It&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Backbone of Observability&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Log management sits at the core of observability strategies. Its main functions include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-time ingestion &amp;amp; search&lt;/strong&gt;: Continuously pulling logs from distributed systems (e.g., microservices, VMs, Kubernetes clusters…).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scalable querying&lt;/strong&gt;: Handling vast volumes of data without sacrificing speed or accuracy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context-rich analysis&lt;/strong&gt;: Enriching logs with timestamps, correlation IDs, user context, transaction context and more for in-depth investigations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key insight:&lt;/strong&gt; When logs integrate seamlessly with metrics and traces, engineers gain a unified view of system health, enabling faster root-cause analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Common Challenges:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite its central role, log management at scale is tough:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ever-growing data&lt;/strong&gt;: As systems expand, log volumes grow exponentially.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manual correlation&lt;/strong&gt;: Searching across multiple environments and services becomes labor-intensive.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Complex, distributed architectures&lt;/strong&gt;: Containerized and serverless platforms add layers of abstraction, making errors harder to isolate.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://logz.io/observability-pulse-2024/?utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=cncf&#34;&gt;2024 Observability Pulse Survey&lt;/a&gt;, only &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt; of organizations report achieving full observability. A large part of that gap is attributed to the difficulty of sifting through massive log streams and correlating events manually. Three-quarters of respondents are evaluating new tools to address these challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Where AI and GenAI Come In: The Role of an AI Agent&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artificial Intelligence&lt;/strong&gt; has traditionally focused on tasks like pattern detection, anomaly detection, and event correlation—all crucial for identifying unusual behaviors or errors in massive log streams. However, &lt;strong&gt;Generative AI&lt;/strong&gt; takes this a step further by leveraging large language models (LLMs), such as GPT, Anthropic’s, BERT…to interpret and generate human-readable text.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A key pillar of modern AI-enabled log management software is the concept of an &lt;strong&gt;“AI Agent.”&lt;/strong&gt; This agent acts like a virtual expert DevOps or SRE partner that continuously monitors, analyzes, and learns from your logs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contextual understanding&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The AI Agent goes beyond simple keyword detection by correlating multiple data points—from service dependencies to error in deployments—across time, microservices, or clusters. This ensures that alerts and insights are grounded in real operational context.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Root-Cause suggestions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Instead of simply alerting on increased error rates, an AI Agent can provide contextualized root causes, referencing related events, configuration changes, and remediation steps. This shortens the time it takes to isolate and fix problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conversational interaction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Leveraging Generative AI, an AI Agent can respond to natural language queries, allowing engineers to “ask” the system for explanations or deeper insights. This conversational approach reduces the learning curve and speeds up investigations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adaptive learning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;By gathering feedback on alert accuracy—like marking false positives or confirming incidents—the AI Agent refines its understanding of what truly matters in your unique environment. Over time, the system becomes increasingly accurate and context-aware.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that we’ve introduced the notion of an AI Agent, it’s time to see how these capabilities translate into tangible benefits. The following use cases illustrate where AI-driven log management software and AI Agents can significantly enhance both operational efficiency and system reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Use Cases for AI in Log Management Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-Time anomaly detection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;AI-driven log management tools can recognize outlier patterns in CPU usage, response times, misconfigurations or error rates—even if those patterns have never been seen before—delivering near-instant visibility into potential incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Root-Cause analysis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;When an incident occurs, the AI Agent automatically correlates logs across microservices, containers, and different cloud regions to pinpoint the origin—whether it’s a faulty deployment, a configuration error, or a specific service malfunction. Trace and log correlation is facilitated by tagging each log event with unique identifiers (e.g., correlation IDs, request IDs) and comparing error signatures or stack traces across multiple telemetry data sources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intelligent incident response&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;When integrated into collaboration platforms like Slack or Microsoft Teams, AI Agents respond to queries about logs or incidents in real time. This fosters a more proactive and conversational approach to incident management.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance tuning and capacity planning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;AI-based log management tools don’t just watch for errors—they also track trends in resource utilization or user behavior. This allows teams to proactively allocate resources or plan for scaling before performance degrades.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security and threat Detection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Generative AI models used in log management software can also learn patterns of malicious activity, helping security teams detect abnormal login attempts, data exfiltration, or suspicious logins from unusual geolocations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost optimization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;AI Agents can monitor usage and billing logs across various services to identify anomalies or trends that could lead to unexpected expenses. By correlating performance metrics and resource consumption with cost data, the AI Agent spots inefficient configurations, wasteful processes, or abnormal usage patterns. Teams can then proactively address these issues—scaling resources up or down as needed—to maintain performance and keep cloud spending under control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future Trends in Log Management Tools and Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The future of log management tools has many new possibilities, thanks to progress in AI, analytics, and infrastructure technology. Here are a few trends to look out for:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI-Driven self-healing and Autonomous Operation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;AI log management tools that automatically detect, diagnose, and remediate incidents in real time, minimizing human intervention. Future systems could auto-roll back buggy deployments or spin up replacement containers when resource usage hits dangerous thresholds.&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key sources&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;– Gartner, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2024-12-11-gartner-identifies-the-top-trends-impacting-infrastructure-and-operations-for-2025&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Top Trends in I&amp;amp;O for 2025&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;– Forrester, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forrester.com/predictions/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Predictions 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Predictive analytics and Long-Term trend analysis &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Greater use of machine learning and time-series forecasting (e.g., LSTM, Prophet) to anticipate resource bottlenecks, performance degradation, and cost overruns. This includes analyzing multi-year log data for capacity planning.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expanding conversational interfaces for Log Management Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;ChatOps and Generative AI–based interfaces will become more sophisticated, enabling engineers to interact with logs using complex natural language queries.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key sources&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;– OpenAI Research Blog, &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/chatgpt/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;LLMs for Conversational Log Analysis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud-Native and Hybrid Observability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;As microservices proliferate across public clouds, private data centers, and edge environments, log management tools must unify log aggregation, indexing, and real-time analytics across these heterogeneous setups.&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key sources&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;– CNCF, &lt;a href=&#34;https://maturitymodel.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cloud Native Maturity Model&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shift toward Open Telemetry Standards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Open Telemetry project will continue to expand, encompassing logs, metrics, traces and beyond. Unified instrumentation will simplify how logs are collected, correlated and analyzed. OTel reduces vendor lock-in, provides an easier portability of observability stacks, and a more holistic approach to application performance monitoring.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key sources&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;– OpenTelemetry Project Documentation&lt;br&gt;– Gartner, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/documents/5486695&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Monitoring and Observability for Infra and Apps&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edge logging and distributed processing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;As edge and IoT deployments multiply, log management systems will evolve to handle distributed, low-latency data ingestion and processing directly at the edge.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting Started with an AI-Driven Log Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we look ahead to the evolving trends in log management, it’s clear that adopting an intelligent solution will be essential to navigate the increasing complexity of modern systems. While self-hosted tools and open source solutions could offer lower upfront costs, they also have many hidden burdens, most commonly the overall cost of maintaining these systems on your own, as well as the lack of innovative capabilities, mainly related to AI/GenAI is also present..&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An AI-driven log management solution addresses these challenges by leveraging advanced artificial intelligence and generative AI techniques to optimize data correlation, enhance root cause analysis, streamline troubleshooting, and automate anomaly detection. These intelligent capabilities help organizations reduce the operational overhead associated with manual investigations, minimize downtime, and significantly improve resource efficiency, ultimately ensuring reliable system performance and cost savings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Key AI-driven capabilities in modern log management solutions include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI-driven Data Analysis:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-Time interaction&lt;/strong&gt;: Chat-based interfaces powered by Natural Language Processing (NLP) allow users to intuitively query log data using conversational language, such as asking “What caused the 500 errors yesterday?” or “Show me recent deployment changes in the last two days.”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smart insights&lt;/strong&gt;: Immediate, actionable insights are automatically surfaced across complex environments without manual querying or detailed knowledge of query syntax.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intelligent Root Cause Analysis (RCA):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated investigation: &lt;/strong&gt;AI-driven solutions correlate data, such as logs, events, infrastructure metrics, services dependencies, deployments, to identify the root cause of incidents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Actionable recommendations: &lt;/strong&gt;Instead of just flagging errors, modern AI-driven log management tools provide detailed next steps, such as suggesting configuration changes or identifying impacted dependencies. This dramatically reduces troubleshooting time and enables faster recovery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proactive Incident Resolution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proactive Event Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Integration with common collaboration tools (such as Slack, Teams, or other ChatOps platforms) enables real-time monitoring of alerts and events, fostering collaborative and proactive incident resolution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Root Cause identification:&lt;/strong&gt; Upon alert triggers, intelligent AI agents automatically analyze and correlate relevant event data, logs, and metrics to rapidly identify the root cause of issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Actionable insights: &lt;/strong&gt;Clear, concise recommendations and actionable insights are delivered directly through collaboration and incident management interfaces, accelerating issue resolution and maintaining system reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By embracing modern AI-driven observability and log management approaches,&amp;nbsp; teams can simplify operations, resolve issues faster, and keep their systems running smoothly and reliably.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Curious to see how it works in action?&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Explore the &lt;a href=&#34;https://logz.io/?home_bypass=1&#34;&gt;Logz.io&lt;/a&gt; interactive guided demo &lt;a href=&#34;https://guide.logz.io/psl/akz0upr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—no calls or scheduling required if you don’t want it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;今天的分布式云本地系统以很高的速度生成日志，因此得出可行的见解变得越来越困难。 &lt;strong&gt; ai &lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;生成的AI（Genai）&lt;/strong&gt;技术（尤其是大型语言模型（LLMS））正在通过使团队能够筛选这些数据，识别异常并提供实时的，上下文富裕的智能来简化疑难解索来改变日志管理工具。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过应用&lt;strong&gt;基于变压器的体系结构&lt;/strong&gt;  - 依靠称为&lt;em&gt;注意力机制的专业过程&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;来突出显示日志数据中最有意义的部分 - 这些模型在解析非结构性文本（如日志消息），理解上下文，甚至是可读的人类的概括或对潜在问题的解释中出色。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们探讨了AI驱动的方法如何将日志管理工具转换为“智能助手”，以更快，更积极的事件解决方案。我们将研究&lt;strong&gt; genai &lt;/strong&gt;技术如何利用注意力机制和语言建模不仅处理异常的检测，还可以处理对日志和用户查询的解释，最终弥合了原始机器数据和可操作的见解之间的差距。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;日志管理软件中AI的演变&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从历史上看，传统的日志管理工具和方法依赖于手动搜索，静态警报或基于规则的严格系统来发现异常。这些方法可以用无用的警报淹没团队，或者需要耗时的深度潜水，以查明单个问题的根本原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; AI如何变换日志管理工具&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代AI驱动的日志管理工具代表了对日志的汇总，分析和解释的重大进步：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;手动查询与自动智能&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;传统：&lt;/strong&gt;工程师依靠手动搜索和预定义的仪表板，通常缺少隐藏的问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; ai/genai：&lt;/strong&gt;连续的背景分析在上下文上解释日志，无需猜测而浮出水面。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;静态规则与自适应检测&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;传统：&lt;/strong&gt;固定阈值可能会随着系统的发展而遇到虚假警报和错过异常。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; AI/Genai：&lt;/strong&gt;模型从历史数据中学习“正常”行为，动态调整工作量变化并减少噪声。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;表面级警报与上下文摘要&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;传统：&lt;/strong&gt;警报通常以最小消息的形式出现 - 也许只是错误代码或阈值漏洞。要了解大局，您必须挖掘多个日志，S您自己的系统或仪表板。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; ai/genai：&lt;/strong&gt;语言模型产生简洁的，可读的错误解释，加快分析。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;基于查询的研究与对话互动&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;传统：&lt;/strong&gt;复杂语法和过滤器创造了陡峭的学习曲线并消耗时间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; AI/Genai：&lt;/strong&gt;自然语言问题，团队可以简单地问&lt;em&gt;“为什么我们在上午10:00看到这么多500个错误？”  &lt;/em&gt;然后，系统提供了直接的，上下文丰富的答案，使协作更加轻松并加快调查。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;反应性故障排除与智能根本原因分析&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;传统：&lt;/strong&gt;事后，团队在服务，依赖关系，部署和错误日志中手动跟踪问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; ai/genai：&lt;/strong&gt;跨系统的自动相关性突出显示了可能的错误来源，通常是在人类干预之前。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;已知的威胁与主动异常检测&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;传统：&lt;/strong&gt;警报在很大程度上关注已知问题或阈值违规，留下了新的问题，直到太晚才被发现为止。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; ai/genai：&lt;/strong&gt;高级模型确定对数模式中的细微变化或例外，及早捕获新兴威胁并预防重大事件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么对数管理对可观察性以及AI/Genai如何提升&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;可观察性的骨干&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;日志管理是可观察性策略的核心。它的主要功能包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;实时摄入＆搜索&lt;/strong&gt;：从分布式系统中连续从分布式系统中拉出日志（例如，微服务，VM，kubernetes簇…）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可扩展查询&lt;/strong&gt;：处理大量数据而不牺牲速度或准确性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;上下文丰富的分析&lt;/strong&gt;：通过时间戳，相关ID，用户上下文，交易上下文以及更多的深入研究来丰富日志。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;关键洞察力：&lt;/strong&gt;当日志与指标和痕迹无缝集成时，工程师会获得统一的系统健康视图，从而实现更快的根本原因分析。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;常见挑战：&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管具有核心作用，但规模上的日志管理还是很难的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;不断增长的数据&lt;/strong&gt;：随着系统的扩展，日志量成倍增长。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;手动相关性&lt;/strong&gt;：跨多种环境和服务搜索变得富有劳动力。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;复杂的，分布式体系结构&lt;/strong&gt;：容器化和无服务器平台添加抽象层，mak错误更难分离。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://logz.io/observability-pulse-2024/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=cncf&#34;&gt;2024 Observability Pulse Survey&lt;/a&gt;, only &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt; of organizations report achieving full observability.该差距的很大一部分归因于筛选大量日志流并手动关联事件的困难。四分之三的受访者正在评估应对这些挑战的新工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; ai和genai进来的地方：AI代理的角色&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;人工智能&lt;/strong&gt;传统上专注于模式检测，异常检测和事件相关的任务，这对于确定大规模日志流中的异常行为或错误至关重要。但是，&lt;strong&gt;生成的ai &lt;/strong&gt;通过利用大型语言模型（LLM）（例如GPT，Anthropic，Bert……）来解释和生成人类可读文本，从而将其进一步发展。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代AI启用AI的日志管理软件的关键支柱是&lt;strong&gt;“ AI代理”的概念。&lt;/strong&gt;该代理像虚拟专家DevOps或SRE合作伙伴一样，可以不断地监视，分析和从您的日志中学习：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;上下文理解&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; AI代理通过将多个数据点（从服务依赖性到部署错误）相关联，超越了简单的关键字检测，即交易时间，微服务或群集。这确保了警报和见解是基于实际操作环境的基础。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自动根本原因建议&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;，而不是简单地警告增加错误率，而是AI代理可以提供上下文化的根本原因，引用相关事件，配置更改和修复步骤。这缩短了隔离和解决问题所需的时间。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;对话互动&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;利用生成的AI，AI代理可以响应自然语言查询，从而使工程师可以“询问”系统以解释或更深入的见解。这种对话方法减少了学习曲线并加快了调查。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自适应学习&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;通过收集有关警报准确性的反馈（例如标记误报或确认事件），AI代理会完善其对您独特环境中真正重要的事情的理解。随着时间的流逝，系统变得越来越准确和背景感。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在我们介绍了AI代理的概念，现在该看看这些功能如何转化为切实的好处了。以下用例说明了AI驱动的日志管理软件和AI代理可以在何处显着提高操作效率和系统可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;日志管理中AI的关键用例软件&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;实时异常检测&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; a-drig驱动的日志管理工具可以识别CPU使用，响应时间，错误配置或错误率中的异常模式，即使这些模式以前从未见过，即使以前从未见过 - 将接近固定的可见性转向潜在的失败。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;根本原因分析&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;当事件发生时，AI代理会自动将跨微服务，容器和不同云区域的日志相关联，以查明原点 - 无论是错误的部署，配置误差还是特定的服务失败。通过用唯一的标识符（例如，相关ID，请求ID）标记每个日志事件，并比较多个遥测数据源的错误签名或堆栈跟踪。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;智能事件响应&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;集成到Slack或Microsoft Teams等协作平台时，AI代理会实时响应有关日志或事件的查询。这为事件管理促进了一种更加主动和对话的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance tuning and capacity planning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;AI-based log management tools don’t just watch for errors—they also track trends in resource utilization or user behavior.这使团队可以主动分配资源或计划在绩效降低之前进行扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;安全性和威胁检测&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;在日志管理软件中使用的生成AI模型还可以学习恶意活动的模式，帮助安全团队检测出异常的登录尝试，数据删除或可疑的登录，或者是从异常地理学中的可疑登录。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;成本优化&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; AI代理可以监视各种服务的使用和计费日志，以识别可能导致意外支出的异常或趋势。通过将绩效指标和资源消耗与成本数据相关联，AI代理点效率低下，浪费过程或使用异常使用模式。然后，团队可以主动解决这些问题（根据需要根据需要提高或减少资源）来保持绩效并保持云支出在控制之下。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;日志管理工具和软件的未来趋势&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于AI，分析和基础架构技术的进步，日志管理工具的未来具有许多新的可能性。这里有几个趋势要注意：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; AI驱动的自我修复和自主操作&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; AI日志管理工具，这些工具会自动检测，诊断和补救实时进行事件，从而最大程度地减少人类干预。未来的系统可以自动滚动越野车部署，或者在资源使用率达到危险阈值时旋转更换容器。&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;关键来源&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;br&gt;  -  Gartner，&lt;a href =“ https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/newsroom/press-releases/2024-12-11-11-gartner-isterifies-the-the-the-the-top-top-top-trends-impstrends-impstimcting-infrend-infrendure-infrastructure-inforule------------ 2025 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/a&gt;  -  Forrester，&lt;a href =“ https://www.forrester.com/predictions/”&gt; &lt;em&gt;预测2024 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;预测分析和长期趋势分析&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;更多地使用机器学习和时间序列预测（例如LSTM，先知），以预测资源瓶颈，绩效降低和成本超支。这包括分析为容量计划的多年日志数据。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;扩大日志管理软件的对话界面&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; chatops和基于AI的生成界面将变得更加复杂，使工程师能够使用复杂的自然语言查询与日志进行交互。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;brngr&gt;关键源&lt;br&gt; openai Research Blog &lt;br&gt;  -  openai Research Blog &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; href =“ https://openai.com/index/chatgpt/”&gt; &lt;em&gt; llms用于对话日志分析&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云原生和混合可观察性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;随着微服务在公共云，私有数据中心和边缘环境之间扩散，日志管理工具必须统一这些异构设置的日志聚合，索引和实时分析。&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;关键来源&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;br&gt;  -  cncf，&lt;a href =“ https://maturitymodel.cncf.io/”&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;转向开放遥测标准&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;开放的遥测项目将继续扩展，涵盖日志，指标，痕迹及以后。统一的仪器将简化如何收集，关联和分析对数。 Otel减少了供应商的锁定，提供了可观察性堆栈的可移植性，并提供了更全面的应用程序性能监控方法。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;brong&gt;关键源&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;  -  Opentelemetry Project Project Project Documentation &lt;br&gt;  -  Gartner，Gartner，Gartner，Gartner，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a a &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a a &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a a &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a a &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a a &lt;/em&gt; &lt;aa href =“ https://www.gartner.com/en/documents/5486695”&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; Infra和Apps and Apps &lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;的监视和可观察性&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;边缘记录和分布式处理&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;作为边缘和物联网部署乘以乘积，日志管理系统将演变为处理分布式，低延迟数据摄入和直接在边缘处的处理。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;从AI驱动的日志管理开始&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们展望日志管理中不断发展的趋势时，很明显，采用智能解决方案对于导航现代系统日益复杂至关重要。尽管自托管工具和开源解决方案可能会提供较低的前期成本，但它们也承担着许多隐藏的负担，最常见的是维护这些负担的总体成本系统本身以及缺乏创新功能，主要与AI/Genai有关的系统也存在。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; AI驱动的日志管理解决方案通过利用先进的人工智能和生成AI技术来优化数据相关性，增强根本原因分析，简化故障排除和自动化异常检测来解决这些挑战。这些智能功能可帮助组织减少与手动调查相关的操作间接费用，最大程度地减少停机时间并显着提高资源效率，最终确保可靠的系统性能和成本节省。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代日志管理解决方案中的关键AI驱动功能包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI-driven Data Analysis:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;实时互动&lt;/strong&gt;：由自然语言处理供电的基于聊天的接口（NLP）允许用户使用对话性语言直观地查询日志数据，例如“问“昨天造成500个错误的原因是什么？”或“向我展示最近两天的部署变化。” &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;智能见解&lt;/strong&gt;：即时，可行的见解会自动在复杂的环境中自动浮出水面，而无需手动查询或查询语法的详细知识。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;智能根本原因分析（RCA）：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自动调查：&lt;/strong&gt; AI驱动的解决方案相关的数据，例如日志，事件，基础架构指标，服务依赖性，部署，以识别事件的根本原因。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可操作的建议：&lt;/strong&gt;而不是仅标记错误，现代AI驱动的日志管理工具提供了详细的下一步，例如建议进行配置更改或识别受影响的依赖性。这大大减少了故障排除时间并实现更快的恢复。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;主动入射分辨率&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;积极主动的事件管理：&lt;/strong&gt;与共同协作工具（例如Slack，Teams或其他ChatOps平台）集成，可以实时监视警报和活动，促进协作和主动的事件解决。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;根本原因识别：&lt;/strong&gt;在警报触发器时，智能AI代理会自动分析并关联相关事件数据，日志和指标，以迅速识别问题的根本原因。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可行的见解：&lt;/strong&gt;清晰，简洁的建议和可行的见解是通过协作和事件管理接口直接提供的，加速了问题解决并维护系统的可靠性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过拥抱现代AI驱动的可观察性和日志管理方法，团队可以简化操作，解决问题的速度更快，并使其系统顺利，可靠地运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;很好奇地看到它在作用中的工作方式？&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;探索&lt;a href =“ https://logz.io/?home_bypass = 1”&gt; logz.io &lt;/a&gt;交互式引导demo &lt;a a href &lt;a href =“如果您不想要的话，需要安排。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>