<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://cloudys-rsshub-ab061133bcab.herokuapp.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【CNCF, Linux Foundation Education and KodeKloud Partner on Training Offering for India】CNCF，Linux基金会教育和Kodekloud的合作伙伴</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/05/cncf-linux-foundation-education-and-kodekloud-partner-on-training-offering-for-india/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdAvENJjGnGjESS-jwccKdjtduRQQnorICtcpOWlAc2id-y0KICMv8Ty9Z1zwHX7FHO0HGv1_H2awuGP34DgQtteFQcO-NuvT5vXScSGZ0CsczhDeuHwcJ2jYChQrzHtmM_sQZZsQ?key=5Vk2I62KEk19BFlJu2xqjA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;The new partnership will offer a new introductory training for the Indian developer community.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF, Linux Foundation Education, and KodeKloud have partnered on an introductory training offering for the Indian developer community. The initial offerings will provide India residents an opportunity to purchase Cloud Native, Kubernetes, and Linux training and certifications for a special bundle price with localized payment options.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;India residents will be able to purchase highly sought after certifications – KCNA, KCSA, CKA, CKAD, CKS and LFCS, in conjunction with KodeKloud’s in-demand training, in local India currency!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KodeKloud will offer Indian residents:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Special bundles including one-attempt certification exams for KCNA, KCSA, CKA, CKAD, CKS and LFCS, along with KodeKloud training subscriptions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Localized payment options for India residents&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information about the program, please visit: &lt;a href=&#34;https://kodekloud.com/linuxfoundation-kodekloud-partnership&#34;&gt;https://kodekloud.com/linuxfoundation-kodekloud-partnership&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdavenjjgngjess-jwcckdjtjtdurqqnorictcpowlac2id-y0kicmv8ty 9Z1ZWHX7FHO0HGV1_H2AWUGP34DGQTTEFQCO-NUVT5VXSCSGZSGZSGZ0CSCZHDEUHWCJ2JYCHQRZHTMM_SQZZSQ？key = 5vk2i662kek19bflju2xxqja alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the-caption class =” wp-element-caption&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ WP-element-caption”&gt;新合作伙伴关系将为印度开发人员社区提供新的介绍性培训。&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figifion&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CNCF，Linux Foundation Education和Kodekloud已为印度开发人员社区提供了介绍性培训。最初的产品将为印度居民提供一个机会，以特殊的捆绑价格购买云本地人，Kubernetes和Linux培训和认证，并提供本地付款方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;印度居民将能够与KCSA，KCSA，CKA，CKAD，CKAD，CKS和LFC一起购买，并与Kodekloud当地的印度货币进行了需求的培训！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Kodekloud将为印度居民提供：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;特别捆绑包，包括针对KCNA，KCSA，CKA，CKAD，CKAD，CKS和LFC的一次性认证考试，以及Kodekloud培训订阅&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;印度居民的本地付款方式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关该程序的更多信息，请访问：&lt;a href =“ https://kodekloud.com/linuxfoundation-kodekloud-partnhers--&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The CFP for KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026 Is Closing 12 October】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon欧洲2026年的CFP即将于10月12日关闭</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/05/the-cfp-for-kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025-is-closing-12-october/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, the CFP for &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026&lt;/a&gt; will &lt;strong&gt;close&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;on 12 October&lt;/strong&gt;, which is earlier than usual because &lt;strong&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe happens earlier than usual&lt;/strong&gt; in March, which compresses the planning window. To deliver the highest-impact event — and ensure the Amsterdam schedule has the time to get the buzz and attention it deserves&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;— we’re shifting the timeline forward.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let the Networking Begin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We encourage you to utilize your CNCF networks to host collaborative brainstorm sessions to discuss ideas. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@cncf/playlists&#34;&gt;Recorded sessions&lt;/a&gt; from other 2025 KubeCon + CloudNativeCons are a great source of inspiration.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the CFP will close on 12 October, the energy and collaboration at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America will be a great place to &lt;strong&gt;refine your cloud native narrative&lt;/strong&gt; — and maybe even plant seeds (peach, of course) for other speaking opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to see your ideas — and we’re here to support you. Let’s shape an unforgettable KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026 together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Dates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CFP Deadline for KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026&lt;/strong&gt;: 12 October, 2025&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/cfp/&#34;&gt;Access the CFP&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Location&lt;/strong&gt;: Amsterdam, The Netherlands&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Event Dates&lt;/strong&gt;: 23 – 26 March 2026&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have questions?&lt;/strong&gt; Email the CFP team at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:cfp@cncf.io&#34;&gt;cfp@cncf.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年，&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/”&gt; kubecon + kubecon + cloubnativecon欧洲2026 &lt;/a&gt;将于10月12日&lt;/strong&gt; kub &lt;/strong &lt;/strong &lt;/strong &lt;/strong &lt;/strong &lt;usim，因为3月份比通常的&lt;/strong&gt;更早地压缩了计划窗口。要提供最大的影响事件 - 并确保阿姆斯特丹时间表有时间获得嗡嗡声和应有的关注&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;  - 我们正在向前移动时间表。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;让网络开始&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们鼓励您利用您的CNCF网络主持协作集思广益会议来讨论想法。 &lt;a href =“ https://www.youtube.com/@cncf/playlists”&gt;录制的会话&lt;/a&gt;来自其他2025年Kubecon + CloudNativeCons的会议是一个很好的灵感来源。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管CFP将于10月12日关闭，但Kubecon + Cloudnativecon北美的能量与合作将是&lt;strong&gt;完善您的云本地叙事&lt;/strong&gt;的好地方 - 甚至可能是其他演讲机会的种子。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴看到您的想法 - 我们在这里为您提供支持。让我们塑造一个难忘的库贝孔 + Cloudnativecon欧洲2026年一起。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;密钥日期&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2026 &lt;/strong&gt;的CFP截止日期：2025年10月12日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/cfp/”&gt;访问CFP &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;活动位置&lt;/strong&gt;：荷兰阿姆斯特丹&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;活动日期&lt;/strong&gt;：23  -  2026年3月26日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;有疑问吗？&lt;/strong&gt;通过&lt;a href =“ mailto：cfp@cncf.io”发送电子邮件给CFP团队。&gt; cfp@cncf.io &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What 500+ Experts Revealed About Kubernetes Adoption and Workloads】500多名专家透露了有关Kubernetes采用和工作量的内容</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/02/what-500-experts-revealed-about-kubernetes-adoption-and-workloads/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Applications running in containers have come a long way. The conversation has shifted from &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; organizations are adopting cloud native technologies like Kubernetes to &lt;em&gt;what kinds&lt;/em&gt; of applications they’re running in these environments. Today, many of these workloads are mission critical, and platform teams must deliver enterprise-grade capabilities to support them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://portworx.com/resources/voice-of-kubernetes-expert-report-2025/?utm_source=newstack&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=px-brand&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Voice of Kubernetes Experts 2025 Report: The Future of VM Workloads&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Portworx by Pure Storage partnered with Dimensional Research to survey over 500 qualified participants who were directly responsible for current or past use of VMware and worked at an enterprise company with more than 500 employees that had made a significant investment in Kubernetes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the full report covers a wide range of insights—including the future of VMware estates—this article focuses on how enterprises are leveraging cloud native environments for modern application development and mission-critical workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the context of this survey, &lt;em&gt;cloud native&lt;/em&gt; refers to the use of technologies like containers, Kubernetes, immutable infrastructure, microservices, and service meshes to build and run scalable applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The industry is building new applications on cloud native&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcdmI7gcM-dkhZS7k5FIONTBgvCR1kt2H0RimmxC5r_KtE0SNnhcfYlCtNRXFQ9xfhGNL1hf_5xwmD9ImNSf3AUR8fJ55gcxtgwLUPZXmCYEpNlxDeNpLnaSbdNh0IQd3eIxQYb0Q?key=F-_-gdsVGbxztQ_SVrfeGg&#34; alt=&#34;Survey results on how enterprises leverage cloud native technologies&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud native infrastructure has undergone a transformational journey. Once used for ephemeral workloads and DevTest environments, technologies like Kubernetes are now becoming the gold standard for application development. In fact, 41% of respondents say their current application footprint is already mostly cloud native.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enterprises are prioritizing their cloud native platforms, with 82% planning to use their cloud native environments as the primary platform for their new applications in the next five years. Many are choosing to run their infrastructure as container-first, signaling a shift in investment for IT teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXe8hm3fOhS7smqDH7frjrRwbxZ9iDZi0nRMuAHJF6aD3yPAk7rLlOIpOdNl7EGFFVw_z7A6DCi1gMzV8MNtZvwrS4Ybn4fbhroIt4zGdMh1JBRjfju9DUb4MF9Dvu42ziVd_8LyqA?key=F-_-gdsVGbxztQ_SVrfeGg&#34; alt=&#34;Data visualization on how most enterprises have hybrid cloud deployments&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud native platforms are being built with hybrid cloud in mind. A staggering 87% of respondents deploy their cloud native environments in hybrid cloud setups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why hybrid? The benefits are clear: flexibility, cost control, and reduced vendor lock-in. Enterprises often run sensitive or regulated workloads on-premises, while taking advantage of public cloud scalability for dynamic workloads. By matching each application with the most appropriate environment, organizations can optimize performance, cost, and compliance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cost is another driver. Placing workloads in the most economical environment—combined with features like thin provisioning—can significantly reduce infrastructure spend. A hybrid cloud approach also protects organizations from being locked into a single vendor. Overreliance on a single vendor can have devastating cost implications. In recent years, enterprises have been caught off guard by hefty contract renewals that have dramatically increased IT spend.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Further, changing economic conditions makes it critical for platforms to remain agile and future-proof. Uncertainty around tariffs and other macroeconomic factors means enterprises need to be ready to adapt at a moment’s notice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mission critical applications are built in cloud native&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXemSU4GhZR_fw3Pss_5PPQ-XKuyk0u3pOsEL__5YnsAoYLJtQzW1T3JaMsQtGN6z-X_Gl0RxOC4D9AG1CgltdTjot4uh9cpOB73w-2SJ5TT2j1lEr5T_kG5AWqRm-R7SyupaXcv-A?key=F-_-gdsVGbxztQ_SVrfeGg&#34; alt=&#34;Data visualization proving mission-critical apps mostly being built on cloud native&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It should come as no surprise, then, that this increased investment in cloud native platforms means that most enterprises are running important applications in containers. In fact, 58% are running mission critical applications in containers, meaning applications that have strict requirements for performance and uptime. These applications tend to require little to no data loss in the event of a disaster, meaning platform teams need to be able to support strict availability requirements.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mission critical applications need to be supported with high performance, high availability, and disaster recovery. This can be a challenge in the cloud native world, as platform teams need to be able to support these critical applications with the functionality they need in order to meet the strict compliance measures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s not just traditional applications moving to containers—data-intensive use cases like databases (69%) and AI/ML workloads (60%) are also increasingly cloud native. In total, 98% of enterprises say they run data-heavy workloads in their cloud native environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud native environments run into challenges with persistent storage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfxTR_RDdXTjnKl3f7CbYXqZWkmpNUZ1CFfYhW_X60hT-lEcIQ7fV4DayHbAHiEgSuBcM11caJBkDWc7jSkj2lHuskM4BXcQNtmWI96xEav4hRD7CL_8Mg3lidgnJLn0r48d57Vzg?key=F-_-gdsVGbxztQ_SVrfeGg&#34; alt=&#34;Data visualization on persistent storage and/or DB management problems for cloud native apps&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, scaling mission-critical workloads in cloud native environments isn’t without its hurdles. Survey respondents cite top challenges such as security (72%), observability (51%), resilience (35%), and persistent storage (31%).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As cloud native adoption scales into the primary development platform, enterprises need to support their platforms with the functionality required for the kind of data-intensive and mission critical applications they are running. Their platforms need to be able to support the preferred hybrid cloud environments with a consistent and centralized platform that allows developers to capture the full benefits of cloud native development.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Platforms also need to be able to address the key issues platform teams are facing with their cloud native applications. Tight integrations with monitoring solutions can help address issues like observability, while solutions that can provide features like high availability and disaster recovery can help with resiliency. Finally, solutions need to be able to provide tools that help platform teams manage their persistent storage. They need to be able to streamline storage operations and make Day 2 management simple.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Portworx by Pure Storage addresses many of the key challenges organizations face while managing their cloud native applications. Portworx is the container data management platform that automates Day 2 storage operations, secures container workloads with disaster recovery, and unifies modern applications in hybrid and multi cloud environments so platform teams can deploy their applications anywhere and still provide a consistent development experience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to learn more? &lt;a href=&#34;https://portworx.com/?utm_source=newstack&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=px-brand&#34;&gt;Visit our website&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://portworx.com/resources/voice-of-kubernetes-expert-report-2025/?utm_source=newstack&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=px-brand&#34;&gt;download your copy of the Voice of Kubernetes Experts Report 2025 today&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在容器中运行的应用程序已经走了很长一段路。如果组织采用诸如kubernetes之类的云本地技术到&lt;em&gt;，对话已经从&lt;em&gt;转变为他们在这些环境中正在运行的应用程序的哪些类型&lt;/em&gt;。如今，许多这些工作负载至关重要，平台团队必须提供企业级的能力来支持他们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://portworx.com/resources/voice-of-kubernetes-expert-report-2025/?utm_source=newstack&amp;utm_medium=web&amp;utm_campaign=px-brand&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Voice of Kubernetes Experts 2025 Report: The Future of VM Workloads &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，由Pure Storage的PortWorx与Dimential Research合作，调查了500多名合格的参与者，这些参与者直接负责当前或过去使用VMware，并在一家企业公司工作，有500多名员工对Kubernetes进行了大量投资。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然完整的报告涵盖了广泛的见解（包括VMware Estates的未来），这篇文章着重于企业如何利用云本地环境来实现现代应用程序开发和关键任务 - 关键任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此调查的背景下，&lt;em&gt; cloud Native &lt;/em&gt;是指使用诸如容器，Kubernetes，不变的基础架构，微服务和服务网格等技术来构建和运行可扩展应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;该行业正在云机构构建新应用&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcdmi7gcm-dkhzs7k5fiontbgvcr1kt2h0rimmxc5r_kte0snnhcfylc TNRXFQ9XFHGNL1HF_5XWMD9IMNSF3AUR8FJ55GCXTGXTGWLUPZXMCYEPNLXDENPLNASBDNASBDNH0IQD3EIXQYB0Q？ alt =“企业如何利用云原生技术的调查结果” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figifrer&gt; &lt;/figion&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云本地基础架构经历了转型之旅。一旦用于短暂的工作负载和DevTest环境，Kubernetes等技术现在正成为应用程序开发的黄金标准。实际上，有41％的受访者表示他们当前的应用程序足迹已经主要是云本地。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;企业正在优先考虑其云本机平台，其中82％的人计划在未来五年内将其云本机环境用作其新应用程序的主要平台。许多人选择以集装箱为优点运行基础架构，这表明投资团队的投资变化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxe8hm3fohs7smqdh7frjrrrwbxz9idzi0nrmuahjf6 ad333 pypak7rllllllllllllllllllllllllloloipo DNL7EGFFVW_Z7A6DCI1GMZV8MNTZVWRS4YBN4FBHROIT4ZGDMH1JBRJBJFJU9DUB4MF9DVU42ZIVD_8LYQA？ alt =“大多数企业如何拥有混合云部署的数据可视化” reverrerpolicy =“ no-toferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云本地平台正在使用混合动力云考虑。惊人的87％的受访者在混合云设置中部署其云本机环境。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为什么要混合？好处是明确的：灵活性，成本控制和减少供应商锁定。企业经常在本地运行敏感或受管制的工作负载，同时利用公共云可扩展性来动态工作负载。通过将每个应用程序与最合适的环境匹配，组织可以优化性能，成本和合规性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成本是另一个驱动程序。将工作负载放在最经济的环境中，并与薄供应之类的功能相结合，可以大大减少基础设施支出。混合云方法还保护组织免于被锁定成单个供应商。对单个供应商的过度依赖可能会产生毁灭性的成本影响。近年来，企业因大量续签而措手不及。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，不断变化的经济状况使得平台保持敏捷和防前状态至关重要。关税和其他宏观经济因素周围的不确定性意味着企业需要准备就绪。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;任务关键应用构建在云本地&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;中&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxemsu4ghzr_fw3pss_5ppq-xkuyk0u3posel__5ynsaoyljtqzw1t3ja MSQTGN6Z-X_GL0RXOC4D9AG1CGLTDTJOT4UH9CPOB73W-2SJ5TT2J1LER5T_KGG5QRM-R7SYUPAXCV-A？key = f-_______-- __-- __-- __- gdsvgbxzztq_svrfegg alt =“数据可视化证明关键任务应用程序主要是在云本机上构建的” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，对云本地平台的投资增加意味着大多数企业都在容器中运行重要的应用程序，这不足为奇。实际上，有58％的人正在容器中运行关键任务应用程序，这意味着对性能和正常运行时间有严格要求的应用程序。在发生灾难时，这些应用程序往往几乎不需要数据丢失，这意味着平台团队需要能够支持严格的可用性要求。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需要高性能，高可用性和灾难恢复的任务关键应用程序。在云土著世界中，这可能是一个挑战，因为平台团队需要能够通过所需的功能来支持这些关键应用程序，以达到严格的合规措施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不仅是传统的应用程序转移到容器中 - 数据库（69％）和AI/ML工作负载（60％）（60％）的用例也越来越多。总共98％&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云本机环境遇到了持续存储的挑战&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https：//lh7-rt.googleusercontent。com/docs/ad_4nxfxtr_rddxtjnkl3f7cbyxqzwkmpnuz1cffyhw_x60ht-leciq7fv4dayhbahiegsubcm1cajb kdwc7jskj2lhuskm4bxcquntmwi96xeav4hrd7cl_8mg3lidgnjln0r48d57vzg？ alt =“云原生应用程序的持续存储和/或数据库管理问题的数据可视化” reverrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当然，在云本地环境中缩放关键任务工作负载并非没有障碍。调查受访者引用了诸如安全性（72％），可观察性（51％），弹性（35％）和持续存储（31％）等最高挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着云本地采用量表缩放到主要开发平台中，企业需要使用其运行的那种数据密集型和任务关键应用程序所需的功能来支持其平台。他们的平台需要能够以一致且集中的平台来支持首选的混合云环境，从而使开发人员能够捕获云原生开发的全部好处。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;平台还需要能够解决平台团队与其云本机应用程序面临的关键问题。与监视解决方案的紧密集成可以帮助解决可观察性之类的问题，而可以提供高可用性和灾难恢复等功能的解决方案可以帮助弹性。最后，解决方案需要能够提供帮助平台团队管理其持续存储的工具。他们需要能够简化存储操作并使第2天的管理变得简单。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; portworx by Pure Storage解决了组织在管理其云本机应用程序时面临的许多关键挑战。 PortWorx是容器数据管理平台，可自动使用第2天的存储操作，确保容器工作负载具有灾难恢复，并在混合和多云环境中统一现代应用程序，因此平台团队可以在任何地方部署其应用程序，并且仍然提供一致的开发经验。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想了解更多吗？ &lt;a href =“ https://portworx.com/?utm_source = newstack&amp;utm_medium = web&amp;utm_campaign=px-brand”&gt;访问我们的网站&lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://portworx.com/resources/voice-of-kubernetes-expert-report-2025/?utm_source = newstack&amp;utm_medium = web&amp;utm_campaign = px-aign = px-brand”&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Terraform Modules to Platform Services: Simplify Infrastructure Management with the Kratix CLI】从Terraform模块到平台服务：使用Kratix CLI简化基础架构管理</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/08/from-terraform-modules-to-platform-services-simplify-infrastructure-management-with-the-kratix-cli/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’ve worked with Terraform for any amount of time, you’ve probably experienced handing Terraform modules directly to application developers. Although this enables teams to get started quickly, it can lead to a world of pain. For example, does the following quote, from an internal developer platform team engineer at a large bank resonate with you?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I handed my developers a reusable Terraform module for Postgres. A week later, three teams forked it, none of them had backups enabled, and I’m on the hook when something goes wrong…”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If so, read on!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Dangers of Providing Terraform Modules to Developers&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, providing developers with Terraform modules appears straightforward; modules encapsulate best practices, making it easy for users to provision infrastructure. However, problems quickly surface:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Teams independently manage Terraform configurations, leading to sprawl and making it challenging to track compliance or govern infrastructure consistently.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Those same independent configurations allow misconfigurations to creep in, resulting in critical applications being provisioned without essential features like backups or high availability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Applying critical security patches or updates becomes a manual, error-prone process involving multiple teams and repositories.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These challenges rapidly diminish the initial benefits of using Terraform modules. Often, teams find themselves pressured to rewrite or drastically refactor their Terraform codebase, a costly, disruptive, and risky process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But what if there was a way to achieve the platform engineering outcomes you need without restarting from scratch?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why Terraform Needs a Platform Layer&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Terraform modules are powerful, but they impose a heavy operational burden on developers. Teams must deeply understand Terraform, handle state management complexities, and maintain secure and up-to-date configurations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moving to a standardised, self-service way to offer services and provisions infrastructure via a platform can deliver the outcomes you want without requiring your team to rebuild everything from scratch..&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is precisely what Kratix, an open-source framework for building &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.syntasso.io/internal-developer-platforms&#34;&gt;internal developer platforms&lt;/a&gt;, provides: a way to incrementally introduce platform engineering APIs and best practices on top of existing Terraform modules without disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Bootstrapping Terraform Modules into Kratix Promises&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kratix provides a concept of a Promise. A Promise is the definition of a service that you want to make available on your platform. With Kratix, converting an existing Terraform module into a managed, self-service capability becomes effortless. For instance, an example Terraform module for provisioning an AWS S3 bucket can quickly be transformed into a managed service with a simple “kratix init” CLI command:&lt;br&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXf3hbPVjtWoY7SjS-5tq1Jp4ewESuY9e26VDxxgccDuhRBxV5r2YtPe-XNlan9S7NFWPHeqwDoroKguKePk9seVBpaWzvbX5YbnFjpbLQzCSjVEUeCGxRBj6au8vmttH6cm-tmBNQ?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; width=&#34;602&#34; height=&#34;136&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This command has generated a Promise for us. This Promise effectively provides an API for the Terraform module, exposing the same set of input values as the module itself.&lt;br&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfB8BPc6HqlkEYNdTTM3nqjRIXZZn5TBkoCHIfvjvdpw2n9cJfltXd0StqFtaxJ_afUC0ed3Crq3GXnG0DJdtxE3fhDmMOa3WrTjgyETWH_Ggd13EPtkMD2JaQObH7vdT6ss4c3?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; width=&#34;602&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can now install the Promise and make the offering available on the platform:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfQT8DwcuVt9t8dZyBD1dNBDFdpv1LhcU70lqtiMYq9k2NG8zaOeXfAhsPpUveRa2sY1mDwzZi56y1M7Ljyr6hPLXi_00Stw3lR_tmhRGWEuptRi2joVYjLQ5Y7F5lA0k74xSIJdw?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this example, I am running Syntasso Kratix Enterprise (SKE) with built-in support for a Backstage portal, so by default, all my Promises are also going to be added to the Backstage instance I have configured:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXf3tciNSxuLFmvwxr1xEWtTznlso0AHU0UzClYiYlAjOIE67J7XoYUvj2yiG3CfbhauH9GLVYHiX-YMOuDs23Er_vzR0n8GYhmK95dce_euiiKeIiG1quu24v3qVkJq5zde9116Fg?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Providing Developers a Seamless Self-Service Experience&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Kratix Promises, developers no longer interact directly with Terraform nor manage the resulting infrastructure. Instead, they utilise familiar interfaces like Kubernetes APIs or developer portals such as Backstage to provision and manage infrastructure, services, and other platform components. This self-service model greatly reduces complexity and keeps developers focused on building applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I am using SKE, I can go straight into Backstage and browse the Promises installed, and instantly get started filling out a form to request an AWS S3 Bucket.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcCJ3zb2gxqX-fSnRUcUH1Qlob46An8cKAnOIsMz0iXxY8B_ifl4edHZ57oP5H7O4d3120Cw9QZe2lHDmAhOdHn9LT_cjb0Gb2zps8aNeVtZV0BSk8pHbPrGdQZPTZVff5QJfbZTw?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After I submit the request in Backstage, Kratix triggers the Workflows defined in the Promise, which will generate the required Terraform code to reconcile the modules with the user’s inputs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this example, I am using a GitHub repo with GitHub Actions configured to reconcile the requests:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcSx1_78T41-cG0R8sO2xxkdtCVnafsTsvmV_6jj_EA4XWLLOrZjzUC20trzgOyNdXjBW5nnpWM0c0mRrngwi8jASzP23J61u6PVoPwWNM5jdZoKuM71YTkuBNUMUGXX9tnruubfg?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; width=&#34;602&#34; height=&#34;251&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Custom Workflows: Approvals and Governance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some service configurations require additional oversight. For instance, you may wish to add manual approvals for AWS S3 buckets provisioned with specific sensitive settings. Kratix makes it straightforward to insert additional logic into your workflows. In this example, let’s add a manual approval step for when users want to create publicly accessible S3 buckets. This code detects when the public configuration property of the bucket promise is set to true, and creates a Jira issue for manual approval. Kratix will wait for this ticket to be closed before proceeding with provisioning the S3 bucket:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXciRMoJMda_3qurgvDLdueyiXK3_K6bN5797a4I9GW4wurNFAkrw_OudwByXQPs7P8neCmEoBk4iD_6otnlnIdwbTRQGN609APZax5kNIGF7AK1QtqJ62qgK36vxT2Rb2ITEkbU?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This approval step will run every time a user makes a request. Let’s make a new request with `public` set to `true`, and you can see that the workflow will wait for&amp;nbsp; approval before outputting the Terraform to GitHub:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeCz_2_HTCx0JsnUIX7yS8DD_xvy8Ujapra22NlHJUSpXKkVkMWDeoHcXQqGrZPP36ugetv_M6y_XkOO8bKbvM9M4-325uAuw1jrsboxUKIWAufX203thhyahXGfH7-yXilQhQFPg?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Fleet Management: Updates Without Disruption&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine your business decides that descriptive cost-tracking FinOps tags must be used by default on all buckets. Without Kratix, rolling out such a policy would require significant manual effort and coordination with every team that manages its own buckets. With Kratix, updating your Promise to enforce tags is simple and automatic:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Update the Promise definition to configure the tags by default.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kratix automatically applies this change across all existing and future bucket instances.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Developers see no disruption or extra workload; the platform seamlessly manages the update.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since each request needs unique tags, let’s add a container to the workflow to inject them into the Terraform file:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdciQjlPjqM81JnNtknURym-jQOgpZXu35I0wkznuZspKzNC3ny7FUV3AvRTU5x47tzIkzsVNzl6KCivUKoWu6Xj5vuLjYOVENUhZuDLy7EElVEuQGLlQ8uVTMSz3LhlBsZFCbsnQ?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; width=&#34;602&#34; height=&#34;168&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After we apply this updated Promise, Kratix will roll out the change to the fleet by reconciling the workflows again with the new definition:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcilGUH6jOCB52GjO6s0RSFON0_9Cmb895zbDPEPChXeJ9yHoeHocq-J0tXbeEf4YlZLvajq-1pxHkfYUkoi8dnvX_8yK1jZ88BSx_VCd9I_m3xYpwHoS5bm2nxTzq_N-BMxvuiwQ?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; width=&#34;602&#34; height=&#34;116&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This results in each individual request getting updated with the required tags:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfZHzFUFsZvvCYVcu9wIZstovN202cCR3scuW-XZnyNWCbrxWaAR9PvIDnFIM4P52J0jrO9aMbhtcNHSzNWGQuebO8lOyvdIzEocyli6ghpIc8eKvcSKpu4J-GzFjOW8PtEuopi?key=cs2U_MELkx96U6Ss20MwfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Conclusion: Empower Your Platform with Terraform and Kratix&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Terraform modules alone aren’t sufficient for sustainable infrastructure management. By leveraging Kratix Promises, you achieve a consistent, secure, and efficient self-service infrastructure. Additionally, you gain powerful integrations with developer portals, simplifying the delivery and ongoing management of your platform as a seamless, intuitive service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Developers gain streamlined tools without complexity, and your organisation benefits from scalable, maintainable infrastructure management.If you want to transform Terraform modules into API-driven platform capabilities, try Kratix today with our &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.kratix.io/main/quick-start&#34;&gt;guided quickstart&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您与Terraform合作了任何时间，则可能会直接将Terraform模块直接交给应用程序开发人员。尽管这使团队能够快速开始，但它可能导致痛苦的世界。例如，以下报价是否来自大型银行的内部开发人员平台团队工程师会引起您的共鸣？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我给了我的开发人员一个可重复使用的Terraform模块，用于Postgres。一周后，三支球队分叉了，他们都没有启用备份，而当出现问题时，我就在挂钩……” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果是这样，请继续阅读！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;向开发人员提供地表模块的危险&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;乍一看，为开发人员提供Terraform模块的情况似乎很简单。模块封装了最佳实践，使用户易于提供基础架构。但是，问题迅速浮出水面：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;团队独立管理Terraform配置，导致蔓延，并始终如一地跟踪合规性或管理基础设施。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;那些相同的独立配置允许错误的配置蔓延，从而导致关键应用程序未经备份或高可用性等基本功能提供。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;应用关键的安全补丁或更新成为一个涉及多个团队和存储库的手动，容易出错的过程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些挑战迅速减少了使用Terraform模块的初始好处。通常，团队发现自己被迫重写或大量重构其Terraform代码库，这是一个昂贵，破坏性和风险的过程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，如果有一种方法可以实现所需的平台工程成果而不从头开始重新启动呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;为什么Terraform需要平台层&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Terraform模块功能强大，但它们对开发人员施加了沉重的运营负担。团队必须深入了解Terraform，处理国家管理的复杂性并保持安全和最新的配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;转到一种标准化的自助服务方式，通过平台提供服务和规定基础架构可以提供您想要的结果，而无需您的团队从头开始重建所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这正是Kratix，Kratix是一个用于构建&lt;a href =“ https:///www.syntasso.io.io/internal-developer-platforms”&gt;内部开发人员平台&lt;/a&gt;提供的方式：&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; boottrapping Terraform模块纳入Kratix Prosise &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kratix提供了承诺的概念。承诺是您要在平台上提供的服务的定义。借助Kratix，将现有的Terraform模块转换为托管的自助服务功能变得毫不费力。例如，使用简单的“ kratix init” cli命令：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy&#39;decoding =“ async”），可以快速将用于AWS S3存储器的示例Terraform模块快速转换为托管服务。 src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxf3hbpvjtwoy7sjs-5tq1jp4ewesuy9e26vdxxxxxgcccduhrbxv5rbxv5r2ytpe--5r2yr2ytpe--- XNLAN9S7NFWPHEQWDOROKGUKEPK9SEVBPAWZVBX5YBNFJPBLQZCSJVEUECGXRBJ6AU8VMTTH6CM-TMBNQ？ width =“ 602” height =“ 136” referrerpolicy =“ no-toferrer”&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此命令为我们产生了承诺。这一承诺有效地提供了Terraform模块的API，公开了与模块本身相同的输入值集。&lt;br&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” Src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfb8bpc6hqlkeyndttm3nqjrixzzn5tbkochifvjvjvjvdppwdpw2n9cjfltxd0 STQFTAXJ_AFUC0ED3CRQ3GXNG0DJDTXE3FHDMMOA3WRTJGYETWH_GGD13EPTKMD2JAQOBH7VDT6SS4C3？ width =“ 602” height =“ 427” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们现在可以安装承诺并在平台上提供产品：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfqt8dwcuvt9t9t8dzybd1dnbd1dnbdfdpv1lhcu70lqtimyqtimyqtimyq9k2ng8zaoexfah sppuvera2sy1mdwzzi56y1m7ljyr6hplxi_00stw3lr_tmhrgweuptri2jovyjlq5y7f5la0k74xsijdw？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此示例中，我正在运行Syntasso kratix Enterprise（SKE），并具有对后台门户的内置支持，因此默认情况下，我所有的承诺也将添加到我已配置的后台实例中：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxf3tcinsxulfmvwxr1xewttznlso0ahu0ahu0ahu0uzclyiyyyylajoie67j7j7xoyuvj 2yig3cfbhauh9glvyHix-ymouds23er_vzr0n88gyhmk95dce_euiikeiig1quu24v3qvkjq5zde9116fg？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;为开发人员提供无缝的自助体验&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有了Kratix的承诺，开发人员不再与Terraform直接互动，也不再管理所得的基础架构。取而代之的是，他们利用了Kubernetes API等熟悉的接口或开发人员门户网站，例如在后台提供和管理基础架构，服务和其他平台组件。这种自助服务模型大大降低了复杂性，并使开发人员专注于构建应用程序。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我使用SKE时，我可以直接进入后台并浏览已安装的承诺，然后立即开始填写表格以请求AWS S3桶。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4NXCCJ3ZB2GXQXFSNRUCUH1QLOB46AN8CKANOISMZ0IXXYIXXY8B_IFL4EDHZ 57OP5H7O4D3120CW9QZE2LHDMAHODHN9LT_CJB0GB2ZPS8ANEVTZV0BSK8PHBPRGDBPRGDQZPTZVFF5QJFBZTW？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我在后台提交请求后，kratix t索具在承诺中定义的工作流程，该工作流将生成所需的Terraform代码，以将模块与用户的输入调和。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此示例中，我使用的GitHub回购与GitHub操作配置为调和请求：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcsx1_78t41-cg0r8so2xxkdtcvnafstsvmv_6jjjj_ea4xwllorzjzuc2 0trzgoyndxjbw5nnpwm0c0mrrngwi8jaszp23j61u6pvopwwwnm5jdzokum71ytkubnumugxx9tnruubfg？ width =“ 602” height =“ 251” referrerpolicy =“ no-toferrer”&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;自定义工作流程：批准和治理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;某些服务配置需要额外的监督。例如，您可能希望为使用特定敏感设置提供的AWS S3存储桶添加手册批准。 Kratix使将其他逻辑插入工作流程中变得直接。在此示例中，让我们添加一个手动批准步骤，以便用户想创建公开访问的S3存储桶。该代码检测何时将Bucket Promise的公共配置属性设置为True，并创建JIRA问题以供手动批准。 Kratix将等待该票关闭，然后再进行S3存储桶：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcirmojmda_3qurgvdldueyixk3_k6bn5797a4i9a4i9gw4w4w4w4w4w4wurnfakrw_ou DWBYXQPS7P8NECMEOBK4ID_6OTNLNIDWBTRQGN609APZAX5KNIGF7KNIGF7K1QTQJ62QGK36VXT2RB2RB2ITEKBU？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每次用户提出请求时，此批准步骤将运行。让我们以“ public”设置为“ true”提出一个新请求，您可以看到工作流将等待批准，然后再将Terraform输出到GitHub：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxecz_2_htcx0jsnuix7yss8dd_xvy8ujapra22nlhjuspxkkkkvkkmwdeohc XQQGRZPP36UGETV_M6Y_XKOO8BKBVM9M4-325UAUW1JRSBOXUKIKIWAUFX203THHYAHXGFH7-YXILQFPG？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;车队管理：无干扰的更新&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想象一下，您的业务决定默认情况下必须在所有存储桶上使用描述性的成本跟踪finops标签。没有克拉蒂克斯，推出这样的政策将需要与每个管理自己的水库的团队进行大量的手动努力和协调。使用Kratix，更新您执行标签的承诺很简单且自动：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更新承诺定义以默认配置标签。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Kratix自动在所有现有和将来的存储桶实例中应用此更改。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开发人员认为没有中断或额外的工作量；该平台无缝管理更新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于每个请求都需要独特的标签，让我们在工作流程中添加一个容器以将其注入Terraform文件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy”解码=“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdciqjlpjqm81jnntknurym-jqogpzxxu35i0wkznuznuznuznuznuzspkznc3ny7fuv3 avrtu5x47tzikzsvnzl6kcivukowu6xj5vuljyovenuhzudlyhzudly7eelveuqgllqgllqgllqgllq8uvtmsz3lhlbszfcbsnq？ width =“ 602” height =“ 168” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;在应用此更新的承诺之后，Kratix将通过再次将工作流程与新定义调和新定义：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcilguh6jocb52gjo6s0rsfon0_9cmb895zbdpepeppeppeppepchxej9yhoehoehocq-j 0TXBEEF4YLZLVAJQ-1PXHKFYUKOI8DNVX_8YK1JZ88BSX_VCD9I_M3XYPWHOS5BM2NXTZQ_N-BMXVUIWQ？ width =“ 602” height =“ 116” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这会导致每个单独的请求使用所需的标签进行更新：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfzhzfufszvvcyvcyvcucu9wizstovn202ccr3scuw-xznynwcbrxbrxbrxbrxbrxbrxbrxbrxbrxbrxbrxwaar9pv IDNFIM4P52J0JRO9AMBHTCNHSZNWGQUEBOBO8LOYVDIZEYOCYLI6GHPIC8EKVCSKPU4J-GZFJOW8PTEUOPI？key = cs2u_melkx96u6sssss20mwfa&#39; alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;结论：用Terraform和Kratix &lt;/h3&gt;授权您的平台&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; terraform模块仅足以实现可持续的基础设施管理。通过利用Kratix承诺，您可以实现一致，安全和高效的自助服务基础架构。此外，您可以与开发人员门户网站获得强大的集成，从而简化了平台的交付和持续管理为无缝，直观的服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开发人员在没有复杂性的情况下获得精简工具，并且您的组织受益于可扩展，可维护的基础架构管理。如果您想将Terraform模块转换为API驱动的平台功能，请立即使用我们的&lt;a href =“ https：// https://docs.kratix.kratix.io/main/quick-/quick-start &lt;/guded QuickSTART &lt;/p. &lt;/p）&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking Talent Through Mentorship: Join Nate Waddington at OSS Europe】通过指导来解锁人才：加入OSS欧洲OSS的Nate Waddington</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/06/unlocking-talent-through-mentorship-join-nate-waddington-at-oss-europe/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdT2nKPBk5oOtVn1joRGTna2aS1Uzywl0dEA5yOqEg43QgJds_KxGMZttwJPf_Hok0eah5_mMceVYUDw5ezjZDeB71dlQ8pxqq_lAxdPGyMTO_ua7wRi93eZPRQq1fV7rIdvjy8Qg?key=d2ZirLi6clPueD9zBvvW-Q&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Open Source Summit EU is excited to return 25-27 August in Amsterdam.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m speaking at &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/open-source-summit-europe/&#34;&gt;Open Source Summit Europe&lt;/a&gt; in Amsterdam next month, and I hope to see you there. My session, &lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://osseu2025.sched.com/event/265cb/sponsored-session-unlock-growth-and-talent-effectiveness-of-mentorship-in-open-source-projects-nate-waddington-cncf?iframe=no&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unlock Growth and Talent—Effectiveness of Mentorship in Open Source Projects,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt; isn’t just about stats or program structure; it’s a direct invitation to reshape how we bring new contributors into open source.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This talk is for maintainers, contributors, community builders, and anyone else who wants to see OSS thrive long-term.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🧭 Why Mentorship and Why Now?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Too often, we lose good people at the start. It’s not a lack of skill but an unclear path that led to their departure. CNCF’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/about/mentoring/&#34;&gt;mentorship programs&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://lfx.linuxfoundation.org/tools/mentorship/&#34;&gt;LFX Mentorship&lt;/a&gt; and community-initiated pathways, provide a structured approach for newcomers to learn, contribute, and eventually lead. Mentorship isn’t about hand-holding; it’s about guiding individuals to discover their own path.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I will demonstrate the outcome of maintainers inviting contributions and providing guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeugdRg9yHpqiYz7kHBGVHh1xiB5B0jiLmbd4dJOOo052yzxlKiljoTAlXsgfpyAMTI0-mykS8hgLPjQeAJ-PGevl-x1WXvPtuv0tx1_hU8oMKdZjG9TDzp6GzfXwVdtA1GJLhBgQ?key=d2ZirLi6clPueD9zBvvW-Q&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Maintainers on site.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🧱 We’ll Talk About the Hard Parts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The real blocker in OSS isn’t lack of interest but a lack of access. I’ll walk through how mentorship helps fix that by:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Aligning project needs with contributor growth&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Designing a mentorship experience that leads to long-term community health&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ll also share mistakes we’ve made and how we adjusted. I will cover how some mentorship projects fell short due to scope creep or unclear expectations. That feedback loop helped us better train mentors and create more focused, achievable proposals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdSGZsQ9_1ntziZnSWtAooX422R5tiwFwOepqPSbCvsWp20f_bT8uDGH3UupXPwuNwNEPOzPgOvTceCek2E17BxeIKooBb3gfqUSIe5ObT9vrkNsL-C_HK6xjRirjboezelg-tjvA?key=d2ZirLi6clPueD9zBvvW-Q&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Peer Group Mentoring at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon EU 2025.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🔍 What You’ll Get from This Session&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ll walk through how to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build a mentorship path in your own project&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set mentees up to actually land PRs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ll share examples of successful mentee pull requests and offer concrete advice on how to give timely feedback without burning out. Expect real-world stories, updated data, and fresh takeaways from recent mentorship terms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🛠 Who Should Come?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintainers&lt;/strong&gt; wondering how to grow contributor pipelines without burning out&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community folks&lt;/strong&gt; working on contributor strategy, DEI, or onboarding&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re any of the above—or are curious what works in practice—this session will be worth your time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcw8spsRjNkyh3WvbXHaSFFTEtJYEGM07MmGvtjrEnWyBJeHoQWhTXU3fyy0zIaS4n2xeO38njrfQeV8-blJMqdQw1m0A3v_bQQ-Urfne6JhdsSmXHlp4Kf8rYCkAMm-gwWSKXUpw?key=d2ZirLi6clPueD9zBvvW-Q&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Curious maintainers and community folks – this could be you!&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🗓 Mark Your Calendar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://osseu2025.sched.com/event/265cb/sponsored-session-unlock-growth-and-talent-effectiveness-of-mentorship-in-open-source-projects-nate-waddington-cncf?iframe=no&#34;&gt;Unlock Growth and Talent—Effectiveness of Mentorship in Open Source Projects&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;When:&lt;/strong&gt; 25 August, 2025, 11:00 – 11:40 CEST&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where:&lt;/strong&gt; Auditorium&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you interested in proposing a mentorship project, applying as a mentee, or simply learning more? Visit&lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/about/mentoring/&#34;&gt; contribute.cncf.io/mentoring&lt;/a&gt; to see timelines, examples, and ways to get involved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bring questions, ideas, or just yourself. I’m looking forward to a real conversation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeUg3tBvXw2fgEie_Sq-U-KpZy6LIE_sd6BCv6-5YY_qzxrOut6NksR6M2Rtw0EGkkGc4Qd24X-Y5EWPNbEEuCnOu5Ly0KWV4oGuiragsA9vea2d6v1zw1EoJ3jfgT5VEn27dxwLg?key=d2ZirLi6clPueD9zBvvW-Q&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Open Source Summit will take place 25-27 August in Amsterdam.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdt2nkpbk5ootvn1jorgtna2as1uzywl0dea5yoqeg43qgjds_kxgmzt TWJPF_HOK0EAH5_MMCEVYUDW5EZJZDEB71DLQ8PXQQQQQQ_LAXDPGYMTO_UA7WRI9WRII9WRI93EZPRQ1FV7RIDVJY8QG？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ wp- element-caption”&gt;开源峰会EU很高兴8月25日至27日在阿姆斯特丹返回。&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我在&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/open-source-summit-europe/”&gt;开放式欧洲峰会&lt;/a&gt;下个月在阿姆斯特丹，我希望在那里见到您。我的会议，&lt;em&gt;“ &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =” https://osseu2025.sched.com/event/265cb/sponsored-session-session-session-session-session-nock-growth-and-talent--talent-talent--talent-smentors-opmentors-open-open-sopen-soupen-source--projects-projects-nate-nate-waddationton-waddington-cncff？项目，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;“ &lt;/em&gt;不仅涉及统计或程序结构；这是重塑我们如何将新贡献者带入开源的直接邀请。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这次演讲适用于维护者，贡献者，社区建筑商以及其他任何想长期蓬勃发展的人。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;经常，我们一开始就失去了好人。这不是缺乏技巧，而是导致他们离开的不清楚的道路。 cncf的&lt;a href =“ https://contribute.cncf.io/about/mentor/”&gt; condorship program &lt;/a&gt;，包括&lt;a href =“ https://lfx.linuxfoundation.org/tools/mentorship/”贡献，最终领导。指导不是关于手持的；这是关于指导个人发现自己的道路。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我将展示维护者邀请贡献并提供指导的结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxeugdrg9yhpqiyz7khbgvhhh1xib5b5b5b0jilmbd4djooo052yzxlkiljota LXSGFPYAMTI0-MYKS8HGLPJQEAJ-pGEVL-X1WXVPTEV0TX1_HU8OMKDZJG9TDZP6GZFXWVDTA1GJLHBGQ？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ WP-元素caption”&gt;站点上的维护器。&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figifion&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OSS中的真正阻滞剂并不是缺乏兴趣，而是缺乏访问权限。我将仔细研究指导如何通过：&lt;/p&gt;来解决这个问题。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将项目需求与贡献者增长保持一致&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;设计导致长期社区健康的指导经验&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我还将分享我们犯的错误以及如何调整。由于范围蠕变或不明确的期望，我将介绍一些指导项目如何缺乏。反馈循环帮助我们更好地培训导师，并提出更加专注，可实现的建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;图Class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdsgzsq9_1ntziznswtaoox422r5tiwfwoepqpsbcpsbcvsbcvsbcvsbcvsbcvsp20f20f_bt8udgh 3UUPXPWUNWNEPOZPGOVTCECEK2E17BXEIKOOBB3GFQUSIE5OBT9VRKNSL-C_HK6XJRIRJBOEEZELG-TJVA？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ wp- element-caption”&gt; kubecon + cloudnativecon eu 2025。&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;🔍&lt;您将从此会话中获得什么&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我将走如何：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在您自己的项目中建立指导道路&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将受训者设置为实际降落PR &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我将分享成功的受训者拉请求的示例，并提供有关如何及时反馈而无需烧毁的具体建议。期待现实世界中的故事，更新的数据以及最近的指导条款的新鲜事项。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;🛠谁应该来？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;维护者&lt;/strong&gt;想知道如何在不燃烧的情况下种植贡献者的管道&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;社区人们&lt;/strong&gt;致力于贡献者策略，DEI或入职&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您是上述任何一种（或者很好奇实践中有效的作用），这将是值得的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcw8spsrjnkyh3wvbxhasfftetjyegm07mmgvtjrenwywybjehoqwhoqwhohoqwhtxu3 FYY0ZIAS4N2XEO38NJRFQEV8-BLJMQDQW1M0A3V_BQ_BQQ-QQ-urfNE6JHDSSSMXHLP4KF8RYCKAMM-GWWSKXKXKXKXKXKXKXKXKXKXKXUPW？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ wp- element-caption”&gt;好奇的维护者和社区人 - 这可能是您！&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;🗓标记您的日历&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://osseu2025.sched.com/event/265cb/sponsored-session-unlock-growth-and-talent-effectiveness-of-mentorship-in-open-source-projects-nate-waddington-cncf?iframe=no&#34;&gt;Unlock Growth and Talent—Effectiveness of Mentorship in Open Source项目&lt;br&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么时候：&lt;/strong&gt; 2025年8月25日，11：00  -  11:40 Cest &lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;礼堂&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您是否有兴趣提出一个指导项目，申请作为受训者，还是只是学习更多？请访问&lt;a href =“ https://contribute.cncf.io/about/mentoring/”&gt; pron produte.cncf.io/mentoring &lt;/a&gt;查看时间表，示例和参与方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;带来问题，想法或您自己。我期待着真正的对话。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在那里见！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxeug3tbvxw2fgeie_sq-u-kpzy6lie_sd6bcv6-5yy_qzxrout6nksr6 M2RTW0EGKKGC4QD24X-Y5EWPNBEEUCNOU5LY0KWV4OGUIRAGSA9VEA2D6V1ZW1EOJ3JFGT5VEN27DX7DX7DXWLG？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ WP-元素caption”&gt;开源峰会将进行8月25日至27日在阿姆斯特丹放置。&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figif&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Chain Reaction in Amsterdam: What’s New in CNCF’s 2025 Supply Chain Security Guide】阿姆斯特丹的连锁反应：CNCF的2025年供应链安全指南中有什么新功能</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/06/chain-reaction-in-amsterdam-whats-new-in-cncfs-2025-supply-chain-security-guide/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;CNCF Security TAG&lt;/a&gt;’s Supply Chain Security Best Practices Guide first launched in 2021, just as high-profile supply chain attacks were beginning to shake public and private sector software systems alike. In 2025, the importance of supply chain security has escalated significantly: in 2023, supply chain breaches resulted in damage exceeding $45 billion, and projections indicate that this damage could reach over $80 billion by 2026 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.juniperresearch.com/press/study-reveals-staggering-cost-of-software-supply/&#34;&gt;Juniper Research&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeZee6mxj6DaH10WJkFGCpl8bujOmulGrSfp5vf0ugmn5LLaU31dqtplM4KrpGbQcfHYW9s23H7OwJ_L-zZMMp-71tSAhUcllXH5mmRPdtF9dzLha_U0_Zabm-r7rC-_wyYHKaIKg?key=Qvw9y3l4V55NUZedUYjXfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Open Source Summit EU will take place in Amsterdam from 25-27 August, 2025.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/open-source-summit-europe/&#34;&gt;Open Source Summit Europe&lt;/a&gt; this August in Amsterdam, CNCF TAG Security co-chair &lt;a href=&#34;https://osseu2025.sched.com/speaker/kjell.john?iframe=no&#34;&gt;John Kjell&lt;/a&gt; (ControlPlane) will present a fresh perspective on the updated guide in his session:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🕒 &lt;strong&gt;Monday, August 25, 14:25–15:05 CEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;📍 &lt;strong&gt;Emerald Room&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 📚 &lt;strong&gt;Session: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://osseu2025.sched.com/event/25VoD/chain-reaction-remixing-cncfs-supply-chain-security-guide-for-2025-john-kjell-controlplane?iframe=no&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chain Reaction: Remixing CNCF’s Supply Chain Security Guide for 2025&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why It Matters Now&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Since 2021, the ecosystem around software supply chain security has exploded. SBOMs, attestations, and software integrity tooling have matured fast, and open source communities have kept pace, building standards, frameworks, and pipelines to detect and defend against tampering, dependency confusion, and unauthorized changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;John’s talk dives into the most impactful updates in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/community/working-groups/supply-chain-security/supply-chain-security-paper-v2/Software_Supply_Chain_Practices_whitepaper_v2.pdf&#34;&gt;second edition&lt;/a&gt; of CNCF’s guide, focusing on:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The role of SBOMs and attestations, now mainstream and backed by robust tooling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Best practices for chaining together tools across the dev, build, and deploy lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Concrete integrations between CNCF and OpenSSF projects that teams can use today&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projects You’ll Hear About&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;John will highlight key projects from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;CNCF&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://openssf.org/projects/&#34;&gt;OpenSSF&lt;/a&gt; ecosystem, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openssf.org/projects/bomctl/&#34;&gt;Bomctl&lt;/a&gt;—a format-agnostic Software Bill of Materials (SBOM) tooling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://guac.sh/&#34;&gt;Graph for Understanding Artifact Composition (GUAC)&lt;/a&gt;—an open source supply chain security project that provides dependency management and actionable insights into the security of software supply chains&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://in-toto.io/&#34;&gt;in-toto&lt;/a&gt;—a framework to secure the integrity of software supply chains&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openssf.org/projects/protobom/&#34;&gt;protobom&lt;/a&gt;—a format-neutral SBOM data representation and I/O library&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sbomit.dev/&#34;&gt;SBOMit&lt;/a&gt;—an SBOM format-independent method for attesting components with additional verification information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://slsa.dev/&#34;&gt;Supply-chain Levels for Software Artifacts (SLSA)&lt;/a&gt;—a set of incrementally adoptable guidelines for supply chain security, established by industry consensus&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://theupdateframework.io/&#34;&gt;The Update Framework (TUF)&lt;/a&gt;—a framework for securing software update systems&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfNRKjkKcgFHGQz4P0W7lWr--NEcxJDA87-6jeqekRbI2yuCmLPUkFLratPgHiXR8vD9hzyvRrNGrYtHqqJcU8hp9DGcBoUzWZEHe7tQE_Sw-TmsC951cDooEgm1HmRwvlH55BAJA?key=Qvw9y3l4V55NUZedUYjXfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;At the event you’ll hear from projects such as Bomctl, GUAC, in-toto, Protobom, SBOMit, SLSA, and TUF.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These tools help organizations automate and verify trust throughout their software lifecycle, protecting both proprietary infrastructure and shared open source components.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Catch: A Deep Dive into Public Sector Software Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Immediately after this session, John will return to the stage to explore supply chain security from a public sector perspective:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🕒 &lt;strong&gt;Monday, August 25, 15:35–16:15 CEST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;📍 &lt;strong&gt;Room G105&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 📚 &lt;strong&gt;Session: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://osseu2025.sched.com/event/25VoM/the-chain-of-command-building-trust-across-public-sector-software-pipelines-john-kjell-controlplane?iframe=no&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Chain of Command: Building Trust Across Public Sector Software Pipelines&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Drawing on the work of CNCF’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/public-sector-user-group/&#34;&gt;Public Sector User Group&lt;/a&gt;, this session looks at the real-world challenges facing government and regulated sector teams. From air-gapped environments to trust frameworks that span agencies and suppliers, John will unpack:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Current challenges in public sector supply chain security&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Emerging needs for trust, attestations, and integration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ideas for equitable, scalable solutions across supplier sizes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This talk builds on recent publications from the user group and aims to foster dialogue around scalable, equitable security strategies for public infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the CNCF Security TAG&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;CNCF’s Technical Advisory Group for Security (TAG Security)&lt;/a&gt; works to improve the security of cloud native applications, platforms, and supply chains. TAG Security produces best practices and threat modeling resources and collaborates across open source projects to elevate the state of secure infrastructure. Their work has led to essential guides, working groups, and contributions across the CNCF and OpenSSF ecosystems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Speaker&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;John Kjell is principal consultant at &lt;a href=&#34;https://control-plane.io/&#34;&gt;ControlPlane&lt;/a&gt;, co-chair of CNCF’s TAG Security, and a maintainer of the in-toto subprojects &lt;a href=&#34;https://witness.dev/&#34;&gt;Witness&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/in-toto/archivista&#34;&gt;Archivista&lt;/a&gt;. He’s also a familiar face in &lt;a href=&#34;https://openssf.org/&#34;&gt;OpenSSF&lt;/a&gt; circles and formerly led open source at TestifySec. With years of hands-on experience building secure pipelines, John brings clarity and pragmatism to an often complex landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;132&#34; height=&#34;132&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcbS0DMs2df7S0wOD96n1d57YfY61ROjS-Daqm8QKOJ_b_rRDG30PQX6qb6NuH_8EL-it-iZkc2uo8OBIydKd3L8f64-lg5cdZ-I17RN0QQjTYhbG-7BcTIRiuFqlpNePo-X_3CQw?key=Qvw9y3l4V55NUZedUYjXfA&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;624&#34; height=&#34;335&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcpZLT4Fe4a40H_G-_pXWMCtqQCUoJ73yfynMFoyM_rd0rBbL2mFyiH66B9dzA_CNlMooLAPuz-apBzotWA362cxdlz1-7YGDPjTcqJ9PU44Zz9SEPxOqwr6BboirIVxcdMObsCeQ?key=Qvw9y3l4V55NUZedUYjXfA&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the Conversation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to contribute to future work on supply chain security? You can get involved with&lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; CNCF TAG Security&lt;/a&gt; by joining a working group, attending an open meeting, or contributing to one of our guides or project assessments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re attending OSS EU, don’t miss this opportunity to engage with one of the lead contributors behind CNCF’s refreshed guidance on supply chain security. Mark your calendar for August 25!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🛡️ &lt;strong&gt;Security is a shared responsibility. Let’s build better chains together.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXf39vJ0AFsg6g_Gc6pR7gSvBJD7baeLrwJHkFSFdnnVWfG3NPVZp_Z1Gfo4qXj0rJgm4B0mg33hoJ0w7gTaLflWSfgnKtksB4rVosOugAz6V0OsPjgxFULrQK4WMzXlzbvfjwwA?key=Qvw9y3l4V55NUZedUYjXfA&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon EU heads to Amsterdam 23-26, March 2026.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://tag-security.cncf.io/”&gt; cncf安全标签&lt;/a&gt;的供应链安全最佳实践指南于2021年首次推出，就像高调供应链攻击一样，开始摇晃公共和私营部门软件系统。 In 2025, the importance of supply chain security has escalated significantly: in 2023, supply chain breaches resulted in damage exceeding $45 billion, and projections indicate that this damage could reach over $80 billion by 2026 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.juniperresearch.com/press/study-reveals-staggering-cost-of-software-supply/&#34;&gt;Juniper研究&lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxezee6mxj6dah10wjkfgcplgcpl8bujomulgrsfp5vfp5vf0ugmn5llau31dqtpl M4KrPGBQCFHYW9S23H7OWJ_L-ZZMMP-71TSAHUCLLXH5MMRPDTF9DZLHA_U0_U0_ZABM-R7RC-R7RC-_WYYHKAIKG？ alt =“” ReferrerPolicy =“ No-Referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ WP-元素caption”&gt;开源峰会将于2025年8月25日至27日在阿姆斯特丹举行。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; at &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/open-source-source-summit-europe/”&gt;开源的欧洲峰会&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; cncf tag cncf tag Security Co-Co-Chair &lt;a a href &lt;a href = a href =“ href =” Kjell &lt;/a&gt;（控制页面）将在其会议中的更新指南中介绍一个新的视角：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 8月25日，星期一，14：25–15：05 Cest &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; emerald Room &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;brang&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; session：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://osseu2025.sched.com/event/25vod/chain-reaction-remixing-cncfs-cncfs-supply-chain-chain-security-guide-for-for-2025-2025-john-john-kjell-controlplane？ 2025 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么现在很重要&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;自2021年以来，软件供应链安全围绕的生态系统已经爆炸。 SBOM，证明和软件完整性工具已经快速成熟，开源社区保持了步伐，建筑标准，框架和管道，以检测和防御篡改，依赖性混乱和未经授权的变化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;约翰的谈话介绍了&lt;a href =“ https://tag-security.cncf.io/community/working-groups/supply-chain-security/supply-chain-security/supply-chain-chain-chain-security-paper-paper-paper-v2/soft-paper-v2/software_supply_chain_chain_chain_prappractrice_prapter_prapter_prapter_prapter_prapter_prapter_praptrice_prapter_prapter_prapter_prapter_pprater&#39; CNCF指南的关注：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; SBOM和证明的作用，现在是主流的，并由强大的工具支持&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将工具融合在一起的最佳实践，建立和部署生命周期&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; CNCF和OpenSSF项目之间的具体集成，团队今天可以使用的项目&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您会听到有关&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; John将从&lt;a a href =“ https:///landscape.cncf.io/”中突出关键项目的项目。tps：//openssf.org/projects/“&gt; openssf &lt;/a&gt;生态系统，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://openssf.org/projects/bomctl/”&gt; bomctl &lt;/a&gt;  -  format-aggnostic软件材料清单（SBOM）工具&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://guac.sh/”&gt;用于理解工件构图（GUAC）的图形&lt;/a&gt;  - 一个开源供应链安全项目，可提供依赖性管理和可行的洞察软件供应链的安全性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://in-toto.io/”&gt; in-toto &lt;/a&gt;  - 确保软件供应链完整性的框架&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://openssf.org/projects/protobom/”&gt; protobom &lt;/a&gt;  - 格式-Neutral SBOM数据表示形式，I/O library &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://sbomit.dev/”&gt; sbomit &lt;/a&gt;  - 一种使用其他验证信息来证明组件的SBOM格式 - 独立方法。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://slsa.dev/”&gt;软件工件（SLSA）的供应 - 链级&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://theupdateframework.io/”&gt; the Update Framework（TUF）&lt;/a&gt;  - 用于确保软件更新系统的框架&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfnrkjkkcgfhgqz4p0w7lwr--necxjda87-6jeqekekrbi2yucmlpukflr ATPGHIXR8VD9HZYVRRNGRYTHQJCU8HP9DGCBOUZWZEHE7TQE_SW-SW-TMSC951CDOOEGM1HMRWVLH55BAJA？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the-caption class =” wp-element-caption =“ wp-element-caption”&gt;在您会从诸如bomctl，guac，guac，intoto，toto，protobom，sbomit，sbomit，slsa和tuf等项目中听到的事件。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些工具可帮助组织在整个软件生命周期中自动化和验证信任，保护专有基础架构和共享开源组件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;也抓住：深入研究公共部门软件安全&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;在本次会议之后，约翰将重返舞台，从公共部门的角度探索供应链安全：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 8月25日，星期一，15：35–16：15 Cest &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; g105 &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;brang&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; session：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://osseu2025.sched.com/event/25vom/the-chain-of-command-building-command-building-command-trust-trust-trust-trust-cublic-sector-soft-software-pipeline-pipelines-pipelines-john-kjell-kjell-controllollam-controllalplane一下：iframe = no”管道&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借鉴CNCF的&lt;a href =“ https://community.cncf.io/public-sector-sector-user-group/”&gt;公共部门用户组&lt;/a&gt;，本届会议着眼于面临政府和受监管的部门团队面临的现实世界挑战。从空地环境到跨越机构和供应商的信任框架，约翰将拆开：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;公共部门供应链安全的当前挑战&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;出现信任，证明和集成的需求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;跨供应商尺寸的公平，可扩展解决方案的想法&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此演讲是建立在用户组的最新出版物的基础上，旨在促进围绕公共基础架构的可扩展，公平安全策略的对话。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;关于CNCF安全标签&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://tag-security.cncf.io/”&gt; CNCF的安全性（TAG Security）技术咨询小组（TAG Security）&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;有助于提高云的本地应用程序，平台和补给界的云安全性。标签安全性可产生最佳实践和威胁建模资源，并在开源项目之间进行协作，以提升安全基础架构的状态。他们的工作导致了CNCF和OpenSSF生态系统的基本指南，工作组和贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;关于讲话者&lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; John Kjell是&lt;a href =“ https:///control-plane.io/”&gt; ControlPlane &lt;/a&gt;，CNCF标签安全性的联合主席，以及Intoto subprosprotss &lt;a href = a href =“ href =” htps &lt;/af control-plane.io/“&gt; controlplane &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/in-toto/archivista”&gt; Archivista &lt;/a&gt;。他也是&lt;a href =“ https://openssf.org/”&gt; openssf &lt;/a&gt;圆圈&lt;/a&gt;圆圈和以前在tistifysec领导的开源的熟悉面孔。约翰拥有多年的动手实践经验，可以使经常复杂的景观带来清晰和实用主义。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img loading =“懒惰”解码=“ async” width =“ 132” height =“ 132” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcbs0dms2df7s0wod96n1d57yfy61Rojs-daqm8qkoj_b_rrdg30pqx6 QB6NUH_8EL-IT-ISKC2UO8OBIYDKD3L8F64-LG5CDZ-I17RN0QQQJJTYHBG-7BCTIRIUFQLPNEPO-X_3CQW？ referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy”解码=“ async” width =“ 624” height =“ 335” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcpzlt4fe4fe4a40h_g-_pxwmctqqccuoj73yfynmfynmfoym_rd0rbbl2mfyih6 6B9DZA_CNLMOOLAPUZ-APBZOTWA362CXDLZ1-7YGDPJTCQJ9PU444zz9SEPXOQWR6BBOIRIVXCDMOBSCEQ？ referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;加入对话&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想为供应链安全的未来工作做出贡献吗？您可以参与&lt;a href =“ https://tag-security.cncf.io/”&gt; cncf标签安全&lt;/a&gt;通过加入工作组，参加公开会议或为我们的指南或项目评估贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您要参加OSS EU，请不要错过这个机会，与CNCF刷新供应链安全指南的主要贡献者之一互动。在8月25日标记您的日历！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;🛡️&lt;strong&gt;安全是共同的责任。让我们一起建造更好的链条。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxf39vj0afsg6g6g_gc_gc6pr7gsvbjd7baelrwjhkfsfsfsfsfsfsfdnnnnnnvwfg3npvzp_p_z1 GFO4QXJ0RJGM4B0MG33HOJ0W7GTALFLWSFGNKTKSB4RVOSOUGAZ6V0OSPJGXFLRQK4WMZXLZBVFFJWWA？ alt =“” Referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ wp- element-caption”&gt; kubecon + cloudnativecon eu前往阿姆斯特丹23-26，2026年3月。&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building smarter, scalable AI applications】构建更智能，可扩展的AI应用程序</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/07/building-smarter-scalable-ai-applications/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;While GenAI has been driving transformative change, WebAssembly (WASM) works in the background to enhance performance and security in web and cross-platform applications. Although WASM and GenAI are distinct in their respective capabilities, combining them unlocks valuable possibilities that can benefit your business, as part of your GenAI adoption.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WASM can deliver near-native performance in constrained environments, which perfectly complements the typically computation-heavy demands of GenAI models. Together, WASM and GenAI create a powerful solution for deploying and scaling AI-driven applications with greater efficiency and flexibility for your business across diverse use cases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we unpack how GenAI and WASM intersect, discuss why your organisation should consider investing, and share strategies to future-proof your AI infrastructure with a strong focus on security and compliance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;is-style-default&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why WASM belongs in your AI infrastructure&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WASM has evolved into a high-performance runtime, enabling efficient execution across diverse computing environments, from edge devices to serverless infrastructures. Its core strengths include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Near-native performance even on constrained or distributed devices&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;True portability, enabling “build once, run anywhere” across browsers, servers, and edge nodes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Built-in sandboxed security, ideal for zero-trust environments and multi-tenant systems&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These attributes position WASM as a compelling solution for modern application development, offering performance, flexibility, and security across a wide range of deployment scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As GenAI platforms grow more fragmented with increased costs, WASM enables faster launches, efficient scaling, and reduced cloud dependency without the need to re-architect. GenAI workloads are typically resource-heavy, so WASM’s lightweight execution model makes it possible to run them securely and efficiently across a wide range of environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re already seeing this shift in action with the rise of Vercel-like WASM-native platforms. This shift means that developers are gaining autonomy, deploying high-performance applications without being locked into heavyweight platforms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, new models like o1 and Deepseek-R1 are expanding GenAI capabilities, such as generating code, content, and insights at scale.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WASM is the lightweight, future-proof runtime that makes these innovations more accessible and manageable.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overcoming GenAI deployment challenges&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional GenAI deployments often struggle to scale in real-time, particularly on lower-end devices like entry-level laptops or smartphones. These performance limitations create bottlenecks as demand grows, driving up infrastructure costs, causing inconsistent user experiences, and limiting GenAI’s reach in mobile or offline-first environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tools like Ollama have shown that running models locally is possible, but performance drops significantly outside of high-spec systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is where WASM comes in. Integrating WASM into your AI infrastructure enables teams to optimise GenAI workloads across a broader range of devices without the burden of expensive infrastructure.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, its impact depends on how well it’s aligned with your specific use case within your business. Key factors to consider:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model size and complexity&lt;/strong&gt;: WASM is ideal for lightweight GenAI tasks like text summarisation or transcription. Larger models may need quantisation or pruning to fit within WASM’s current memory limits. Tools like WebLLM demonstrate how browser-based LLMs can work with WebGPU support.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance and acceleration:&lt;/strong&gt; WASM offers near-native speeds but lacks direct GPU support, which limits compute-heavy GenAI workloads. WebGPU is starting to close this gap for in-browser inference.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Portability: &lt;/strong&gt;WASM’s platform-neutral design lets you “write once, run anywhere” across browsers and server environments, simplifying your deployment pipeline.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scalability:&lt;/strong&gt; Combining WASM with serverless platforms reduces cold start times and improves resource efficiency, making it easier to scale GenAI apps.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security:&lt;/strong&gt; WASM’s sandboxing enhances runtime isolation, crucial for secure AI execution, especially in multi-tenant or zero-trust setups.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy:&lt;/strong&gt; Local-first deployment through WASM keeps sensitive data on-device, reducing reliance on external servers and enhancing user trust.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To fully take advantage of pairing WASM and GenAI, your team must navigate a few current technical limitations, such as access to specialised hardware, like GPUs and the availability of AI-ready development tools. A practical way to address this limitation is by using modern tools like Turso.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Turso is a lightweight, distributed database designed to run efficiently on a wide range of devices, even without high-end infrastructure. Turso is well-suited for AI workloads because it can quickly search and retrieve information using built-in vector search and compress large datasets to run smoothly on local machines. This means:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Faster responses for your AI applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lower cloud dependency, which can reduce costs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Better data control, helping with privacy and compliance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Incorporating a tool like Turso into your AI stack makes it easier to run GenAI apps locally, securely, and at scale, without needing to overhaul your entire infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strengthening AI security and compliance with WASM&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adhering to regulations like GDPR is not an option, so as your organisational needs grow and your teams’ use of AI models grows, safeguarding sensitive data, confidential information, and proprietary business data needs to be a top priority. It’s not just a box to tick, but a core part of building trustworthiness and future-ready systems. When AI models are deployed using WASM, it offers meaningful security and compliance benefits for organisations deploying GenAI, particularly in highly regulated industries like finance and healthcare.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By executing code in a sandboxed environment, WASM isolates applications from the host system and other modules. This separation significantly reduces the risk of unauthorised access, helping to contain potential vulnerabilities and safeguard sensitive data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Local data processing is another major advantage. WASM allows AI workloads to run directly on user devices or within defined geographic boundaries, supporting data sovereignty requirements. This approach limits exposure to cross-border data transfer risks and simplifies compliance with regulations like the GDPR.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In healthcare, for instance, WASM can be used to run AI models locally, ensuring patient information such as electronic Protected Health Information (ePHI) stays on-device. Similarly, financial institutions can handle sensitive customer data without sending it to external servers, lowering the risk of breaches and maintaining compliance with industry-specific standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For senior technology leaders, the opportunity is clear. Start by assessing which AI workloads are best suited to local execution. Integrate WASM into your development workflows to take advantage of its built-in security architecture. And finally, stay ahead of regulatory changes to ensure ongoing compliance. Taken together, these steps will help future-proof your AI investments, strengthen your security posture, and give you greater control over how data is processed and protected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-world use cases and business impact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WASM and GenAI are already converging in ways that evoke a more efficient and decentralised future for AI. We’re seeing real-world applications like &lt;a href=&#34;https://whisper.ggerganov.com/&#34;&gt;Whisper running directly in the browser&lt;/a&gt;, which is proof that you can deploy GenAI models without relying on heavyweight infrastructure.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This hybrid model gives users more control, letting them select the model and fine-tune performance based on local constraints, which means faster performance, lower costs, and more flexibility in where and how you run AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a glimpse at what’s emerging:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-browser AI assistants&lt;/strong&gt;: Deploy lightweight GenAI models directly in browsers using WASM, providing real-time assistance without network latency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edge device applications&lt;/strong&gt;: Run WASM-optimised GenAI models on IoT devices for tasks like image recognition or anomaly detection.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serverless AI APIs&lt;/strong&gt;: Host GenAI models as WASM modules on serverless platforms, reducing operational costs while improving scalability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These use cases demonstrate how WASM empowers GenAI to operate efficiently in diverse environments, from cloud servers to smaller edge devices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When should companies invest in WASM for GenAI?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To enhance security and compliance:&lt;/strong&gt; Industries such as finance and healthcare handle sensitive data that requires stringent security measures. WASM’s sandboxed execution environment ensures that AI models run in isolation, reducing the risk of unauthorised access. Moreover, processing data locally on devices rather than in the cloud can help meet data sovereignty requirements, ensuring compliance with regulations like GDPR.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To optimise performance and scalability:&lt;/strong&gt; WASM allows AI models to run efficiently across various platforms, from browsers to edge devices. This capability is particularly beneficial for applications requiring real-time processing with minimal latency. For instance, deploying lightweight GenAI models directly in browsers using WASM can provide real-time assistance without network latency, enhancing user experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To reduce operational costs:&lt;/strong&gt; Leverage WASM’s lightweight nature, organisations can run AI models locally, reducing the need for extensive cloud infrastructure. This approach not only cuts down on operational costs but also minimises dependency on external servers, leading to more efficient resource utilisation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to leverage WASM for AI at scale&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, advancements in both WASM and GenAI promise to deepen their integration through the following ways:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WebGPU Support&lt;/strong&gt;: Introducing WebGPU to WASM environments will enable hardware acceleration for AI workloads. However, it’s worth noting that &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/API/WebGPU_API&#34;&gt;WebGPU is still an experimental API&lt;/a&gt;, and its integration with WASM for AI workloads is in the early stages, requiring further development and testing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model Optimisation&lt;/strong&gt;: Techniques like quantisation and pruning will make it easier to deploy GenAI models within WASM’s constraints.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Standardised Toolchains&lt;/strong&gt;: Improved tooling will simplify the process of compiling and deploying GenAI models as WASM modules.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Private Personal Assistants&lt;/strong&gt;: Running the model locally will give users greater control over their data, reducing the need for constant data sharing, which is something that becomes inevitable as AI adoption grows.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These developments are set to enable real-time, AI-driven applications that are fast, portable, and accessible to a wide range of users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building smarter and deploying faster&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WASM and GenAI are two disruptive technologies poised to change how we build and deploy software. WASM’s portability and performance make it an ideal runtime for GenAI, enabling the creation of applications that are both powerful and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As these technologies continue to evolve, now is the time for developers to explore their synergy. Whether you’re building the next-gen AI assistant, an innovative edge computing solution, or serverless applications, the pairing of WASM and GenAI offers endless possibilities to be unlocked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当Genai一直在推动变革性变化时，WebAssembly（WASM）在后台工作以增强Web和跨平台应用程序的性能和安全性。尽管Wasm和Genai在各自的能力上是与众不同的，但是将它们结合起来可以解锁有益的可能性，可以使您的业务受益，这是您采用Genai的一部分。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; WASM可以在受约束的环境中提供近乎本地的性能，从而完美地补充了Genai模型的典型计算需求。 Wasm和Genai共同创建了一个强大的解决方案，用于部署和扩展AI驱动的应用程序，在各种用例中为您的业务提供了更大的效率和灵活性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们解开了Genai和Wasm如何相交，讨论您的组织应该考虑投资，并分享对未来的AI基础架构的策略，重点关注安全性和合规性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class =“ is style-default”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么WASM属于您的AI基础架构&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; WASM已演变为高性能运行时，从边缘设备到无服务器基础架构，可以在各种计算环境中有效执行。它的核心优势包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;即使在受约束或分布的设备上，近乎本地的性能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;真正的可移植性，启用“构建一次，在任何地方运行”跨浏览器，服务器和边缘节点&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;内置的沙盒安全性，非常适合零信任环境和多租户系统&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些属性位置WASM作为现代应用程序开发的引人注目的解决方案，在各种部署方案中提供性能，灵活性和安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着Genai平台的成本增加而变得更加分散，WASM可以更快地发布，有效的扩展和降低云依赖性，而无需重新构造。 Genai的工作负载通常是资源繁多的，因此Wasm的轻量化执行模型使得可以在各种环境中安全有效地运行它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经看到了这种行动的转变，随着Vercel般的WASM本地平台的兴起。这种转变意味着开发人员正在获得自主权，部署高性能应用程序而不锁定在重量级平台中。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同时，诸如O1和DeepSeek-R1之类的新模型正在扩大Genai功能，例如生成代码，内容和洞察力。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; WASM是轻巧，防止未来的运行时，使这些创新更容易访问和可管理。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;克服Genai部署挑战&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统的Genai部署通常很难实时扩展，尤其是在入门级笔记本电脑或智能手机等低端设备上。这些绩效限制会随着需求的增长而造成瓶颈，驾驶提高基础设施成本，导致不一致的用户体验，并限制Genai在移动或离线环境中的影响力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Ollama这样的工具表明，本地运行模型是可能的，但是性能在高规格系统之外大大下降。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是WASM进来的地方。将WASM集成到您的AI基础架构中，使团队能够在不带昂贵的基础架构负担的情况下优化更广泛的设备上的Genai工作负载。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，它的影响取决于它与业务中特定用例保持一致。要考虑的关键因素：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;模型大小和复杂性&lt;/strong&gt;：WASM非常适合轻巧的Genai任务，例如文本摘要或转录。较大的模型可能需要定量或修剪以适合WASM当前内存限制。像Webllm这样的工具展示了基于浏览器的LLM如何与WebGPU支持一起使用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;性能和加速度：&lt;/strong&gt; WASM提供近速度，但缺乏直接的GPU支持，这限制了计算重型Genai的工作负载。 WebGPU开始缩小浏览器推理的差距。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可移植性：&lt;/strong&gt; WASM的平台 - 中立设计使您可以在浏览器和服务器环境中“写一次，在任何地方运行”，简化您的部署管道。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可伸缩性：&lt;/strong&gt;将WASM与无服务器平台相结合可降低冷启动时间并提高资源效率，从而更容易扩展Genai应用程序。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;安全性：&lt;/strong&gt; WASM的沙箱增强了运行时隔离，对于安全AI执行至关重要，尤其是在多租户或零值的设置中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;隐私：&lt;/strong&gt;通过WASM进行本地优先部署，将敏感的数据保持在设备上，减少对外部服务器的依赖并增强用户信任。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要充分利用配对WASM和Genai，您的团队必须驾驶一些当前的技术限制，例如访问专业硬件，例如GPU和AI-Ready开发工具的可用性。解决此限制的一种实用方法是使用Turso等现代工具。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; turso是一个轻巧的分布式数据库，即使没有高端基础架构，旨在在各种设备上有效运行。 TURSO非常适合AI工作负载，因为它可以使用内置矢量搜索快速搜索和检索信息，并压缩大型数据集以在本地计算机上平稳运行。这意味着：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;对您的AI应用程序的更快响应&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;较低的云依赖性，可以降低成本&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更好的数据控制，帮助隐私和合规性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将像TURSO这样的工具纳入您的AI堆栈使得在本地，安全和大规模运行Genai应用程序无需大规模大修。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4类=“ WP-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;增强AI安全性并遵守WASM &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;遵守GDPR之类的法规不是一个选择，因此随着您的组织需求的增长，并且您的团队使用AI模型的增长，维护敏感数据，机密信息和专有业务数据需要成为重中之重。这不仅是一个可以打勾的盒子，而且是建立可信赖性和未来就绪系统的核心部分。当使用WASM部署AI模型时，它为部署Genai的组织提供了有意义的安全性和合规性利益，尤其是在金融和医疗保健等高度监管的行业中。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过在沙盒环境中执行代码，从主机系统和其他模块中的WASM隔离物应用程序。这种分离大大降低了未经授权访问的风险，有助于遏制潜在的漏洞并保护敏感数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本地数据处理是另一个主要优势。 WASM允许AI工作负载直接在用户设备或定义的地理边界内运行，从而支持数据主权要求。这种方法限制了暴露于跨境数据传输风险，并简化了诸如GDPR &lt;/p&gt;之类的法规的遵守情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;例如，在医疗保健中，WASM可用于本地运行AI模型，以确保患者信息（例如电子保护的健康信息（EPHI））保持在设备上。同样，金融机构可以处理敏感的客户数据而无需将其发送给外部服务器，降低违规风险并保持符合特定于行业的标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于高级技术领导者来说，机会很明显。首先评估哪些AI工作负载最适合本地执行。将WASM集成到您的开发工作流程中，以利用其内置的安全体系结构。最后，保持监管更改以确保持续的合规性。综上所述，这些步骤将有助于您的AI投资，增强您的安全姿势，并为您提供更大的控制方式。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; WASM和Genai已经以唤起AI的更有效和分散的未来的方式融合。我们正在看到现实世界中的应用程序，例如&lt;a href =“ https://whisper.ggerganov.com/”&gt;直接在浏览器中运行的窃窃私语&lt;/a&gt;，这证明您可以在不依靠重量级基础架构的情况下部署Genai模型。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种混合模型可为用户提供更多的控制，让他们根据本地约束选择模型和微调性能，这意味着更快的性能，较低的成本以及在何处以及如何运行AI的方式中的灵活性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是对正在出现的事物的一瞥：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;内浏览器AI助手&lt;/strong&gt;：直接在浏览器中部署轻量级genai模型ASM，在没有网络延迟的情况下提供实时帮助。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;边缘设备应用程序&lt;/strong&gt;：在物联网设备上运行WASM优化的Genai模型，用于图像识别或异常检测。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;无服务器AI API &lt;/strong&gt;：主机genai模型和无服务器平台上的WASM模块，降低了操作成本的同时提高可扩展性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些用例证明了WASM如何使Genai在从云服务器到较小边缘设备的不同环境中有效运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;公司何时应该投资Genai？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;增强安全性和合规性：&lt;/strong&gt;行业，例如金融和医疗保健处理需要严格的安全措施的敏感数据。 WASM的沙盒执行环境可确保AI模型孤立地运行，从而降低了未经授权访问的风险。此外，在设备而不是在云中本地处理数据可以帮助满足数据主权要求，从而确保遵守GDPR等法规。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;优化性能和可扩展性：&lt;/strong&gt; WASM允许AI模型在从浏览器到边缘设备的各个平台上有效运行。此功能对于需要最小的延迟进行实时处理的应用特别有益。例如，使用WASM直接在浏览器中部署轻量级Genai模型可以提供实时帮助，而无需网络延迟，增强用户体验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;降低运营成本：&lt;/strong&gt;杠杆WASM的轻量级性质，组织可以在本地运行AI模型，从而减少了对广泛的云基础架构的需求。这种方法不仅降低了运营成本，而且可以最大程度地减少对外部服务器的依赖，从而导致更有效的资源利用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;如何在比例尺上利用AI的WASM &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;展望未来，WASM和Genai的进步都承诺通过以下方式加深它们的整合：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; WebGPU支持&lt;/strong&gt;：将WebGPU引入WASM环境将启用AI工作负载的硬件加速度。但是，值得注意的是，&lt;a href =“ https://develveper.mozilla.org/en-us/docs/web/web/web/web/webgpu_api”&gt; webgpu仍然是实验性的API &lt;/a&gt;，它与AI工作的整合及其早期的发展，需要进一步的发展和测试。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;模型优化&lt;/strong&gt;：诸如定量和修剪之类的技术将使在WASM的约束中部署Genai模型变得更加容易。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;标准化工具链&lt;/strong&gt;：改进的工具将简化编译和部署Genai模型的过程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;私人个人助理&lt;/strong&gt;：在本地运行模型将为用户提供更大的续ROL掌握了他们的数据，减少了对数据共享的需求，这是随着AI采用的增长而变得不可避免的。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些开发设置为启用快速，便携式和可用于广泛用户访问的实时，AI驱动的应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; WASM和Genai是两种颠覆性技术，他们有助于改变我们构建和部署软件的方式。 WASM的可移植性和性能使其成为Genai的理想运行时，从而实现了功能强大且易于访问的应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着这些技术继续发展，现在是开发人员探索其协同作用的时候了。无论您是构建下一代AI助手，创新的边缘计算解决方案还是无服务器应用程序，WASM和Genai的配对都提供了无限的可能性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026: Returning to Amsterdam, 23–26 March】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon欧洲2026年：3月23日至26日返回阿姆斯特丹</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/05/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2026-returning-to-amsterdam-23-26-march/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2026/&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026&lt;/a&gt; is heading back to Amsterdam from 23–26 March, 2026! As the flagship event for the cloud native community, it’s an unmissable opportunity to connect with project maintainers, end users, and technologists building the future of infrastructure. Following a record-setting event in London this year and a memorable gathering in Amsterdam in 2023, this return to the Netherlands is set to deliver even more momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfpFvt_ob-nqoZg6-Fe0HuvTocKSJxTVEcq94IOe_8irztPwzjJzsmEr9zR_fZwPOU8uEIRJGCJLwYT-QmPsjlsp5bS9kvu-bkQR7JZ7tM6N5ywlQAQvs4paLdxcGS-kwr_wjixHA?key=8KrlfYTuDZSu2B-1mOV6eA&#34; alt=&#34;KubeCon Paris graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon EU 2023&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Attend in 2026&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Netherlands: An Emerging Tech Powerhouse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Netherlands is quickly establishing itself as a hub for cloud native and digital innovation in Europe. The country hosts several CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/?group=projects-and-products&amp;amp;view-mode=grid&amp;amp;country=The+Netherlands&#34;&gt;projects&lt;/a&gt;, 21 &lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/?group=members&amp;amp;view-mode=grid&amp;amp;country=The+Netherlands&#34;&gt;member&lt;/a&gt; organizations, and 14 &lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/?group=certified-partners-and-providers&amp;amp;view-mode=grid&amp;amp;country=The+Netherlands&#34;&gt;certified partners and providers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2024, Dutch venture funding reached €3.1 billion—a 47% year-over-year increase—placing the Netherlands as the fourth-largest destination for VC investment in Europe, behind only the UK, Germany, and France (&lt;a href=&#34;https://techleap.nl/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2025/02/State-of-Dutch-Tech-Report-2025-updated.pdf&#34;&gt;Techleap&lt;/a&gt;). The nation’s innovation infrastructure is anchored by campuses like&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hightechcampus.com/&#34;&gt; High Tech Campus Eindhoven&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amsterdamsciencepark.nl/&#34;&gt; Amsterdam Science Park&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rug.nl/jantina-tammes-school/&#34;&gt;Jantina Tammes School for Digital Society, Technology and AI&lt;/a&gt; at the University of Groningen, supporting digital society, technology, and AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Amsterdam in particular is one of the leaders in applied AI, housing renowned institutions like the University of Amsterdam’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.icai.ai/&#34;&gt;Innovation Center for Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt; (ICAI) and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cwi.nl/en/collaboration/partnerships/ads/&#34;&gt;Amsterdam Data Science&lt;/a&gt; network. The city’s tech sector benefits from strong digital infrastructure, an internationally diverse talent pool, and public-private collaboration focused on responsible innovation (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.iamsterdam.com/en/business/key-sectors-for-business/technology/about&#34;&gt;I amsterdam&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hosting KubeCon + CloudNativeCon in Amsterdam offers direct engagement with one of Europe’s most dynamic and future-facing tech ecosystems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcwFTiy_hrsW1Td4Ji8zu1K91BlA3Q6kFk3TFwkHT8FlSmptcz3UGXbHk2Y6AB_GSbcRbQrpjM6Sp9SCm2o6vL6P2jB9CGEHCXE9gXQiSDBLCkSnbeI3fFmKNVoSGWgWYHjKT8T_A?key=8KrlfYTuDZSu2B-1mOV6eA&#34; alt=&#34;KubeCon Amsterdam Graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Amsterdam is host to several CNCF projects such as AppSignal, StackState, Vamp, and Weaviate.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Built with End Users in Mind&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This event isn’t just for contributors; it’s shaped by and for end users. From breakout sessions featuring case studies to lightning talks by practitioners running Kubernetes at scale, KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe offers perspectives from real-world operations. If you’re an engineer or architect solving cloud native challenges in production, this is your community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Themes: Platform Engineering, AI, Observability, and More&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026 will spotlight critical themes that matter to developers, operators, platform engineers, and open source contributors: from GitOps and service mesh patterns to real-world AI integration and cost-aware observability strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re managing multi-cluster Kubernetes deployments, scaling internal platforms, securing workloads, or contributing upstream, this event offers content tailored to your day-to-day challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Expect in 2026&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Co-located Events&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Dedicated events for Platform Engineering, Observability, and AI—emphasizing real-world deployments and integrations of generative AI and ML pipelines&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Project Pavillion&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Projects and working groups under the CNCF umbrella have the opportunity to engage, network, and collaborate with peers and like-minded people in the cloud native community.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Keynotes &amp;amp; Vision Talks&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Deep dives into the intersection of AI and cloud native, with maintainers, researchers, and end users sharing what’s working now—and what’s next&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Maintainer Summit&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;An exclusive event for the people behind our projects to gather face-to-face, collaborate, and celebrate the projects that make “Cloud Native.”&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Certifications and Education&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Expanded&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/&#34;&gt; CNCF training, exams, and programs&lt;/a&gt; for developers, SREs, and platform teams, with growing emphasis on AI operations and observability skills&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;What to expect from the event including co-located events, Project Pavillion, Keynotes, Vision Talks, Maintainer Summit, Certifications &amp;amp; Education, and more.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who Should Attend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cloud architects, SREs, and platform teams seeking practical guidance on multi-cluster ops and platform delivery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developers and security professionals contributing to&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/&#34;&gt; CNCF projects&lt;/a&gt; or securing Kubernetes environments&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;End users looking to optimize operations, improve observability, and embrace sustainability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Project maintainers, SIG leads, and working group contributors driving roadmap alignment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Newcomers entering cloud native with support from beginner content, tutorials, and mentoring programs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfL-LRe8JqJ6YRgyRjkRbxP7_GVw0Le2t5GElCA8vrePt5j4Sj34PIt9BTvFX61z5GRaW3zle_bPgHfvCAj5NC6c0U1FlNpaBM8k3TR53mMQhYRg8L59sIXCDtd_hlALnjsNTMG5Q?key=8KrlfYTuDZSu2B-1mOV6eA&#34; alt=&#34;Ambassador picture&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Join the fun at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe in Amsterdam!&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plan Your Trip&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mark your calendar: 23–26 March, 2026&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/program/cfp/&#34;&gt;CFPs&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://cncf.io/sponsor&#34;&gt;sponsorship opportunities&lt;/a&gt; are open&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Get involved in &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;CNCF community groups&lt;/a&gt; and SIGs that shape AI, observability, and platform engineering&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Watch for travel tips, venue details, and event sustainability updates on the&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2026/&#34;&gt; event site&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Get Involved Now&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to help shape the event? You don’t need to wait until March. Join a CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/about/working-groups/&#34;&gt;Working Group&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf-tags&#34;&gt;TAG&lt;/a&gt; today to collaborate on standards, share feedback, or contribute content. Whether you’re an end user with production insights or a contributor passionate about tooling, your voice helps guide what’s featured at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc-S_GE1ZMYI42JFlvYbgL-Y7tvrq-wAw3rkyRyRanV3vUp5vdgNKMf2QLWlsfBAFR0oHTHxO5exCpciW9OQCixXz9zDweHDr6FyhprLFzDNJAF-HRjU3du-HPEWA4U71GgfhAhJA?key=8KrlfYTuDZSu2B-1mOV6eA&#34; alt=&#34;Image of collaboration at a table&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Join a CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/about/working-groups/&#34;&gt;Working Group&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf-tags&#34;&gt;TAG&lt;/a&gt; today to collaborate on standards, share feedback, or contribute content. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Follow CNCF on&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/company/cloud-native-computing-foundation/&#34;&gt; LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sign up for the CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/newsletter/&#34;&gt;newsletter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Explore the CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/events/#/list&#34;&gt;community calendar&lt;/a&gt; for upcoming meetups and project calls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See You There!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026 returns to Amsterdam with deeper technical content, stronger contributor engagement, and broader community impact. Whether you’re deploying production-grade Kubernetes, building observability stacks, securing supply chains, or scaling platforms, this conference is your opportunity to learn, connect, and shape the future of cloud native.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bookmark the&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2026/&#34;&gt; event site&lt;/a&gt;, subscribe for updates, and get ready to meet us in Amsterdam!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2026/”&gt; kubecon + Cloubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2026 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;是2026年3月23日至23日回到阿姆斯特丹！作为云土著社区的旗舰活动，它是与项目维护人员，最终用户和技术人员建立基础设施未来的不可错过的机会。在今年在伦敦举行了纪录的比赛以及2023年在阿姆斯特丹举行的令人难忘的聚会之后，这次返回荷兰将带来更多的动力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfpfvt_ob-nqozg6-fe0huvtocksjxtvecq94ioe_8irztppwzjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjjzsmer 9ZR_FZWPOU8UEIRJGCJLWYT-QMPSJLSP5BS9KVU-BKQR7JZ7JZ7TM6N5YWLQAQVS4PALDXCGS-KWR_WJIXHA？ alt =“ kubecon paris图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ wp- element-caption”&gt; kubecon + cloudnativecon eu 2023 &lt;/figcatpaption&gt; &lt;/figifion&gt; &lt;/figifion&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么在2026年参加&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;荷兰：新兴技术强国&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;荷兰正在迅速将自己确立为欧洲云本土和数字创新的枢纽。该国主持了几个CNCF &lt;a href =“ https://landscape.cncf.io/?group=projects-and-products＆view-mode = grid＆country＆country =+intherlands”&gt; projects&gt; projects &lt;/a&gt; 21 &lt;a href =“ https://landscape.cncf.io/?group=members&amp;view-mode = grid＆country =+intherlands”&gt;成员&lt;/a&gt;组织，14 &lt;a href =“ https://landscape.cncf.io/?group=certified-partners-and-providers&amp;view-mode = grid＆country = exherlands”&gt;认证的合作伙伴和提供者&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2024年，荷兰风险投资达到31亿欧元，同比增长47％，将荷兰作为VC在欧洲投资的第四大目的地，仅次于英国，德国和法国（&lt;a） href =“ https://techleap.nl/wp-content/uploads/sites/2/2/2025/02/state-of-dutch-tech-tech-report-2025-upded.pdf”&gt; techleap &lt;/a&gt;）。该国的创新基础设施由诸如&lt;a href =“ https://www.hightechcamppus.com/”之类的校园锚定。 href =“ https://www.rug.nl/jantina-tammes-school/”&gt; Jantina Tammes数字社会，技术和AI &lt;/a&gt;在Groningen大学，支持数字社会，技术和AI。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;阿姆斯特丹尤其是Applied AI的领导人之一，例如阿姆斯特丹大学的&lt;a href =“ https://www.icai.ai/”&gt;人工智能创新中心&lt;/a&gt;（ICAI）和&lt;a a &lt;a， href =“ https://www.cwi.nl/en/collaboration/partnership/ads/”&gt;阿姆斯特丹数据科学&lt;/a&gt;网络。该市的技术领域受益于强大的数字基础设施，国际多样化的人才库，以及专注于负责任创新的公私合作（&lt;a href =“ https：//www.iamsterdam。com/en/业务/钥匙界，企业/技术/关于“&gt; i amsterdam &lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在阿姆斯特丹举办Kubecon + Cloudnativecon，直接与欧洲最具动态和面向未来的技术生态系统之一。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcwftiy_hrsw1td4ji8zu1k91bla3q6kfk3tfk3tfwkhtfwkht8flsmptcz3ugxbh K2Y6AB_GSBCRBQRPJM6SP9SCM2O6VL6P2JB9CGEHCXE9GXQISDBLCKSNBEI3FFMKNVMKNVOSGWGWYHJKT8T_A？ alt =“ Kubecon Amsterdam Graphic” ReferrerPolicy =“ No-Referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ WP-Element-Caption”&gt; Amsterdam是多个CNCF项目的主机&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;构建了最终用户&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此活动不仅适合贡献者；它是由最终用户形成的。从以案例研究为特色的突破性会议到大规模运行Kubernetes的从业人员的闪电演讲，库贝肯 + Cloudnativecon欧洲提供了现实世界中的观点。如果您是解决生产中云本地挑战的工程师或建筑师，这是您的社区。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubecon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2026将聚焦关键主题，这些主题对开发人员，运营商，平台工程师和开源贡献者至关重要：从Gitops和Service网格模式到现实世界中的AI集成和成本了解的可观察性策略。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是管理多群体Kubernetes部署，扩展内部平台，确保工作负载还是在上游贡献，此活动都为您的日常挑战量身定制了内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 2026年期望&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-table”&gt; &lt;table class =“固定的layout”&gt; &lt;tbody&gt; &lt;tbody&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;共同定位的事件&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;用于平台工程，可观察性和AI的专用事件 - 强调现实的AI和ML Pipeelines &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; Pavillion &lt;/td&gt; &lt;TD&gt; CNCF伞下的项目和工作组有机会与云土著社区中的同龄人和志趣相投的人进行互动，交流和合作。 &lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Keynotes &amp; Vision Talks&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Deep dives into the intersection of AI and cloud native, with maintainers, researchers, and end users sharing what’s working now—and what’s next&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Maintainer Summit&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;An exclusive event for the people behind our projects to gather face-to-face, collaborate,并庆祝成为“云本地”的项目。&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;证书和教育&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;扩展&lt;a href =“ https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/”技能&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ WP-元素捕获”&gt;对活动的期望，包括共同的事件，Project Pavillion，Keynotes，Vision Talks，Mainterer Summit，Searterer Summit，认证和教育等等。&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;谁应该参加&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;云建筑师，SRES和平台团队寻求有关多群集操作和平台交付的实用指导&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;开发人员和安全专业人员为&lt;a href =&#39;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;希望优化操作，提高可观察性和拥抱可持续性的最终用户&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;项目维护人员，SIG LEAD和工作组贡献者驾驶路线图表&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;新来者在初学者内容，教程和指导程序的支持下进入云本地人&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfl-lre8jqj6yrgyrjkrbxp7_gvw0le2t5gelca8vrept5j4sj4sj34pit9 BTVFX61Z5GRAW3ZLE_BPGHFVCAJJ5NC6C0U1FLNPABM8K3TR53MMQHYRG8L59SIXCDTD_HLALNJSNTMG5Q？ alt =“大使图片” ReferrerPolicy =“ No-Referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ WP-元素caption”&gt;在阿姆斯特丹的kubecon + Cloudnativecon欧洲加入乐趣&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;计划您的旅行&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;标记您的日历：2026年3月23日至26日&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/progr/progm/progm/cfp/”&gt; cfps &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ http://cncf.io/sponsor”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;参与&lt;a href =“ https://community.cncf.io/”&gt; cncf社区组&lt;/a&gt;和塑造AI，可观察性和平台工程的SIGS &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;请注意&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2026/” &lt;a href =“&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;现在如何参与&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想帮助塑造活动？您不需要等到三月。加入cncf &lt;a href =“ https://contribute.cncf.io/about/working-groups/”&gt;工作组&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf-tags”&gt; TAG&gt; TAG&gt; TAG &lt;/a&gt;今天可以协作在标准上共享标准，共享Feedebebal或撰写内容。无论您是具有生产见解的最终用户还是对工具充满热情的贡献者，您的声音都可以指导Kubecon + Cloudnativecon的特色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxc-s_ge1zmyi42jflvybgl-y7tvrq-waw3rkyryranv3v3vup5vdgnkmf2 qlwlsfbafr0ohthxo5excpciw9oqcixxz9zdwehdr6fyhprlfzdnjaf-hrju3du-hpewa4u71ggfhahja？ alt =“表格上的协作图像” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ wp-element-caption”&gt;加入cncf &lt;a href &lt;a href =“ https://contribute.cncf.io/about/working groups/“&gt;工作组&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href =” https://github.com/cncf-tags“&gt; tag &lt;/a&gt;今天进行协作，共享标准，共享反馈或贡献内容。&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figapaption&gt; &lt;/figif&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您也可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ https:/https://www.linkedin.com/company/cloud-native-native-computing-foundation/”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;注册cncf &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/newsletter/”&gt;新闻通讯&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;探索cncf &lt;a href =“ https://community.cncf.io/events/#/list”&gt;社区日历&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在那里见！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2026返回阿姆斯特丹，具有更深的技术内容，更强的贡献者参与和更广泛的社区影响。无论您是部署生产级Kubernetes，建造可观察性堆栈，确保供应链还是扩展平台，这次会议都是您学习，连接和塑造Cloud Native的未来的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;书签&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2026/”&gt;事件网站&lt;/a&gt;，订阅更新，并准备在阿姆斯特丹与我们见面！&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing k0rdent v1.0.0: Manage Distributed Infrastructure at Massive Scale Leveraging Kubernetes】宣布K0rdent v1.0.0：在大规模管理分布式基础架构利用Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/07/announcing-k0rdent-v1-0-0-manage-distributed-infrastructure-at-massive-scale-leveraging-kubernetes/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The community was just getting started with k0rdent v0.3.0 that we pushed a surprise for them to cherish with a super quick and very special release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to announce &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.k0rdent.io/v1.0.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0rdent v1.0.0&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a milestone release that solidifies our vision for unified observability and cost optimization in multi-cloud environments. Driven by the &lt;strong&gt;k0rdent Cluster Manager (KCM)&lt;/strong&gt; and enhanced &lt;strong&gt;k0rdent Observability &amp;amp; FinOps (kOF) &lt;/strong&gt;capabilities, this release brings production-grade stability, powerful new features, and significant operational improvements to help platform engineering teams reduce complexity, gain visibility, and control infrastructure costs at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a recap, &lt;a href=&#34;https://k0rdent.io/&#34;&gt;k0rdent&lt;/a&gt; is a Kubernetes-native distributed container management environment (DCME) that helps platform engineers manage infrastructure at scale. Acting as a “super control plane,” it enables centralized, template-driven lifecycle management of clusters and services across on-prem, cloud, and hybrid environments. Built on open standards, it simplifies the creation of secure, consistent Internal Developer Platforms (IDPs) for modern workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Components of k0rdent as you know,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KCM (Cluster Manager):&lt;/strong&gt; Manages lifecycle, upgrades, and scaling of Kubernetes clusters via Cluster API&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KSM (State Management):&lt;/strong&gt; Deploys and manages services (e.g., Istio, Flux, cert-manager) using templated, declarative ServiceTemplates&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;kOF (Observability &amp;amp; FinOps):&lt;/strong&gt; Provides metrics, logging, dashboards, and cost visibility through integrations with VictoriaMetrics and OpenCost&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Documentation:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.k0rdent.io/next/quickstarts&#34;&gt; QuickStart Guide&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Source Code:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent&#34;&gt; GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Highlights in v1.0.0&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The key highlights of version1.0.0 include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Stabilized v1beta1 APIs across all components&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Production Grade Multi-Cluster Support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enterprise-ready service templating and orchestration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Integrated observability for GPU and Kubernetes control plane metrics&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea behind this release was to focus on new capabilities:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhancements to k0rdent cluster manager (kcm)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ServiceTemplateChains:&lt;/strong&gt; Enable conditional, ordered service deployments with defined upgrade paths ([#1433])&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The previous design of &lt;strong&gt;ServiceTemplateChains&lt;/strong&gt; fell short in enabling effective upgrade path management for services on managed clusters. Key limitations included ambiguous chain selection when multiple chains reference the same template, lack of visibility into upgrade availability, and no distinction between sequential and direct upgrades. Additionally, the absence of versioning and unclear relationships between core resources hinder upgrade validation and system predictability. Addressing these gaps were essential for delivering safe, transparent, and manageable service upgrades at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To improve clarity and control in service upgrades, we are introducing a structured resource hierarchy—&lt;strong&gt;CD / MCS → ServiceTemplateChain → ServiceTemplate&lt;/strong&gt;—alongside &lt;strong&gt;versioning for ServiceTemplates&lt;/strong&gt; to define explicit upgrade paths. Additionally, &lt;strong&gt;environment-specific upgrade strategies&lt;/strong&gt; can now be modeled using distinct ServiceTemplateChains, enabling safer and more predictable rollouts across diverse infrastructure contexts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Values: &lt;/strong&gt;The ability to share reusable variables across templates to support consistent multi-cluster configurations (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/pull/1535&#34;&gt;[#1535]&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We tested the installation and AWS cluster creation with/without global values. All templates rendered via helm template and checked that all were rendered correctly. If global values aren’t set the template will behave exactly the same as before these changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We didn’t touch templates where this makes no sense: managed Kubernetes (like EKS) clusters or adopted clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IPAM Controller Integration:&lt;/strong&gt; Automate IP address management across heterogeneous environments ([#1260])&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;The goal was to deliver a solution that automates IP address allocation and DNS record updates using Cluster API’s In-Cluster IPAM Provider. This solution aims to reduce manual intervention, ensure network consistency, and improve overall operational efficiency. It would benefit&amp;nbsp; stakeholders including Platform Leads, network operations managers, and security teams from reduced manual tasks, improved accuracy in network records, and greater operational efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The major deliverables were:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automated IP Allocation: A solution that assigns IP addresses based on approved business rules and policies, reducing manual effort.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automated DNS Updates: A process that ensures DNS records are updated accurately and on time when IPs are allocated.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reusable ServiceTemplate: A clear, declarative template that encapsulates the business logic for IP management.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Assumptions:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The underlying infrastructure supports the proposed automation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Existing business policies for IP allocation are clear and can be effectively translated into the solution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Limitations:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The initial release will focus solely on one automated IPAM solution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Customization is limited to the predefined business rules and policies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;More advanced network or DNS configurations will not be included in this phase.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0rdent Observability &amp;amp; FinOps (kOF)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As organizations scale Kubernetes operations across cloud and on-prem environments, &lt;strong&gt;observability and financial accountability&lt;/strong&gt; become critical. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0rdent Observability &amp;amp; FinOps (kOF&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; module is purpose-built to address these needs by integrating robust metrics, logging, and cost visibility into the k0rdent platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kOF repository delivers a complete, composable observability stack with first-class support for &lt;strong&gt;multi-cluster monitoring&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;GPU utilization tracking&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;control plane health visibility&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes-native FinOps reporting&lt;/strong&gt; using open standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It builds on industry-leading tools such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VictoriaMetrics&lt;/strong&gt; for scalable, long-term time series metrics and logging&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana&lt;/strong&gt; for customizable, pre-configured dashboards&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenCost&lt;/strong&gt; for Kubernetes cost monitoring and FinOps alignment&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/strong&gt; for structured observability of control plane components&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. NVIDIA GPU Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Out-of-the-box Grafana dashboards provide real-time GPU utilization metrics for workloads running on NVIDIA-powered nodes. This is especially useful for AI/ML environments where GPU resources must be carefully tracked and optimized.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The dashboard is based on the official &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/NVIDIA/dcgm-exporter/blob/main/grafana/dcgm-exporter-dashboard.json&#34;&gt;NVIDIA dcgm-exporter&lt;/a&gt; with few additional template key inherited from other existing dashboards in the repo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;The dashboard assumes that the DCGM Exporter metrics are being scraped. This requires a ServiceMonitor resource to be present, which directs to the DCGM Exporter’s metrics endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note – While the NVIDIA GPU Operator deploys the DCGM Exporter, it does not, by default, create a ServiceMonitor resource for it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcehANdHygQu5iBFSA42XaWSgBnM4rFRqKSuc8NIeX7ExForv5oBRjDKcClDgZnBtK3nSTgZeMSQemSHiVHUl6aRkhLP5Eu9lXLpzlLvwTBPfVttlmmt48_pGGMUsDhOVulVHtU?key=HaQSqHwXqIEB9UjRUkro_w&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feature reference: [&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/pull/257&#34;&gt;#257&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Refactoring API Metrics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;In this new release for kof, the Kubernetes API metrics collection has been refactored and&amp;nbsp; the misconfiguration of the Prometheus receiver has been fixed, this is a small step towards the unification with &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-helm-charts/tree/main/charts/opentelemetry-kube-stack&#34;&gt;opentelemetry-kube-stack&lt;/a&gt; helm chart collectors.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The changes made include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Moving kubernetes-api metrics collection to a service monitor&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removing prometheus receiver from cluster collector&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feature reference: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/pull/259&#34;&gt;[#259&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Advanced Logging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The community feedback was to ensure that log storage should be highly available and scalable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;VLS used is a cool tool, but it does not have a clustered version (yet), so I suggest we provide a layer of configuration to allow us to deploy other solutions such as OpenSearch/Loki&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;this would come handy with an intermediate buffer for logs (#177) against which we can run a “fanout” mechanism such as kafka connectors/logstash, thus making it possible to add any specific storages that users might need easily.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;UPDATE: Use https://docs.victoriametrics.com/victorialogs/cluster/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With support for &lt;strong&gt;VictoriaLogs in clustered mode&lt;/strong&gt;, kOF enhances log management performance, retention, and query scalability. The transition from victoria-logs-single to victoria-logs-cluster introduces support for multi-tenant log storage and long-term archival.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feature reference: [&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/pull/274&#34;&gt;#274&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Per-Cluster Configuration via Annotations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kof users were trying to set up labs (with a lot of users) and installing self-signed certs was a normal part of setting up quick labs, which was expected to be done by the community too at some point.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So we needed the ability to configure tls_skip_verify for the promxyservergroup and grafanadatasource objects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We were passing HTTPClientConfig &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/blob/v0.3.0/kof-operator/internal/controller/clusterdeployment_kof_cluster_role.go#L532&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; which included TLSConfig.InsecureSkipVerify &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/blob/v0.3.0/kof-operator/api/v1alpha1/promxyservergroup_types.go#L43-L56&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; but there really was no way to pass it nicely via values, and the same for GrafanaDataSource.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/pull/276&#34;&gt;PR[#276] &lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;allows per-cluster customization of HTTP client parameters for Promxy and Grafana data sources using Kubernetes annotations. This helps fine-tune cross-cluster communication and security settings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Resource Configuration and Cost Controls&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Administrators can &lt;strong&gt;customize CPU and memory limits&lt;/strong&gt; for observability stack components to ensure consistent performance across heterogeneous environments and optimize infrastructure costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feature reference: [#263]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FinOps Integration: OpenCost&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kOF module integrates &lt;strong&gt;OpenCost&lt;/strong&gt;, a CNCF sandbox project, to bring transparent cost visibility directly into Kubernetes-native workflows. This enables platform teams and finance stakeholders to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Analyze cost by namespace, workload, or label&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Correlate resource usage with actual spend&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drive cost optimization decisions with accurate data&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The image below is a diagrammatic representation of kof indicating what is happening in a regional cluster:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfvipNR5HTkfAUDaivvKzo_9qLo3IcTObqB5ngRMZ27kNtnWz0muQtrwGccVo4DcCkChcBudjQx6KsxC9_oCYmBuauKOEx42AU9gLXuXA2eLvxIIU7MfDyM2SAllvBoKkuRwFFY?key=HaQSqHwXqIEB9UjRUkro_w&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitOps-Ready and Enterprise-Compatible&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kOF Helm charts and manifests are fully compatible with GitOps workflows, including ArgoCD and FluxCD. Configurations are declarative and support secure delivery pipelines across environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Stability and Reliability Improvements for v1.0.0:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resolved CR reference issues in IPAM and OpenStack providers ([#1522], [#1496])&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;K0rdent had the need to implement the IPAM controller which would reconcile ClusterIpamClaims and produce ClusterIpams which would reference IPAddressClaims.&lt;br&gt;As mentioned in Issue [&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/issues/1198&#34;&gt;#1198&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced end-to-end test reliability and configuration handling ([#1517], [#1463])&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved Helm chart resource tuning for VictoriaMetrics services ([#279])&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed Helm repository compatibility and remote secret issues for Istio ([#282], [#270])&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upgrade Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;v1alpha1 APIs remain available in this release but are now officially deprecated. Users should migrate to v1beta1 versions of ClusterTemplate, ServiceTemplate, and ProviderTemplate resources.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All custom tooling should be updated to accommodate v1beta1 as support for v1alpha1 will be removed in a future release.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It is recommended to back up the management cluster using Velero prior to upgrading.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A detailed upgrade guide is available at&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.k0rdent.io/1.0.0/admin/upgrade/&#34;&gt; Upgrade Documentation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deprecations and Known Issues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deprecated&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All v1alpha1 APIs&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The legacy victoria-logs-single logging backend (migrate to victoria-logs-cluster)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Known Issues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Grafana dashboards may take up to 60 seconds to initialize following cluster deployment&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Conflicting priorities in MultiClusterService definitions may require manual resolution&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;IPAM reconciliation may be delayed in high-latency network environments&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Velero restores across cloud providers may require exclusion of certain resources (see documentation for guidance)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Release Metadata&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Value&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Helm Charts&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;kcm: 1.0.0, kof: 1.0.0, ksm: 1.0.0&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;OCI Registry&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;ghcr.io/k0rdent&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;SBOM&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Not included in OSS&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;OCI Signature Support&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Enterprise only&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Release Tags&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v1.0.0 across all components&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🙌 Contributors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Huge thanks to the following contributors for making this release possible:&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gmlexx&#34;&gt;@gmlexx&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/denis-ryzhkov&#34;&gt;@denis-ryzhkov&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ramessesii2&#34;&gt;@ramessesii2&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/aglarendil&#34;&gt;@aglarendil&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kylewuolle&#34;&gt;@kylewuolle&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/a13x5&#34;&gt;@a13x5&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/eromanova&#34;&gt;@eromanova&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/zerospiel&#34;&gt;@zerospiel&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/BROngineer&#34;&gt;@BROngineer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cdunkelb&#34;&gt;@cdunkelb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Component &amp;amp; Provider Versions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Component / Provider&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Version&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Cluster API&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v1.9.7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider AWS&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v2.8.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider Azure&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v1.19.4&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider Docker&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v1.9.6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider GCP&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v1.8.1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider Infoblox&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v0.1.0-alpha.8&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider IPAM&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v0.18.0&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider k0smotron&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v1.5.2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider OpenStack (ORC)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v0.12.3 / v2.1.0&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CAPI Provider vSphere&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v1.13.0&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Project Sveltos&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;v0.54.0&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn More&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/releases/tag/v1.0.0&#34;&gt;kcm v1.0.0 Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/releases/tag/v1.0.0&#34;&gt;kof v1.0.0 Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.k0rdent.io/1.0.0/quickstarts/&#34;&gt;v1.0.0 Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the k0rdent Community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Platform engineers today face increasing demands—but they don’t have to tackle them alone. k0rdent is 100% open-source and community-driven, offering the flexibility, tools, and ecosystem needed to manage distributed infrastructure efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Built by an international team of passionate developers, k0rdent thrives on collaboration. We welcome contributions and ideas to expand and improve the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get Involved:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;⭐️Drop a star to support the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/k0rdent&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0rdent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; project&lt;br&gt;✅ Explore the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/community&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0rdent Community repo on GitHub&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;✅ Join the #k0rdent channel on &lt;a href=&#34;http://slack.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF Community Slack &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;(Sign up for CNCF Slack, then join #k0rdent)&lt;br&gt;✅ Sign up via our &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/EDwvAH11fsKmrar78&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Invitation Form&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to attend Team k0rdent’s regular Office Hours&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be part of the movement—let’s build the future of Kubernetes-native infrastructure together!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Getting Started&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can try out &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.k0rdent.io/1.0.0/&#34;&gt;k0rdent v1.0.0&lt;/a&gt; today by following the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.k0rdent.io/1.0.0/quickstarts/&#34;&gt;QuickStart guide&lt;/a&gt; and deployment instructions. For feedback, questions, or support, please reach out via email, Slack, or GitHub Issues. We look forward to hearing about your experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;社区才刚刚开始使用K0rdent v0.3.0，我们为他们带来了惊喜，以超级快速，非常特别的发行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴宣布&lt;a href =“ https://docs.k0rdent.io/v1.0.0/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k0rdent v1.0.0.0 &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，这是一个里程碑式的释放，可以巩固我们对统一的观察力和成本优化环境中的愿景。在&lt;strong&gt; k0rdent集群经理（KCM）&lt;/strong&gt;和增强&lt;strong&gt; k0rdent的可观察性与填充性（KOF）&lt;/strong&gt;功能的驱动器中，此版本带来了生产量稳定性，有力的新功能，有力的新功能，并具有重大的运营改进，以帮助平台工程团队降低相关性，可降低知名度，增强基础，并降低尺度的尺度尺度。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于回顾，&lt;a href =“ https://k0rdent.io/”&gt; k0rdent &lt;/a&gt;是一个Kubernetes-Native分布式集装箱管理环境（DCME），可帮助平台工程师以大规模管理基础架构。它充当“超级控制平面”，它可以在本地，云和混合环境中实现集中式模板驱动的生命周期管理。基于开放标准，它简化了现代工作负载的安全，一致的内部开发人员平台（IDP）的创建。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k0rdent的核心组件如您所知，&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kcm（集群管理器）：&lt;/strong&gt;通过群集API &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;管理生命周期，升级和缩放kubernetes簇&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; KSM（国家管理）：&lt;/strong&gt;使用模板，声明性的服务范围&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kof（可观察性和填充）：&lt;/strong&gt;通过与VictoriAmetrics和Opencost集成，提供指标，记录，仪表板和成本可见性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;文档：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://docs.k0rdent.io/next/quickstarts”&gt; QuickStart Guide &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;源代码：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href = &lt;a href =“&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; v1.0.0 &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;中的钥匙要点&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;版本1.0.0的关键亮点包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;稳定所有组件的V1BETA1 API &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;生产等级多群集支持&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;企业就绪的服务模板和编排&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; GPU和Kubernetes控制平面指标的集成可观察性&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本背后的想法是专注于新功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k0rdent cluster Manager（KCM）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;增强功能&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; ServiceTemplatechains：&lt;/strong&gt;启用有条件的，有条件的服务部署，并具有定义的升级路径（[＃1433]）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; ServiceTemplatechains的先前设计&lt;/strong&gt;在有效的升级路径管理方面缺席了法术力GED集群。关键局限性包括当多个链条引用相同的模板，对升级可用性缺乏可见性以及连续升级和直接升级之间没有区别时，关键限制包括歧义链的选择。此外，核心资源之间没有版本控制和不清楚的关系阻碍了升级验证和系统可预测性。解决这些差距对于按大规模提供安全，透明和可管理的服务升级至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了提高服务升级的清晰度和控制，我们正在引入结构化资源层次结构 -  &lt;strong&gt; CD/MCS→ServiceTemplateChain→ServiceTemplate &lt;/strong&gt;  -  ServiceTemplates &lt;/strong&gt;的Alongside &lt;strong&gt;版本&lt;/strong&gt;以定义明显的上升路径。此外，&lt;strong&gt;特定环境特定的升级策略&lt;/strong&gt;现在可以使用不同的ServiceTemplatechains进行建模，从而在不同的基础架构环境中实现更安全，更可预测的推出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;全局价值：&lt;/strong&gt;能够在模板上共享可重复使用的变量以支持一致的多群集配置（&lt;a href =“ https:/ https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/kcm/pull/pull/1535&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们测试了使用/没有全局值的安装和AWS群集创建。所有模板通过舵机模板呈现，并检查了所有模板是否正确渲染。如果未设置全局值，模板的行为将与这些更改完全相同。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们没有触摸模板没有任何意义：托管的kubernetes（如EKS）簇或采用簇。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; IPAM控制器集成：&lt;/strong&gt;在异质环境之间自动化IP地址管理（[＃1260]）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;目标是提供一种解决方案，该解决方案使用集群API的群集IPAM提供商自动化IP地址分配和DNS记录更新。该解决方案旨在减少手动干预，确保网络一致性并提高整体操作效率。这将使利益相关者受益，包括平台潜在客户，网络运营经理以及从减少的手动任务，提高网络记录准确性以及更高的运营效率的安全团队。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主要可交付成果是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自动化IP分配：一种根据批准的业务规则和政策分配IP地址的解决方案，减少了手动工作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自动DNS更新：确保DNS记录准确更新IP时的过程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可重复使用的ServiceTemplate：一个清晰的声明模板，封装了IP管理业务逻辑。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;假设：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;基础架构支持拟议的自动化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; IP分配的现有业务政策清晰，可以有效地转化为解决方案。&lt;/l我&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;限制：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;初始版本将仅关注一个自动IPAM解决方案。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自定义仅限于预定义的业务规则和政策。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更高级的网络或DNS配置将不包括在此阶段中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着组织的规模kubernetes跨越云和本地环境的运营，&lt;strong&gt;可观察性和财务问责制&lt;/strong&gt;变得至关重要。 &lt;a a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k0rdent可观察性和finops（kof &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;模块是专门解决这些需求的目的，可以通过整合稳健的衡量标准，登录和成本的平台来解决这些需求。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; KOF存储库提供了一个完整的，可组合的可观察性堆栈，并为&lt;strong&gt;多群集监控&lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;strong&gt; GPU利用率跟踪&lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;strong&gt;控制平面的健康可见度&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt; kubernetes-kubernetes-native finops报告&lt;/strong&gt;使用开放标准&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它以行业领先的工具为基础：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; victoriametrics &lt;/strong&gt;用于可扩展的长期时间序列和记录&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; grafana &lt;/strong&gt;用于可自定义的，预先配置的仪表板&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; opencost &lt;/strong&gt; kubernetes成本监控和填充一致性&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; opentelemetry &lt;/strong&gt;用于控制平面组件的结构化可观察性&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。 NVIDIA GPU监视&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开箱即用的Grafana仪表板提供实时的GPU利用率指标，用于在NVIDIA驱动的节点上运行的工作负载。这对于必须仔细跟踪和优化GPU资源的AI/ML环境特别有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仪表板基于官方&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/nvidia/dcgm-exporter/blob/main/main/main/grafana/grafana/dcgm-exporter-dashboard.json”&gt; nvidia dcgm-exporter &lt;/a&gt;与其他现有的dashbooard persbooard nvidia dcgm-exporter &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;仪表板假定DCGM出口商指标正在刮擦。这需要一个服务对象资源，该资源直接导致DCGM出口商的指标端点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意 - 虽然NVIDIA GPU操作员部署DCGM出口商，但默认情况下，它不会为其创建ServiceMonitor资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcehandhygqu5ibfsa42xawsgbnm4rfrqksuc8niex7exforv5obrjd kccldgznbtk3nstgzemsqemshivhul6arkhlp5eu9lxlpzllpzllvwtbpfvttlmmt48_pggmusdhovulvhtu？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;功能参考：[&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/pull/257”&gt;＃257 &lt;/a&gt;] &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ Wp块头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 2。重构API指标&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;在此新版本的KOF中，Kubernetes API指标集合已经进行了重构，并且Prometheus接收器的错误配置已固定，这是朝着与&lt;a的统一的一小步href =“ https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-helm-charts/tree/main/main/main/charts/opentelemetry-kube-stack”&gt; opentelemetry-kube-stack&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所做的更改包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将Kubernetes-API指标收集到服务监视器&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;从集群收集器中删除Prometheus接收器&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;功能参考：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/pull/259”&gt; [＃259 &lt;/a&gt;] &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 3。高级记录&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;社区反馈是为了确保日志存储应高可用且可扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; vls使用的是一个很酷的工具，但是它没有群集版本（尚未），因此我建议我们提供一层配置，以允许我们部署其他解决方案，例如OpenSearch/loki &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这将带有用于日志的中间缓冲区（＃177），我们可以使用诸如Kafka Connectors/logStash之类的“粉丝”机制，从而可以添加用户可能需要的任何特定储藏。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更新：使用https://docs.victoriametrics.com/victorialogs/cluster/ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在群集模式下&lt;strong&gt; victorialogs的支持&lt;/strong&gt;，KOF可以增强日志管理性能，保留和查询可扩展性。从维多利亚 -  logs-single到维多利亚 - 库群岛的过渡引入了对多租户日志存储和长期档案的支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;功能参考：[&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/pull/274”&gt;＃274 &lt;/a&gt;] &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 4。通过注释&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;通过群集配置&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; KOF用户试图设置实验室（带有很多用户），并且安装自签名证书是设置快速实验室的正常部分，该实验室预计在某个时候也将由社区完成。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，我们需要能够为PromXyserverGroup和Grafanadatasource对象配置TLS_SKIP_VERIFY。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在通过httpclientConfig &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/kof/blob/blob/v0.3.0/kof-operator/kof-operator/internal/controll/controller/clusterdeployment_kof_kof_cluster_cluster_cluster_role.go#l532 href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/kof/blob/v0.3.0/kof-operator/api/api/v1alpha1/promxyservergroup_types.go#l43-l43-l56”&gt;在这里&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，但实际上没有值得通过的方式来通过价值和&lt;/plane &lt;/per &lt;/pc。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; new &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/pull/276”&gt; pr [＃276] &lt;/a&gt;允许使用kubernetes antotations使用http client client参数来定制http client client参数。这有助于微调跨集群沟通和安全设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 5。资源配置和成本控制&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;管理员可以&lt;strong&gt;自定义CPU和内存限制&lt;/strong&gt;可观察性堆栈组件，以确保在异质环境中保持一致的性能并优化基础架构成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;功能参考：[＃263] &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; KOF模块集成了CNCF沙盒项目&lt;strong&gt; Opencost &lt;/strong&gt;，以将透明的成本可见性直接带入Kubernetes-native Workfrows。这使平台团队和财务利益相关者能够：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;按名称空间，工作量或标签分析成本&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将资源使用与实际支出相关联&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用准确数据的驱动成本优化决策&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下图是KOF的图表表示，指示区域集群中发生了什么：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfvipnr5htkfaudaivvkzo_9qlo3ictobqb5ngrmz27kntnwz0muqtr wgccvo4dcckchcbudjqx6ksxc9_ocymbuaukoex42au9glxuxa2elvxiiu7mfdym2sallvbokkurwffy？ alt =“” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; gitops准备和企业兼容&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; KOF头盔图和表现与gitops工作流程完全兼容，包括argoCD和fluxcd。配置是声明性的，并且支持跨环境的安全交付管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; v1.0.0的稳定性和可靠性改进：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在IPAM和OpenStack提供商中解决的CR参考问题（[＃1522]，[＃1496]）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; k0rdent需要实现IPAM控制器，该控制器可以调和clusterIpamClaims并产生簇状pam，以引用ipaddressclaims。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;增强端到端测试可靠性和配置处理（[＃1517]，[＃1463]）&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;改进的Vicoriametrics Services（[＃279]）的Helm图表资源调整&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;修复了ISTIO（[＃282]，[＃270]）的固定Helm存储库兼容性和远程秘密问题&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;升级注释&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; v1alpha1 API在此版本中仍然可用，但现在已正式弃用。用户应迁移到clusterTemplate，serviceTemplate和providertemplate资源的V1BETA1版本。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;应更新所有自定义工具以容纳V1BETA1，作为对V1alpha1的支持，将在以后的版本中删除。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;建议在升级之前使用Velero备份管理集群。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;详细的升级指南可用&lt;a href =“ https://docs.k0rdent.io/1.0.0.0/admin/upgrade/”&gt; upgrade documentation。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;折旧和已知问题&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;弃用&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;所有v1alpha1 apis &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;遗产维多利亚logs-single登录后端（迁移到维多利亚 - 洛格斯群集）&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;已知问题&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Grafana仪表板可能需要长达60秒才能在集群部署后初始化&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多量隙服务定义中的优先级相互冲突可能需要手动分辨率&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; IPAM对帐可能会在高延迟网络环境中延迟&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; velero恢复跨云提供商可能需要排除某些资源（有关指导请参见文档）&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;释放元数据&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Value&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Helm Charts&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;kcm: 1.0.0, kof: 1.0.0, ksm: 1.0.0 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; OCI注册表&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; ghcr.io/k0rdent &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; sbom &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; oss &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tt&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;ttd&gt; &lt;ttd&gt; oci sighter Suppert &lt;/仅&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;发布标签&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; v1.0.0在所有组件中&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; contrutors &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;非常感谢以下贡献者使此版本成为可能：&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/gmlexx”&gt; @gmlexx &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/github.com/denis-denis-denis-renis-renis-ryzhkkov”&gt; href =“ https://github.com/ramessesii2”&gt;@ramessei2 &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/aglarendil”&gt; @aglarendil“&gt; @aglarendil &lt;/a&gt;，，&lt;br&gt;，&lt;br&gt; &lt;A href =“ https://github.com/a13x5”&gt;@a13x5 &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;br&gt; &lt;a a href =“ https:/ https://github.com/eromanova&gt; @eromanova”&gt; @eromanova &lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://github.com/brongineer”&gt; @brongineer &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cdunkelb”&gt; @cdunkelb &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;组件和提供商版本&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-table”&gt; &lt;table class =“固定layout”&gt; &lt;thead&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;th&gt; &lt;strong&gt;组件/提供者&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/th&gt; &lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt; &lt;strong&gt;版本Api &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; V1.9.7 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; CAPI提供者AWS &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; v2.8.2 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;ttd&gt; capi Provider azure azure azure &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; docker &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; v1.9.6 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; CAPI提供者GCP &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; v1.8.1 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;ttd&gt; capi provid provider infoder infoblox infob &lt;/td&gt;提供者IPAM &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; V0.18.0 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; CAPI提供商K0SMOTRON &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; v1.5.5.2.5.2 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tt&gt; v2.1.0 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; CAPI提供r vsphere &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; v1.13.0 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;项目&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;了解更多&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/releases/tag/v1.0.0”&gt; kcm v1.0.0发行笔记&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/releases/tag/v1.0.0”&gt; kof v1.0.0发行说明&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://docs.k0rdent.io/1.0.0/quickstarts/”&gt; v1.0.0文档&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;加入K0rdent社区&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;平台工程师如今面临着越来越多的需求，但他们不必独自解决。 K0rdent是100％开源和社区驱动的，提供了有效管理分布式基础设施所需的灵活性，工具和生态系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由国际热情开发人员团队建立的K0rdent在协作方面蓬勃发展。我们欢迎贡献和想法扩展和改进项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;参与：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;⭐️Dropa星可支持&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/k0rdent”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k0rdent &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; project &lt;br&gt; project &lt;br&gt;✅ github &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;✅&lt;&lt;a href =“ http:/ http://slack.cncf.io/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; cncf community slack&gt; &lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://forms.gle/edwvah11fskmrar78”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;社区邀请表格&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;参加K0rdent团队的常规办公时间&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;成为运动的一部分 -  LET的建立Kubernetes-Native基础设施的未来！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;入门&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以尝试&lt;a href =“ https://docs.k0rdent.io/1.0.0/”&gt; k0rdent v1.0.0.0.0.0.0 &lt;/a&gt;今天，通过关注&lt;a a href =“ https:///docs.k0rdent.io/1.io/1.0.0.0.0.0.0.0.0/quickstarts/ deriverions andiranction and&gt;有关反馈，问题或支持，请通过电子邮件，松弛或GitHub问题与您联系。我们期待听到您的经历。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating EKS CIS Compliance with Kyverno and KubeBench】自动化EKS CIS符合Kyverno和Kubebench</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/04/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A practical approach to implementing CIS security controls using CNCF cloud native tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;introduction-the-challenge-of-eks-compliance-at-scale&#34;&gt;Introduction: The Challenge of EKS Compliance at Scale&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#introduction-the-challenge-of-eks-compliance-at-scale&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maintaining CIS Benchmarks compliance for Amazon EKS across multiple clusters is a common challenge in cloud native environments. Traditional manual approaches don’t scale, and existing solutions often lack comprehensive coverage or real-time enforcement capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores a practical approach to automating CIS compliance for EKS using Kyverno (a CNCF Kubernetes-native policy engine), combined with OpenTofu for infrastructure provisioning, and kube-bench for node-level CIS scanning. This solution demonstrates how CNCF ecosystem tools can work together to provide comprehensive security validation across the entire infrastructure and application stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The open source project:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno&#34;&gt;cis-eks-kyverno&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;implements 62 CIS controls with a multi-tool plan time and runtime validation strategy, comprehensive testing, and automated reporting. This framework showcases cloud native security automation and has been tested extensively with KIND (Kubernetes in Docker) clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;the-compliance-challenge-in-cloud-native-environments&#34;&gt;The Compliance Challenge in Cloud Native Environments&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#the-compliance-challenge-in-cloud-native-environments&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CIS Amazon EKS Benchmark v1.7.0 contains 46 security recommendations across five critical areas:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Control Plane Configuration&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Section 2): Audit logging, endpoint security – 2 controls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Worker Node Security&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Section 3): Kubelet configuration, file permissions – 13 controls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RBAC &amp;amp; Service Accounts&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Section 4): Access controls, service account security – 15 controls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod Security Standards&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Section 5): Container runtime security – 9 controls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managed Services&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(Section 5): ECR, networking, encryption – 7 additional controls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional compliance approaches typically involve:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manual kubectl commands for configuration checks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;SSH access to worker nodes for file permission audits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Periodic reviews of infrastructure configurations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manual report generation for security assessments&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reactive remediation after issues are discovered&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;challenges-with-manual-approaches&#34;&gt;Challenges with manual approaches:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#challenges-with-manual-approaches&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scale limitations&lt;/strong&gt;: Manual processes don’t scale across multiple Kubernetes clusters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time-intensive&lt;/strong&gt;: Comprehensive audits can take days per cluster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Error-prone&lt;/strong&gt;: Human oversight can miss critical security configurations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reactive nature&lt;/strong&gt;: Issues discovered weeks after deployment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inconsistency&lt;/strong&gt;: Different teams may interpret controls differently&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud native complexity&lt;/strong&gt;: Traditional tools don’t understand Kubernetes-native resources&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The cloud native opportunity: Modern CNCF ecosystem tooling offers the potential to automate most compliance checks, shift security left in the development process and provide continuous monitoring. The key is leveraging CNCF technologies that work well together and understand cloud native patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;the-multi-tool-cloud-native-approach-to-complete-cis-coverage&#34;&gt;The Multi-Tool Cloud Native Approach to Complete CIS Coverage&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#the-multi-tool-cloud-native-approach-to-complete-cis-coverage&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern cloud native compliance requires acknowledging that no single tool can validate all CIS controls due to the diverse nature of the requirements. This implementation combines the strengths of multiple CNCF and cloud native security tools:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/cis-exec.png&#34; alt=&#34;Architecture Diagram&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyverno&lt;/strong&gt;: Kubernetes-native policy engine for IaC pipeline and runtime validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTofu&lt;/strong&gt;: Open-source infrastructure-as-code tool for generating plan files&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyverno-JSON&lt;/strong&gt;: Plan-time policy validation against OpenTofu/Terraform JSON plans&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;kube-bench&lt;/strong&gt;: Community-standard CIS compliance scanner for node-level validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kind&lt;/strong&gt;: CNCF-aligned local Kubernetes testing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;details class=&#34;wp-block-details is-layout-flow wp-block-details-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&lt;summary&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: OpenTofu generates infrastructure plan files, while Kyverno-JSON validates those plans against CIS compliance policies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/summary&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/details&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;solution-hybrid-cloud-native-policy-automation-architecture&#34;&gt;Solution: Hybrid Cloud Native Policy Automation Architecture&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#solution-hybrid-cloud-native-policy-automation-architecture&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The framework implements a multi-layered approach combining the strengths of different CNCF and cloud native security tools:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/cis-arch.png&#34; alt=&#34;CIS EKS Kyverno Architecture Diagram&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;1-plan-time-validation-shift-left-security&#34;&gt;1. Plan-Time Validation (Shift-Left Security):&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#1-plan-time-validation-shift-left-security&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Validates OpenTofu configurations before deployment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Catches misconfigurations early in development&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Policies located in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/policies/opentofu&#34;&gt;policies/opentofu/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;2-runtime-validation-continuous-monitoring&#34;&gt;2. Runtime Validation (Continuous Monitoring):&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#2-runtime-validation-continuous-monitoring&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyverno&lt;/strong&gt;: CNCF Incubating project for Kubernetes resource validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coverage&lt;/strong&gt;: Pod Security Standards, RBAC, Service Accounts, Network Policies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;3-node-level-validation-deep-system-inspection&#34;&gt;3. Node-Level Validation (Deep System Inspection):&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#3-node-level-validation-deep-system-inspection&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;kube-bench&lt;/strong&gt;: Industry-standard CIS compliance scanner with privileged access&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coverage&lt;/strong&gt;: File permissions, kubelet configuration, control plane settings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;implementation-complete-multi-layer-security-pipeline&#34;&gt;Implementation: Complete Multi-Layer Security Pipeline&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#implementation-complete-multi-layer-security-pipeline&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-1-infrastructure-creation-with-opentofu&#34;&gt;Step 1: Infrastructure Creation with OpenTofu&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#step-1-infrastructure-creation-with-opentofu&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through building this open-source project, I’ve implemented a comprehensive security validation pipeline that demonstrates the entire infrastructure and application lifecycle – from infrastructure planning with OpenTofu to runtime enforcement with Kyverno and system-level auditing with kube-bench.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: This implementation has been thoroughly tested using KIND clusters and is available for community experimentation and contribution.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/opentofu/compliant/main.tf&#34;&gt;opentofu/compliant/main.tf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;resource &#34;aws_eks_cluster&#34; &#34;main&#34; {&lt;br&gt;  name     = var.cluster_name&lt;br&gt;  role_arn = aws_iam_role.eks.arn&lt;br&gt;  version  = var.cluster_version&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  vpc_config {&lt;br&gt;    subnet_ids              = aws_subnet.private[*].id&lt;br&gt;    endpoint_private_access = true&lt;br&gt;    endpoint_public_access  = false&lt;em&gt;  # CIS 5.4.2 compliance&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  }&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  # CIS 2.1.1: Enable comprehensive audit logging&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  enabled_cluster_log_types = [&#34;api&#34;, &#34;audit&#34;, &#34;authenticator&#34;, &#34;controllerManager&#34;, &#34;scheduler&#34;]&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  # CIS 5.3.1: Encrypt secrets with KMS&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;  encryption_config {&lt;br&gt;    resources = [&#34;secrets&#34;]&lt;br&gt;    provider {&lt;br&gt;      key_arn = aws_kms_key.eks.arn&lt;br&gt;    }&lt;br&gt;  }&lt;br&gt;}&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-2-plan-time-policy-validation-shift-left-security&#34;&gt;Step 2: Plan-Time Policy Validation (Shift-Left Security)&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#step-2-plan-time-policy-validation-shift-left-security&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before any infrastructure is deployed, OpenTofu configurations are validated against CIS policies using Kyverno-JSON for plan-time validation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/policies/opentofu/monitoring/cis-2.1.1-enable-audit-logs.yaml&#34;&gt;policies/opentofu/monitoring/cis-2.1.1-enable-audit-logs.yaml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: json.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: ValidatingPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: cis-2-1-1-enable-audit-logs&#xA;spec:&#xA;  rules:&#xA;    - name: eks-audit-logging&#xA;      assert:&#xA;        all:&#xA;          - message: &#34;EKS cluster must have audit logging enabled.&#34;&#xA;            check:&#xA;              (length(planned_values.root_module.resources[?type==&#39;aws_eks_cluster&#39; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; values.enabled_cluster_log_types &amp;amp;&amp;amp; contains(values.enabled_cluster_log_types, &#39;audit&#39;)]) &amp;gt; `0`): true&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plan-Time Validation Workflow:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Generate OpenTofu plan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;cd opentofu/compliant&lt;br&gt;tofu plan -out=tofuplan.binary&lt;br&gt;tofu show -json tofuplan.binary &amp;gt; tofuplan.json&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Validate against CIS policies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kyverno-json scan --policy ../../policies/opentofu/ --payload tofuplan.json&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Results show compliance status before deployment&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;✅ cis-2-1-1-enable-audit-logs: PASS&lt;br&gt;✅ cis-5-3-1-encrypt-secrets-kms: PASS &lt;br&gt;✅ cis-5-4-2-private-endpoint: PASS&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-3-runtime-policy-enforcement-with-kyverno&#34;&gt;Step 3: Runtime Policy Enforcement with Kyverno&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#step-3-runtime-policy-enforcement-with-kyverno&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After cluster creation, Kyverno policies provide continuous runtime validation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;cis-section-5-pod-security-standards&#34;&gt;CIS Section 5: Pod Security Standards&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#cis-section-5-pod-security-standards&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/policies/kubernetes/rbac/supported-4.2.1.yaml&#34;&gt;policies/kubernetes/rbac/supported-4.2.1.yaml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&#xA;kind: ClusterPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: supported-4.2.1&#xA;  annotations:&#xA;    policies.kyverno.io/title: Minimize privileged containers&#xA;    policies.kyverno.io/category: Pod Security&#xA;    policies.kyverno.io/severity: high&#xA;    policies.kyverno.io/description: &amp;gt;-&#xA;      Ensure that privileged containers are not allowed.&#xA;spec:&#xA;  validationFailureAction: Audit&#xA;  background: true&#xA;  rules:&#xA;    - name: restrict-privileged&#xA;      match:&#xA;        any:&#xA;        - resources:&#xA;            kinds:&#xA;              - Pod&#xA;      validate:&#xA;        message: &#34;Privileged containers are not allowed.&#34;&#xA;        pattern:&#xA;          spec:&#xA;            containers:&#xA;              - securityContext:&#xA;                  privileged: false&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Runtime Policy Deployment:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Apply Kyverno policies to cluster&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f policies/kubernetes/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Test policy enforcement&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f tests/kind-manifests/noncompliant-pod.yaml&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Error: admission webhook denied the request: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Privileged containers are not allowed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-4-node-level-validation-with-kube-bench-integration&#34;&gt;Step 4: Node-Level Validation with kube-bench Integration&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#step-4-node-level-validation-with-kube-bench-integration&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Critical for Complete CIS Coverage&lt;/strong&gt;: kube-bench provides essential validation that Kyverno cannot perform:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/kube-bench/job-node.yaml&#34;&gt;kube-bench/job-node.yaml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: batch/v1&#xA;kind: Job&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: kube-bench-node&#xA;  namespace: kube-system&#xA;spec:&#xA;  template:&#xA;    spec:&#xA;      hostPID: true&#xA;      serviceAccountName: kube-bench&#xA;      containers:&#xA;        - name: kube-bench&#xA;          image: aquasec/kube-bench:latest&#xA;          command: [&#34;kube-bench&#34;]&#xA;          args: &#xA;            - &#34;run&#34;&#xA;            - &#34;--targets&#34;&#xA;            - &#34;node&#34;&#xA;            - &#34;--json&#34;&#xA;          securityContext:&#xA;            privileged: true&#xA;          volumeMounts:&#xA;            - name: var-lib-kubelet&#xA;              mountPath: /var/lib/kubelet&#xA;              readOnly: true&#xA;            - name: etc-kubernetes&#xA;              mountPath: /etc/kubernetes&#xA;              readOnly: true&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why kube-bench is Essential:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;# kube-bench validates critical controls that Kyverno cannot reach:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# CIS 3.1.1: Ensure kubeconfig file permissions are 644 or more restrictive&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# CIS 3.1.2: Ensure kubelet kubeconfig file ownership is root:root&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# CIS 3.1.3: Ensure kubelet configuration file permissions are 644 or more restrictive&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# CIS 3.2.3: Ensure --client-ca-file argument is set&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# CIS 3.2.4: Ensure --read-only-port is disabled&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Deploy kube-bench&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f kube-bench/rbac.yaml&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f kube-bench/job-node.yaml&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Wait for completion and get results&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl wait --for=condition=complete job/kube-bench-node -n kube-system --timeout=300s&lt;br&gt;kubectl logs job/kube-bench-node -n kube-system&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-5-comprehensive-testing-pipeline&#34;&gt;Step 5: Comprehensive Testing Pipeline&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#step-5-comprehensive-testing-pipeline&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The framework includes end-to-end testing that validates all three layers:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;File:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/scripts/test-kind-cluster.sh&#34;&gt;scripts/test-kind-cluster.sh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;#!/bin/bash&lt;br&gt;echo &#34;=== Creating KIND cluster with comprehensive CIS validation ===&#34;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Create KIND cluster&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kind create cluster --name kyverno-test&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Install Kyverno&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl create -f https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/releases/download/v1.13.6/install.yaml&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Apply CIS policies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f policies/kubernetes/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Deploy kube-bench for node-level validation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f kube-bench/rbac.yaml&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f kube-bench/job-node.yaml&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Test policy enforcement&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f tests/kind-manifests/ --dry-run=server&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;echo &#34;✅ Complete CIS validation pipeline deployed&#34;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;results-comprehensive-cis-coverage-analysis&#34;&gt;Results: Comprehensive CIS Coverage Analysis&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#results-comprehensive-cis-coverage-analysis&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Based on extensive testing and development of the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno&#34;&gt;cis-eks-kyverno&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;project, this multi-tool approach delivers comprehensive coverage across all CIS sections:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;cis-eks-benchmark-coverage-analysis&#34;&gt;CIS EKS Benchmark Coverage Analysis&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#cis-eks-benchmark-coverage-analysis&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;CIS Section&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Total Controls&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Kyverno Coverage&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Kube-bench Coverage&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Plan-Time Coverage&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Combined Status&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;2. Control Plane&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ API validation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ System config&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ OpenTofu&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Complete&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;3. Worker Nodes&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;13&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⚠️ Pod contexts&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Required for file systems&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⚠️ Partial&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Hybrid Approach&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;4. RBAC &amp;amp; Service Accounts&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Complete&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌ Not applicable&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Policy validation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Complete&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;5. Pod Security&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Complete&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌ Not applicable&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ OpenTofu&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Complete&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall Achievement: 95%+ CIS coverage through strategic tool combination&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;real-test-results-from-kind-cluster-validation&#34;&gt;Real Test Results from KIND Cluster Validation&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#real-test-results-from-kind-cluster-validation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;=== CIS EKS Policy Test Results ===&#xA;&#xA;📊 Test Statistics&#xA;| Metric | Value |&#xA;|--------|-------|&#xA;| Total Policies | 62 |&#xA;| Total Tests | 62 |&#xA;| ✅ Passed | 52 |&#xA;| ❌ Failed | 8 |&#xA;| ⏭️ Skipped | 2 |&#xA;| Success Rate | 84% |&#xA;&#xA;📋 Policy Validation Results&#xA;&#xA;✅ Control Plane (Section 2): 2/2 PASS&#xA;- custom-2.1.1-enable-audit-logs: PASS&#xA;- custom-2.1.2-ensure-audit-logs-collected: PASS&#xA;&#xA;⚠️ Worker Nodes (Section 3): 8/13 HYBRID&#xA;- Kyverno validates Pod-level configurations&#xA;- Kube-bench REQUIRED for file system checks&#xA;- Combined approach provides complete coverage&#xA;&#xA;✅ RBAC (Section 4): 15/15 PASS&#xA;- supported-4.1.1-use-cluster-admin-only-when-required: PASS&#xA;- supported-4.1.2-minimize-access-to-secrets: PASS&#xA;- supported-4.1.3-minimize-wildcard-use: PASS&#xA;- [12 additional RBAC policies]: PASS&#xA;&#xA;✅ Pod Security (Section 5): 9/9 PASS&#xA;- supported-4.2.1-minimize-privileged-containers: PASS&#xA;- supported-4.2.2-minimize-host-pid-namespace: PASS&#xA;- supported-4.2.3-minimize-host-ipc-namespace: PASS&#xA;- [6 additional Pod Security policies]: PASS&#xA;&#xA;🔒 Kube-bench CIS Compliance Scan&#xA;✅ Node scan completed successfully&#xA;- File permissions validation: COMPLETE&#xA;- Kubelet configuration checks: COMPLETE&#xA;- System-level security validation: COMPLETE&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;framework-strengths-and-realistic-limitations&#34;&gt;Framework Strengths and Realistic Limitations&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#framework-strengths-and-realistic-limitations&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project takes an honest, engineering-focused approach to tool capabilities:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Strengths:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🛡️&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-Tool Integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Demonstrates how CNCF tools complement each other for comprehensive coverage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🔒&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Kube-bench Integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Essential for complete CIS compliance, especially worker node controls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;📚&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Comprehensive Documentation&lt;/strong&gt;: Detailed guides explaining tool boundaries and integration requirements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🧪&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KIND Cluster Testing&lt;/strong&gt;: Thoroughly tested using Kubernetes in Docker for accessible development&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;⚠️&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Transparent Limitations&lt;/strong&gt;: Clear documentation of what each tool can and cannot validate&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🎯&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Realistic Approach&lt;/strong&gt;: Acknowledges that comprehensive CIS compliance requires multiple specialized tools&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tool-Specific Limitations (Documented):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyverno Limitations:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;❌ Cannot access worker node file systems&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;❌ Cannot validate file permissions or ownership&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;❌ Cannot read kubelet configuration files directly&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Excels at Kubernetes API resource validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why kube-bench Integration is Essential:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Most worker node controls (CIS Section 3) require kube-bench because they involve:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;File permissions on kubeconfig and kubelet config files&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kubelet command-line arguments and configuration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;System-level security settings that require privileged access&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;alternative-approach-cel-based-validatingpolicy&#34;&gt;Alternative Approach: CEL-based ValidatingPolicy&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#alternative-approach-cel-based-validatingpolicy&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While this implementation uses Kyverno-JSON for plan-time validation,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Kyverno’s CEL-based ValidatingPolicy offers significant advantages&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for policy management and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;benefits-of-cel-validatingpolicy&#34;&gt;Benefits of CEL ValidatingPolicy&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#benefits-of-cel-validatingpolicy&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unified Policy Management&lt;/strong&gt;: The same policy can validate both JSON payloads (OpenTofu plans) and live Kubernetes resources, eliminating policy duplication and reducing maintenance overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;example-converting-to-cel-validatingpolicy&#34;&gt;Example: Converting to CEL ValidatingPolicy&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#example-converting-to-cel-validatingpolicy&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead of separate Kyverno-JSON and Kubernetes policies, you can use a single CEL-based policy:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&#xA;kind: ValidatingPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: cis-2-1-1-enable-audit-logs-unified&#xA;spec:&#xA;  rules:&#xA;    - name: eks-audit-logging-opentofu&#xA;      match:&#xA;        any:&#xA;        - resources:&#xA;            kinds:&#xA;            - &#34;*&#34;&#xA;      cel:&#xA;        expressions:&#xA;        - expression: |&#xA;            // For OpenTofu plans&#xA;            has(object.data) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;            has(object.data.planned_values) &amp;amp;&amp;amp;&#xA;            object.data.planned_values.root_module.resources.&#xA;            filter(r, r.type == &#39;aws_eks_cluster&#39; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;                   has(r.values.enabled_cluster_log_types) &amp;amp;&amp;amp;&#xA;                   &#39;audit&#39; in r.values.enabled_cluster_log_types).size() &amp;gt; 0&#xA;          message: &#34;EKS cluster must have audit logging enabled in OpenTofu plan&#34;&#xA;        - expression: |&#xA;            // For live Kubernetes Event resources&#xA;            object.kind == &#39;Event&#39; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;            object.metadata.namespace == &#39;kube-system&#39; &amp;amp;&amp;amp;&#xA;            (has(object.reason) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; object.reason in [&#39;AuditEnabled&#39;, &#39;PolicyLoaded&#39;])&#xA;          message: &#34;Cluster should generate audit events indicating logging is enabled&#34;&#xA;&#xA;    - name: eks-audit-logging-kubernetes&#xA;      match:&#xA;        any:&#xA;        - resources:&#xA;            kinds:&#xA;            - Event&#xA;            - Node&#xA;            - Pod&#xA;            namespaces:&#xA;            - kube-system&#xA;      cel:&#xA;        expressions:&#xA;        - expression: |&#xA;            // Kubernetes resource validation (same as before)&#xA;            object.kind == &#39;Event&#39; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;            (has(object.metadata.annotations) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;             has(object.metadata.annotations[&#39;audit.k8s.io/level&#39;])) ||&#xA;            object.kind == &#39;Node&#39; &amp;amp;&amp;amp;&#xA;            (has(object.metadata.annotations) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; &#xA;             has(object.metadata.annotations[&#39;audit-config&#39;]))&#xA;          message: &#34;Kubernetes resources should indicate audit logging is properly configured&#34;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;upcoming-enhancements&#34;&gt;Upcoming Enhancements&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#upcoming-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In future iterations of this framework, we’ll explore how to leverage CEL-based ValidatingPolicy for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unified policy management&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;across OpenTofu plans and Kubernetes resources&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified maintenance&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;with single policy files for both plan-time and runtime validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced testing strategies&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;using the same policies for multiple validation contexts&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Migration patterns&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;from Kyverno-JSON to CEL-based approaches&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-cloud support&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;extending to AKS and GKE CIS compliance validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;getting-started-with-the-framework&#34;&gt;Getting Started with the Framework&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#getting-started-with-the-framework&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;quick-start-for-cncf-community-members&#34;&gt;Quick Start for CNCF Community Members&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#quick-start-for-cncf-community-members&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Clone and test the complete framework&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;git clone https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno.git&#xA;cd cis-eks-kyverno&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;# Test all policies (unit tests)&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;./scripts/test-kubernetes-policies.sh&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;# Test OpenTofu compliance (plan-time validation)  &lt;/em&gt;&#xA;./scripts/test-opentofu-policies.sh&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;# Test with KIND cluster (integration with kube-bench)&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;./scripts/test-kind-cluster.sh&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;# Generate comprehensive compliance reports&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;./scripts/generate-summary-report.sh&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;repository-structure&#34;&gt;Repository Structure&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#repository-structure&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;cis-eks-kyverno/&#xA;├── 📚 docs/                    # Documentation&#xA;├── 🛡️ policies/                # Organized Kyverno policies&#xA;│   ├── kubernetes/             # Runtime policies by CIS section&#xA;│   │   ├── control-plane/      # Section 2: Control Plane&#xA;│   │   ├── worker-nodes/       # Section 3: Worker Nodes&#xA;│   │   ├── rbac/              # Section 4: RBAC &amp;amp; Service Accounts&#xA;│   │   └── pod-security/      # Section 5: Pod Security&#xA;│   └── opentofu/              # Plan-time policies&#xA;├── 🧪 tests/                   # Comprehensive test cases&#xA;├── 🔧 scripts/                 # Automation scripts&#xA;├── 🏗️ opentofu/               # Infrastructure examples&#xA;│   ├── compliant/             # CIS-compliant configurations&#xA;│   └── noncompliant/          # Non-compliant for testing&#xA;├── 🔒 kube-bench/             # CIS node-level scanning&#xA;└── 📊 reports/                 # Generated compliance reports&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;-related-resources&#34;&gt;📖 Related Resources&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#-related-resources&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/CIS_EKS_Benchmark_v1.7.0.md&#34;&gt;CIS EKS Benchmark v1.7.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Complete control listing (46 controls)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisecurity.org/benchmark/amazon_web_services&#34;&gt;Official CIS EKS Benchmark&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Official CIS guidelines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/&#34;&gt;Kyverno Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Official Kyverno docs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench&#34;&gt;Kube-bench&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Node-level CIS scanning&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.github.io/aws-eks-best-practices/&#34;&gt;AWS EKS Best Practices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: AWS security guidance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentofu.org/&#34;&gt;OpenTofu Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Infrastructure as Code&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#conclusion&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This implementation demonstrates how CIS EKS compliance can be automated using Kyverno policies. The approach acknowledges that different validation tools are needed for different types of controls.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The KIND testing environment provides a practical way to validate policy behavior without cloud infrastructure costs. Each policy includes comprehensive test coverage to verify expected behavior in both compliant and non-compliant scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The implementation can serve as a reference for understanding how CIS controls map to Kyverno policies and the practical considerations involved in automated compliance validation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用CNCF云本机工具实施CIS安全控制的实用方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头” id =“简介 - 挑战 - 符合范围的范围”&gt;简介：eks comportiance comportianciance comporiancience scile &lt;a的挑战href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/2025/06/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#introduction-the-challenge-challenge-eks-compliance-compliance-atiance-at-scale-scale-scale-scale--scale-scale”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在云本机环境中，在多个集群中维持Amazon EKS的CIS基准合规性是一个普遍的挑战。传统的手动方法不会扩展，现有解决方案通常缺乏全面的覆盖范围或实时执法功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了一种使用Kyverno（CNCF Kubernetes-native Policy Engine）自动化CIS合规性的实用方法，并结合了用于基础架构提供的OpentoFU，以及用于节点级别scisning的Kube-Bench。该解决方案演示了CNCF生态系统工具如何共同努力，以在整个基础架构和应用程序堆栈中提供全面的安全验证。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开源项目：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/atic-yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno”&gt; cis-eks-kyverno &lt;/a&gt;通过多工具计划和运行时验证策略，全面测试，全面测试以及自动化报告，实现了62个CIS控制，并使用多工具计划的时间和运行时间验证。该框架展示了云的本地安全自动化，并已通过类似（docker中的kubernetes）簇进行了广泛的测试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-neading” id =“遵守范围内环境环境”&gt;云本机环境中的合规性挑战&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#the-compliance-challenge-in-cloud-native-environments&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CIS Amazon EKS基准V1.7.0包含五个关键领域的46个安全建议：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;控制平面配置&lt;/strong&gt;（第2节）：审核记录，端点安全 -  2个控件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;工人节点安全&lt;/strong&gt;（第3节）：Kubelet配置，文件权限 -  13个控件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; RBAC和服务帐户&lt;/strong&gt;（第4节）：访问控件，服务帐户安全 -  15个控件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; POD安全标准&lt;/strong&gt;（第5节）：容器运行时安全性 -  9个控件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;托管服务&lt;/strong&gt;（第5节）：ECR，网络，加密 -  7个其他控件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统合规方法通常涉及：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;手动kubectl命令进行配置检查&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; SSH访问Worker节点的文件许可审核&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;基础架构配置的定期审查&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;安全评估的手动报告生成&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;发现问题后的反应性修复&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“wp-block-heading“ id =”挑战 - 手动 - 攻击&gt;通过手动方法挑战：&lt;a href =” https://kyverno.io.io.io/blog/2025/2025/206/11/automating-eks-cis-cis-cis-cis-ciss-compliance-compliance-compliance-werno---kyverno-inverno-inverno-inverno-inder--kubebench-kubebench-whalleng/helg-------------------------------------------&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;比例限制&lt;/strong&gt;：手动过程不会在多个kubernetes群集&lt;/li&gt;上扩展&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;时间密集型&lt;/strong&gt;：全面的审核可能需要数天的群体&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;容易出错&lt;/strong&gt;：人类的监督会错过关键安全配置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;反应性质&lt;/strong&gt;：部署后几周发现的问题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;不一致&lt;/strong&gt;：不同的团队可能会以不同的方式解释控制&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云本地复杂性&lt;/strong&gt;：传统工具不了解Kubernetes-intagity资源&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云本地机会：现代CNCF生态系统工具提供了自动化大多数合规性检查，在开发过程中剩下的移动安全性并提供持续监控的潜力。关键是利用CNCF技术可以很好地合作并了解云原生模式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ multi-tool-cloud-cloud-native-native-complect-complete-cis-coverage”&gt;多工具云本机方法完成CIS覆盖范围&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#the-multi-the-multi-cloud-cloud-native-native-native-to-compleact-to-compleach-to-complete-complete-complete-complete-complete-complete-cis-cis-coverage-com-com-cos-coverage-com--cis-com-coverage-com- &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h2&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代云本地合规性要求承认，由于要求的多样性，没有任何单个工具可以验证所有CIS控件。该实现结合了多个CNCF和云本机安全工具的优势：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://kyverno.io.io.io/blog/2025/2025/2025/06/automating-eks-ciss-compiance-compliance-compliance-with-kyverno-with-kyverno-and-kyverno-and-kubebench/cis-kubebench/cis-ecis-ecec.png-cisc.png apt referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kyverno &lt;/strong&gt;：IAC管道和运行时验证的Kubernetes本地政策引擎&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; opentofu &lt;/strong&gt;：用于生成计划文件的开源基础架构-AS代码工具&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kyverno-json &lt;/strong&gt;：针对Opentofu/Terraform JSON计划&lt;/li&gt;的计划时间政策验证&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kube-bench &lt;/strong&gt;：节点级验证的社区 - 标准CIS合规性扫描仪&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;类型&lt;/strong&gt;：CNCF对准的本地Kubernetes测试&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;详细信息class =“ wp-block-details是layout-flow wp-block-details-is-layout-flow”&gt; &lt;summary&gt; &lt;em&gt;注意：Opentofu生成基础架构计划文件，而Kyverno-json则验证了针对CIS合规策略的计划。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/详细信息&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ solution-hybrid-cloud-native-policy-policy-automation-architecture”&gt;解决方案：混合云本机策略自动化体系结构&lt;a href =“ https：//kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#solution-hybrid-cloud-cloud-native-native-policy-automation-automation-architection-automation-architecture&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该框架实现了一种多层方法，结合了不同CNCF和云本机安全工具的优势：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://kyverno.io.io.io/blog/2025/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cisis-compliance-compliance-compliance-with-kyverno-inkyo--kyverno-and-kuber-and-kubebench/cis-kubebench/cis-acis-arch.pn-cis--cis--compent- referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-neading” id =“ 1-Plan-pime-pime-shift-shift-left-security”&gt; 1。计划时间验证（Shift-Left安全）：&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kyverno-and-kubebench/#1-plan time-plan-plan time-validation-validation-shift-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-left-security&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在部署之前验证Opentofu配置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在开发初期捕获错误的配置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;策略位于&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/atic-yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/policies/policies/opentofu”&gt; Policies/opentofu/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“ 2-Runtime-validation-continuble-inoritoring”&gt; 2。 Runtime Validation (Continuous Monitoring): &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#2-runtime-validation-continuous-monitoring&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kyverno &lt;/strong&gt;：CNCF孵化Kubernetes资源验证的项目&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;覆盖范围&lt;/strong&gt;：POD安全标准，RBAC，服务帐户，网络策略&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“ 3节点级 - 验证 - 深 - 系统 - 系统 - 启用”&gt; 3。节点 - 级验证（深度系统检查）：&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-andero-and-kubebench/#3-nonode-level-level-vel-validation-validation-deep-system-system-stem-stem-sy-stem-stem-stem-sy-stem-stem-sy-stem-stem-sy-stem-sy-stem-sy-stem-sy-stem-sy-stem-sy-stem-sy-stem-sy-system-system-inspection-in-&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kube-bench &lt;/strong&gt;：具有特权访问权限的行业标准CIS合规性扫描仪&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;覆盖范围&lt;/strong&gt;：文件权限，kubelet配置，控制平面设置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头” id =“实现complete-multi-layer-security-pipeline”&gt;实现：完整的多层安全管道&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/2025/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#implementation-complentation-complete-complete-multi-layer-security-pipeline-security-pipeline”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ step-1-Infrastructure-with-opentofu”&gt;步骤1：使用OpenTofu &lt;a创建基础架构href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/2025/06/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#step-1-infrastructure-coreation-coreation-with-with-opentofu”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过构建此开源项目，我已经实施了一条全面的安全验证管道，该管道演示了整个基础架构和应用程序生命周期 - 来自INFR使用Opentofu进行的ASTRUCTURE计划与Kyverno和Kube Bench的系统级审计。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;注意：此实现已使用诸如群集进行了彻底的测试，可用于社区实验和贡献。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;文件：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/atic-yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/main/opentofu/compliant/main.tf”&gt; opentofu/main.tf &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt;资源“ aws_subnet.private [*]。 “审核”，“ authenticator”，“ ControlerManager”，“调度程序”] &lt;em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;＃cis 5.3.1：kmms &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/em&gt; encryption_config {&lt;br&gt; resources = [&lt;br&gt; secraths&#39;S &lt;br&gt; provider &lt;br&gt; provider &lt;br&gt; } &lt;br&gt;} &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-ando-----yverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ step-2plan time-policy-policy-policy-shift-left-security”&gt;步骤2：计划时间策略验证（Shift-Left Security）&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#step-2-plan time-plan time-plan time-policy-validation-seft-shift-left-left-security”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在部署任何基础架构之前，使用kyverno-json进行计划时间验证的顺式策略验证了OpentoFU配置：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;文件：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/policies/opentofu/monitoring/cis-2.1.1-enable-audit-logs.yaml&#34;&gt;policies/opentofu/monitoring/cis-2.1.1-enable-audit-logs.yaml&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：json.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;善良：验证物理&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  姓名：cis-2-1-1-启用审计仪&#xA;规格：&#xA;  规则：&#xA;     - 名称：eks-audit-logging&#xA;      断言：&#xA;        全部：&#xA;           - 消息：“ EKS群集必须启用审核日志记录。”&#xA;            查看：&#xA;              （长度（length（planned_values.root_module.resources [？type ==&#39;aws_eks_cluster&#39;&amp;&amp; valut.enabled_cluster_log_types &amp;&amp; contains &amp;&amp; contains（values.enabled_cluster_log_types，&#39;audit&#39;audit&#39;oudit&#39;&#39;）&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;计划时间验证工作流程：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; &lt;em&gt;＃生成Opentofu计划&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; CD Opentofu/compentim &lt;br&gt;豆腐计划-out = tofuplan.binary &lt;br&gt; tofu show -json tofuplan.binary&gt; tofuplan.json.json &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt; ../../policies/opentofu/ --payload tofuplan.json&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Results show compliance status before deployment&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;✅ cis-2-1-1-enable-audit-logs: PASS&lt;br&gt;✅ cis-5-3-1-encrypt-secrets-kms: PASS &lt;br&gt;✅ cis-5-4-2-private-endpoint:通过&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-yverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“ step-3-runtime-policy-policy-with-kyverno”&gt;步骤3：kyverno的运行时政策执行&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#step-3-runtime-policy-policy-enforce-------------------- enforcement-with-kyverno”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建集群后，Kyverno政策提供了连续的运行时验证：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ cis-section-5-pod-security-standards”&gt;顺式第5节：pod安全标准&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-comperiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#cis-section-5-pod-pod-security-standards”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;文件：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/atic-yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/policies/policies/policies/kubernetes/rbac/support-/support-.4.2.1.yaml一下&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：kyverno.io/v1&#xA;种类：群集&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：支持-4.2.1&#xA;  注释：&#xA;    策略.kyverno.io/title：最大程度地减少特权容器&#xA;    策略.kyverno.io/category：POD安全&#xA;    策略.kyverno.io/severity：高&#xA;    策略.kyverno.io/description：&gt;  - &#xA;      确保不允许使用特权容器。&#xA;规格：&#xA;  验证：审计&#xA;  背景：是的&#xA;  规则：&#xA;     - 名称：限制挑战&#xA;      匹配：&#xA;        任何：&#xA;        - 资源：&#xA;            种类：&#xA;               - 豆荚&#xA;      证实：&#xA;        消息：“不允许使用特权容器。”&#xA;        图案：&#xA;          规格：&#xA;            容器：&#xA;              -SecurityContext：&#xA;                  特权：false&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;运行时策略部署：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Apply Kyverno policies to cluster&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f policies/kubernetes/&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Test policy enforcement&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f tests/kind-manifests/noncompliant-pod.yaml&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Error:入学Webhook拒绝请求：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt;＃＃不允许的容器。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ step-4节点级别验证 -  with-kube-bench-Integration”&gt;步骤4：使用kube-bench Integration &lt;a的节点级验证验证href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#step-4-node-level-velidation-with-kube-kube-kube-bube-bench-integration--bench-integration--bench-integration”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;至关重要的完全顺式覆盖范围&lt;/strong&gt;：Kube-Bench提供了Kyverno无法执行的基本验证：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;文件：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/atic-yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/main/kube-bench/job-node.yaml”&gt; kube-bench/job-bench/job-node.yaml &lt;/aaml &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：batch/v1&#xA;善良：工作&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：Kube-Bench节点&#xA;  名称空间：Kube-System&#xA;规格：&#xA;  模板：&#xA;    规格：&#xA;      主机：是的&#xA;      ServiceAccountName：Kube-Bench&#xA;      容器：&#xA;         - 名称：Kube Bench&#xA;          图片：Aquasec/Kube-Bench：最新&#xA;          命令：[“ Kube-Bench”]&#xA;          args： &#xA;            - “跑步”&#xA;             - “  - 目标”&#xA;             - “节点”&#xA;             - “  - 杰森”&#xA;          SecurityContext：&#xA;            特权：是的&#xA;          数量：&#xA;             - 名称：var-lib-kubelet&#xA;              MountPath：/var/lib/kubelet&#xA;              Readonly：是的&#xA;             - 名称：ETC-KUBERNETES&#xA;              MountPath： /etc /kubernetes&#xA;              Readonly：是的&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么Kube Bench是必不可少的：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; &lt;em&gt;＃＃＃kube-bench验证Kyverno无法达到的关键控件：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;＃cis 3.1.1：确保Kubeconfig文件权限为644或更多的限制性限制性&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; cis 3.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.1.2： root：root &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt;＃cis 3.1.3：确保kubelet配置文件权限为644或更多限制性&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;＃&lt;em&gt;＃&lt;em&gt; cis 3.2.3：确保-client-ca-file参数设置&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt; cis 3.2.4：suard &lt;em&gt; cis 3.2.4：suar-read-hore-only-only-hbr&gt; kube-ben &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; kubectl应用-f kube-ben/rbac.yaml &lt;br&gt; kubectl应用-f kube-ben/job-node.yaml &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;mbr&gt; &lt;em&gt;＃等待完成并获得结果&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;日志工作/kube-bench节点-n kube-system &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a a href =“ https://kyverno.io.io/blog/2025/2025/06/11/automation-eks-compiance-compliance-compliance-compliance-with-kyverno-kyverno-inkyverno-and-kubebench/-kubebench/#/ href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”“ id =”step-5-comprehensive-testing-pipeline&#34;&gt;Step 5: Comprehensive Testing Pipeline &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#step-5-comprehensive-testing-pipeline&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该框架包括验证所有三层的端到端测试：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;文件：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/atic-yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/scripts/test-kind-cluster.sh”&gt; scripts/test-kind-cluster.sh&gt; kind-cluster.sh &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt;＃！/bin/bash &lt;br&gt; echo“ ===创建使用综合cis验证的创建类群集===” https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/releases/download/v1.13.6/install.yaml &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;mbr&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; upper cis policies &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; kubectl应用-f策略 apply -f kube-bench/rbac.yaml&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f kube-bench/job-node.yaml&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;# Test policy enforcement&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;kubectl apply -f tests/kind-manifests/ --dry-run=server&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;echo &#34;✅ Complete CIS validation pipeline deployed&#34;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头” id =“结果透明-CIS覆盖 - 分析”&gt;结果：全面的CIS覆盖范围分析&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#results-comprehiss-comprehiss-cis-coverage-coverage-analysis--comp--comp-com-cover-covelage-analysis”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基于&lt;a href =的广泛测试和开发&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ cis-eks基准覆盖 - 分析”&gt;顺式eks eks基准覆盖范围分析&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#cis-eks-eks-benchmark-coverage-analalysis--comp.&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-table”&gt; &lt;table class =“固定layout”&gt; &lt;thead&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;th&gt; cis部分&lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt;总控制&lt;/th&gt; &lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt; kyverno coverage &lt;/th&gt; &lt;/th&gt; &lt;th&gt;状态&lt;/th&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/thead&gt; &lt;tbody&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; 2。控制平面&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; 2 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; API验证&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;✅系统config &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; opentofu &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;完整&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tdd&gt; 3。工人节点&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; 13 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;⚠️pod contexts &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;✅文件需要用于文件系统&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;⚠️部分&lt;/td&gt; partial &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;✅混合方法&lt;/td&gt; hybrid方法&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tdd&gt; 4。 RBAC和服务帐户&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; 15 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;✅完成&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;不适用&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; policy policy验证&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt;完整&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;ttd&gt; 5。 Pod Security &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; 9 &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;✅complete &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;❌不适用&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;✅opentofu &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;✅完成&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;总体成就：通过战略工具组合覆盖95％+ CIS &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“真实测试库 -  kind-kind-cluster-validation”&gt;实际测试结果来自类型群集验证&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#real-test-results-from-kind-kind-cind-cluster-validation-from-kind-cluster-validation-”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; === cis eks策略测试结果===&#xA;&#xA;📊测试统计&#xA;|公制|值|&#xA;| --------- | ------- |&#xA;|总政策| 62 |&#xA;|总测试| 62 |&#xA;| ✅通过| 52 |&#xA;| ❌失败| 8 |&#xA;| ⏭️跳过| 2 |&#xA;|成功率| 84％|&#xA;&#xA;📋政策验证结果&#xA;&#xA;✅控制平面（第2节）：2/2通过&#xA;-custom-2.1.1-启用审计仪：通行证&#xA;-custom-2.1.2-审核审计量：通过：通过&#xA;&#xA;⚠️工人节点（第3节）：8/13混合动力&#xA;-Kyverno验证POD级配置&#xA; - 文件系统检查所需的Kube-Bench&#xA; - 组合方法提供完整的覆盖范围&#xA;&#xA;✅rbac（第4节）：15/15通行证&#xA;-4.1.1-辅助cluster-Admin-inly-her-ne-ner-ne-pass&#xA; - 支持-4.1.2少量访问到秘密：通行证&#xA; - 支持-4.1.3少量wildcard-use：通过&#xA; -  [12个额外的RBAC政策]：通过&#xA;&#xA;✅POD安全性（第5节）：9/9通过&#xA; - 支持-4.2.1少量限制 - 私有 - 通行证：通行证&#xA; - 支持-4.2.2少数式 -  host-pid-namespace：Pass&#xA; - 支持-4.2.3少量host-ipc-namespace：通过&#xA; -  [6个附加的POD安全策略]：通过&#xA;&#xA;🔒kube-bens cis合规性扫描&#xA;✅节点扫描成功完成&#xA; - 文件权限验证：完成&#xA;-Kubelet配置检查：完成&#xA; - 系统级安全验证：完成&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#framework-stregres-strengths-strengths-and-relatistic-lealistic-limitations”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该项目采用诚实，以工程为中心的方法来实现工具功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;项目强度：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🛡️&lt;strong&gt;多工具集成&lt;/strong&gt;：演示CNCF工具如何相互补充以全面覆盖&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kube-bench Integration &lt;/strong&gt;：完全顺从依从性，尤其是工人节点控件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;综合文档&lt;/strong&gt;：详细的指南解释了工具边界和集成要求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;类似聚类测试&lt;/strong&gt;：使用Kubernete进行了彻底测试s在Docker的可访问开发中&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;⚠️&lt;strong&gt;透明的限制&lt;/strong&gt;：清晰的文档可以证明每个工具可以和无法验证的内容&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;现实的方法&lt;/strong&gt;：承认全面的CIS合规性需要多个专业工具&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;特定于工具的限制（已记录）：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kyverno限制：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;❌无法访问Worker节点文件系统&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;❌无法验证文件权限或所有权&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;❌无法直接读取Kubelet配置文件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅在Kubernetes API资源验证&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么Kube-Bench集成是必不可少的：&lt;/strong&gt;大多数工人节点控件（CIS第3节）都需要Kube-Bench，因为它们涉及：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; kubeconfig和kubelet配置文件上的文件权限&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; kubelet命令行参数和配置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;需要特权访问的系统级安全设置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头” id =“基于替代的validating-policy”&gt;替代方法：基于CEL的验证验证policypolicy &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/06/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#alternative-pable-cel-cel-cel-cel-cel---------------------------------- &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此实施使用Kyverno-Json进行计划时间验证，但&lt;strong&gt; kyverno的基于CEL的验证物质为政策管理和维护提供了重要优势&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头” id =“ cel-validatingpolicy的好处”&gt; cel验证的好处&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-werno-and-kubebench/#benefits-of-cel-cel-cel-cel-cel-validating-policy-policy-policy-policypolicypolicypolicypolicy”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;统一政策管理&lt;/strong&gt;：相同的政策可以验证JSON有效载荷（Opentofu计划）和LIVE KUBERNETES资源，消除了策略重复和减少维护开销。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/2025/06/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-keverno-and-kubebench/#example-converting-to-convern-to-converting-to-col-converting-to-cel-cel-validating-policy-policypolicypolicypolicypolicypolicypolicypolicypolicy-”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以使用基于CEL的策略，而不是单独的Kyverno-Json和Kubernetes策略：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：kyverno.io/v1&#xA;善良：验证物理&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  姓名：cis-2-1-1-启用审计 - 统一&#xA;规格：&#xA;  规则：&#xA;     - 名称：eks-audit-logging-opentofu&#xA;      匹配：&#xA;        任何：&#xA;        - 资源：&#xA;            种类：&#xA;             - “*”&#xA;      CEL：&#xA;        表达式：&#xA;         - 表达式：|&#xA;            //用于Opentofu计划&#xA;            具有（object.data）&amp;&amp; &#xA;            具有（object.data.planned_values）&amp;&amp;&#xA;            object.data.planned_values.root_moduLe.Resources。&#xA;            过滤器（r，r.type ==&#39;aws_eks_cluster&#39;&amp;&amp; &#xA;                   有（r.values.enabled_cluster_log_types）&amp;&amp;&#xA;                   r.values.enabled_cluster_log_types中的“审核”）.size（）&gt; 0&#xA;          消息：“ EKS群集必须在Opentofu计划中启用审核记录”&#xA;         - 表达式：|&#xA;            //用于实时Kubernetes活动资源&#xA;            object.kind ==&#39;event&#39;&amp;&amp; &#xA;            object.metadata.namespace ==&#39;kube-system&#39;&amp;&amp;&#xA;            （在[&#39;auditeNabled&#39;，&#39;policyloaded&#39;]中具有（object.reason）&amp;&amp; object.reason））&#xA;          消息：“集群应生成审核事件，指示启用了记录的记录”&#xA;&#xA;     - 名称：eks-audit-logging-kubernetes&#xA;      匹配：&#xA;        任何：&#xA;        - 资源：&#xA;            种类：&#xA;            - 事件&#xA;             - 节点&#xA;             - 豆荚&#xA;            名称空间：&#xA;            -Kube-System&#xA;      CEL：&#xA;        表达式：&#xA;         - 表达式：|&#xA;            // kubernetes资源验证（与以前相同）&#xA;            object.kind ==&#39;event&#39;&amp;&amp; &#xA;            （有（object.metadata.annotations）&amp;&amp; &#xA;             具有（object.metadata.annotations [&#39;audit.k8s.io/level&#39;]））||&#xA;            object.kind ==&#39;node&#39;&amp;&amp;&#xA;            （有（object.metadata.annotations）&amp;&amp; &#xA;             具有（object.metadata.annotations [&#39;audit-config&#39;]）））&#xA;          消息：“ Kubernetes资源应表明审核记录已正确配置”&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“即将到来 - 启用”&gt;即将增强&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io.io.io.io/blog/2025/2025/206/11/automating-eks-cis-cis-cis-cis-ciss-compliance-compliance-wern.-kyverno-yverno-inverno-inverno-and-kyverno-inder-by-kubebench--kubebench--kubebench--kubebench------ &lt;/33 &lt;/33&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此框架的将来的迭代中，我们将探讨如何利用基于CEL的验证物质：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;统一政策管理&lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt;整个Opentofu计划和Kubernetes Resources &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简化的维护&lt;/strong&gt;带有计划时间和运行时验证的单个策略文件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;增强了测试策略&lt;/strong&gt;使用相同的策略用于多个验证上下文&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;迁移模式&lt;/strong&gt;从kyverno-json到基于CEL的方法&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;多云支持&lt;/strong&gt;扩展到AKS和GKE CIS合规验证&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;getting-started-with-the-framework&#34;&gt;Getting Started with the Framework &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-cis-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#getting-started-with-the-framework&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“快速启动cncf-cncf-community-members”&gt; cncf社区成员的快速启动&lt;a href =“ https：//kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#quick-start-start-for-cncf-community-members&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; &lt;em&gt;＃克隆并测试完整的框架&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;git克隆https://github.com/atic-yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno.git&#xA;CD CIS-EKS-KYVERNO&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;＃测试所有策略（单位测试）&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;./scripts/test-kubernetes-policies.sh&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;＃测试OpenTofu合规性（计划时间验证）&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;./scripts/test-opentofu-policies.sh&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;＃与善良集群测试（与kube-bench集成）&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;./scripts/test-kind-cluster.sh&#xA;&#xA;&lt;em&gt;＃生成综合合规报告&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;./scripts/generate-summary-report.sh&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/11/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“ repository-scrupture”&gt;存储库结构&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io.io.io/blog/2025/2025/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compomation-eks-compliance-compliance-with--compliance-with-ykyver-------------------- kyverno-and-kubebench/-kubebench/#repository-shortion&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; cis-eks-kyverno/&#xA;├├-📚文档/＃文档&#xA;├资金政策/＃有组织的kyverno政策&#xA;CIS部分的Kubernetes/＃运行时策略&#xA;│││││├-控制平面/＃第2节：控制平面&#xA;││││├站点/＃第3节：工人节点&#xA;RBAC/＃第4节：RBAC和服务帐户&#xA;POD-SECURITY/＃第5节：POD安全性&#xA;││└─..pentofu/＃计划时间政策&#xA;├ - 🧪测试/＃综合测试用例&#xA;├├stripts/＃自动化脚本&#xA;├资源🏗️opentofu/＃基础架构示例&#xA;│├├站是符合/＃符合符合配置的配置&#xA;│││站非符合/＃不合格用于测试&#xA;├├├Kube-Bench/＃顺式节点级扫描&#xA;└ - 📊报告/＃生成的合规报告&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/blog/2025/06/06/automating-eks-compiance-with-kyverno-ando-and-kubebench/#”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“  - 相关 - 介绍”&gt;📖相关资源&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io.io.io/blog/2025/06/06/11/automating-eks-ciss-compomation-eks-compliance-compliance-compliance-with--------------------------- kyverno-and-kubebench/-kubebench/#- related-related-related-related--related--related--related--related--relast------&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ATIC-Yugandhar/cis-eks-kyverno/blob/main/CIS_EKS_Benchmark_v1.7.0.md&#34;&gt;CIS EKS Benchmark v1.7.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Complete control listing (46 controls)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cisecurity.org/benchmark/amazon_web_services”&gt;官方顺式eks eks eks基准&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;：官方CIS指南&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/docs/”&gt; kyverno文档&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;：官方kyverno文档&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/aquasecurity/kube-bench”&gt; kube-bench &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;：node-level cis cis scanning &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://aws.github.io/aws-eks-best-practices/”&gt; aws eks eks最佳实践&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;：AWS安全指南&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://opentofu.org/”&gt; opentofu文档&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;：基础结构为代码&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading” id =“结论”&gt;结论&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io.io.io/blog/2025/206/11/automating-eks-cis-cis-ciss-compiance-compliance-with-kyverno-and-kyverno-and-kyverno-and-kubebench/#conclusion/#conclusion”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此实现说明了如何使用kyverno策略来自动化顺式符合性。该方法承认，不同类型的控件需要不同的验证工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;友善的测试环境提供了一种实用的方法来验证政策行为而无需云基础架构成本。每个政策都包括全面的测试覆盖范围，以验证符合和不合规情况下的预期行为。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该实施可以作为了解CIS如何控制kyverno政策以及自动合规验证中涉及的实际考虑的参考。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>