<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://cloudys-rsshub-ab061133bcab.herokuapp.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【Testing asynchronous workflows using OpenTelemetry and Istio】使用 OpenTelemetry 和 Istio 测试异步工作流程</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/09/testing-asynchronous-workflows-using-opentelemetry-and-istio/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn how to test complex asynchronous workflows in cloud native applications using OpenTelemetry for context propagation and Istio for traffic routing. Explore cost-effective approaches to isolate test environments without duplicating infrastructure.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Asynchronous architectures have become a cornerstone of modern cloud native applications, enabling services to operate independently while maintaining system resilience and scalability. These architectures typically rely on message queues and event-driven communication patterns to decouple services, allowing them to handle varying loads and failures gracefully.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Popular message systems in the cloud native ecosystem include Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, Redis Streams, Google Cloud Pub/Sub, AWS SQS, and Azure Service Bus. Each offers unique capabilities for different use cases, from high-throughput streaming to reliable message delivery. Regardless of which system you choose, testing end-to-end workflows that span multiple services and asynchronous boundaries presents unique challenges that traditional testing approaches struggle to address effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores how two CNCF projects—OpenTelemetry for distributed tracing and context propagation, and Istio for traffic management—can work together to create cost-effective, scalable testing environments for asynchronous workflows without the overhead of duplicating entire infrastructure stacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Challenges in testing asynchronous systems&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Testing asynchronous systems introduces several complex challenges not found in synchronous, request-response architectures:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environment setup complexity&lt;/strong&gt;: Asynchronous systems require multiple coordinated components—brokers, producers, consumers, and often additional infrastructure like schema registries or monitoring tools. Setting up these components correctly with proper security, replication, and partitioning requires significant expertise and time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test isolation&lt;/strong&gt;: Unlike synchronous calls where requests can be easily isolated, asynchronous messages in shared systems can interfere with each other. Ensuring that test data from one scenario doesn’t impact another requires careful coordination.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resource costs&lt;/strong&gt;: Traditional approaches often require duplicating entire message infrastructure for each test environment, leading to exponential cost growth as teams scale their testing practices.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Timing and ordering&lt;/strong&gt;: Asynchronous systems introduce timing dependencies and message ordering considerations that make tests more complex to design and more prone to flaky behavior.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environment drift&lt;/strong&gt;: Maintaining multiple isolated environments often leads to configuration drift, where test environments diverge from production, reducing test confidence.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this context, we define a &lt;em&gt;test tenant&lt;/em&gt; as an isolated testing context that needs to run test scenarios without interfering with other concurrent tests or production traffic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Three approaches to test environment isolation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are three primary approaches to achieving test isolation in asynchronous systems, each with different trade-offs in terms of cost, complexity, and isolation guarantees:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Infrastructure-level isolation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most straightforward approach is to create completely separate infrastructure for each test tenant. This means deploying independent instances of message brokers, databases, and all supporting services for every test scenario.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;220&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Infrastructure-level isolation&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149193&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol1.png 640w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol1-300x103.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol1-582x200.png 582w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advantages:&lt;/strong&gt; Complete isolation between test environments with no risk of cross-tenant interference. Tests can modify any infrastructure configuration without affecting others.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Considerations:&lt;/strong&gt; This approach becomes prohibitively expensive as the number of concurrent tests grows. Managing numerous independent environments creates significant operational overhead. Without automation, environments quickly become stale and drift from production configurations, reducing test reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Resource-level isolation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This approach shares core infrastructure (like message brokers) between tenants but creates isolated resources within that infrastructure. For example, using dedicated topics in Kafka, separate queues in RabbitMQ, or isolated namespaces in Redis for each test tenant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;302&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol2.png&#34; alt=&#34;Resource-level isolation&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149194&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol2.png 640w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol2-300x142.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol2-424x200.png 424w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advantages:&lt;/strong&gt; Significant cost savings compared to full duplication while maintaining good isolation. Shared infrastructure components reduce operational complexity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Considerations:&lt;/strong&gt; Still requires duplicating and reconfiguring all producer and consumer services for each tenant. Complex automation is needed to create and tear down resources dynamically. Configuration management becomes challenging as the number of tenants grows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Request-level isolation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most cost-effective approach establishes a shared baseline environment with all infrastructure and services running in production-like configurations. Test isolation is achieved through dynamic routing of requests and messages based on tenant context, rather than physical resource separation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this model, each test tenant has a unique identifier that gets propagated through all synchronous and asynchronous communication. Services use this identifier to determine whether they should process a given request or message. When testing specific service versions, only those services under test are deployed as separate instances—everything else uses the shared baseline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;517&#34; height=&#34;421&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3.png&#34; alt=&#34;Request-level isolation&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149195&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3.png 517w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3-300x244.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3-246x200.png 246w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3-491x400.png 491w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 517px) 100vw, 517px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advantages:&lt;/strong&gt; Minimal infrastructure duplication leads to dramatic cost savings (often 85%+ reduction). No environment drift since the baseline is continuously updated through existing CI/CD pipelines. Fastest environment creation (seconds vs. minutes/hours). Lowest operational overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Considerations:&lt;/strong&gt; Requires instrumenting services for context propagation and implementing selective message processing. May not be suitable for scenarios requiring infrastructure-level isolation or testing infrastructure changes themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The remainder of this article focuses on implementing this request-level isolation approach using OpenTelemetry and Istio.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Implementing request-level isolation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Implementing request-level isolation requires two key capabilities: propagating tenant context across service boundaries, and routing traffic based on that context. OpenTelemetry and Istio provide complementary solutions to these challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The architecture works by assigning each test tenant a unique identifier with mappings to specific service versions being tested. This tenant ID gets propagated through both synchronous (HTTP/gRPC) and asynchronous (message queue) communication paths, enabling dynamic routing decisions at every hop.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Central RouteService for tenant mapping&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A critical component in this architecture is a central RouteService that maintains the authoritative mapping of tenant IDs to specific service versions under test. This service acts as the source of truth that all consumers consult to determine whether they should process a given message.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When multiple versions of a consumer service are running (baseline and under-test versions), each instance receives all messages from the shared message queue. However, only one consumer should process each message based on the tenant context. The RouteService solves this consumer contention problem by providing a centralized decision point:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Centralized configuration:&lt;/strong&gt; All tenant-to-service mappings are stored in one place, making it easy to create, modify, and delete test scenarios without coordinating across multiple services.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consumer coordination:&lt;/strong&gt; Multiple consumer instances can safely coexist, with each consulting the RouteService to determine if they should process a message based on the tenant ID and their own service version.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dynamic updates:&lt;/strong&gt; Test scenarios can be created and destroyed without restarting consumers—they simply get updated routing information from the RouteService.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1288&#34; height=&#34;724&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Code&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149196&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM.jpg 1288w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-900x506.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-356x200.jpg 356w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-712x400.jpg 712w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1288px) 100vw, 1288px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Using OpenTelemetry for context propagation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; provides the foundation for propagating tenant context across service boundaries through its powerful context propagation capabilities. The key mechanisms are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baggage for custom context:&lt;/strong&gt; OpenTelemetry’s&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/concepts/signals/baggage/&#34;&gt; Baggage&lt;/a&gt; feature allows you to attach custom key-value pairs (like tenant IDs) to traces that automatically propagate across service calls. This works for both HTTP/gRPC requests and can be extended to asynchronous messaging systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automatic header propagation:&lt;/strong&gt; OpenTelemetry’s auto-instrumentation libraries for languages like Java, Node.js, Python, and Go automatically handle header propagation for popular frameworks, reducing the implementation burden on development teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Message queue integration:&lt;/strong&gt; OpenTelemetry provides specific guidance and libraries for propagating context through message queues. For example, when publishing messages to Kafka, producers automatically inject trace context (including baggage) into message headers. Consumers can then extract this context to make routing decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1292&#34; height=&#34;576&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Code - adding tenant ID to OTel baggage&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149197&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM.jpg 1292w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-300x134.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-1024x457.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-768x342.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-900x401.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-449x200.jpg 449w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-897x400.jpg 897w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1292px) 100vw, 1292px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the consumer side, services can extract the tenant ID from the propagated context and decide whether to process the message based on their tenant mappings:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1274&#34; height=&#34;502&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Code - Consumer side&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149202&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM.jpg 1274w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-300x118.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-1024x403.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-768x303.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-900x355.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-508x200.jpg 508w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-1015x400.jpg 1015w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1274px) 100vw, 1274px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Leveraging Istio for traffic routing&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While OpenTelemetry handles context propagation,&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/&#34;&gt; Istio&lt;/a&gt; provides sophisticated traffic routing capabilities that complement this by enabling dynamic routing of HTTP/gRPC requests based on headers, including the tenant context propagated by OpenTelemetry.&lt;strong&gt;Virtual services for header-based routing:&lt;/strong&gt; Istio Virtual Services can route requests to different service versions based on header values. This allows you to direct traffic from specific tenants to the service versions under test while sending all other traffic to the baseline services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1270&#34; height=&#34;1066&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Code - Istio VirtualService&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149201&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM.jpg 1270w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-300x252.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-1024x860.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-768x645.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-900x755.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-238x200.jpg 238w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-477x400.jpg 477w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1270px) 100vw, 1270px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Destination rules for service subsets:&lt;/strong&gt; Istio Destination Rules define the different versions of services (baseline vs. under-test) and their load balancing policies:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1270&#34; height=&#34;764&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Code - Destination Rule&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149203&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM.jpg 1270w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-300x180.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-1024x616.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-768x462.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-900x541.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-332x200.jpg 332w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-665x400.jpg 665w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1270px) 100vw, 1270px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key benefits of Istio integration:&lt;/strong&gt; Transparent routing without application code changes, sophisticated traffic shaping capabilities (weighted routing, fault injection, timeouts), and comprehensive observability of routing decisions through built-in metrics and tracing integration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Implementation considerations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While this approach offers significant benefits, there are several important considerations for successful implementation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Non-request-scoped workflows:&lt;/strong&gt; Some asynchronous workflows aren’t triggered by external requests—batch jobs, scheduled tasks, or event-driven processes that start from database changes or time-based triggers. These scenarios require alternative approaches, such as embedding tenant context in data sources or using separate scheduling mechanisms for test scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distributed cache management:&lt;/strong&gt; When services cache tenant mappings for performance, cache invalidation becomes critical. Implementing proper cache coherence mechanisms (like Redis pub/sub notifications or short TTL values) ensures that services quickly recognize new tenants or mapping changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consumer group lifecycle:&lt;/strong&gt; Message queue consumer groups require careful lifecycle management. Create unique consumer group names for test services, ensure proper offset handling (often starting from the baseline consumer’s current offset), and clean up consumer groups when tests complete to avoid resource leaks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data isolation strategies:&lt;/strong&gt; Different levels of data isolation may be needed depending on your use case. Options include tenant-prefixed keys in databases, separate database schemas, or carefully designed test data that doesn’t conflict with baseline data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observability and debugging:&lt;/strong&gt; Implement comprehensive logging and metrics around tenant routing decisions. OpenTelemetry’s distributed tracing helps track how tenant context flows through the system and identify where routing decisions are made.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security considerations:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensure tenant IDs can’t be spoofed or manipulated by unauthorized actors. Consider using signed tokens or validating tenant context against authorized test scenarios to prevent accidental or malicious cross-tenant access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Testing asynchronous workflows in cloud native applications presents unique challenges that traditional testing approaches struggle to address cost-effectively. The combination of OpenTelemetry for context propagation and Istio for traffic routing provides a powerful foundation for implementing request-level isolation that dramatically reduces infrastructure costs while maintaining high-quality testing practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The vendor-neutral nature of both OpenTelemetry and Istio makes this solution broadly applicable across different cloud providers, message systems, and application architectures. Success with this approach requires careful planning for edge cases, such as batch workflows, and proper lifecycle management of shared resources, but the benefits—reduced costs, faster feedback loops, and elimination of environment drift—make it a compelling choice for teams serious about scaling their testing practices in cloud native environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;了解如何使用 OpenTelemetry 进行上下文传播，使用 Istio 进行流量路由，在云原生应用程序中测试复杂的异步工作流程。探索经济高效的方法来隔离测试环境，而无需重复基础设施。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;简介&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;异步架构已成为现代云原生应用程序的基石，使服务能够独立运行，同时保持系统弹性和可扩展性。这些架构通常依赖消息队列和事件驱动的通信模式来解耦服务，从而使它们能够优雅地处理变化的负载和故障。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云原生生态系统中流行的消息系统包括 Apache Kafka、RabbitMQ、Redis Streams、Google Cloud Pub/Sub、AWS SQS 和 Azure Service Bus。每个都为不同的用例提供了独特的功能，从高吞吐量流到可靠的消息传递。无论您选择哪种系统，测试跨越多个服务和异步边界的端到端工作流程都会带来传统测试方法难以有效解决的独特挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了两个 CNCF 项目（用于分布式跟踪和上下文传播的 OpenTelemetry 以及用于流量管理的 Istio）如何协同工作，为异步工作流程创建经济高效、可扩展的测试环境，而无需复制整个基础设施堆栈的开销。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;测试异步系统的挑战&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;测试异步系统引入了同步请求响应架构中未发现的几个复杂挑战：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;环境设置复杂性&lt;/strong&gt;：异步系统需要多个协调组件——代理、生产者、消费者，通常还需要额外的基础设施，例如模式注册表或监控工具。通过适当的安全性、复制和分区来正确设置这些组件需要大量的专业知识和时间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;测试隔离&lt;/strong&gt;：与可以轻松隔离请求的同步调用不同，共享系统中的异步消息可能会相互干扰。确保一种场景的测试数据不会影响另一种场景需要仔细协调。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;资源成本&lt;/strong&gt;：传统方法通常需要为每个测试环境复制整个消息基础架构，导致随着团队扩展测试实践，成本呈指数级增长。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;计时和排序&lt;/strong&gt;：异步系统引入了计时依赖性和消息排序注意事项，使测试设计更加复杂，并且更容易出现不稳定的行为。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;环境漂移&lt;/strong&gt;：维护多个隔离环境通常会导致配置漂移，即测试环境与产品环境不同行动，降低测试信心。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这种情况下，我们将&lt;em&gt;测试租户&lt;/em&gt;定义为一个独立的测试上下文，需要运行测试场景而不干扰其他并发测试或生产流量。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;测试环境隔离的三种方法&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在异步系统中实现测试隔离有三种主要方法，每种方法在成本、复杂性和隔离保证方面都有不同的权衡：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.基础设施级隔离&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最直接的方法是为每个测试租户创建完全独立的基础架构。这意味着为每个测试场景部署消息代理、数据库和所有支持服务的独立实例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34;解码=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;220&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol1.png&#34; alt=&#34;基础设施级隔离&#34; class =“wp-image-149193”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol1.png 640w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol1-300x103.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol1-582x200.png 582w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：640px）100vw，640px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;优点：&lt;/strong&gt;测试环境之间完全隔离，没有跨租户干扰的风险。测试可以修改任何基础设施配置而不影响其他配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意事项：&lt;/strong&gt;随着并发测试数量的增加，这种方法的成本变得异常昂贵。管理众多独立环境会产生巨大的运营开销。如果没有自动化，环境很快就会变得陈旧并偏离生产配置，从而降低测试可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.资源级隔离&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此方法在租户之间共享核心基础设施（如消息代理），但在该基础设施内创建隔离的资源。例如，为每个测试租户使用 Kafka 中的专用主题、RabbitMQ 中的单独队列或 Redis 中的隔离命名空间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34;解码=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;302&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol2.png&#34; alt=&#34;资源级隔离&#34; 类=“wp-image-149194”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol2.png 640w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol2-300x142.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol2-424x200.png 424w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：640px）100vw，640px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;优点：&lt;/strong&gt;与完全复制相比，可显着节省成本，同时保持良好的隔离性。共享基础架构组件降低了运营复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;考虑口粮：仍然需要为每个租户复制和重新配置所有生产者和消费者服务。动态创建和拆除资源需要复杂的自动化。随着租户数量的增长，配置管理变得具有挑战性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.请求级隔离&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最具成本效益的方法是建立一个共享基线环境，所有基础设施和服务都在类似生产的配置中运行。测试隔离是通过基于租户上下文动态路由请求和消息来实现的，而不是物理资源分离。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此模型中，每个测试租户都有一个唯一的标识符，该标识符通过所有同步和异步通信进行传播。服务使用此标识符来确定它们是否应该处理给定的请求或消息。测试特定服务版本时，只有那些被测试的服务才会部署为单独的实例，其他所有服务都使用共享基线。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;517&#34;height=&#34;421&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3.png&#34;alt=&#34;请求级隔离&#34; class =“wp-image-149195”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3.png 517w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3-300x244.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3-246x200.png 246w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/isol3-491x400.png 491w&#34; 尺寸=“自动，（最大宽度：517px）100vw，517px”referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;优点：&lt;/strong&gt;最少的基础设施重复可以显着节省成本（通常减少 85% 以上）。由于基线通过现有 CI/CD 管道不断更新，因此没有环境漂移。最快的环境创建（秒与分钟/小时）。最低的运营开销。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意事项：&lt;/strong&gt;需要用于上下文传播和实现选择性消息处理的检测服务。可能不适合需要基础设施级隔离或测试基础设施变更本身的场景。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文的其余部分重点介绍使用 OpenTelemetry 和 Istio 实现这种请求级隔离方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;实现请求级隔离&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;实现请求级隔离需要两个关键功能：跨服务边界传播租户上下文，以及基于该上下文路由流量。 OpenTelemetry 和 Istio 为这些挑战提供了补充解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该架构的工作原理是为每个测试租户分配一个唯一标识符，并映射到正在测试的特定服务版本。此租户 ID 通过同步 (HTTP/gRPC) 和异步（消息队列）通信路径传播，从而在每一跳实现动态路由决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;用于租户映射的中央 RouteService&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此架构中的一个关键组件是中央 RouteService，它维护租户 ID 到正在测试的特定服务版本的权威映射。该服务充当所有消费者参考以确定是否应该处理给定消息的事实来源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当消费者服务的多个版本运行时（基准版本和测试版本），每个实例都会接收来自共享消息队列的所有消息。但是，只有一个消费者应该根据租户上下文处理每条消息。 RouteService 通过提供集中决策点解决了消费者争用问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;集中配置&lt;/strong&gt;：所有租户到服务的映射都存储在一个位置，从而可以轻松创建、修改和删除测试场景，而无需跨多个服务进行协调。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;消费者协调：&lt;/strong&gt;多个消费者实例可以安全地共存，每个实例都会咨询 RouteService 以确定它们是否应该根据租户 ID 和自己的服务版本处理消息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;动态更新：&lt;/strong&gt;无需重新启动消费者即可创建和销毁测试场景 - 它们只需从 RouteService 获取更新的路由信息​​即可。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1288”高度=“724” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;代码&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149196&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM.jpg 1288w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-300x169.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-1024x576.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-768x432.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-900x506.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-356x200.jpg 356w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.01.05-PM-712x400.jpg 712w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1288px）100vw，1288px“ referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;使用 OpenTelemetry 进行上下文传播&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; 通过其强大的上下文传播功能，为跨服务边界传播租户上下文提供了基础。关键机制是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自定义上下文的 Baggage：&lt;/strong&gt;OpenTelemetry 的&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/concepts/signals/baggage/&#34;&gt; Baggage&lt;/a&gt; 功能允许您将自定义键值对（例如租户 ID）附加到自动传播 acros 的跟踪的服务电话。这适用于 HTTP/gRPC 请求，并且可以扩展到异步消息系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自动标头传播：&lt;/strong&gt;OpenTelemetry 针对 Java、Node.js、Python 和 Go 等语言的自动检测库可自动处理流行框架的标头传播，从而减轻开发团队的实施负担。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;消息队列集成：&lt;/strong&gt;OpenTelemetry 提供了通过消息队列传播上下文的具体指南和库。例如，当向 Kafka 发布消息时，生产者会自动将跟踪上下文（包括行李）注入到消息标头中。然后，消费者可以提取此上下文来做出路由决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1292”高度=“576” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;代码 - 将租户 ID 添加到 OTel 行李&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149197&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM.jpg 1292w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-300x134.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-1024x457.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-768x342.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-900x401.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-449x200.jpg 449w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.03.00-PM-897x400.jpg 897w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1292px）100vw，1292px“ referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在消费者方面，服务可以从传播的上下文中提取租户 ID，并根据其租户映射决定是否处理消息：&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1274”高度=“502” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;代码-消费者端&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149202&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM.jpg 1274w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-300x118.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-1024x403.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-768x303.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-900x355.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-508x200.jpg 508w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.36-PM-1015x400.jpg 1015w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1274px）100vw，1274px“referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;利用 Istio 进行流量路由&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 OpenTelemetry 处理上下文传播，&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/&#34;&gt;Istio&lt;/a&gt; 提供了复杂的流量路由功能，通过基于标头（包括 OpenTelemetry 传播的租户上下文）启用 HTTP/gRPC 请求的动态路由来补充这一功能。&lt;strong&gt;基于标头路由的虚拟服务：&lt;/strong&gt; Istio 虚拟服务可以根据标头值将请求路由到不同的服务版本。这使您可以将特定租户的流量引导至正在测试的服务版本，同时将所有其他流量发送至基准服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1270”高度=“1066” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;代码 - Istio VirtualService&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149201&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM.jpg 1270w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-300x252.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-1024x860.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-768x645.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-900x755.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-238x200.jpg 238w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.09.08-PM-477x400.jpg 477w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1270px）100vw，1270px“ referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;服务子集的目标规则：&lt;/strong&gt; Istio 目标规则定义不同版本的服务（基准与测试中）及其负载平衡策略：&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1270”高度=“764” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;代码 - 目标规则&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149203&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM.jpg 1270w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-300x180.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-1024x616.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-768x462.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-900x541.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-332x200.jpg 332w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-08-at-1.11.08-PM-665x400.jpg 665w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1270px）100vw，1270px“referrerpolicy=”无-re费雷尔&#34;&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Istio 集成的主要优势：&lt;/strong&gt;无需更改应用程序代码即可实现透明路由、复杂的流量整形功能（加权路由、故障注入、超时）以及通过内置指标和跟踪集成实现路由决策的全面可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;实施注意事项&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然这种方法具有显着的优势，但成功实施有几个重要的考虑因素：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;非请求范围的工作流：&lt;/strong&gt;某些异步工作流不是由外部请求触发的 - 批处理作业、计划任务或从数据库更改或基于时间的触发器开始的事件驱动流程。这些场景需要替代方法，例如在数据源中嵌入租户上下文或针对测试场景使用单独的调度机制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;分布式缓存管理：&lt;/strong&gt;当服务缓存租户映射以提高性能时，缓存失效变得至关重要。实施适当的缓存一致性机制（例如 Redis 发布/订阅通知或短 TTL 值）可确保服务快速识别新租户或映射更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;消费者组生命周期：&lt;/strong&gt;消息队列消费者组需要仔细的生命周期管理。为测试服务创建唯一的消费者组名称，确保正确的偏移量处理（通常从基线消费者的当前偏移量开始），并在测试完成时清理消费者组以避免资源泄漏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据隔离策略：&lt;/strong&gt;根据您的使用案例，可能需要不同级别的数据隔离。选项包括数据库中的租户前缀密钥、单独的数据库架构或精心设计的不与基线数据冲突的测试数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可观察性和调试&lt;/strong&gt;：围绕租户路由决策实施全面的日志记录和指标。 OpenTelemetry 的分布式跟踪有助于跟踪租户上下文如何流经系统并确定路由决策的位置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安全注意事项&lt;/strong&gt;：确保租户 ID 不会被未经授权的行为者欺骗或操纵。考虑使用签名令牌或根据授权测试场景验证租户上下文，以防止意外或恶意的跨租户访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;结论&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在云原生应用程序中测试异步工作流程带来了传统测试方法难以经济有效地解决的独特挑战。用于上下文传播的 OpenTelemetry 和用于流量路由的 Istio 相结合，为实现请求级隔离提供了强大的基础，从而显着降低基础设施成本，同时保持高质量的测试实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry 和 Istio 的供应商中立性质使得该解决方案具有广泛的适用性跨不同的云提供商、消息系统和应用程序架构。这种方法的成功需要对边缘情况进行仔细规划，例如批处理工作流程和共享资源的适当生命周期管理，但它的好处——降低成本、更快的反馈循环和消除环境漂移——使其成为认真考虑在云原生环境中扩展测试实践的团队的一个令人信服的选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A TPM-based combined remote attestation method for confidential computing】一种基于TPM的机密计算组合远程认证方法</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/08/a-tpm-based-combined-remote-attestation-method-for-confidential-computing/</link>
      <description>【&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Problem statement&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Confidential computing technologies such as Intel TDX and AMD SNP rely on hardware-controlled Roots of Trust (RoT), inherently binding remote attestation to specific CPU vendors. While these solutions offer strong security guarantees, they also introduce challenges for enterprises seeking compliance, transparency, and independence in managing their Trusted Execution Environments (TEEs). This raises key questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How can organizations leverage TEE security features (e.g., memory encryption, attestation) without being fully dependent on vendor-controlled RoT?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is it possible to partially decouple the RoT while maintaining robust security guarantees?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Scenario&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consider a large enterprise deploying Intel TDX or AMD SNP servers, but with a requirement that the Root of Trust (RoT) be shared with a third-party authority—such as an internal certificate authority (CA) or an industry-wide trust anchor—to enable independent verification and operational flexibility. The goal is to retain the security benefits of TEEs while mitigating vendor lock-in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Representative existing approaches&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1.&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/conference/atc22/presentation/jia-yuekai&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt; HyperEnclave&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Strengths:&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fully vendor-agnostic and open-source.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Utilizes TPM for attestation, minimizing reliance on CPU vendors.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Considerations:&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Adopts an SGX-like, process-based isolation model, which, as of the time of this blog, may present compatibility challenges for integration with TDX/SNP ecosystems. (It is possible that HyperEnclave may support TDX in the future or may already have added support since the time of writing.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;May require additional adaptation efforts for existing TEE workloads to leverage its architecture.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2.&lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/confidential-computing/how-to-leverage-virtual-tpms-in-azure-confidential-vms&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Azure vTPM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Strengths:&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Facilitates partial decoupling of attestation through virtual TPMs in confidential VMs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Seamlessly integrates with mainstream confidential computing (CoCo) platforms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Considerations:&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Relies on Azure’s proprietary hypervisor and vTPM implementation, which may affect transparency and portability across different environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Our solution: Hybrid attestation with TPM and TEE integration&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We propose a unified attestation framework that combines TEE-native reports (e.g., TDX/SNP attestation) with TPM-based quotes, enabling a shared RoT between hardware and third-party authorities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1318&#34; height=&#34;878&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;unified attestation framework&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148995&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM.jpg 1318w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-300x200.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-1024x682.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-900x600.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-600x400.jpg 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1318px) 100vw, 1318px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This solution presents a hybrid root-of-trust attestation framework for confidential computing environments, integrating both hardware-based Trusted Execution Environments (TEEs) and Trusted Platform Modules (TPMs), while supporting flexible certificate authority (CA) management.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Workflow overview&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Deployment (registration) phase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The physical TPM generates an Attestation Identity Key (AIK), which is securely stored within the TPM.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The AIK private key remains protected and cannot be extracted from the TPM; only the public key is exported.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The AIK public key is submitted to a Privacy CA, which issues an AIK certificate, establishing a trust anchor for subsequent attestations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Runtime phase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Each time a new Confidential VM (CVM) is launched, the vTPM instance running within the Secure Virtual Machine Monitor (SVSM) requests a certificate for its virtual AIK (vAIK) via a custom hypercall provided by the KVM hypervisor. This request is forwarded to the physical TPM, which collaborates with the Privacy CA to issue the vAIK certificate.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The vTPM is responsible for trusted boot and integrity measurement of the CVM.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Applications running inside the CVM obtain the vTPM Attestation Report through the/dev/tpm-guestinterface provided by the guest kernel.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The guest kernel requests the vTPM to generate and return a vTPM Attestation Report for the CVM. This report is signed by the vAIK, providing cryptographic assurance of its origin and integrity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;vTPM Integration:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The virtual TPMs (vTPMs) run inside secure partitions:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;AMD SNP&lt;/em&gt;: Utilizes VMPL0 (highest privilege level) for isolation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intel TDX&lt;/em&gt;: Leverages TD partitions for secure execution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Verification phase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The verifier checks the certificate chain: CA certificate → AIK certificate → vAIK certificate → vTPM Attestation Report.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If the vTPM Attestation Report is valid and correctly signed, the verifier extracts the measurement values contained within the report.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;These measurements are compared against baseline images to confirm the integrity and expected state of the software environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Combined attestation approach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;TPM-based attestation and TEE-native attestation coexist within the architecture and do not conflict with each other.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;This joint attestation mechanism allows both TPM and TEE evidence to be collected, verified, and combined, providing enhanced security guarantees for both the hardware and software layers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The combined attestation report offers a comprehensive trust foundation, leveraging the strengths of both TPM and TEE technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The architecture supports aggregation of TEE and TPM attestation evidence into a combined attestation report, providing comprehensive trust guarantees for both hardware and software integrity. This hybrid approach enables enterprises to flexibly manage root-of-trust anchors, enhance transparency, and support independent verification by trusted third-party CAs.In addition, our solution offers significant cost advantages. The TPM hardware modules required are highly standardized, modular, and inexpensive, making our architecture both practical and economical for large-scale deployment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Implementation with Hygon CSV&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1390&#34; height=&#34;720&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Implementation with Hygon CSV&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148997&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM.jpg 1390w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-300x155.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-1024x530.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-768x398.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-900x466.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-386x200.jpg 386w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-772x400.jpg 772w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1390px) 100vw, 1390px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The current solution has been successfully developed and deployed in production on the Hygon CSV platform, where the first version is already supporting real-world applications. This implementation is based on the CoCo/trustee remote attestation framework, which provides the foundation for secure attestation and trust management. In addition, development efforts are underway to extend support to AMD SNP and Intel TDX platforms, further enhancing the versatility and coverage of this hybrid attestation architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Advantages of the combined approach&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vendor neutrality:&lt;/strong&gt; RoT is shared between TEE hardware and a third-party TPM, reducing vendor lock-in.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customizable trust architecture: &lt;/strong&gt;Provides organizations with the ability to define and manage their own TEE trust anchors and attestation mechanisms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexibility &amp;amp; scalability:&lt;/strong&gt;The architecture is highly flexible and easily extensible, supporting integration with multiple hardware platforms and evolving security needs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost-effectiveness &amp;amp; large-scale deployment:&lt;/strong&gt;By leveraging standardized and modular TPM hardware, the solution is low-cost and well-suited for economical, large-scale deployments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;问题陈述&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Intel TDX 和 AMD SNP 等机密计算技术依赖于硬件控制的信任根 (RoT)，本质上将远程认证绑定到特定的 CPU 供应商。虽然这些解决方案提供了强大的安全保证，但它们也给在管理可信执行环境 (TEE) 方面寻求合规性、透明度和独立性的企业带来了挑战。这就提出了关键问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;组织如何在不完全依赖供应商控制的 RoT 的情况下利用 TEE 安全功能（例如内存加密、证明）？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;是否可以部分解耦 RoT，同时保持强大的安全保证？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;场景&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设一家大型企业部署了 Intel TDX 或 AMD SNP 服务器，但要求与第三方机构（例如内部证书颁发机构 (CA) 或行业范围的信任锚）共享信任根 (RoT)，以实现独立验证和操作灵活性。目标是保留 TEE 的安全优势，同时减少供应商锁定。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;代表性的现有方法&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1.&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usenix.org/conference/atc22/presentation/jia-yuekai&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;超飞地&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;优势：&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;完全与供应商无关且开源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;利用 TPM 进行证明，最大限度地减少对 CPU 供应商的依赖。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意事项：&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;采用类似 SGX、基于流程的隔离模型，截至本博客发表时，该模型可能会对与 TDX/SNP 生态系统的集成带来兼容性挑战。 （HyperEnclave 将来可能支持 TDX，或者自撰写本文以来可能已经添加了支持。）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可能需要对现有 TEE 工作负载进行额外的调整才能利用其架构。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2.&lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/confidential-computing/how-to-leverage-virtual-tpms-in-azure-confidential-vms&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Azure vTPM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;优势：&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过机密虚拟机中的虚拟 TPM 促进证明的部分解耦。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;与主流机密计算 (CoCo) 平台无缝集成。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意事项：&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;依赖 Azure 专有的虚拟机管理程序和 vTPM 实施，这可能会影响不同环境之间的透明度和可移植性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;我们的解决方案：TPM 和 TEE 集成的混合证明&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们提出统一认证该框架将 TEE 原生报告（例如 TDX/SNP 证明）与基于 TPM 的报价相结合，从而在硬件和第三方权威机构之间实现共享 RoT。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1318”高度=“878” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;统一认证框架&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148995&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM.jpg 1318w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-300x200.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-1024x682.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-768x512.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-900x600.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-8.59.09-AM-600x400.jpg 600w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1318px）100vw，1318px“ referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该解决方案为机密计算环境提供了混合信任根证明框架，集成了基于硬件的可信执行环境 (TEE) 和可信平台模块 (TPM)，同时支持灵活的证书颁发机构 (CA) 管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;工作流程概述&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.部署（注册）阶段&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;物理 TPM 生成证明身份密钥 (AIK)，该密钥安全地存储在 TPM 中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;AIK 私钥仍然受到保护，无法从 TPM 中提取；仅导出公钥。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;AIK 公钥被提交给隐私 CA，该 CA 会颁发 AIK 证书，为后续证明建立信任锚。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.运行时阶段&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;每次启动新的机密虚拟机 (CVM) 时，安全虚拟机监视器 (SVSM) 中运行的 vTPM 实例都会通过 KVM 虚拟机管理程序提供的自定义超级调用为其虚拟 AIK (vAIK) 请求证书。该请求将转发到物理 TPM，该 TPM 与隐私 CA 合作颁发 vAIK 证书。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;vTPM 负责 CVM 的可信启动和完整性测量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CVM 内运行的应用程序通过来宾内核提供的 /dev/tpm-guest 接口获取 vTPM 证明报告。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;来宾内核请求 vTPM 生成并返回 CVM 的 vTPM 证明报告。该报告由 vAIK 签署，提供其来源和完整性的加密保证。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;vTPM 集成：&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;虚拟 TPM (vTPM) 在安全分区内运行：&#xA;&lt;ul 类s=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;AMD SNP&lt;/em&gt;：利用 VMPL0（最高权限级别）进行隔离。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intel TDX&lt;/em&gt;：利用 TD 分区实现安全执行。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.验证阶段&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;验证者检查证书链：CA 证书 → AIK 证书 → vAIK 证书 → vTPM 证明报告。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果 vTPM 证明报告有效且签名正确，验证者将提取报告中包含的测量值。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将这些测量结果与基线图像进行比较，以确认软件环境的完整性和预期状态。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4。组合证明方法&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;基于 TPM 的证明和 TEE 原生证明在架构中共存，并且不会相互冲突。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;这种联合证明机制可以收集、验证和组合 TPM 和 TEE 证据，为硬件和软件层提供增强的安全保证。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;综合认证报告利用 TPM 和 TEE 技术的优势，提供全面的信任基础。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该架构支持将 TEE 和 TPM 证明证据聚合为组合证明报告，为硬件和软件完整性提供全面的信任保证。这种混合方法使企业能够灵活管理信任根锚点、增强透明度并支持受信任的第三方 CA 进行独立验证。此外，我们的解决方案还具有显着的成本优势。所需的TPM硬件模块高度标准化、模块化且价格低廉，使得我们的架构对于大规模部署来说既实用又经济。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;使用 Hygon CSV 实施&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1390”高度=“720” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;使用 Hygon CSV 实现&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148997&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM.jpg 1390w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-300x155.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-1024x530.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-768x398.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-900x466.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-386x200.jpg 386w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-9.01.45-AM-772x400.jpg 772w“尺寸=”自动，（最大-width: 1390px) 100vw, 1390px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当前的解决方案已在 Hygon CSV 平台上成功开发并部署在生产中，其中第一个版本已经支持实际应用程序。该实现基于CoCo/受托人远程证明框架，该框架为安全证明和信任管理提供了基础。此外，我们正在努力扩展对 AMD SNP 和 Intel TDX 平台的支持，进一步增强这种混合认证架构的多功能性和覆盖范围。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;组合方法的优点&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;供应商中立性&lt;/strong&gt;：RoT 在 TEE 硬件和第三方 TPM 之间共享，从而减少供应商锁定。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可定制的信任架构：&lt;/strong&gt;使组织能够定义和管理自己的 TEE 信任锚和证明机制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;灵活性和可扩展性：&lt;/strong&gt;该架构高度灵活且易于扩展，支持与多个硬件平台集成并满足不断变化的安全需求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;成本效益和大规模部署：&lt;/strong&gt;通过利用标准化和模块化 TPM 硬件，该解决方案成本低廉，非常适合经济的大规模部署。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Auditing user activity in pods and nodes with the Security-Profiles-Operator】使用 Security-Profiles-Operator 审核 pod 和节点中的用户活动</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/07/auditing-user-activity-in-pods-and-nodes-with-the-security-profiles-operator/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/tasks/debug/debug-cluster/audit/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes’ native audit logs&lt;/a&gt; are essential for tracking control plane activities, but they fail to capture what happens &lt;em&gt;inside&lt;/em&gt; a container or on the host node itself during kubectl debugging sessions. This creates a security and compliance gap, as malicious or unauthorized actions within a pod or on the node go unrecorded. Without this visibility, it’s impossible to fully understand user actions, conduct an incident investigation, or meet regulatory compliance requirements. The newly added audit logging feature in &lt;strong&gt;Security-Profiles-Operator (SPO)&lt;/strong&gt; addresses this by enabling detailed, server-side logging of user activity at the node level.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s imagine a scenario: A team of engineers is responsible for maintaining an application that processes financial transactions. The application is deployed on Kubernetes, with various containers (in pods) running different workloads. When a customer reports a bug, an engineer is granted access to the pod via &lt;strong&gt;kubectl exec&lt;/strong&gt; to debug the issue (also kubectl debug node). However, during the session, they accidentally delete/modify a crucial configuration file. The application fails, leading to financial losses and business disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During a post-incident audit, the security team can see from the Kubernetes control plane logs that the engineer initiated a kubectl exec session. But the logs don’t reveal &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; commands were run inside the container. It’s an operational black box. The engineer could have accidentally deleted the file, or a malicious actor could have used their credentials to intentionally cause harm. Since client-side logging can be easily manipulated or faked, it’s not a reliable solution. This is where the audit logging feature of SPO comes in. It provides the crucial, unalterable record of actions taken inside the container, closing this critical security gap.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other scenarios include tracking the syscalls made by the containers themselves, the processes/executables invoked by container images when deployed on kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the audit logging feature in SPO works&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator&#34;&gt; Security-Profiles-Operator (SPO)&lt;/a&gt; provides a new&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator/blob/main/installation-usage.md#audit-json-log-enricher&#34;&gt; JSON audit logging feature&lt;/a&gt; that generates detailed, structured logs of user activity. Similar to how Kubernetes records its own API server audit logs, this feature generates logs in a JSON Lines format, making them easy to parse and analyze. This process provides a powerful, server-side solution for granularly logging user activity, effectively closing the node-level security gap.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1326&#34; height=&#34;860&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;closing the node-level security gap&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149026&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM.jpg 1326w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-300x195.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-1024x664.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-768x498.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-900x584.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-308x200.jpg 308w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-617x400.jpg 617w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1326px) 100vw, 1326px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SPO enables easier distribution of seccomp profiles to the Kubernetes nodes. Here the main source of information is the audit log generated by configuring seccomp profiles to log (not restrict) process creations. When an auditor configures both Kubernetes control plane and SPO audit logging, the &lt;strong&gt;json-audit-log enricher&lt;/strong&gt; container starts within the SPO DaemonSet. This container watches for logs in the host’s audit log (/var/log/audit/audit.log). For each log statement, it fetches command-line/environment information from /proc/&amp;lt;pid&amp;gt; and, optionally, from eBPF. It then filters the log based on your configuration and sends the output to either a file or standard output.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, &lt;strong&gt;kubectl exec&lt;/strong&gt; doesn’t pass user authentication (user) details into the exec session on the container, making it hard to audit user-specific actions. The audit logger in SPO addresses this with &lt;strong&gt;mutating webhooks&lt;/strong&gt; that inject the &lt;strong&gt;request UID&lt;/strong&gt; from the Kubernetes API server as an environment variable into the session. Every request to the API server including the request to start a new exec session contains a request UID. This request ID is then logged by SPO’s audit log enricher and can be used to correlate the activity with the API server’s audit logs (&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/reference/config-api/apiserver-audit.v1/#audit-k8s-io-v1-Event&#34;&gt;annotations&lt;/a&gt;), providing a complete trail of who did what.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature introduces&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator/blob/main/installation-usage.md#filtering-logs&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;advanced log filtering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; through an array of filter rules. These rules, defined on the SPOD resource, allow users to control which log statements are emitted (“Metadata”) and which are dropped (“None”). Rules are evaluated in ascending order of their &lt;strong&gt;priority&lt;/strong&gt;, and the first matching rule determines the action. A rule is a match if all specified &lt;strong&gt;matchKeys&lt;/strong&gt; are present in the log statement. If &lt;strong&gt;matchValues&lt;/strong&gt; are also provided, at least one of the values must match. This system provides granular control, ensuring only relevant security events are logged, and a default behavior of logging is applied if no rules match. When auditing user actions, the filters are configured to log only those that contain the requested UID.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each log line includes critical information about an event: Timestamp, Executable Name, Command Line Arguments, User and Group IDs, and System Calls (syscalls). This granular logging is particularly useful for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Seeing what users and automated processes are doing inside a pod.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tracking when someone uses commands like kubectl exec to run commands or scripts within a container.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Monitoring activities in debug containers where users might run various tools.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to enable it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To enable this auditing with SPO, you first install &lt;strong&gt;cert-manager &lt;/strong&gt;(optional in some environments) and the &lt;strong&gt;SPO&lt;/strong&gt; itself. Next, you configure the operator to store its logs locally on the host, external volume or output to standard output. You then enable the &lt;strong&gt;JSON Enricher&lt;/strong&gt; and specify a set of filters to only log user activity. Finally, you create a &lt;strong&gt;SeccompProfile&lt;/strong&gt; to log specific syscalls like execve and clone, and a &lt;strong&gt;ProfileBinding&lt;/strong&gt; to automatically apply this profile to pods in a target namespace.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Detailed instructions are available in the&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator/blob/main/doc/audit-logging-guide.md&#34;&gt; user guide&lt;/a&gt; and the&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator/blob/main/installation-usage.md&#34;&gt; documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Considerations while using privileged containers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When using &lt;strong&gt;kubectl debug&lt;/strong&gt; for node debugging, a privileged pod may be created for host file system access, which can introduce differences in behavior based on the container runtime. For the &lt;strong&gt;CRI-O&lt;/strong&gt; runtime, a specific feature is needed to apply a seccomp profile to a privileged container.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With CRI-O versions 1.33 and newer, a feature was introduced to “&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cri-o/cri-o/pull/9190&#34;&gt;allow seccomp profiles for privileged containers&lt;/a&gt;.” This allows you to apply the secomp profile we created to the cri-o configuration. The key is to configure the CRI-O runtime to use the profile by passing an additional flag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To do this, you must add the flag &lt;strong&gt;–privileged-seccomp-profile &lt;/strong&gt;to the CRI-O runtime configuration. This step ensures that even privileged debugging pods are subject to the secomp profile’s logging, maintaining complete audit coverage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance considerations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s important to acknowledge the performance implications of using seccomp profiles for extensive logging. The SPO is designed to minimize this impact by primarily logging only process creations and handling them asynchronously. This approach helps prevent logging from becoming a bottleneck on your nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The feature uses eBPF as a supplemental data source. While it’s possible for eBPF to be used as a primary data source for this type of logging, that functionality isn’t currently a configurable feature within the operator. For most use cases, the default asynchronous, process-creation-focused logging approach provides an excellent balance between security visibility and cluster performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By leveraging the &lt;strong&gt;Security-Profiles-Operator&lt;/strong&gt;, you can overcome the limitations of standard Kubernetes audit logs and gain complete visibility into user actions within your pods and on the host nodes. This solution is a powerful and necessary tool for any organization that requires comprehensive security monitoring, threat detection, and compliance for its containerized environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/tasks/debug/debug-cluster/audit/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 的本机审核日志&lt;/a&gt;对于跟踪控制平面活动至关重要，但它们无法捕获 kubectl 调试会话期间容器内部或主机节点本身发生的情况。这会造成安全性和合规性差距，因为 Pod 内或节点上的恶意或未经授权的操作不会被记录。如果没有这种可见性，就不可能完全了解用户操作、进行事件调查或满足法规遵从性要求。 &lt;strong&gt;Security-Profiles-Operator (SPO)&lt;/strong&gt; 中新添加的审核日志记录功能通过在节点级别启用详细的服务器端用户活动日志记录来解决此问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们想象一个场景：一个工程师团队负责维护一个处理金融交易的应用程序。该应用程序部署在 Kubernetes 上，各种容器（在 Pod 中）运行不同的工作负载。当客户报告错误时，工程师将被授予通过 kubectl exec 访问 pod 的权限来调试问题（也是 kubectl 调试节点）。然而，在会话期间，他们不小心删除/修改了一个关键的配置文件。应用程序失败，导致财务损失和业务中断。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在事件后审核期间，安全团队可以从 Kubernetes 控制平面日志中看到工程师启动了 kubectl exec 会话。但日志并没有透露容器内运行的命令。这是一个可操作的黑匣子。工程师可能意外删除了该文件，或者恶意行为者可能使用其凭据故意造成伤害。由于客户端日志记录很容易被操纵或伪造，因此它不是一个可靠的解决方案。这就是 SPO 的审核日志记录功能的用武之地。它提供了容器内所采取操作的关键且不可更改的记录，从而弥补了这一关键的安全漏洞。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其他场景包括跟踪容器本身进行的系统调用、部署在 kubernetes 上时由容器映像调用的进程/可执行文件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPO 中的审核日志记录功能如何工作&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator&#34;&gt;Security-Profiles-Operator (SPO)&lt;/a&gt; 提供了新的&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator/blob/main/installation-usage.md#audit-json-log-enricher&#34;&gt; JSON 审核日志记录功能&lt;/a&gt;，可生成用户活动的详细结构化日志。与 Kubernetes 记录自己的 API 服务器审核日志的方式类似，此功能以 JSON Lines 格式生成日志，使其易于解析和分析。此过程提供了强大的服务器端解决方案，用于精细记录用户活动，有效缩小节点级安全漏洞。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; 装饰ding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1326&#34; height=&#34;860&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;缩小节点级安全漏洞&#34; 类=“wp-image-149026”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM.jpg 1326w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-300x195.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-1024x664.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-768x498.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-900x584.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-308x200.jpg 308w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-07-at-10.18.59-AM-617x400.jpg 617w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1326px）100vw，1326px“ referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SPO 可以更轻松地将 seccomp 配置文件分发到 Kubernetes 节点。这里的主要信息来源是通过配置 seccomp 配置文件来记录（而不是限制）进程创建而生成的审核日志。当审核员配置 Kubernetes 控制平面和 SPO 审核日志记录时，&lt;strong&gt;json-audit-log richer&lt;/strong&gt; 容器会在 SPO DaemonSet 中启动。此容器监视主机审核日志 (/var/log/audit/audit.log) 中的日志。对于每个日志语句，它从 /proc/&lt;pid&gt; 以及（可选）eBPF 中获取命令行/环境信息。然后，它根据您的配置过滤日志，并将输出发送到文件或标准输出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认情况下，&lt;strong&gt;kubectl exec&lt;/strong&gt; 不会将用户身份验证（用户）详细信息传递到容器上的 exec 会话中，这使得审核特定于用户的操作变得困难。 SPO 中的审核记录器通过&lt;strong&gt;变异 Webhook&lt;/strong&gt; 解决了这个问题，这些 Webhook 将来自 Kubernetes API 服务器的&lt;strong&gt;请求 UID&lt;/strong&gt; 作为环境变量注入到会话中。对 API 服务器的每个请求（包括启动新执行会话的请求）都包含一个请求 UID。然后，SPO 的审核日志丰富器会记录此请求 ID，并可用于将活动与 API 服务器的审核日志（&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/reference/config-api/apiserver-audit.v1/#audit-k8s-io-v1-Event&#34;&gt;注释&lt;/a&gt;）关联起来，从而提供完整的跟踪 谁做了什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能通过一系列过滤规则引入了&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator/blob/main/installation-usage.md#filtering-logs&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高级日志过滤&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。这些在 SPOD 资源上定义的规则允许用户控制发出哪些日志语句（“元数据”）和删除哪些日志语句（“无”）。规则按其&lt;strong&gt;优先级&lt;/strong&gt;的升序进行评估，第一个匹配的规则确定是行动。如果日志语句中存在所有指定的 &lt;strong&gt;ma​​tchKey&lt;/strong&gt;，则规则是匹配的。如果还提供了 &lt;strong&gt;ma​​tchValues&lt;/strong&gt;，则至少有一个值必须匹配。该系统提供精细控制，确保仅记录相关的安全事件，并且如果没有规则匹配，则应用默认的日志记录行为。审核用户操作时，过滤器配置为仅记录包含所请求的 UID 的操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个日志行都包含有关事件的关键信息：时间戳、可执行文件名称、命令行参数、用户和组 ID 以及系统调用 (syscall)。这种精细的日志记录对于以下方面特别有用：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;查看用户和自动化流程在 Pod 内执行的操作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;跟踪某人何时使用 kubectl exec 等命令在容器内运行命令或脚本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;监控调试容器中用户可能运行各种工具的活动。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;如何启用&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要使用 SPO 启用此审核，您首先要安装 &lt;strong&gt;cert-manager &lt;/strong&gt;（在某些环境中可选）和 &lt;strong&gt;SPO&lt;/strong&gt; 本身。接下来，您将操作员配置为将其日志本地存储在主机、外部卷或输出到标准输出上。然后，您启用 &lt;strong&gt;JSON Enricher&lt;/strong&gt; 并指定一组过滤器以仅记录用户活动。最后，您创建一个 &lt;strong&gt;SeccompProfile&lt;/strong&gt; 来记录特定的系统调用（例如 execve 和 clone），并创建一个 &lt;strong&gt;ProfileBinding&lt;/strong&gt; 来自动将此配置文件应用到目标命名空间中的 Pod。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;详细说明请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator/blob/main/doc/audit-logging-guide.md&#34;&gt;用户指南&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/security-profiles-operator/blob/main/installation-usage.md&#34;&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用特权容器时的注意事项&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用&lt;strong&gt;kubectl debug&lt;/strong&gt;进行节点调试时，可能会创建一个特权 Pod 来访问主机文件系统，这可能会根据容器运行时引入行为差异。对于 &lt;strong&gt;CRI-O&lt;/strong&gt; 运行时，需要特定功能才能将 seccomp 配置文件应用到特权容器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 CRI-O 1.33 及更高版本中，引入了一项功能“&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cri-o/cri-o/pull/9190&#34;&gt;允许特权容器使用 seccomp 配置文件&lt;/a&gt;”。这允许您将我们创建的 secomp 配置文件应用到 cri-o 配置。关键是通过传递附加标志来配置 CRI-O 运行时以使用配置文件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为此，您必须将标志&lt;strong&gt;–privileged-seccomp-profile &lt;/strong&gt;添加到 CRI-O 运行时配置中。此步骤确保即使是特权调试 Pod 也受到 secomp 配置文件的日志记录的约束，main获得完整的审计覆盖范围。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;性能注意事项&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;认识到使用 seccomp 配置文件进行大量日志记录的性能影响非常重要。 SPO 旨在通过主要仅记录流程创建并异步处理它们来最大程度地减少这种影响。这种方法有助于防止日志记录成为节点上的瓶颈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该功能使用 eBPF 作为补充数据源。虽然 eBPF 可以用作此类日志记录的主要数据源，但该功能目前不是操作员内的可配置功能。对于大多数用例，默认的异步、以流程创建为中心的日志记录方法在安全可见性和集群性能之间提供了良好的平衡。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;结论&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过利用&lt;strong&gt;Security-Profiles-Operator&lt;/strong&gt;，您可以克服标准 Kubernetes 审核日志的限制，并全面了解 Pod 内和主机节点上的用户操作。对于任何需要对其容器化环境进行全面安全监控、威胁检测和合规性的组织来说，该解决方案都是一个强大且必要的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Managing Kubernetes Workloads Using the App of Apps Pattern in ArgoCD-2】使用 ArgoCD-2 中的 App of Apps 模式管理 Kubernetes 工作负载</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/07/managing-kubernetes-workloads-using-the-app-of-apps-pattern-in-argocd-2/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Managing a cloud native infrastructure at scale is no longer just about deploying single applications – it’s about organizing environments, defining clear boundaries and keeping everything version-controlled, consistent, automated and easily managed within a simple and clear lifecycle process. This is where GitOps practices – tools like&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;ArgoCD –&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;truly shine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of ArgoCD’s most powerful patterns is called&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;App of Apps&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;– a design where a&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;single parent ArgoCD Application&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;manages and deploys multiple&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;child ArgoCD Applications&lt;/em&gt;. It brings order to potentially chaotic deployments, improves observability and aligns perfectly with GitOps methodologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll explore the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;App of Apps&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;pattern in ArgoCD, including its concept, structure, pros and cons, as well as a production-grade way to configure child applications via dedicated&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;values files&lt;/strong&gt;. You’ll learn how to build a reusable, scalable pattern by deploying two example applications:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NGINX Ingress Controller&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cert-Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is the App of Apps Pattern in ArgoCD?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;text-decoration: underline;&#34;&gt;Concept&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;App of Apps&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;pattern is an ArgoCD deployment strategy where one central ArgoCD&amp;nbsp;Application&amp;nbsp;(the “parent”) is responsible for managing and deploying several other&amp;nbsp;Applications&amp;nbsp;(the “children”). Each child application corresponds to a logical unit (e.g., a microservice, controller, or platform component) and is fully managed by ArgoCD.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This enables a modular, hierarchical structure – especially useful in environments where infrastructure is composed of many separate but related components.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;647&#34; height=&#34;412&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Hierarchical applications graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149098&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3.jpg 647w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3-300x191.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3-314x200.jpg 314w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3-628x400.jpg 628w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 647px) 100vw, 647px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-World Analogy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Think of the parent app as a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;conductor of an orchestra&lt;/strong&gt;. Each instrument (child app) has its own sheet music (Helm chart or manifest) but plays in harmony through coordination by the conductor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suitability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Great for modular test setups&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Staging/UAT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Ideal for environment replication and control&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Production&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ Yes — with clearly defined sync policies, health checks and RBAC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Modular Management&lt;/strong&gt;: Each application is independently versioned and controlled.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Reusability&lt;/strong&gt;: Easily clone environments by reapplying the App of Apps.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Central Visibility&lt;/strong&gt;: One view to manage all applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;GitOps-Driven&lt;/strong&gt;: Every change is tracked via Git, allowing for auditability and rollback.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drawbacks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;⚠️&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Complexity Overhead&lt;/strong&gt;: Initial learning curve and additional manifests.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;⚠️&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Drift Risks&lt;/strong&gt;: Improper sync policies may result in applications going out of sync.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;⚠️&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Too Many Levels&lt;/strong&gt;: Avoid deeply nested Apps of Apps, which can lead to confusion and debugging difficulty.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before proceeding, ensure you have the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A running Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ArgoCD installed and configured in your cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;kubectl&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;helm&amp;nbsp;installed on your local machine.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A Git repository to store your ArgoCD application manifests.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1: Create Directory Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s build a structure where we have a main app of apps YAML definition. I store it only as a reference as I will create that main app manually in ArgoCD. Each child application uses a dedicated Helm Chart with&amp;nbsp;values.yaml&amp;nbsp;file for configuration. Apps folder will keep all my applications defined as separate applications in ArgoCD. For reference you can refer to my repository URL:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps.git&#34;&gt;https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps.git&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1526&#34; height=&#34;816&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Indented code example&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149092&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2.jpg 1526w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-300x160.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-1024x548.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-768x411.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-900x481.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-374x200.jpg 374w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-748x400.jpg 748w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1526px) 100vw, 1526px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Define Child Applications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you have created the structure,&amp;nbsp; you need to create the manifests for the child applications. Each&amp;nbsp;Application&amp;nbsp;points to the Helm chart in our Git repo. In my case, as mentioned above, I will create NGINX Ingress as well as Cert-Manager applications. Here you have both files:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: argoproj.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: Application&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: nginx-ingress&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: argocd&#xA;spec:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;project: default&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;source:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;repoURL: https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;targetRevision: HEAD&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;path: charts/nginx-ingress&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;helm:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;valueFiles:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- values.yaml&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;destination:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;server: https://kubernetes.default.svc&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: ingress-nginx&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;syncPolicy:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;automated:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;prune: true&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;selfHeal: true&#xA;apiVersion: argoproj.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: Application&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: cert-manager&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: argocd&#xA;spec:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;project: default&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;source:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;repoURL: https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;targetRevision: HEAD&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;path: charts/cert-manager&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;helm:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;valueFiles:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- values.yaml&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;destination:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;server: https://kubernetes.default.svc&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: cert-manager&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;syncPolicy:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;automated:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;prune: true&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;selfHeal: true&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3: Define the Parent App (App of Apps)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s create the main app now. Login to ArgoCD and click on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Create Application&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;button. Next, click on&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Edit as YAML&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on the right hand site and paste a main app with the following content:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: argoproj.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: Application&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: app-of-apps&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: argocd&#xA;spec:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;project: default&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;source:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;repoURL: https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;targetRevision: HEAD&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;path: apps&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;destination:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;server: https://kubernetes.default.svc&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: argocd&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;syncPolicy:&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;automated: null&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and then&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on top to create the main application.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you have done that, you should have a similar state as the one presented in the picture below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;300&#34; height=&#34;261&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;App-of-Apps Graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149101&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-4.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-4-230x200.jpg 230w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is ok to have “OutOfSync” status as we intentionally chosen Manual sync policy in the definition. This&amp;nbsp; is a safe option and gives you full control of everything is deployed or updated in the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Click on this item and navigate inside the apps. You will see the definitions of the two applications that are missing. This is exactly the mirror of our apps directory. Two applications that are missing from our cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;415&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dashboard graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149103&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-300x122.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-900x365.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-493x200.jpg 493w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-987x400.jpg 987w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Sync&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;button and then select all out-of-sync applications and finally click&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Synchronize&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;390&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Dashboard graphic after clicking Synchronize&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149105&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6-300x114.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6-768x293.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6-900x343.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6-525x200.jpg 525w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The missing applications should start a creation process. In a few seconds you should see that the applications are synced and two additional items have been created.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;444&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Healthy dashboard graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149106&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-300x130.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-768x333.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-900x390.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-461x200.jpg 461w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-923x400.jpg 923w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;402&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image of application dashboard&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148993&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-300x118.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-768x302.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-900x353.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-509x200.jpg 509w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-1019x400.jpg 1019w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4: Verify the Deployment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just to double check all is set and deployed fine, login to your Kubernetes cluster and validate all applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;$ kubectl get all -n ingress-nginx&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;$ kubectl get all -n cert-manager&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;758&#34; height=&#34;195&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture7.png&#34; alt=&#34;Student Ubuntu code graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149109&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture7.png 758w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture7-300x77.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture7-600x154.png 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;758&#34; height=&#34;250&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture8.png&#34; alt=&#34;Student Ubuntu code graphic example&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149111&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture8.png 758w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture8-300x99.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture8-600x198.png 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 758px) 100vw, 758px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All looks good, the application’s pods are running and the final check is done.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;App of Apps&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;pattern in ArgoCD is a production-ready, scalable and modular approach to managing multi-component Kubernetes environments. By structuring your deployments this way and using dedicated&amp;nbsp;values.yaml&amp;nbsp;files, you gain flexibility, reusability and clarity across environments. You can monitor any changes in YAML files that are stored in Git and track all changes made into them. It’s an ideal solution for platform teams, GitOps advocates and anyone managing more than one service in Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大规模管理云原生基础设施不再只是部署单个应用程序，而是组织环境、定义清晰的边界，并在简单而清晰的生命周期流程中保持所有内容的版本控制、一致、自动化和轻松管理。这就是 GitOps 实践（例如 &lt;strong&gt;ArgoCD&lt;/strong&gt;）真正发挥作用的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ArgoCD 最强大的模式之一称为&lt;strong&gt;App of Apps&lt;/strong&gt;，这是一种单父 ArgoCD 应用程序管理和部署多个子 ArgoCD 应用程序的设计。它为潜在混乱的部署带来了秩序，提高了可观察性并与 GitOps 方法完美契合。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨 ArgoCD 中的&lt;strong&gt;应用的应用&lt;/strong&gt;模式，包括其概念、结构、优缺点，以及通过专用&lt;strong&gt;值文件&lt;/strong&gt;配置子应用程序的生产级方法。您将通过部署两个示例应用程序来学习如何构建可重用、可扩展的模式：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NGINX 入口控制器&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;证书管理器&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们深入了解一下。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ArgoCD中的App of Apps模式是什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;text-decoration: underline;&#34;&gt;概念&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;应用中的应用&lt;/strong&gt;模式是一种 ArgoCD 部署策略，其中一个中央 ArgoCD 应用程序（“父应用程序”）负责管理和部署多个其他应用程序（“子应用程序”）。每个子应用程序对应一个逻辑单元（例如微服务、控制器或平台组件），并由 ArgoCD 完全管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这实现了模块化、分层结构——在基础设施由许多独立但相关的组件组成的环境中特别有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“647”height =“412”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3.jpg”alt =“分层应用程序图形” 类=“wp-image-149098”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3.jpg 647w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3-300x191.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3-314x200.jpg 314w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-3-628x400.jpg 628w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：647px）100vw，647px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;现实世界的类比&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将父应用视为&lt;strong&gt;管弦乐队的指挥&lt;/strong&gt;。每个乐器（子应用程序）都有自己的乐谱（Helm 图表或清单），但通过指挥的协调可以和谐地演奏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;适用性&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;开发&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅非常适合模块化测试设置&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;登台/UAT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅非常适合环境复制 和控制&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;生产&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✅ 是的 - 具有明确定义的同步策略、运行状况检查和 RBAC&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;好处&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅&lt;strong&gt;模块化管理&lt;/strong&gt;：每个应用程序都独立进行版本控制和控制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅&lt;strong&gt;可重用性&lt;/strong&gt;：通过重新应用应用中的应用轻松克隆环境。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅&lt;strong&gt;集中可见性&lt;/strong&gt;：一个视图即可管理所有应用程序。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅&lt;strong&gt;GitOps 驱动&lt;/strong&gt;：每个更改都通过 Git 进行跟踪，从而实现审核和回滚。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;缺点&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;⚠️ &lt;strong&gt;复杂性开销&lt;/strong&gt;：初始学习曲线和其他清单。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;⚠️ &lt;strong&gt;偏差风险&lt;/strong&gt;：不正确的同步策略可能会导致应用程序不同步。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;⚠️ &lt;strong&gt;级别太多&lt;/strong&gt;：避免应用程序的深层嵌套，这可能会导致混乱和调试困难。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;先决条件&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在继续之前，请确保您具备以下条件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;正在运行的 Kubernetes 集群。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在您的集群中安装并配置了 ArgoCD。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;kubectl 和 helm 安装在您的本地计算机上。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;用于存储 ArgoCD 应用程序清单的 Git 存储库。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 1 步：创建目录结构&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们构建一个结构，其中有应用程序 YAML 定义的主应用程序。我仅将其存储作为参考，因为我将在 ArgoCD 中手动创建该主应用程序。每个子应用程序都使用专用的 Helm Chart 和 value.yaml 文件进行配置。 Apps 文件夹将保留我在 ArgoCD 中定义为单独应用程序的所有应用程序。作为参考，您可以参考我的存储库网址：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps.git&#34;&gt;https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps.git&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“1526”height =“816”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2.jpg”alt =“缩进代码示例” 类=“wp-image-149092”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2.jpg 1526w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-300x160.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-1024x548.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-768x411.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-900x481.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/up加载/2025/10/image-3-2-374x200.jpg 374w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-2-748x400.jpg 748w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1526px）100vw，1526px“ referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 2 步：定义子应用程序&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建结构后，您需要为子应用创建清单。每个应用程序都指向我们的 Git 存储库中的 Helm 图表。就我而言，如上所述，我将创建 NGINX Ingress 以及 Cert-Manager 应用程序。这里有两个文件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：argoproj.io/v1alpha1&#xA;种类： 应用&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：nginx-ingress&#xA;  命名空间：argocd&#xA;规格：&#xA;  项目：默认&#xA;  来源：&#xA;    仓库地址：https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps&#xA;    目标修订版：HEAD&#xA;    路径：charts/nginx-ingress&#xA;    舵：&#xA;      值文件：&#xA;        - 值.yaml&#xA;  目的地：&#xA;    服务器：https://kubernetes.default.svc&#xA;    命名空间：ingress-nginx&#xA;  同步策略：&#xA;    自动化：&#xA;      修剪：真实&#xA;      自我修复：正确&#xA;api版本：argoproj.io/v1alpha1&#xA;种类： 应用&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  姓名： 证书经理&#xA;  命名空间：argocd&#xA;规格：&#xA;  项目：默认&#xA;  来源：&#xA;    仓库地址：https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps&#xA;    目标修订版：HEAD&#xA;    路径：图表/证书管理器&#xA;    舵：&#xA;      值文件：&#xA;        - 值.yaml&#xA;  目的地：&#xA;    服务器：https://kubernetes.default.svc&#xA;    命名空间：证书管理器&#xA;  同步策略：&#xA;    自动化：&#xA;      修剪：真实&#xA;      selfHeal：true&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 3 步：定义父应用（应用中的应用）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在让我们创建主应用程序。登录 ArgoCD 并点击&lt;strong&gt;创建应用程序&lt;/strong&gt;按钮。接下来，点击右侧网站上的&lt;strong&gt;编辑为 YAML&lt;/strong&gt;，并粘贴包含以下内容的主应用：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：argoproj.io/v1alpha1&#xA;种类： 应用&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：应用程序中的应用程序&#xA;  命名空间：argocd&#xA;规格：&#xA;  项目：默认&#xA;  来源：&#xA;    仓库地址：https://github.com/mariano-italiano/argocd-apps&#xA;    目标修订版：HEAD&#xA;    路径：应用程序&#xA;  目的地：&#xA;    服务器：https://kubernetes.default.svc&#xA;    命名空间：argocd&#xA;  同步策略：&#xA;    自动：空&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;点击&lt;strong&gt;保存&lt;/strong&gt;，然后点击顶部的&lt;strong&gt;创建&lt;/strong&gt;来创建主应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成此操作后，您应该具有与下图所示类似的状态。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“300”height =“261”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-4.jpg”alt =“App-of-Apps Graphic” class =“wp-image-149101”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-4.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-4-230x200.jpg 230w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：300px）100vw，300px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;出现“OutOfSync”状态是可以的，因为我们在定义中特意选择了手动同步策略。这是一个安全的选项，让您可以完全控制集群中部署或更新的所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;单击此项目并在应用程序内导航。您将看到缺少的两个应用程序的定义。这正是我们的应用程序目录的镜像。我们的集群中缺少两个应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“1024”height =“415”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5.jpg”alt =“仪表板图形” 类=“wp-image-149103”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-300x122.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-768x311.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-900x365.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-493x200.jpg 493w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-5-987x400.jpg 987w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1024像素）100vw，1024像素“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;点击&lt;strong&gt;同步&lt;/strong&gt;按钮，然后选择所有不同步的应用程序，最后点击&lt;strong&gt;同步&lt;/strong&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;390&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;点击后的仪表板图形 同步&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149105&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6-300x114.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6-768x293.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6-900x343.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-6-525x200.jpg 525w&#34; 尺寸=“自动，（最大宽度：1024px）100vw，1024px”referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;丢失的应用程序应该启动创建过程。几秒钟后你应该看到应用程序已同步并且已创建两个附加项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“1024”height =“444”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7.jpg”alt =“健康仪表板图形” 类=“wp-image-149106”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-300x130.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-768x333.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-900x390.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-461x200.jpg 461w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-7-923x400.jpg 923w&#34;sizes=&#34;auto,(最大宽度:1024px)100vw,1024px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;1024&#34;height=&#34;402&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;应用程序仪表板的图像&#34; class =“wp-image-148993”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2.jpg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-300x118.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-768x302.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-900x353.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-509x200.jpg 509w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-1019x400.jpg 1019w“尺寸=”自动， （最大宽度：1024px）100vw，1024px“referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 4 步：验证部署&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了仔细检查所有设置和部署是否正常，请登录到您的 Kubernetes 集群并验证所有应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;$ kubectl 获取所有 -n ingress-nginx&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;$ kubectl 获取所有 -n 证书管理器&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“758”height =“195”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture7.png”alt =“学生Ubuntu代码图形” 类=“wp-image-149109”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture7.png 758w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture7-300x77.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture7-600x154.png 600w“尺寸=”自动， （最大宽度：758px）100vw，758px“referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;758&#34; height=&#34;250&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture8.png&#34; alt=&#34;学生 Ubuntu 代码图形示例&#34; class =“wp-image-149111”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture8.png 758w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture8-300x99.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Picture8-600x198.png 600w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：758px）100vw，758px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一切看起来都不错，应用程序on 的 Pod 正在运行，最终检查已完成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;结论&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ArgoCD 中的&lt;strong&gt;应用中的应用&lt;/strong&gt;模式是一种用于管理多组件 Kubernetes 环境的生产就绪型、可扩展且模块化的方法。通过以这种方式构建部署并使用专用的 value.yaml 文件，您可以跨环境获得灵活性、可重用性和清晰度。您可以监视存储在 Git 中的 YAML 文件中的任何更改，并跟踪对这些文件所做的所有更改。对于平台团队、GitOps 倡导者以及在 Kubernetes 中管理多个服务的任何人来说，这是一种理想的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Karmada v1.15 Released! Enhanced Resource Awareness for Multi-Template Workloads】Karmada v1.15 发布！增强多模板工作负载的资源感知</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/07/karmada-v1-15-released-enhanced-resource-awareness-for-multi-template-workloads/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Karmada is an open multi-cloud and multi-cluster container orchestration engine designed to help users deploy and operate business applications in a multi-cloud environment. With its compatibility with the native Kubernetes API, &lt;a href=&#34;https://karmada.io/&#34;&gt;Karmada&lt;/a&gt; can smoothly migrate single-cluster workloads while still maintaining coordination with the surrounding Kubernetes ecosystem tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1600&#34; height=&#34;752&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Karmada release enhancements graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149039&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1.jpg 1600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-300x141.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-1024x481.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-768x361.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-900x423.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-426x200.jpg 426w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-851x400.jpg 851w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/releases/tag/v1.15.0&#34;&gt;Karmada v1.15&lt;/a&gt; has been released, this version includes the following new features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Precise resource awareness for multi-template workloads&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced cluster-level failover functionality&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Structured logging&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Significant performance improvements for Karmada controllers and schedulers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of New Features&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Precise Resource Awareness for Multi-Template Workloads&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Karmada utilizes a resource interpreter to retrieve the replica count and resource requests of workloads. Based on this data, it calculates the total resource requirements of the workloads, thereby enabling advanced capabilities such as resource-aware scheduling and federated quota management. This mechanism works well for traditional single-template workloads. However, many AI and big data application workloads (e.g., FlinkDeployments, PyTorchJobs, and RayJobs) consist of multiple Pod templates or components, each with unique resource demands. Since the resource interpreter can only process resource requests from a single template and fails to accurately reflect differences between multiple templates, the resource calculation for multi-template workloads is not precise enough.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this version, Karmada has strengthened its resource awareness for multi-template workloads. By extending the resource interpreter, Karmada can now obtain the replica count and resource requests of different templates within the same workload, ensuring data accuracy. This improvement also provides more reliable and granular data support for federated quota management of multi-template workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Suppose you deploy a FlinkDeployment with the following resource-related configuration:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;spec:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;jobManager:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;replicas: 1&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resource:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: 1&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: 1024m&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;taskManager:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;replicas: 1&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resource:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: 2&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: 2048m&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through ResourceBinding, you can view the replica count and resource requests of each template in the FlinkDeployment parsed by the resource interpreter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;spec:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;components:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;– name: jobmanager&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;replicaRequirements:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resourceRequest:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: “1”&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: “1.024”&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;replicas: 1&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;– name: taskmanager&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;replicaRequirements:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resourceRequest:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: “2”&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: “2.048”&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;replicas: 1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At this point, the resource usage of the FlinkDeployment calculated by FederatedResourceQuota is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;status:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;overallUsed:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: “3”&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: 3072m&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: &lt;/strong&gt;This feature is currently in the Alpha stage and requires enabling the MultiplePodTemplatesScheduling feature gate to use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As multi-template workloads are widely adopted in cloud-native environments, Karmada is committed to providing stronger support for them. In upcoming versions, we will further enhance scheduling support for multi-template workloads based on this feature and offer more granular resource-aware scheduling—stay tuned for more updates!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information about this feature, please refer to: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/tree/master/docs/proposals/scheduling/multi-podtemplate-support&#34;&gt;Multi-Pod Template Support&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced Cluster-Level Failover Functionality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In previous versions, Karmada provided basic cluster-level failover capabilities, allowing cluster-level application migration to be triggered through custom failure conditions. To meet the requirement of preserving the running state of stateful applications during cluster failover, Karmada v1.15 supports an application state preservation policy for cluster failover. For big data processing applications (e.g., Flink), this capability enables restarting from the pre-failure checkpoint and seamlessly resuming data processing to the state before the restart, thus avoiding duplicate data processing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The community has introduced a new StatePreservation field under .spec.failover.cluster in the PropagationPolicy/ClusterPropagationPolicy API. This field is used to define policies for preserving and restoring state data of stateful applications during failover. Combined with this policy, when an application is migrated from a failed cluster to another cluster, key data can be extracted from the original resource configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The state preservation policy StatePreservation includes a series of StatePreservationRule configurations. It uses JSONPath to specify the segments of state data that need to be preserved and leverages the associated AliasLabelName to pass the data to the migrated cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taking a Flink application as an example: in a Flink application, jobID is a unique identifier used to distinguish and manage different Flink jobs. When a cluster fails, the Flink application can use jobID to restore the state of the job before the failure and continue execution from the failure point. The specific configuration and steps are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;apiVersion: policy.karmada.io/v1alpha1&lt;br&gt;kind: PropagationPolicy&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; name: foo&lt;br&gt;spec:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; #…&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; failover:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; cluster:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; purgeMode: Directly&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; statePreservation:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; rules:&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; – aliasLabelName: application.karmada.io/cluster-failover-jobid&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; jsonPath: “{ .jobStatus.jobID }”&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Before migration, the Karmada controller extracts the job ID according to the path configured by the user.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;During migration, the Karmada controller injects the extracted job ID into the Flink application configuration in the form of a label, such as application.karmada.io/cluster-failover-jobid: &amp;lt;jobID&amp;gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kyverno running in the member cluster intercepts the Flink application creation request, obtains the checkpoint data storage path of the job based on the jobID (e.g., /&amp;lt;shared-path&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;job-namespace&amp;gt;/&amp;lt;jobId&amp;gt;/checkpoints/xxx), and then configures initialSavepointPath to indicate starting from the savepoint.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Flink application starts based on the checkpoint data under initialSavepointPath, thereby inheriting the final state saved before migration.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This capability is widely applicable to stateful applications that can start from a specific savepoint. These applications can follow the above process to implement state persistence and restoration for cluster-level failover.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: This feature is currently in the Alpha stage and requires enabling the StatefulFailoverInjection feature gate to use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Function Constraints&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The application must be restricted to run in a single cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The migration cleanup policy (PurgeMode) is limited to Directly—this means ensuring that the failed application is deleted from the old cluster before being restored in the new cluster to guarantee data consistency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Structured Logging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logs are critical tools for recording events, states, and behaviors during system operation, and are widely used for troubleshooting, performance monitoring, and security auditing. Karmada components provide rich runtime logs to help users quickly locate issues and trace execution scenarios. In previous versions, Karmada only supported unstructured text logs, which were difficult to parse and query efficiently, limiting its integration capabilities in modern observability systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Karmada v1.15 introduces support for structured logging, which can be configured to output in JSON format using the –logging-format=json startup flag. An example of structured logging is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;{&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;“ts”:“日志时间戳”,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;“logger”:”cluster_status_controller”,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;“level”: “info”,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;“msg”:”Syncing cluster status”,&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;“clusterName”:”member1″}&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The introduction of structured logging significantly improves the usability and observability of logs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Efficient Integration&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp; Integration with mainstream logging systems such as Elastic, Loki, and Splunk, without relying on complex regular expressions or log parsers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Efficient Query&lt;/strong&gt;: Structured fields support fast retrieval and analysis, significantly improving troubleshooting efficiency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced Observability&lt;/strong&gt;: Key context information (e.g., cluster name, log level) is presented as structured fields, facilitating cross-component and cross-time event correlation for accurate issue localization.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintainability&lt;/strong&gt;: Structured logging makes it easier for developers and operators to maintain, parse, and evolve log formats as the system changes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Significant Performance Improvements for Karmada Controllers and Schedulers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this version, the Karmada performance optimization team has continued to focus on improving the performance of Karmada’s key components, achieving significant progress in both controllers and schedulers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In terms of the controller&lt;/strong&gt;, by introducing &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/controller-runtime/issues/2374&#34;&gt;controller-runtime priority queue&lt;/a&gt;, the controller can give priority to responding to user-triggered resource changes after a restart or leader transition, thereby significantly reducing the downtime during service restart and failover processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The test environment included 5,000 Deployments, 2,500 Policies, and 5,000 ResourceBindings. The Deployment and Policy were updated when the controller restarted with a large number of pending events still in the work queue. Test results showed that &lt;strong&gt;the controller could immediately respond to and prioritize processing these update events, verifying the effectiveness of this optimization&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note: &lt;/strong&gt;This feature is currently in the Alpha stage and requires enabling the ControllerPriorityQueue feature gate to use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In terms of the scheduler&lt;/strong&gt;, by reducing redundant computations in the scheduling process and decreasing the number of remote call requests, the scheduling efficiency of the Karmada scheduler has been significantly improved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tests were conducted to record the time taken to schedule 5,000 ResourceBindings with the precise scheduling component karmada-scheduler-estimator enabled. The results are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The scheduler throughput QPS increased from approximately 15 to about 22, representing a 46% performance improvement.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The number of gRPC requests decreased from approximately 10,000 to around 5,000, a reduction of 50%.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These tests confirm that the performance of Karmada controllers and schedulers has been greatly improved in version 1.15. In the future, we will continue to conduct systematic performance optimizations for controllers and schedulers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the detailed test report, please refer to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/issues/6516&#34;&gt;[Performance] Overview of performance improvements for v1.15&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acknowledging Our Contributors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Karmada v1.15 release includes 269 code commits from 39 contributors. We would like to extend our sincere gratitude to all the contributors:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@abhi0324&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@abhinav-1305&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@Arhell&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@Bhaumik10&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@CaesarTY&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@cbaenziger&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@deefreak&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@dekaihu&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@devarsh10&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@greenmoon55&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@iawia002&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@jabellard&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@jennryaz&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@liaolecheng&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@linyao22&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@LivingCcj&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@liwang0513&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@mohamedawnallah&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@mohit-nagaraj&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@mszacillo&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@RainbowMango&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@ritzdevp&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@ryanwuer&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@samzong&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@seanlaii&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@SunsetB612&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@tessapham&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@wangbowen1401&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@warjiang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@wenhuwang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@whitewindmills&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@whosefriendA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@XiShanYongYe-Chang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zach593&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zclyne&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zhangsquared&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zhuyulicfc49&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zhzhuang-zju&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zzklachlan&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;601&#34; height=&#34;750&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Contributor collage&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-149038&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2.jpg 601w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2-240x300.jpg 240w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2-160x200.jpg 160w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2-321x400.jpg 321w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 601px) 100vw, 601px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;References：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[1] Karmada: &lt;a href=&#34;https://karmada.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://karmada.io/&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[2] Karmada v1.15: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/releases/tag/v1.15.0&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/releases/tag/v1.15.0&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[3] Multi-Pod Template Support: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/tree/master/docs/proposals/scheduling/multi-podtemplate-support&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/tree/master/docs/proposals/scheduling/multi-podtemplate-support&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[4] [Performance] Overview of performance improvements for v1.15: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/issues/6516&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/issues/6516&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[5] Karmada GitHub：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Karmada 是一个开放的多云和多集群容器编排引擎，旨在帮助用户在多云环境中部署和运营业务应用程序。凭借与原生 Kubernetes API 的兼容性，&lt;a href=&#34;https://karmada.io/&#34;&gt;Karmada&lt;/a&gt; 可以平滑迁移单集群工作负载，同时仍保持与周围 Kubernetes 生态系统工具的协调。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34;解码=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1600&#34; height=&#34;752&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Karmada 版本增强图形&#34; 类=“wp-image-149039”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1.jpg 1600w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-300x141.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-1024x481.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-768x361.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-900x423.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-426x200.jpg 426w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-3-1-851x400.jpg 851w&#34; 尺寸=“自动，（最大宽度：1600px）100vw，1600px”referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/releases/tag/v1.15.0&#34;&gt;Karmada v1.15&lt;/a&gt;已发布，该版本包含以下新功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;针对多模板工作负载的精确资源感知&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;增强的集群级故障转移功能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;结构化日志记录&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Karmada 控制器和调度程序的性能显着提升&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;新功能概述&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;多模板工作负载的精确资源感知&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Karmada 利用资源解释器来检索工作负载的副本计数和资源请求。根据这些数据，它可以计算工作负载的总资源需求，从而实现资源感知调度和联合配额管理等高级功能。此机制非常适合传统的单模板工作负载。然而，许多 AI 和大数据应用程序工作负载（例如 FlinkDeployments、PyTorchJobs 和 RayJobs）由多个 Pod 模板或组件组成，每个模板或组件都有独特的资源需求。由于资源解释器只能处理单个模板的资源请求，无法准确反映多个模板之间的差异，因此多模板工作负载的资源计算不够精确。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此版本中，Karmada 增强了对多模板工作负载的资源感知。通过扩展资源解释器，Karmada 现在可以获取同一工作负载内不同模板的副本数量和资源请求，确保数据准确性。这一改进也证明为多模板工作负载的联合配额管理提供更可靠、更精细的数据支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设您使用以下资源相关配置部署 FlinkDeployment：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;规格：  jobManager：    副本：1    资源：      cpu：1      内存：1024m  taskManager：    副本：1    资源：      cpu： 2      内存：2048m&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过ResourceBinding，可以查看资源解释器解析出的FlinkDeployment中各个模板的副本数量和资源请求情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;规格：  组件：  – 名称：jobmanager    replicaRequirements：      resourceRequest：        cpu：“1”        内存：“1.024”    副本：1  – 名称：任务管理器    副本要求：      资源请求：        CPU：“2”        内存： “2.048”    副本：1&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此时FederatedResourceQuota计算出的FlinkDeployment的资源使用情况如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;状态：    总体已使用：      cpu：“3”      内存：3072m&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;此功能目前处于 Alpha 阶段，需要启用 MultiplePodTemplatesScheduling 功能门才能使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着多模板工作负载在云原生环境中的广泛采用，Karmada 致力于为其提供更强大的支持。在即将推出的版本中，我们将基于此功能进一步增强对多模板工作负载的调度支持，并提供更细粒度的资源感知调度——更多更新敬请期待！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关此功能的更多信息，请参阅：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/tree/master/docs/proposals/scheduling/multi-podtemplate-support&#34;&gt;多 Pod 模板支持&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;增强的集群级故障转移功能&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在之前的版本中，Karmada 提供了基本的集群级故障转移功能，允许通过自定义故障条件触发集群级应用程序迁移。满足保存r的要求在集群故障转移期间取消有状态应用程序的状态，Karmada v1.15 支持集群故障转移的应用程序状态保存策略。对于大数据处理应用（例如Flink），该能力可以从故障前的检查点重新启动，并无缝地将数据处理恢复到重新启动前的状态，从而避免重复的数据处理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;社区在 PropagationPolicy/ClusterPropagationPolicy API 的 .spec.failover.cluster 下引入了新的 StatePreservation 字段。该字段用于定义在故障转移期间保留和恢复有状态应用程序的状态数据的策略。结合此策略，当应用程序从故障集群迁移到另一个集群时，可以从原始资源配置中提取关键数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;状态保存策略StatePreservation包含一系列StatePreservationRule配置。它使用 JSONPath 指定需要保留的状态数据段，并利用关联的 AliasLabelName 将数据传递到迁移的集群。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以Flink应用为例：在Flink应用中，jobID是唯一的标识符，用于区分和管理不同的Flink作业。当集群发生故障时，Flink应用程序可以通过jobID将作业恢复到故障前的状态，并从故障点继续执行。具体配置及步骤如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;apiVersion：policy.karmada.io/v1alpha1&lt;br&gt;kind：PropagationPolicy&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;  name：foo&lt;br&gt;spec：&lt;br&gt;  #…&lt;br&gt;  故障转移：&lt;br&gt;    cluster：&lt;br&gt;      purgeMode：直接&lt;br&gt;      statePreservation：&lt;br&gt;        规则：&lt;br&gt;          – aliasLabelName：application.karmada.io/cluster-failover-jobid&lt;br&gt;            jsonPath：“{ .jobStatus.jobID }”&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;迁移之前，Karmada 控制器会根据用户配置的路径提取作业 ID。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在迁移过程中，Karmada 控制器会将提取的作业 ID 以标签的形式注入到 Flink 应用程序配置中，例如 application.karmada.io/cluster-failover-jobid: &lt;jobID&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;成员集群中运行的Kyverno拦截Flink应用创建请求，根据jobID获取作业的checkpoint数据存储路径（例如/&lt;shared-path&gt;/&lt;job-namespace&gt;/&lt;jobId&gt;/checkpoints/xxx），然后配置initialSavepointPath表示从savepoint开始。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Flink应用程序根据initialSavepointPath下的检查点数据启动，从而继承迁移前保存的最终状态。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能广泛适用于有状态应用程序可以从特定保存点开始的离子。这些应用可以按照上述流程实现集群级故障切换的状态持久和恢复。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意：此功能目前处于 Alpha 阶段，需要启用 StatefulFailoverInjection 功能门才能使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;功能限制&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;应用程序必须限制为在单个集群中运行。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;迁移清理策略 (PurgeMode) 仅限于“直接”，这意味着确保故障应用程序先从旧集群中删除，然后再在新集群中恢复，以保证数据一致性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;结构化日志记录&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;日志是记录系统运行过程中的事件、状态和行为的重要工具，广泛用于故障排除、性能监控和安全审计。 Karmada组件提供丰富的运行时日志，帮助用户快速定位问题、追踪执行场景。在之前的版本中，Karmada仅支持非结构化文本日志，难以高效解析和查询，限制了其在现代可观测系统中的集成能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Karmada v1.15 引入了对结构化日志记录的支持，可以使用 –logging-format=json 启动标志将其配置为以 JSON 格式输出。结构化日志记录的示例如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;{  “ts”:“日志时钟”,  “logger”:”cluster_status_controller”,  “level”: “info”,  “msg”:”正在同步集群 status”,  “clusterName”:“member1”}&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结构化日志记录的引入显着提高了日志的可用性和可观察性：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高效集成&lt;/strong&gt;：与 Elastic、Loki 和 Splunk 等主流日志记录系统集成，无需依赖复杂的正则表达式或日志解析器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高效查询&lt;/strong&gt;：结构化字段支持快速检索和分析，大幅提升排查效率。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;增强的可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;：关键上下文信息（例如集群名称、日志级别）以结构化字段的形式呈现，促进跨组件和跨时间事件关联，从而实现准确的问题定位。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可维护性&lt;/strong&gt;：结构化日志记录使开发人员和运维人员可以更轻松地在系统发生变化时维护、解析和改进日志格式。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Karmada 控制器和调度程序的性能显着提升&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这个版本中，Karmada性能优化团队继续专注于提高Karmada的性能关键组件，在控制器和调度器方面取得了重大进展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;控制器方面&lt;/strong&gt;，通过引入&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/controller-runtime/issues/2374&#34;&gt;controller-runtime优先级队列&lt;/a&gt;，控制器可以在重启或leader过渡后优先响应用户触发的资源变化，从而显着降低 服务重启和故障转移过程中的停机时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;测试环境包括 5,000 个部署、2,500 个策略和 5,000 个资源绑定。当控制器重新启动且工作队列中仍有大量待处理事件时，部署和策略已更新。测试结果表明，&lt;strong&gt;控制器能够立即响应并优先处理这些更新事件，验证了本次优化的有效性&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;此功能目前处于 Alpha 阶段，需要启用 ControllerPriorityQueue 功能门才能使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在调度器方面&lt;/strong&gt;，通过减少调度过程中的冗余计算，减少远程调用请求的数量，Karmada调度器的调度效率得到了显着提升。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们进行了测试，记录在启用精确调度组件 karmada-scheduler-estimator 的情况下调度 5,000 个资源绑定所需的时间。结果如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;调度程序吞吐量 QPS 从大约 15 增加到大约 22，性能提高了 46%。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;gRPC 请求数量从大约 10,000 减少到大约 5,000，减少了 50%。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些测试证实 Karmada 控制器和调度器的性能在 1.15 版本中得到了极大的提高。未来我们将继续对控制器和调度器进行系统性的性能优化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;详细测试报告请参考&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/issues/6516&#34;&gt;【性能】v1.15性能改进概览&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;感谢我们的贡献者&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Karmada v1.15 版本包含来自 39 位贡献者的 269 项代码提交。我们向所有贡献者致以诚挚的谢意：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;表 class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@abhi0324&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@abhinav-1305&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@Arhell&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@Bhaumik10&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@Caesa rTY&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@cbaenziger&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@deefreak&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@dekaihu&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@devarsh10&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@greenmoon55&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@iawia 002&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@jabellard&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@jennryaz&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@liaole Cheng&lt;/​​td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@linyao22&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@LivingCcj&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@liwan g0513&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@mohamedawnallah&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@mohit-nagaraj&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@mszacillo&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@RainbowMango&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@ritzdevp&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@ryanwuer&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@samzong&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@seanlaii&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@SunsetB612&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@tessapham&lt;/td&gt;&lt; /tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@wangbowen1401&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@war Jiang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@wenhuwang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@whitewindmills&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@ whofriendA&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@XiShanYongYe-Chang&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zach593&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zclyne&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zhangsquared&lt;/td&gt; td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zhuyulicfc49&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zhzhuang-zju&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;@zzklachlan&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“601”height =“750”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2.jpg”alt =“贡献者拼贴” 类=“wp-image-149038”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2.jpg 601w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2-240x300.jpg 240w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2-160x200.jpg 160w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-2-2-321x400.jpg 321w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：601px）100vw，601px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;参考文献：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[1] Karmada：&lt;a href=&#34;https://karmada.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://karmada.io/&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[2] Karmada v1.15：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/releases/tag/v1.15.0&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/releases/tag/v1.15.0&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[3] 多 Pod 模板支持：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/tree/master/docs/proposals/scheduling/multi-podtemplate-support&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt; https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/tree/master/docs/proposals/scheduling/multi-podtemplate-support&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[4] [性能] v1.15 性能改进概述：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/issues/6516&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada/issues/6516&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[5] Karmada GitHub：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://github.com/karmada-io/karmada&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2025 Co-Located Event Deep Dive: Open Source SecurityCon】KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 北美 2025 年同期活动深度探讨：开源 SecurityCon</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/06/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2025-co-located-event-deep-dive-open-source-securitycon/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1744&#34; height=&#34;296&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Open Source SecurityCon header graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-147356&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5.jpg 1744w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-300x51.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1024x174.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-768x130.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-900x153.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-600x102.jpg 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1200x204.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1744px) 100vw, 1744px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Open Source SecurityCon has always been about bringing people together to strengthen trust in open source. From its beginnings within TAG Security to its growth as a standalone conference, and now returning to KubeCon + CloudNativeCon alongside the &lt;a href=&#34;http://openssf.org/&#34;&gt;Open Source Security Foundation (OpenSSF)&lt;/a&gt;, the event has become a gathering place for anyone passionate about securing our shared ecosystem. As a co-located event, it will bring together software developers, security engineers, public sector leaders, CISOs, CIOs, and technology innovators. Through interactive discussions, expert-led sessions, and hands-on activities, participants will dive into emerging security challenges, explore the latest industry innovations, and share best practices that are shaping the future of secure software development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Who will get the most out of attending this event?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You don’t need to be a security practitioner to attend! This event will have lots of great security content, but it is a place for all developers to come and get their security questions answered. Whether you are a security engineer, DevOps professional, software developer, cloud architect, IT manager, risk and compliance officer, or open source contributor, this event has something for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join us if you’re an open source contributor or maintainer who wants to improve the security of their projects and learn about the landscape of open source security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Security is no longer just a consideration. It is a necessity. Open Source SecurityCon 2025 is a welcoming space for anyone interested in building more secure, scalable software. Even if you’re not an open source developer, the ways of securing open source can be applied to any code and development process. The best part, all the tools and frameworks that will be showcased are open source. That means you can leverage these things anywhere!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What will the day look like?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Open Source SecurityCon 2025, your day will be a mix of learning and connecting. We have an amazing lineup of talks on topics from software supply chain security to AI security to security policy. There will be three talk tracks for most of the event with breaks and lunch where all attendees can come together for a hallway track.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Should I do any homework first?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just have a look at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://colocatedeventsna2025.sched.com/overview/type/Open+Source+SecurityCon?iframe=no&#34;&gt;schedule&lt;/a&gt; before you come! We will have a lot of content, so make sure you add the talks you’re interested in to your calendar.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Find your community!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Collaboration is the heartbeat of open source, and in security it becomes our greatest strength. Meet the changemakers shaping a safer future, and explore how you can help protect every project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;A note from the co-chairs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re excited about all things security! The fun will continue on with the Security track of the main conference. There’s a great TAG Security &amp;amp; Compliance blog post about all these fun things: &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/blog/kubecon-na-2025-schedule-announced/&#34;&gt;https://tag-security.cncf.io/blog/kubecon-na-2025-schedule-announced/&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ll also have a TAG Security and Compliance booth in the Project Pavillion. Be sure to come by and say “Hi!”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“1744”height =“296”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5.jpg”alt =“开源SecurityCon标题图形” 类=“wp-image-147356”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5.jpg 1744w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-300x51.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1024x174.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-768x130.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-900x153.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-600x102.jpg 600w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1200x204.jpg 1200w“尺寸=”自动， （最大宽度：1744px）100vw，1744px“referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Open Source SecurityCon 始终致力于将人们聚集在一起，加强对开源的信任。从 TAG Security 的起源到发展成为独立会议，再到现在与&lt;a href=&#34;http://openssf.org/&#34;&gt;开源安全基金会 (OpenSSF)&lt;/a&gt; 一起回归 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon，该活动已成为所有热衷于保护我们的共享生态系统的人的聚会场所。作为同地举办的活动，它将汇集软件开发人员、安全工程师、公共部门领导、首席信息安全官 (CISO)、首席信息官 (CIO) 和技术创新者。通过互动讨论、专家主导的会议和实践活动，参与者将深入探讨新出现的安全挑战，探索最新的行业创新，并分享塑造安全软件开发未来的最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;谁将从参加本次活动中获益最多？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您无需成为安全从业人员即可参加！该活动将有很多精彩的安全内容，但它是所有开发人员都可以来回答安全问题的地方。无论您是安全工程师、DevOps 专业人员、软件开发人员、云架构师、IT 经理、风险与合规官还是开源贡献者，本次活动都适合您。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您是开源贡献者或维护者，想要提高项目的安全性并了解开源安全的概况，请加入我们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;安全不再只是一个考虑因素。这是必要的。 Open Source SecurityCon 2025 对于任何有兴趣构建更安全、可扩展软件的人来说都是一个受欢迎的空间。即使您不是开源开发人员，保护开源的方法也可以应用于任何代码和开发过程。最好的部分是，将展示的所有工具和框架都是开源的。这意味着您可以在任何地方利用这些东西！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;这一天会是什么样子？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Open Source SecurityCon 2025 上，您的一天将是学习和交流的结合。我们拥有令人惊叹的阵容讨论的主题从软件供应链安全到人工智能安全再到安全政策。活动的大部分时间将有三个谈话轨道，包括休息和午餐，所有与会者都可以聚集在一起进行走廊谈话。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;我应该先做作业吗？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来之前先看看&lt;a href=&#34;https://co locatedeventsna2025.sched.com/overview/type/Open+Source+SecurityCon?iframe=no&#34;&gt;时间表&lt;/a&gt;！我们将有很多内容，因此请确保将您感兴趣的演讲添加到您的日历中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;找到您的社区！&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;协作是开源的心跳，在安全方面它成为我们最大的优势。与塑造更安全未来的变革者见面，并探索如何帮助保护每个项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;联合主席的说明&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们对安全方面的一切感到兴奋！主会议的安全主题将继续带来乐趣。有一篇很棒的 TAG 安全与合规性博客文章介绍了所有这些有趣的事情：&lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/blog/kubecon-na-2025-schedule-announced/&#34;&gt;https://tag-security.cncf.io/blog/kubecon-na-2025-schedule-announced/&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还将在项目馆设立 TAG 安全与合规展位。一定要过来打个招呼“嗨！”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing ORAS v1.3.0: Elevating artifact and registry management workflows】发布 ORAS v1.3.0：提升工件和注册表管理工作流程</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/06/announcing-oras-v1-3-0-elevating-artifact-and-registry-management-workflows/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The ORAS community is thrilled to announce the release of ORAS CLI v1.3.0, a version packed with stability improvements and pioneering capabilities. In addition to strengthening existing functionality, this release introduces three major new features designed to enhance artifact and registry management workflows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Portable backup and restore of repositories and artifacts&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-platform image and artifact management&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rich formatted output for scripting and pipelines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, ORAS is now fully compliant with OCI distribution-spec v1.1.1.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your registry’s safety net: Portable backup &amp;amp; restore&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With oras backup and oras restore, ORAS now lets you save your registry content into local directories or tarballs (OCI image layout format) as a snapshot and restore to any registry. All manifests, along with any optional tags and referrers, will be included in the backup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use cases include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Air-gapped environments:&lt;/strong&gt; Organizations operating in isolated or high-security environments can use oras backup to export artifacts from a registry to the local filesystem, and oras restore to import them into an internal registry with restricted access.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disaster recovery and audit archival:&lt;/strong&gt; Take periodic snapshots of repositories and store them off-site. In case of accidental deletions, outages, or long-term storage for regulatory audits, oras restore can quickly recover full registry content.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Registry migration:&lt;/strong&gt; When moving from one container registry provider to another, these commands enable a full repository export, preserving tags, manifests, layers, and referrers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance and supply chain security:&lt;/strong&gt; Back up and restore images along with their supply chain artifacts, such as SBOMs, signatures, and vulnerability scanning reports.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Repository duplication or promotion:&lt;/strong&gt; Move artifacts from dev to staging to production registries reliably using an intermediate backup file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out the user guide &lt;em&gt;Backup and Restore of OCI Artifacts, Images, and Repositories&lt;/em&gt; for details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1168&#34; height=&#34;1250&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Save the repo from remote to local &lt;image&gt;&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148936&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM.jpg 1168w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-280x300.jpg 280w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-957x1024.jpg 957w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-768x822.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-900x963.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-187x200.jpg 187w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-374x400.jpg 374w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1168px) 100vw, 1168px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-platform image and artifact management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multi-platform images are commonly used in IoT and Edge computing, particularly in heterogeneous deployments. In addition, OpenTofu or Terraform modules are often packaged as platform-specific artifacts and stored as multi-platform artifacts in OCI registries. Thanks to our community partner OpenTofu, multi-platform artifact management is now introduced in v1.3.0.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With oras manifest index create and oras manifest index update, you can easily assemble, update, distribute, and annotate multi-architecture images and artifacts across local environments and registries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out the user guide &lt;em&gt;Create and Manage Multi-architecture Artifacts&lt;/em&gt; for details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1146&#34; height=&#34;776&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ORAS &lt;image&gt;&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148937&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM.jpg 1146w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-300x203.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-1024x693.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-768x520.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-900x609.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-295x200.jpg 295w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-591x400.jpg 591w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1146px) 100vw, 1146px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable scripting and automation: Formatted output&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In automation pipelines, the difference between human-readable and machine-usable output can be critical.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this release, ORAS enables users to use the –format flag to output metadata in structured data (e.g., JSON) and optionally the –template flag with the Go template language. This has been enabled for commands like pull, push, attach, discover, and manifest fetch with support for formats including JSON, Go templates, trees, and tables. You can even run computations with Sprig template functions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use –format &amp;lt;DATA_FORMAT&amp;gt; to transform the output of ORAS commands into formats including prettified JSON, tree, table view, and Go template (–format json|tree|table|go-template=GO_TEMPLATE).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use –template GO_TEMPLATE to compute and manipulate the output using Go templates based on the chosen data format.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Formatted output transforms ORAS from a simple terminal tool into a DevOps-friendly, integrable developer tool. Check out the user guide &lt;em&gt;Formatted Output&lt;/em&gt; for details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stability &amp;amp; user experience polish&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release also includes a number of enhancements that provide better overall stability and user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feature stability promotions:&lt;/strong&gt; oras attach, oras pull –include-subject, and more are now Stable. oras resolve has moved from Experimental to Preview.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discover UX:&lt;/strong&gt; oras discover now displays referrers recursively by default. The maximum recursion depth can be controlled via the –depth flag.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loong64 support:&lt;/strong&gt; More platform options, including loong64, are now available.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer experience:&lt;/strong&gt; Improved clarity in error messages, debugging logs, and numerous documentation updates.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why this release matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re looking to back up and restore entire registries, publish multi-architecture bundles, or integrate ORAS into CI/CD pipelines, v1.3.0 brings the tools and end-to-end artifact management solutions you need.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform teams&lt;/strong&gt; gain robust disaster recovery and migration tooling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DevOps engineers&lt;/strong&gt; benefit from multi-arch flexibility for heterogeneous infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CI/CD and platform builders&lt;/strong&gt; leverage structured data outputs for reliable, scriptable workflows.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintainers&lt;/strong&gt; deliver safer, cleaner, and more future-proof artifact workflows.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are also a few bug fixes and a deprecated feature in this release. For a detailed changelog, please see the [ORAS v1.3.0 Release Notes].&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thanks to all contributors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to our existing maintainers &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Wwwsylvia&#34;&gt;@Wwwsylvia&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/TerryHowe&#34;&gt;@TerryHowe&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/FeynmanZhou&#34;&gt;@FeynmanZhou&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/shizhMSFT&#34;&gt;@shizhMSFT&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sabre1041&#34;&gt;@sabre1041&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sajayantony&#34;&gt;@sajayantony&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/qweeah&#34;&gt;@qweeah&lt;/a&gt; who contributed to ORAS v1.3.0 and new contributors 🎉 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/bcho&#34;&gt;@bcho&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/njucjc&#34;&gt;@njucjc&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nmiyake&#34;&gt;@nmiyake&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mauriciovasquezbernal&#34;&gt;@mauriciovasquezbernal&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Horiodino&#34;&gt;@Horiodino&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chrisguitarguy&#34;&gt;@chrisguitarguy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kysucix&#34;&gt;@kysucix&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/RohanMishra315&#34;&gt;@RohanMishra315&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/apparentlymart&#34;&gt;@apparentlymart&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tanyabhatnagar&#34;&gt;@tanyabhatnagar&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/amazingfate&#34;&gt;@amazingfate&lt;/a&gt; 🚀.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can follow the installation guidance to install ORAS v1.3.0 and try it out yourself. End-user feedback is essential in any open source project. If you run into issues or have suggestions, please open an issue. To engage with the community, join the CNCF Slack and find us in the #oras channel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;ORAS 社区很高兴地宣布发布 ORAS CLI v1.3.0，该版本包含稳定性改进和开创性功能。除了增强现有功能之外，此版本还引入了三个主要新功能，旨在增强工件和注册表管理工作流程：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;存储库和工件的便携式备份和恢复&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多平台图像和工件管理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;用于脚本和管道的丰富格式输出&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，ORAS 现在完全符合 OCI 发行版规范 v1.1.1。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注册表的安全网：便携式备份和恢复&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过 oras 备份和 oras 恢复，ORAS 现在允许您将注册表内容作为快照保存到本地目录或 tarball（OCI 映像布局格式）中，并恢复到任何注册表。所有清单以及任何可选标签和引荐来源网址都将包含在备份中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用例包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;气隙环境：&lt;/strong&gt;在隔离或高安全性环境中运行的组织可以使用 oras 备份将项目从注册表导出到本地文件系统，并使用 oras 恢复将其导入访问受限的内部注册表。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;灾难恢复和审计归档：&lt;/strong&gt;定期拍摄存储库快照并将其存储在异地。如果发生意外删除、中断或长期存储以进行监管审计，oras 恢复可以快速恢复完整的注册表内容。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注册表迁移&lt;/strong&gt;：从一个容器注册表提供商迁移到另一个容器注册表提供商时，这些命令可启用完整的存储库导出，保留标签、清单、层和引荐来源网址。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;合规性和供应链安全&lt;/strong&gt;：备份和恢复映像及其供应链工件，例如 SBOM、签名和漏洞扫描报告。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;存储库复制或升级：&lt;/strong&gt;使用中间备份文件可靠地将工件从开发环境移动到暂存环境到生产注册表。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查看用户指南&lt;em&gt;OCI 工件、图像和存储库的备份和恢复&lt;/em&gt;了解详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1168”高度=“1250” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;将存储库从远程保存到本地 &lt;image&gt;&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148936&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM.jpg 1168w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-280x300.jpg 280w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-957x1024.jpg 957w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-768x822.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-900x963.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-187x200.jpg 187w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.49.57-AM-374x400.jpg 374w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1168px）100vw，1168px“ referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;多平台图像和工件管理&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多平台映像通常用于物联网和边缘计算，特别是在异构部署中。此外，OpenTofu 或 Terraform 模块通常打包为特定于平台的工件，并作为多平台工件存储在 OCI 注册表中。感谢我们的社区合作伙伴 OpenTofu，v1.3.0 现已引入多平台工件管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过 oras 清单索引创建和 oras 清单索引更新，您可以轻松地跨本地环境和注册表组装、更新、分发和注释多架构映像和工件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查看用户指南&lt;em&gt;创建和管理多架构工件&lt;/em&gt;了解详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1146”高度=“776” src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ORAS &lt;图像&gt;&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148937&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM.jpg 1146w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-300x203.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-1024x693.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-768x520.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-900x609.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-295x200.jpg 295w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Screenshot-2025-10-06-at-11.50.52-AM-591x400.jpg 591w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1146px）100vw，1146px“ referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;启用脚本和自动化：格式化输出&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在自动化管道中，人类可读的输出和机器可用的输出之间的差异可能至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此版本中，ORAS 允许用户使用 –format 标志以结构化数据（例如 JSON）输出元数据，并且可以选择使用 Go 模板语言的 –template 标志。已为拉取、推送、附加、发现和清单获取等命令启用此功能，并支持 JSON、Go 模板、树和表等格式。您甚至可以使用 Sprig 模板函数运行计算。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用 –format &lt;DATA_FORMAT&gt; 转换 ORAS com 的输出要求转换为格式，包括美化的 JSON、树、表视图和 Go 模板（–format json|tree|table|go-template=GO_TEMPLATE）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用 –template GO_TEMPLATE 根据所选数据格式使用 Go 模板计算和操作输出。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;格式化输出将 ORAS 从简单的终端工具转变为 DevOps 友好的可集成开发人员工具。查看用户指南&lt;em&gt;格式化输出&lt;/em&gt;了解详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;稳定性和用户体验优化&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本还包括许多增强功能，可提供更好的整体稳定性和用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;功能稳定性提升：&lt;/strong&gt;oras Attach、oras pull –include-subject 等更多功能现已稳定。 oras resolve 已从实验版转为预览版。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;发现用户体验&lt;/strong&gt;：oras discovery 现在默认以递归方式显示引荐来源网址。最大递归深度可以通过 –depth 标志控制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loong64 支持：&lt;/strong&gt;现在提供更多平台选项，包括 loong64。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;开发者体验：&lt;/strong&gt;提高了错误消息、调试日志和大量文档更新的清晰度。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么此版本很重要&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是希望备份和恢复整个注册表、发布多架构捆绑包，还是将 ORAS 集成到 CI/CD 管道中，v1.3.0 都能提供您所需的工具和端到端工件管理解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;平台团队&lt;/strong&gt;获得强大的灾难恢复和迁移工具。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DevOps 工程师&lt;/strong&gt;受益于异构基础设施的多架构灵活性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CI/CD 和平台构建者&lt;/strong&gt;利用结构化数据输出来实现可靠、可编写脚本的工作流程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;维护人员&lt;/strong&gt;提供更安全、更清洁且面向未来的工件工作流程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本中还有一些错误修复和已弃用的功能。有关详细变更日志，请参阅[ORAS v1.3.0 发行说明]。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;感谢所有贡献者&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;感谢我们现有的维护者&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Wwwsylvia&#34;&gt;@Wwwsylvia&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/TerryHowe&#34;&gt;@TerryHowe&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/FeynmanZhou&#34;&gt;@FeynmanZhou&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/shizhMSFT&#34;&gt;@shizhMSFT&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sabre1041&#34;&gt;@sabre1041&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sajayantony&#34;&gt;@sajayantony&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/qweeah&#34;&gt;@qweeah&lt;/a&gt; 为 ORAS v1.3.0 做出了贡献，还有新贡献者 🎉 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/bcho&#34;&gt;@bcho&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/njucjc&#34;&gt;@njucjc&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nmiyake&#34;&gt;@nmiyake&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mauriciovasquezbernal&#34;&gt;@mauriciovasquezbernal&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Horiodino&#34;&gt;@Horiodino&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chrisguitarguy&#34;&gt;@chrisguitarguy&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kysucix&#34;&gt;@kysucix&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/RohanMishra315&#34;&gt;@RohanMishra315&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/apparentlymart&#34;&gt;@apparentlymart&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tanyabhatnagar&#34;&gt;@tanyabhatnagar&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/amazingfate&#34;&gt;@amazingfate&lt;/a&gt; 🚀。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以按照安装指导安装ORAS v1.3.0并自行尝试。最终用户的反馈对于任何开源项目都是至关重要的。如果您遇到问题或有建议，请提出问题。要与社区互动，请加入 CNCF Slack 并在 #oras 频道中找到我们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2025 Co-Located Event Deep Dive: Kubernetes on Edge Day】KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 北美 2025 年同期活动深度探讨：边缘日上的 Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/03/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2025-co-located-event-deep-dive-kubernetes-on-edge-day/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1744&#34; height=&#34;398&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;K8s on Edge Day header graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-147352&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4.jpg 1744w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-300x68.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1024x234.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-768x175.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-900x205.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-600x137.jpg 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1200x274.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1744px) 100vw, 1744px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The inaugural Edge Day launched as a co-located event at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon EU in 2022, recognizing that data at the edge is here to stay. Once called the ‘Internet of Things’ and later ‘Industry 4.0,’ today ‘edge computing’ has emerged as the unifying term, reflecting the evolution from centralized data centers and cloud computing to the very edge of the network. Kubernetes on Edge Day embraces this shift with a thoughtful agenda that brings together academic research, real-world enterprise use cases, and insights from peers across the Kubernetes community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Who will get the most out of attending this event?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a wonderful event for everyone who wants to get as close to the newest technology as they can, without going to a quantum computing conference 😊. Engineers working at large companies who are looking to modernize and containerize their applications will be able to explore real-world business applications of technological innovation. Students and researchers will hear from other academics on what and how they are doing to push the limits of what is typically thought to be possible. At Kubernetes on Edge Day, we bring together experts for an audience who are tackling some of the most exciting and complex problems in cloud computin today, and tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What is new and different this year?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We did our best to limit the topics to stay as close to true “edge computing” as we could, but the reality is edge computing is the future that is leaking into all other categories, verticals, industries, and technologies. This year, we had submissions covering artificial intelligence at the edge, edge computing for telco deployments, the effect and importance of data on Kubernetes, the vitality of observability at scale for these systems, and many more. We hope that this year’s agenda tells an interesting story about Kubernetes at the Edge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What will the day look like?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The event will kick off in the main room with a welcome from the chairs. After that, we’ll dive straight into the featured sessions. Throughout the day, there will be dedicated breaks for coffee and networking, giving attendees the chance to connect with project leaders, maintainers, and fellow practitioners. Expect a mix of insightful discussions, hands-on knowledge sharing, and plenty of opportunities to engage with the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Should I do any homework first?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out our sponsors – we are very grateful for them and their commitment to sponsoring collocated events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Find your community!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can’t wait to see you. If this is something you enjoy and want to see more of, please let the CNCF know so we can continue to expand the Day, adding more and more sessions and continuing to put the focus on edge computing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We look forward to connecting with friends and peers across the industry who we’ve had the joy of seeing in person a few times a year at the various CNCF events across the world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“1744”height =“398”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4.jpg”alt =“K8s on Edge Day标题图形” 类=“wp-image-147352”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4.jpg 1744w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-300x68.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1024x234.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-768x175.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-900x205.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-600x137.jpg 600w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1200x274.jpg 1200w“尺寸=”自动， （最大宽度：1744px）100vw，1744px“referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首届边缘日于 2022 年在 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon EU 同期举办，旨在认识到边缘数据将继续存在。曾经被称为“物联网”和后来的“工业 4.0”，如今“边缘计算”已成为统一术语，反映了从集中式数据中心和云计算到网络边缘的演变。 Kubernetes on Edge Day 通过深思熟虑的议程来迎接这一转变，该议程汇集了学术研究、实际企业用例以及 Kubernetes 社区同行的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;谁将从参加本次活动中获益最多？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于每个想要尽可能接近最新技术而无需参加量子计算会议的人来说，这是一次精彩的活动😊。在大公司工作、希望实现应用程序现代化和容器化的工程师将能够探索技术创新的实际业务应用。学生和研究人员将听取其他学者的意见，了解他们正在做什么以及如何突破通常被认为可能的极限。在 Kubernetes Edge Day 上，我们为观众聚集了专家，他们正在解决当今和未来云计算中一些最令人兴奋和最复杂的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;今年有什么新的和不同的？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们尽力限制主题，使其尽可能接近真正的“边缘计算”，但现实是边缘计算是正在渗透到所有其他类别、垂直行业、行业和技术的未来。今年，我们提交的内容涵盖边缘人工智能、电信部署的边缘计算、数据对 Kubernetes 的影响和重要性、这些系统的大规模可观测性的活力等等。我们希望今年的议程讲述一个关于边缘 Kubernetes 的有趣故事。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;这一天会是什么样子？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;活动将在主厅开始，并受到主席的欢迎。之后，我们���将直接进入特色会议。全天都会有专门的休息时间喝咖啡和交流，让与会者有机会与项目负责人、维护人员和其他从业者建立联系。期待富有洞察力的讨论、实践知识共享以及大量与社区互动的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;我应该先做作业吗？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查看我们的赞助商 - 我们非常感谢他们以及他们对赞助同期活动的承诺。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;找到您的社区！&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们迫不及待地想见到你。如果您喜欢并希望看到更多内容，请告知 CNCF，以便我们可以继续扩大该日的规模，增加越来越多的会议，并继续将重点放在边缘计算上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们期待与行业内的朋友和同行建立联系，我们每年都有幸在世界各地的各种 CNCF 活动中亲眼见到他们几次。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fluentd to Fluent Bit: A migration guide】Fluentd 到 Fluent Bit：迁移指南</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/10/01/fluentd-to-fluent-bit-a-migration-guide/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Fluentd was created over 14 years ago and still continues to be one of the most widely deployed technologies for log collection in the enterprise. Fluentd’s distributed plugin architecture and highly permissive licensing made it ideal as part of the&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/&#34;&gt; Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF)&lt;/a&gt; as a now graduated project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, enterprises drowning in telemetry data are now requiring solutions that have higher performance, more native support for evolving schemas and formats, and increased flexibility in processing. &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit/&#34;&gt;Enter Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When and why to migrate?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/fluent-bit-v4-0/&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt;, while initially growing as a sub-project within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://fluentbit.io/&#34;&gt;Fluent ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;, expanded from Fluentd to support all telemetry types – logs, metrics, and traces. Fluent Bit now is the more popular of the two with over 15 billion deployments and used by Amazon, Google, Oracle and Microsoft to name a few.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit also is fully aligned with OpenTelemetry signals, format and protocol, which ensures that users will be able to continue handling telemetry data as it grows and evolves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Among the most frequent questions we get as the maintainers of the projects are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How do we migrate?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What should we watch out for?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And what business value do we get for migrating?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article aims to answer these questions with examples. We want to help make it an easy decision to migrate from &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit-academy/&#34;&gt;Fluentd to Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why Migrate?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is a quick list of the reasons users switch from Fluentd to Fluent Bit:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Higher performance for the same resources you are already using&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Full OpenTelemetry support for logs, metrics, and traces as well as Prometheus support for metrics&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simpler configuration and routing ability to multiple locations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Higher velocity for adding custom processing rules&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Integrated monitoring to better understand performance and dataflows&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fluentd vs. Fluent Bit: What are the Differences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To understand all the differences between the projects, it is important to understand the background of each project and the era it was built for. With Fluentd, the main language is Ruby and initially designed to help users push data to big data platforms such as Hadoop.The project follows a distributed architecture, where plugins are installed after the main binary is installed and deployed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit on the other hand, is written in C, with a focus on hyper performance in smaller systems (containers, embedded Linux). The project learned from Fluentd’s plugins and instead opts for fully embedded plugins that are part of the core binary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Performance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The obvious difference and main value of switching from Fluentd to Fluent Bit is the performance. With Fluent Bit, the amount of logs you can process with the same resources could be anywhere from 10 to 40 times greater depending on the plugin you are using.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit was written from the ground up to be hyper performant, with a focus of shipping data as fast as possible for data analysis. Later on, performance was found to be efficient enough that more edge processing could be added without compromising on the mission to make the agent as fast as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Routing&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other parts of Fluent Bit evolved from challenges encountered with Fluentd, such as buffering and routing. With Fluentd multirouting was an afterthought and users needed to “copy” the data streams to route data to multiple points.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This made configuration management a nightmare, in addition to essentially duplicating the resource requirements for routing that data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Fluent Bit the buffers are stored once, which allows multiple plugins to “subscribe” to a stream of data. This ensures that data is stored once and subscribed many times allowing for multirouting without the trade-offs of performance and configuration fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Telemetry signal focus&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Fluentd was initially a data shipper, it grew into a logging agent used within projects such as Kubernetes and companies like Splunk. Fluent Bit on the other hand started as an embedded metrics collector with log files coming in after. As Fluent Bit adoption started to outweigh Fluentd’s functionality, capabilities such as OpenTelemetry logs/metrics/traces, Prometheus Scrape and Remote Write Support, eBPF and profiling support were all added.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today Fluent Bit is aligned with OpenTelemetry schema, formats and protocols and meant to be a lightweight implementation that is highly performant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Custom processing&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluentd and Fluent Bit have many of the same processor names, but when it comes to custom processing the options are quite different.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Fluentd the option is `enable_ruby`, which allows custom Ruby scripts within a configuration to perform actions. This can work effectively for small tasks; however it has a large penalty as logic gets more complicated, adding more performance bottlenecks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Fluent Bit, custom processing is done in the language Lua, which gives tremendous flexibility. However, unlike Fluentd, Fluent Bit’s Lua processor is quite performant and can be used at scale (100+ TB/day).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Custom plugins&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both projects allow custom plugins to help you connect with your source or destination. With Fluentd, these custom plugins are “Ruby Gems” that you can download and install into existing or new installations or deployments. With Fluent Bit, custom plugins are written and compiled in Go. There are also new initiatives for writing custom plugins in any language you want and compiling them into WebAssembly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One lesson we learned from Fluentd’s distributed plugin architecture was the number of plugins can increase exponentially. However, the quality and maintenance required generally left many of the plugins abandoned and unsupported. With Fluent Bit, plugins are all incorporated into the source code itself, which ensures compatibility with every release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Custom plugins still remain independent of the main repository. However, we are looking at ways to allow these to also share the same benefit of native C plugins within the main GitHub repository.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Monitoring&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understanding how data is traversing your environment is generally a top request from users who deploy Fluentd or Fluent Bit. With Fluentd, enabling these settings could require complicated configuration via “monitor_agent” or using a third party prometheus exporter plugin. These monitoring plugins also add maintenance overhead for Fluentd, which can affect performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit has monitoring as part of its core functionality and is retrievable via a native plugin (`fluentbit_metrics`) or scrapeable on an HTTP port. Fluent Bit’s metrics also incorporate more information than Fluentd’s, which allows you to understand bytes, records, storage and connection information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to get started with a Fluentd to Fluent Bit migration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The next question we’re answering is: How do you get started?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first important step is to understand how Fluentd is deployed, what processing happens in the environment and where data is flowing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What you don’t need to worry about:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architecture support:&lt;/strong&gt; Both applications support x86 and ARM.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform support:&lt;/strong&gt; Fluent Bit supports the same and more as Fluentd does today. Legacy systems may differ, however it is important to note those are not maintained in either OSS project.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular expressions:&lt;/strong&gt; If you built a large library of regular expressions using the Onigmo parser library, you can rest comfortably knowing that Fluent Bit supports it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Deployment&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deployed as an Agent (Linux or Windows Package)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When Fluentd is deployed as an agent on Linux or Windows, its primary function is to collect local log files or Windows event logs and route them to a particular destination.Thankfully, Fluent Bit’s local collection capabilities are equal to Fluentd’s, including the ability to resume on failure, store last log lines collected and local buffering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deployed in Kubernetes as a DaemonSet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If Fluentd is running as a DaemonSet in your Kubernetes cluster, you should first check the image that is running. As Fluentd has distributed plugins, the DaemonSet image may have specific plugins included, which ensures you can go directly from reading Kubernetes logs to the end destination.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This example has OpenSearch and Kafka included as plugins, so you should validate that the image you are using has the same plugins as Fluent Bit. Fluent Bit also supports Kubernetes enrichment on all logs, giving data around namespace, pod, labels and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Deployed as an Aggregator / Collector&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your Fluentd is deployed collecting logs from syslog, network devices or HTTP requests, you can first verify that Fluent Bit has the same capability. For example, Fluent Bit has syslog, TCP, HTTP and UDP plugins that can cover a majority of these use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, Fluent Bit also can receive OpenTelemetry HTTP1/gRPC, Prometheus Remote Write, HTTP gzip and Splunk HTTP Event Collector (HEC) as additional inbound signals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Adding a Telemetry Pipeline&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When migrating from Fluentd to Fluent Bit, we would also recommend looking at adding a Telemetry Pipeline in the middle of the agents and the destinations. This allows you to move larger pieces of processing logic within Fluentd agents downstream.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1024&#34; height=&#34;470&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image.png&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic on Fluentd to Fluent Bit&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-148542&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-300x138.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-768x353.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-900x413.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-436x200.png 436w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-871x400.png 871w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Configuration&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The configuration syntax between Fluentd and Fluent Bit is vastly different. While both have started to support YAML more recently, most legacy Fluentd configurations will still be written in the domain-specific configuration language that is XML-esque.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some general notes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Look at validating a single plugin at a time, and then at expanding to a single route (such as system logs to OpenSearch).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Buffering and thread settings are not as important within Fluent Bit.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Security settings should be similar.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When in doubt, reaching out to the Fluent community is useful in helping with some of the more granular settings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Custom Plugins&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When migrating, it’s important to ensure that Fluent Bit supports all plugins (sources and destinations). You should also check that it supports particular settings around authentication, authorization or access. This will be a manual process that can take some time. However, this will also allow you a chance to revisit decisions on specific data formats or plugin settings that you made in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Custom Processing Logic&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have labels, filters or other processing logic within Fluentd, it is important to note the functionality you are trying to achieve. While it may seem like just swapping those filters over might be easiest, you should also look at ways to migrate those directly into &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/explaining-the-fluent-bit-processor/&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit processors.&lt;/a&gt; If you have a significant amount of custom Ruby, you can use large language models (LLMs) to help convert it into suitable Lua.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Migrating Portions at a Time&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You don’t need to migrate all your functionality at once. Because Fluent Bit is lightweight and performant, you can look at ways to have each agent handle different portions of the workload. Over time you can follow the logic above to continue migrating without having to worry about log collection disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While migrating from Fluentd to Fluent Bit might seem like an enormous task, you have many options about how to attack and where to focus to achieve the highest impact. Of course migrations are also a great time to re-evaluate certain logic for improvement and even introduce new architecture patterns such as a telemetry pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for guided or assisted help, let me know. I have helped many folks migrate from Fluentd to Fluent Bit and even assisted with modernizing certain portions to a telemetry pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why migrate from Fluentd to Fluent Bit&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Fluent Bit you will get higher performance for the same resources you are already using; full OpenTelemetry support for logs, metrics, and traces as well as Prometheus support for metrics; simpler configuration and routing ability to multiple locations; higher velocity for adding custom processing rules; and integrated monitoring to better understand performance and dataflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What are some differences between Fluentd and Fluent Bit?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Fluentd, the main language is Ruby and initially designed to help users push data to big data platforms such as Hadoop. Meanwhile, Fluent Bit is written in C, with a focus on hyper performance in smaller systems (containers, embedded Linux).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Can Fluentd and Fluent Bit work together?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes Fluent Bit and Fluentd can work together, which means it’s possible to capture from more sources by using Fluentd and introduce the data into a Fluent Bit deployment. The Forward plugin has a defined standard that Fluent Bit and Fluentd both use. Some external products have also adopted this protocol so they can be connected directly to Fluent Bit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Fluentd 创建已有 14 年多了，并且仍然是企业中部署最广泛的日志收集技术之一。 Fluentd 的分布式插件架构和高度宽松的许可使其成为&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;云原生计算基金会 (CNCF)&lt;/a&gt; 现已毕业的项目的理想组成部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，淹没在遥测数据中的企业现在需要具有更高性能、对不断发展的模式和格式提供更多本机支持以及更高的处理灵活性的解决方案。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/ Fluent-bit/&#34;&gt;输入 Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;何时以及为何迁移？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/fluent-bit-v4-0/&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt; 最初是作为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://fluentbit.io/&#34;&gt;Fluent 生态系统&lt;/a&gt;中的一个子项目发展起来的，后来从 Fluentd 扩展到支持所有遥测类型 - 日志、指标和 痕迹。 Fluent Bit 现在是两者中更受欢迎的一个，部署量超过 150 亿次，亚马逊、谷歌、甲骨文和微软等公司都在使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit 还与 OpenTelemetry 信号、格式和协议完全一致，这确保用户能够随着遥测数据的增长和发展而继续处理遥测数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为项目维护者，我们最常见的问题是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我们如何迁移？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我们应该注意什么？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;迁移能给我们带来什么商业价值？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文旨在通过示例回答这些问题。我们希望帮助您轻松做出从 &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit-academy/&#34;&gt;Fluentd 迁移到 Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt; 的决定。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;为什么迁移？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是用户从 Fluentd 切换到 Fluent Bit 的原因的快速列表：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在您已使用的相同资源下获得更高的性能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;对日志、指标和跟踪的完整 OpenTelemetry 支持以及对指标的 Prometheus 支持&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更简单的配置和路由至多个位置的能力&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;添加自定义处理规则的速度更快&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;集成监控可更好地了解性能和数据流&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fluentd 与 Fluent Bit：有什么区别&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;背景&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解项目之间的所有差异，了解每个项目的背景及其构建的时代非常重要。 Fluentd 的主要语言是 Ruby，最初旨在帮助用户将数据推送到 Hadoop 等大数据平台。该项目遵循分布式架构，在安装和部署主二进制文件后安装插件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit 另一方面，是用 C 编写的，重点是炒作较小系统（容器、嵌入式 Linux）中的性能。该项目借鉴了 Fluentd 的插件，而是选择了作为核心二进制文件一部分的完全嵌入式插件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;性能&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从 Fluentd 切换到 Fluent Bit 的明显区别和主要价值是性能。使用 Fluent Bit，使用相同资源可以处理的日志量可能会增加 10 到 40 倍，具体取决于您使用的插件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit 是从头开始编写的，具有超高性能，重点是尽可能快地传输数据以进行数据分析。后来，我们发现性能足够高效，可以添加更多边缘处理，而不会影响使代理尽可能快的任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;路由&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit 的其他部分是从 Fluentd 遇到的挑战演变而来的，例如缓冲和路由。使用 Fluentd 时，多路由是事后才想到的，用户需要“复制”数据流以将数据路由到多个点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这使得配置管理成为一场噩梦，此外还实质上重复了路由该数据的资源需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Fluent Bit 中，缓冲区仅存储一次，这允许多个插件“订阅”数据流。这可确保数据存储一次并订阅多次，从而允许多路由，而无需权衡性能和配置疲劳。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;遥测信号焦点&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 Fluentd 最初是一个数据传送器，但它后来发展成为 Kubernetes 等项目和 Splunk 等公司中使用的日志记录代理。另一方面，Fluent Bit 最初是一个嵌入式指标收集器，随后出现日志文件。随着 Fluent Bit 的采用开始超过 Fluentd 的功能，OpenTelemetry 日志/指标/跟踪、Prometheus Scrape 和远程写入支持、eBPF 和分析支持等功能都被添加了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如今，Fluent Bit 与 OpenTelemetry 架构、格式和协议保持一致，旨在成为高性能的轻量级实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;自定义处理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluentd 和 Fluent Bit 有许多相同的处理器名称，但在自定义处理方面，选项却截然不同。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于 Fluentd，选项是“enable_ruby”，它允许配置中的自定义 Ruby 脚本执行操作。这可以有效地完成小任务；然而，随着逻辑变得更加复杂，它会带来很大的损失，从而增加更多的性能瓶颈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用 Fluent Bit，自定义处理是用 Lua 语言完成的，这提供了巨大的灵活性。然而，与 Fluentd 不同的是，Fluent Bit 的 Lua 处理器性能相当出色，并且可以大规模使用（100+ TB/天）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;自定义插件&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;两个项目都允许自定义插件可帮助您连接源或目的地。使用 Fluentd，这些自定义插件是“Ruby Gems”，您可以下载并将其安装到现有或新的安装或部署中。使用 Fluent Bit，可以用 Go 编写和编译自定义插件。还有一些新举措可以用您想要的任何语言编写自定义插件并将其编译到 WebAssembly 中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们从 Fluentd 的分布式插件架构中学到的一个教训是插件的数量可以呈指数级增长。然而，所需的质量和维护通常导致许多插件被放弃和不受支持。使用 Fluent Bit，插件全部合并到源代码本身中，这确保了与每个版本的兼容性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自定义插件仍然独立于主存储库。不过，我们正在寻找方法，让这些插件也能够在主 GitHub 存储库中共享原生 C 插件的相同优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;监控&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解数据如何穿越您的环境通常是部署 Fluentd 或 Fluent Bit 的用户的首要要求。使用 Fluentd，启用这些设置可能需要通过“monitor_agent”或使用第三方 prometheus 导出器插件进行复杂的配置。这些监控插件还会增加 Fluentd 的维护开销，从而影响性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit 将监控作为其核心功能的一部分，并且可以通过本机插件（“fluentbit_metrics”）检索或在 HTTP 端口上抓取。 Fluent Bit 的指标还比 Fluentd 包含更多信息，使您能够了解字节、记录、存储和连接信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;如何开始从 Fluentd 到 Fluent Bit 迁移&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们要回答的下一个问题是：您如何开始？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第一个重要的步骤是了解 Fluentd 是如何部署的、环境中发生什么处理以及数据在哪里流动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您不需要担心的事情：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;架构支持：&lt;/strong&gt;这两个应用程序都支持 x86 和 ARM。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;平台支持：&lt;/strong&gt;Fluent Bit 支持与 Fluentd 目前相同的功能，甚至更多。遗留系统可能有所不同，但重要的是要注意这些系统在两个 OSS 项目中都没有维护。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;正则表达式：&lt;/strong&gt;如果您使用 Onigmo 解析器库构建了一个大型正则表达式库，那么您就可以放心地知道 Fluent Bit 支持它。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;部署&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;作为代理部署（Linux 或 Windows 软件包）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当 Fluentd 在 Linux 或 Windows 上部署为代理时，其主要功能是收集本地日志文件或 Windows 事件日志并将它们路由到特定目的地。值得庆幸的是，Fluent Bit 的本地 col阅读功能与 Fluentd 相同，包括故障恢复、存储最后收集的日志行和本地缓冲的能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;作为 DaemonSet 部署在 Kubernetes 中&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果 Fluentd 在 Kubernetes 集群中作为 DaemonSet 运行，您应该首先检查正在运行的映像。由于 Fluentd 具有分布式插件，DaemonSet 镜像可能包含特定插件，这确保您可以直接从读取 Kubernetes 日志到达最终目的地。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此示例包含 OpenSearch 和 Kafka 作为插件，因此您应该验证您使用的图像是否具有与 Fluent Bit 相同的插件。 Fluent Bit 还支持 Kubernetes 对所有日志进行丰富，提供有关命名空间、pod、标签等的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;部署为聚合器/收集器&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的 Fluentd 部署为从 syslog、网络设备或 HTTP 请求收集日志，您可以首先验证 Fluent Bit 是否具有相同的功能。例如，Fluent Bit 具有 syslog、TCP、HTTP 和 UDP 插件，可以涵盖大多数这些用例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，Fluent Bit 还可以接收 OpenTelemetry HTTP1/gRPC、Prometheus Remote Write、HTTP gzip 和 Splunk HTTP Event Collector (HEC) 作为附加入站信号。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;添加遥测管道&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从 Fluentd 迁移到 Fluent Bit 时，我们还建议考虑在代理和目标中间添加遥测管道。这使您可以将 Fluentd 代理内的较大处理逻辑向下游移动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“1024”height =“470”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image.png”alt =“Fluentd 到 Fluent Bit 上的图形” 类=“wp-image-148542”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image.png 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-300x138.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-768x353.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-900x413.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-436x200.png 436w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/image-871x400.png 871w“尺寸=”自动， （最大宽度：1024px）100vw，1024px“referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;配置&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluentd 和 Fluent Bit 之间的配置语法有很大不同。虽然两者最近都开始支持 YAML，但大多数旧版 Fluentd 配置仍将使用 XML 式的特定于域的配置语言编写。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一些一般注意事项：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;考虑一次验证一个插件，然后扩展到单个路由（例如 OpenSearch 的系统日志）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;缓冲和线程设置在 Fluent Bit 中并不那么重要。&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;安全设置应该类似。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如有疑问，联系 Fluent 社区有助于帮助进行一些更精细的设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;自定义插件&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;迁移时，确保 Fluent Bit 支持所有插件（源和目标）非常重要。您还应该检查它是否支持有关身份验证、授权或访问的特定设置。这将是一个手动过程，可能需要一些时间。但是，这也让您有机会重新审视过去对特定数据格式或插件设置所做的决定。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;自定义处理逻辑&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果 Fluentd 中有标签、过滤器或其他处理逻辑，请务必注意您要实现的功能。虽然看起来只是交换这些过滤器可能是最简单的，但您还应该考虑将它们直接迁移到 &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/explaining-the-fluent-bit-processor/&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit 处理器/&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit 处理器的方法。&lt;/a&gt;如果您有大量自定义 Ruby，则可以使用大型语言模型 (LLM) 来帮助将其转换为合适的 Lua。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;一次迁移部分&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您不需要立即迁移所有功能。由于 Fluent Bit 是轻量级且高性能的，因此您可以考虑让每个代理处理工作负载的不同部分的方法。随着时间的推移，您可以按照上述逻辑继续迁移，而不必担心日志收集中断。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;结论&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然从 Fluentd 迁移到 Fluent Bit 似乎是一项艰巨的任务，但您可以选择多种方式进行攻击以及重点关注何处以实现最大影响。当然，迁移也是重新评估某些逻辑以进行改进甚至引入新的架构模式（例如遥测管道）的好时机。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您正在寻求指导或辅助帮助，请告诉我。我帮助许多人从 Fluentd 迁移到 Fluent Bit，甚至协助对遥测管道的某些部分进行现代化改造。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;常见问题&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;为什么从 Fluentd 迁移到 Fluent Bit&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用 Fluent Bit，您将在已使用的相同资源下获得更高的性能；对日志、指标和跟踪的完整 OpenTelemetry 支持以及对指标的 Prometheus 支持；更简单的配置和到多个位置的路由能力；添加自定义处理规则的速度更快；和集成监控，以更好地了解性能和数据流。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Fluentd 和 Fluent Bit 之间有哪些区别？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluentd的主要语言是Ruby，最初旨在帮助用户将数据推送到Hadoop等大数据平台p。同时，Fluent Bit 是用 C 编写的，重点是较小系统（容器、嵌入式 Linux）中的超性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Fluentd 和 Fluent Bit 可以一起工作吗？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;是的，Fluent Bit 和 Fluentd 可以一起工作，这意味着可以使用 Fluentd 从更多来源捕获数据并将数据引入 Fluent Bit 部署中。 Forward 插件有一个 Fluent Bit 和 Fluentd 都使用的定义标准。一些外部产品也采用了该协议，因此可以直接连接到Fluent Bit。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【🏆 How I passed the Certified Argo Project Associate (CAPA) exam — and why it was worth it】🏆 我如何通过 Argo 项目助理 (CAPA) 考试——以及为什么它值得</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/30/%f0%9f%8f%86-how-i-passed-the-certified-argo-project-associate-capa-exam-and-why-it-was-worth-it/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been working with ArgoCD or exploring GitOps, you’ve probably come across the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/certified-argo-project-associate-capa/&#34;&gt;Certified Argo Project Associate (CAPA)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;exam. I recently passed it, and in this post, I want to share:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Why I took the exam&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How I prepared (including all the resources I used)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What the experience was like&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Whether I’d recommend it&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a sales pitch. It’s a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;real-world guide&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;to help you prepare — and understand whether this certification is right for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;👩‍💻 My Background with Argo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working with&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;ArgoCD&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for over a year now as a senior cloud engineer. I’ve had first-hand experience managing real-world GitOps workflows, and designing deployment strategies using ArgoCD.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CAPA exam&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;doesn’t just focus on ArgoCD. It covers&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;four Argo projects&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Workflows&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo CD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Rollouts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Events&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While I had a solid foundation in GitOps and ArgoCD (which makes up 34% of the exam), I had little to no hands-on experience with&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Workflows, Rollouts, or Events&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;— and that’s where most of my preparation efforts went.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📚 My Study Strategy (1-Month Plan)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I prepared for the exam over the course of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;1 month&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;— with a focused, hands-on approach. Here’s the breakdown of how I studied and what resources I used:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🎓 1. Linux Foundation Course (LFS256)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a CNCF Ambassador, I had the opportunity to get the exam for free, and I also opted to purchase the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;“DevOps and Workflow Management with Argo (LFS256)”&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;training course.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pros:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Great introduction to the overall Argo ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cons:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;A bit high-level —&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;not deep enough&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;for actual exam configs or edge cases&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Verdict:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Good as a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;first stop&lt;/strong&gt;, but&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;not sufficient&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;alone&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🧪 2. Practice Repos, Examples, and Real Configs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once I understood the basics, I needed to go deeper. These resources helped me get&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;hands-on&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;with the kind of configurations and scenarios that appear in the exam:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📘 CNCF Exams GitLab Repository&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;👉&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/cncf-exams/certified-argo-project-associate-capa&#34;&gt;Certified Argo Project Associate CAPA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Contains&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;sample YAMLs&lt;/strong&gt;, key&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;resource definitions&lt;/strong&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;config settings&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;you need to know&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;practice exam section&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;is very close in difficulty to the actual test:&lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/cncf-exams/certified-argo-project-associate-capa/-/blob/main/5.%20Practice%20Exam.md?ref_type=heads&#34;&gt;Practice Exam Link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;✍️ Study Guides from the Community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These two blog posts were&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;absolute gold&lt;/strong&gt;. Both authors shared their notes while preparing, and their attention to detail helped me immensely:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://paulyu.dev/article/capa-study-guide&#34;&gt;Paulyu.dev CAPA Study Guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Al-HusseinHameedJasim/certified-argo-project-associate&#34;&gt;Al-Hussein Hameed Jasim’s GitHub Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They covered &lt;strong&gt;corner-case configurations, lesser-known CLI behaviors, and practical tips&lt;/strong&gt; that often go unmentioned in the official documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📝 3. Udemy Mock Exams&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also bought the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.udemy.com/course/certified-argo-project-associate-capa-mock-exams-2025-m/?couponCode=2021PM20&#34;&gt;CAPA Mock Exams Course on Udemy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Useful to get a feel for question formats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;However, the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;difficulty level was lower&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;than the real exam&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Great for&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;confidence building&lt;/strong&gt;, but&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t rely on it alone&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🧠 Exam Format &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what the actual exam looked like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;90 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;60 multiple-choice questions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You need&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;70% to pass&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You get&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;1 free retake&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;if you fail&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;majority of questions&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;were scenario-based. You won’t get by with just theory. You really need to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;understand YAML configuration&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;resource relationships&lt;/strong&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;use-case trade-offs&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;💡 My Favorite Part of the Journey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most fun part for me? Whenever I encountered a tricky ArgoCD config question, my mind immediately went to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Wait… could this solve that issue in our current project?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Studying for the CAPA exam gave me&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;new perspectives&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;on how to use ArgoCD better in production. It wasn’t just about passing — it was about&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;learning practical skills&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I could apply the next day at work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;✅ Would I Recommend It?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Absolutely —&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;if you’re already working with GitOps&lt;/strong&gt;, or planning to adopt Argo tools in your team. It’s not an “easy pass” cert, but with&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;1–2 months of focused prep&lt;/strong&gt;, you’ll gain:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-project knowledge&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(CD, Rollouts, Workflows, Events)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hands-on YAML and config skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;stronger grasp of GitOps principles&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;in action&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And a shiny CNCF-backed credential to show for it 🎉&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📎 TL;DR — My Tips&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Start with the LFS256 course&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Move on to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/cncf-exams/certified-argo-project-associate-capa&#34;&gt;CNCF GitLab repo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and hands-on YAMLs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://paulyu.dev/article/capa-study-guide&#34;&gt;Paulyu’s guide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Al-HusseinHameedJasim/certified-argo-project-associate&#34;&gt;Al-Hussein’s repo&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to go deep&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Practice with&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.udemy.com/course/certified-argo-project-associate-capa-mock-exams-2025-m/?couponCode=2021PM20&#34;&gt;Udemy mocks&lt;/a&gt;, but don’t rely on them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Learn actively — apply what you learn to your real-world projects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您一直在使用 ArgoCD 或探索 GitOps，您可能遇到过&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/certified-argo-project-associate-capa/&#34;&gt;认证 Argo 项目助理 (CAPA)&lt;/a&gt; 考试。我最近通过了它，在这篇文章中，我想分享：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我为什么参加考试&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我是如何准备的（包括我使用的所有资源）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;体验如何&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我是否会推荐&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这不是推销。这是一本&lt;strong&gt;现实世界指南&lt;/strong&gt;，可帮助您做好准备并了解该认证是否适合您。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;👩‍💻我与Argo的背景&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为一名高级云工程师，我已经在 &lt;strong&gt;ArgoCD&lt;/strong&gt; 工作了一年多。我拥有管理现实世界的 GitOps 工作流程以及使用 ArgoCD 设计部署策略的第一手经验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，&lt;strong&gt;CAPA 考试&lt;/strong&gt;不仅仅关注 ArgoCD。它涵盖&lt;strong&gt;四个 Argo 项目&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo 工作流程&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo CD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo 推出&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo 活动&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然我在 GitOps 和 ArgoCD 方面拥有坚实的基础（占考试的 34%），但我在&lt;strong&gt;工作流程、部署或事件&lt;/strong&gt;方面几乎没有任何实践经验 - 而这正是我大部分准备工作的方向。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📚我的学习策略（1个月计划）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我用了&lt;strong&gt;1个月&lt;/strong&gt;的时间准备考试 - 采用专注、实践的方法。以下是我的学习方式和使用的资源的详细信息：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🎓 1.Linux基础课程(LFS256)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为 CNCF 大使，我有机会免费参加考试，并且我还选择购买&lt;strong&gt;“使用 Argo 进行开发运营和工作流程管理 (LFS256)”&lt;/strong&gt;培训课程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;优点&lt;/strong&gt;：对整个 Argo 生态系统的精彩介绍&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;缺点：&lt;/strong&gt;层次有点高 - 对于实际考试配置或边缘情况&lt;strong&gt;不够深入&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;结论：&lt;/strong&gt;作为&lt;strong&gt;第一站&lt;/strong&gt;不错，但&lt;strong&gt;单独使用还不够&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🧪 2. 练习存储库、示例和真实配置&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;理解基础知识后，我需要更深入。这些资源帮助我&lt;strong&gt;亲身实践&lt;/strong&gt;考试中出现的配置和场景：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📘 CNCF 考试 GitLab 存储库理论&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;👉 &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/cncf-exams/certified-argo-project-associate-capa&#34;&gt;Argo 项目助理 CAPA 认证&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;包含您需要了解的&lt;strong&gt;示例 YAML&lt;/strong&gt;、关键&lt;strong&gt;资源定义&lt;/strong&gt;以及&lt;strong&gt;配置设置&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;模拟考试部分&lt;/strong&gt;的难度与实际考试非常接近：&lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/cncf-exams/certified-argo-project-associate-capa/-/blob/main/5.%20Practice%20Exam.md?ref_type=heads&#34;&gt;模拟考试链接&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;✍️来自社区的学习指南&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这两篇博文&lt;strong&gt;绝对是黄金&lt;/strong&gt;。两位作者在准备时分享了他们的笔记，他们对细节的关注对我帮助很大：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://paulyu.dev/article/capa-study-guide&#34;&gt;Paulyu.dev CAPA 学习指南&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Al-HusseinHameedJasim/certified-argo-project-associate&#34;&gt;Al-Hussein Hameed Jasim 的 GitHub 笔记&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它们涵盖了官方文档中经常未提及的&lt;strong&gt;极端情况配置、鲜为人知的 CLI 行为以及实用技巧&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📝 3. Udemy 模拟考试&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我还在 Udemy 上购买了&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.udemy.com/course/certified-argo-project-associate-capa-mock-exams-2025-m/?couponCode=2021PM20&#34;&gt;CAPA 模拟考试课程&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;有助于了解问题格式&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;但是，&lt;strong&gt;难度级别低于&lt;/strong&gt;低于真实考试&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;非常适合&lt;strong&gt;建立信心&lt;/strong&gt;，但&lt;strong&gt;不要单独依赖它&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🧠考试形式和体验&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;实际考试如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;90 分钟&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;60 道多项选择题&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;您需要&lt;strong&gt;70% 才能通过&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果失败，您可以&lt;strong&gt;免费重考 1 次&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;大多数问题&lt;/strong&gt;都是基于场景的。仅靠理论是行不通的。您确实需要&lt;strong&gt;了解 YAML 配置&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;资源关系&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;用例权衡&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;💡旅程中我最喜欢的部分&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对我来说最有趣的部分是什么？每当我遇到棘手的 ArgoCD 配置问题时，我的想法立即转向：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“等等......这可以解决我们当前项目中的问题吗？”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;学习中CAPA 考试让我对如何在生产中更好地使用 ArgoCD 有了&lt;strong&gt;新的看法&lt;/strong&gt;。这不仅仅是为了通过，而是为了&lt;strong&gt;学习实用技能&lt;/strong&gt;，我可以在第二天的工作中应用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;✅ 我会推荐它吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当然 - &lt;strong&gt;如果您已经在使用 GitOps&lt;/strong&gt;，或者计划在您的团队中采用 Argo 工具。这不是一个“轻松通过”的证书，但通过&lt;strong&gt;1-2 个月的集中准备&lt;/strong&gt;，您将获得：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;跨项目知识&lt;/strong&gt;（CD、部署、工作流程、活动）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YAML 和配置实践技能&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在实践中&lt;strong&gt;更好地掌握 GitOps 原则&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;还有一个由 CNCF 支持的闪亮证书 🎉&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;📎 TL;DR — 我的建议&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;从 LFS256 课程开始&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;继续学习&lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/cncf-exams/certified-argo-project-associate-capa&#34;&gt;CNCF GitLab 存储库&lt;/a&gt;和实践 YAML&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://paulyu.dev/article/capa-study-guide&#34;&gt;Paulyu 的指南&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Al-HusseinHameedJasim/certified-argo-project-associate&#34;&gt;Al-Hussein 的存储库&lt;/a&gt;深入了解&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.udemy.com/course/certified-argo-project-associate-capa-mock-exams-2025-m/?couponCode=2021PM20&#34;&gt;Udemy 模拟&lt;/a&gt;进行练习，但不要依赖它们&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;积极学习 - 将所学知识应用到实际项目中&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>