<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://rsshub.rssforever.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud Native Bangkok launched as the official chapter for Thailand】云本地曼谷作为泰国的官方章节推出</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/16/cloud-native-bangkok-launched-as-the-official-chapter-for-thailand/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We’re happy to announce that, following the growing interest in and adoption of Cloud Native technologies in Thailand, an official chapter was just launched within the CNCF platform: &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/cloud-native-bangkok/&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Bangkok&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXd37UXiNnJl1lLm-_tJCNR4h7U6te3NAH6Ysez-eplEsHPttuQVldzcvY74jQG_Q0fawWg0hFDl6etu8QcI3RQBvzTiiugwBvxSbI7Jxex2y2GZpTrnd7X6WQoHz1vaOlML-zE5WQ?key=hLMLLOePdSc-GDmLEGKMGQ&#34; alt=&#34;Cloud Native Bangkok logo&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Local enthusiasts from various companies formed it to connect the community of developers, operators, and users of Kubernetes and other Cloud Native technologies in Thailand. The new chapter will host regular online and offline events to spread knowledge, facilitate Cloud Native adoption, establish new professional connections, and collaborate on projects focused on fulfilling local needs, such as translating official documentation in Thai.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Cloud Native Bangkok organizers include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Saritrat Jirakulphondchai, Co-Founder at Jumpbox;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Jirayut Nimsaeng, CEO at Opsta (Thailand) Co., Ltd.;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Phisinee Sagulvanitchaporn, Co-Founder / Community Builder Lead at Jumpbox;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mongkol Thongkraikaew, Head of Platform Engineering at Ascend Money;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Damrongsak Reetanon, Chief Information Security Officer at MFEC;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sharkrit Impat, Head of Platform Engineering at Ascend Bit Company (ABC);&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Natechawin Suthison, Chief Technology and Product Officer at R’ket;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dmitry Shurupov, Co-Founder at Palark, a CNCF Ambassador;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sureeporn Yau, Co-Founder / Creative Community Builder Lead at Jumpbox.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud Native Bangkok’s first event will be held in a virtual format and is scheduled later this month, on May 22nd. It will use a bilingual approach, featuring talks in Thai and English.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The organizers of this community plan to host more meetups in the future and eventually bring a bigger Kubernetes Community Day (KCD) event to Thailand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join the newly created &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/cloud-native-bangkok/&#34;&gt;community group&lt;/a&gt; and the CNCF Slack’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud-native.slack.com/archives/C08RNTWCRK5&#34;&gt;#thailand channel&lt;/a&gt; to connect with Cloud Native enthusiasts in Thailand and stay informed about further activities! If you’re based in Thailand or know someone who might be interested in joining this new community, feel free to spread the word.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴地宣布，随着对泰国云本地技术的日益兴趣和采用，刚刚在CNCF平台内推出了官方章节：&lt;a href =“ https：//community.cncf.io/cloud-native-native-native-native-bangkok/”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-qw.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxd37uxinnjl1llm-_tjcnr4h7u6te3nah6nah6ysez-epleshpttttupttuqvldzcv Y74JQG_Q0FAWWG0HFDL6ETU8QCI3RQBVZTIIUGWBVXSBI7JXEX2Y2Y2GZPTRND7X6WQOHZ1VAOLML-ZE5WQ？ alt =“云本机曼谷徽标” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;各种公司的本地爱好者组成了IT，以连接泰国Kubernetes和其他Cloud Native Technologies的开发人员，经营者和用户社区。新章节将举办常规的在线和离线活动，以传播知识，促进云土著采用，建立新的专业联系并在满足本地需求的项目上进行合作，例如翻译泰国的官方文档。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云本地曼谷组织者包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Saritrat Jirakulphondchai，Jumpbox的联合创始人; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; OPSTA（泰国）Co.，Ltd的首席执行官Jirayut Nimsaeng; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Phisinee Sagulvanitchaporn，Jumpbox的联合创始人 /社区建设者的负责人&lt; / li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Mongkol Thongkraikaew，Aspend Money的平台工程主管； &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; MFEC首席信息安全官Damrongsak Reetanon; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Sharkrit Impat，Ascend Bit Company（ABC）的平台工程主管; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Natechawin Suthison，R&#39;Ket的首席技术和产品官; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; CNCF大使Palark的联合创始人Dmitry Shurupov; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Jumpbox的联合创始人 /创意社区建设者Leadeeporn Yau。&lt; / li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Cloud Native Bangkok的第一个活动将以虚拟格式举行，计划于5月22日晚些时候举行。它将使用双语方法，以泰语和英语为特色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个社区的组织者计划将来举办更多聚会，并最终将更大的Kubernetes社区日（KCD）活动带到泰国。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;加入新创建的&lt;a href =“ https://community.cncf.io/cloud-native-native-bangkok/cloud-native-bangkok/ href =“ https://cloud-native.slack.com/archives/c08rntwcrk5”&gt; #Thailand频道&lt;/a&gt;与泰国的云本地爱好者联系，并了解进一步的活动！如果您居住在泰国，或者认识可能有兴趣加入这个新社区的人，请随时传播。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Platform Democracy: Rethinking Who Builds and Consumes Your Internal Platform】平台民主：重新思考谁建立和消耗您的内部平台</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/23/platform-democracy-rethinking-who-builds-and-consumes-your-internal-platform/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Platform engineering has gone through multiple iterations over the years. First, there was the split between Development and Operations, a model that broke the flow of value by creating dependencies, bottlenecks, and misaligned incentives. Then came &lt;a href=&#34;https://devops.com/the-origins-of-devops-whats-in-a-name/&#34;&gt;DevOps&lt;/a&gt;, a movement that aimed to bridge the gap, but often resulted in teams taking on more responsibilities than they could sustainably manage, leading to inefficiencies and even security risks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To solve these challenges, &lt;a href=&#34;https://teamtopologies.com/key-concepts&#34;&gt;Platform Teams&lt;/a&gt; emerged. Their mission? To provide self-service infrastructure, tooling, and workflows that help developers ship faster and more safely. However, as organisations scaled, platform teams found themselves overwhelmed, collapsing under the weight of demand as they tried to be the single point of control for everything.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enter the concept of the Platform Group. This structure acknowledges that the boundaries of platform engineering are not rigid. Instead of a single team acting as the gatekeeper, multiple teams collaborate—some closer to infrastructure, others focusing on developer enablement. But even within this model, a key question remains: Who is a producer, and who is a consumer? Who defines business rules across services? And does it make sense to keep drawing such hard lines between platform builders and platform users?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What If Your Platform Was a Democracy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What if we moved beyond the idea of strict ownership and control? What if everyone could participate in shaping the platform, not just a central team? Imagine if internal platforms worked in &lt;a href=&#34;https://devops.com/game-on-go-multiplayer-mode-to-supercharge-your-internal-platform/&#34;&gt;multiplayer mode&lt;/a&gt;, where the production and consumption of platform capabilities were democratised.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the vision of Platform Democracy: a model where developers, security teams, SREs, and even external service providers collaborate seamlessly, instead of waiting on a central platform team to deliver everything.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Producers and Consumers: A New Perspective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To achieve Platform Democracy, we need to rethink the roles of &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/the-missing-piece-in-platform-engineering-recognizing-producers/&#34;&gt;producers and consumers within an internal platform&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Producers: These are teams that create and maintain services. But they aren’t just the central platform team. Producers can be:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;External providers offering managed services.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Internal teams build custom tools, APIs, or infrastructure components.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Compliance and security engineers ensure governance and policy adherence.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Consumers: These are teams that consume platform services. Their expectations are clear:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fast – They need services on demand, not through tickets or informal requests.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Safe – They should never feel like using a platform-provided service puts them at risk of failure, compliance issues, or job insecurity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Efficient – The platform should help them work at a higher level of abstraction, reducing toil and cognitive load.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Future of Platform Engineering Is Democratic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the goal is to empower everyone to quickly, safely, and efficiently produce and consume platform capabilities, how do we get there? The basic building blocks need to include:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Promises – A contract-driven approach that lets teams buy, build, or blend platform capabilities based on their needs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Plugins – A mechanism for ensuring security and compliance without slowing teams down.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fleet Upgrades – A way to continuously improve the platform without forcing disruptive migrations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enabling Platform Democracy with Kratix&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As platform engineering matures, the organizations that succeed won’t be the ones that rely on centralized, bottlenecked teams. Instead, they’ll be the ones that embrace &lt;strong&gt;Platform Democracy&lt;/strong&gt;, enabling developers, platform engineers, security teams, and even external providers to participate in building and maintaining internal platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/?group=projects-and-products&amp;amp;view-mode=grid&amp;amp;item=provisioning--automation-configuration--kratix&#34;&gt;Platform orchestrators&lt;/a&gt; like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kratix.io/&#34;&gt;Kratix&lt;/a&gt; provide the foundational building blocks for this shift. Kratix enables organizations to move from top-down control to collaborative, scalable platform engineering, ensuring that platform capabilities evolve dynamically as needs change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;平台工程多年来经历了多次迭代。首先，开发和操作之间存在分歧，该模型通过创建依赖性，瓶颈和未对准激励措施来打破价值流。然后来&lt;a href =“ https://devops.com/the-origins-of-devops-whats-whats-in-a-name/”&gt; devops &lt;/a&gt;，旨在弥合差距的运动&lt;/a&gt;通常导致团队承担更多的责任，使他们无法可持续地管理，导致了无效的风险和效率。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要解决这些挑战，&lt;a href =“ https://teamtopologies.com/key-concepts”&gt;平台团队&lt;/a&gt;出现。他们的使命？提供自助服务基础架构，工具和工作流程，以帮助开发人员更快，更安全地运输。但是，随着组织的扩大规模，平台团队发现自己不知所措，在需求的重量下崩溃，因为他们试图成为所有事物的单个控制点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;输入平台组的概念。这种结构承认平台工程的边界并不严格。多个团队与其担任守门人的团队不是一个团队，而是靠近基础架构，而其他团队则专注于开发人员启用。但是即使在该模型中，关键问题仍然存在：谁是生产者，谁是消费者？谁在服务跨服务定义业务规则？在平台构建器和平台用户之间保持如此硬的线路是有意义的吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;如果您的平台是民主的？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果我们超越了严格所有权和控制的想法，该怎么办？如果每个人都可以参与塑造平台，而不仅仅是一个中央团队，该怎么办？想象一下，如果内部平台在&lt;a href =“ https://devops.com/game-on-go-multiplayer-mode-to-supercharge-your-internal-platform/”&gt;多人游戏模式&lt;/a&gt;中，平台功能的生产和消费是民主。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是平台民主的愿景：开发人员，安全团队，SRES甚至外部服务提供商无缝协作，而不是等待中央平台团队提供所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要实现平台民主，我们需要重新考虑&lt;a href =“ https://thenewstack.io/the-missing-piece-piece-in-platform-eenderming-recognizing-producers/”&gt;生产者和消费者在内部平台内&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;生产者：这些团队创建和维护服务。但是他们不仅是中央平台团队。生产者可以：&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;提供托管服务的外部提供商。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;内部团队构建自定义工具，API或基础架构组件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;合规性和安全工程师确保治理和政策遵守。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;消费者：这些团队消耗PLATFORM服务。他们的期望很明显：&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;快 - 他们需要按需服务，而不是通过门票或非正式请求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;安全 - 他们永远不应该使用平台提供的服务会使他们处于失败，合规性问题或工作不安全感的风险。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;高效 - 该平台应帮助他们以更高水平的抽象工作，减少辛劳和认知负担。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;平台工程的未来是民主&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果目标是使每个人都能快速，安全，有效地生产和消耗平台功能，那么我们如何到达那里？基本构建块需要包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;承诺 - 一种以合同驱动的方式，可以根据他们的需求购买，构建或融合平台功能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;插件 - 确保安全和合规性而不会减慢团队的机制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;舰队升级 - 一种不强迫颠覆性迁移而不断改进平台的方法。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;启用kratix &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;的平台民主&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着平台工程的成熟，成功的组织将不会依靠集中式瓶颈团队。相反，他们将成为&lt;strong&gt;平台民主&lt;/strong&gt;的人，使开发人员，平台工程师，安全团队甚至外部提供商能够参与建立和维护内部平台。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://landscape.cncf.io/?group=projects-and-products＆view-mode = grid＆ode = grid＆item = provisioning-- automation-configuration--configuration--kratix-kratix”&gt;平台上的乐团为此转变提供基础构建块。 Kratix使组织能够从自上而下的控制转变为协作，可扩展的平台工程，以确保平台功能随着需求而动态发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Moving secure GitOps forward with Flux】向前移动安全的gitops用助手向前移动</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/19/moving-secure-gitops-forward-with-flux/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Spirits were high as the Flux team came together in London for KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe this year. With plenty to celebrate and even more to accomplish, one theme stood out as omnipresent: &lt;em&gt;project security&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project’s recent efforts have included a Workload Identity RFC and participation in the CNCF’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/security-slam-2025/&#34;&gt;Security Slam&lt;/a&gt;, and this is par for the course — Flux has always taken special care to build resilient software that is resistant to attack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This starts with the secure design of Flux’s components themselves:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Flux is built and signed at &lt;a href=&#34;https://slsa.dev/spec/v1.1/levels#build-l3-hardened-builds&#34;&gt;SLSA Build Level 3&lt;/a&gt; to prevent tampering of the upstream images.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Flux does not shell out to external binaries. We use native Go code and libraries for all of the reconcilers. This is true for Git, Helm, Kubernetes, Kustomize, and everything else, with the only exception being GPG.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All of Flux’s API state is stored directly within Kubernetes, and NetworkPolicy controls any network traffic to the flux-system namespace.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Each controller works on separate concerns and has RBAC scoped down to what is minimally necessary.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;https://fluxcd.io/flux/security/&#34;&gt;Security Documentation&lt;/a&gt; shows how security is first in Flux’s design.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That secure design is extended into a secure delivery mechanism with signing and verification of all assets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Git-less GitOps&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Flux supports reconciling desired state configuration from OCI Artifacts. It can also verify cosign signatures on those artifacts. This first-class support of OCI founds a scalable and secure basis for continuous delivery in even the most challenging software deployments.&lt;br&gt;Members of the Flux community have built the &lt;a href=&#34;https://fluxcd.control-plane.io/guides/d2-architecture-reference/&#34;&gt;D2 Reference Architecture&lt;/a&gt; with example &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/controlplaneio-fluxcd/d2-fleet&#34;&gt;repos&lt;/a&gt; that can run on a kind cluster.&lt;br&gt;Desired state is split up into separate fleet, infra, and apps repos, and the configuration of individual add-ons and components are built into signed OCI artifacts that can then be deployed independently to different target clusters from the fleet control artifacts:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1306&#34; height=&#34;1312&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25%E2%80%AFPM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;D2 Architecture - repository structure&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-132507&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM.jpg 1306w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-300x300.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-1019x1024.jpg 1019w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-150x150.jpg 150w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-768x772.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-900x904.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-199x200.jpg 199w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-398x400.jpg 398w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1306px) 100vw, 1306px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These OCI artifacts have their GitHub Actions build runner’s workflow and branch name encoded into the artifact signature, so it is possible for clusters to only accept builds that verifiably come from a specific workflow on the `main` branch.&lt;br&gt;This is enforced via OCIRepository’s spec.verify.matchOIDCIdentity field in the ResourceSets that deploy the tenants for apps, infra, and policy. Here is one example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/controlplaneio-fluxcd/d2-fleet/blob/09236f4/tenants/apps.yaml#L68-L83&#34;&gt;controlplaneio-fluxcd/d2-fleet@09236f4/tenants/apps.yaml#L68-L83&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;With this configuration, Flux rejects artifacts with improper build and source provenance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Multi-tenant workload identity&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Flux has a multi-tenant API — users can reconcile with least privilege using native Kubernetes ServiceAccounts. However, configuring access to Kubernetes-external cloud resources and API’s requires per-tenant secrets management.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are working on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/fluxcd/flux2/blob/main/rfcs/0010-multi-tenant-workload-identity/README.md&#34;&gt;RFC-0010&lt;/a&gt; to allow multi-tenant, namespaced usage of Workload Identity for speaking to external APIs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some use-cases where this strengthens security and simplifies configuration are fetching sources from OCI and using KMS keys for secrets decryption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Moving Flux forward&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re so thankful to the folks who took time during KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/orgs/fluxcd/projects/10&#34;&gt;make contributions&lt;/a&gt; on the Flux Security Slam. This group effort improved our CI workflows, added security-related metadata to the repo, and drafted the project’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-security.cncf.io/community/assessments/projects/flux/self-assessment/&#34;&gt;self assessment&lt;/a&gt; with TAG Security. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/security-slam-2025/&#34;&gt;Read about the Security Slam Transparency Report for more.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Flux strives to provide a secure, stable, scalable basis for cloud native continuous delivery.&lt;br&gt;The Flux Project is incredibly active right now, so come join our &lt;a href=&#34;https://fluxcd.io/community/&#34;&gt;project meetings&lt;/a&gt; and get involved!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;烈酒很高，因为今年的助力团队在伦敦参加了库贝康 + Cloudnativecon欧洲的聚会。有很多值得庆祝的事物，甚至还有更多要完成的主题，以无处不在：&lt;em&gt;项目安全&lt;/em&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project’s recent efforts have included a Workload Identity RFC and participation in the CNCF’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/security-slam-2025/&#34;&gt;Security Slam&lt;/a&gt;, and this is par for the course — Flux has always taken special care to build resilient software that is resistant to attack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这始于通量的安全设计本身的安全设计：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通量是在&lt;a href =“ https://slsa.dev/spec/spec/v1.1/levels#build-l3-hardend-builds”&gt; slsa构建级别3 &lt;/a&gt;以防止对上游图像进行篡改。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通量不会弹出外部二进制文件。我们为所有和解者使用本机GO代码和库。对于git，helm，kubernetes，kustomize和其他所有东西都是如此，唯一的例外是gpg。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Flux的所有API状态都直接存储在Kubernetes中，并且网络电池控制着磁通系统名称空间的任何网络流量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;每个控制器都在单独的问题上工作，并且RBAC范围降低了最必要的内容。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的&lt;a href =“ https://fluxcd.io/flux/security/”&gt; Security Documentation &lt;/a&gt;显示了Flux Design中的安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，通过签署和验证所有资产的安全设计将扩展到安全的交付机构中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;无git-gitops &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通量支持OCI伪像调和所需的状态配置。它还可以验证这些文物上的签名签名。对OCI的这种一流的支持也发现了即使是最具挑战性的软件部署也可以进行可扩展的基础。 href =“ https://github.com/controlplaneio-fluxcd/d2-fleet”&gt; repos&gt; repos &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;可以在一个类似的集群上运行。&lt;br&gt;所需的状态被分成单独的机队，iftra和apps存储库，并可以从单独的附加组件和组成的范围内组成，从而将其建立在各个方面，从而将其内置为独立的oci averts，该目标是独立的。控制工件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/screenshot-2025-2025-05-19-AT-2.25.25％2.25%E2%80%80%; srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/screenshot-2025-05-19-AT-2.25.25.25pgm.jpg 1306W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-300x300.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-1019x1024.jpg 1019w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Screenshot-2025-05-19-at-2.25.25 PM-150x150.jpg 150w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/screenshot-2025-2025-05-19-AT-2.25.25.255pm-768x77772.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/screenshot-2025-2025-05-19-at-2.25.2555555pm-900x904.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/screenshot-2025-05-19-AT-2.25.25.25.2555pm-199x200.jpg 199W，199W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/screenshot-2025-2025-05-19-AT-2.25.255pm-398x400.jpg 398W 398W 398W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些OCI伪像具有其github的动作，建立了跑步者的工作流程和编码为伪影签名的分支名称，因此群集只能接受从“主分支”上的特定工作流程中确定的构建。&lt;br&gt;这是通过Ocirepository的Spec.verify.verify.verify.matchoidcentity in the Inflaimestity intra Inflaimity infraimestity and Infraistity infra infra Inflaimestity infraimess and Infraimes infra and Infraist and Infraist and Infraimes infra。这是一个例子：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/controlplaneio-fluxcd/d2-fleet/blob/09236f4/tenants/apps.yaml#L68-L83&#34;&gt;controlplaneio-fluxcd/d2-fleet@09236f4/tenants/apps.yaml#L68-L83&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;With this配置，通量拒绝构建和源来源不当的工件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;多租户工作负载身份&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Flux具有多租户API  - 用户可以使用本机Kubernetes ServiceAccounts与最少特权调和。但是，配置访问Kubernetes-外部云资源，API需要每个秘密管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在研究&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/fluxcd/fluxcd/flux2/blob/main/rfcs/0010-multi-tenant-work-work-work-work-istentity/readme.me.md“&gt; rfc-0010 &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;某些用例加强安全性并简化配置正在从OCI获取源，并使用KMS键进行秘密解密。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;向前移动通量&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们非常感谢那些在库贝肯 + cloudnativecon欧洲花时间到&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/orgs/orgs/fluxcd/projects/10”&gt;“ https：//10”&gt;“ https://gith”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。该小组的努力改善了我们的CI工作流，将与安全相关的元数据添加到了存储库中，并起草了该项目的&lt;a href =“ https://tag-security.cncf.io/community/community/assessments/projects/projects/projects/projects/prox/flux/flux/flux/self-self-self-assessment/”&gt;自我评估&lt;/a&gt; with witt witch with witage &lt;/a&gt;与标记安全。 &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/reports/security-slam-2025/”&gt;阅读有关更多信息的安全SLAM透明度报告。&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Flux努力为云本机连续交付提供安全，稳定，可扩展的基础。&lt;br&gt;通量项目现在非常活跃，因此，加入我们的&lt;a a href =“ https://fluxcd.io/community/”&gt;项目会议&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style =“高度：80px” aria-hidded =“ true” class =“ WP-block-pacer是风格的80-120”&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing k0rdent v0.3.0: Smarter observability, smoother operations】介绍K0rdent v0.3.0：更明智的可观察性，更顺畅的操作</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/14/introducing-k0rdent-v0-3-0-smarter-observability-smoother-operations/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/02/24/introducing-k0rdent-design-deploy-and-manage-kubernetes-based-idps/&#34;&gt;previous blog&lt;/a&gt; I wrote a detailed version describing how k0rdent eases platform engineering at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those of you who are unaware, &lt;a href=&#34;https://k0rdent.io/&#34;&gt;k0rdent&lt;/a&gt; is a Kubernetes-native distributed container management environment (DCME) designed to help platform engineers manage infrastructure at massive scale. Built on Kubernetes’ maturity, stability, and wide adoption, k0rdent leverages community-driven standards to minimize adoption risks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Acting as a “super control plane,” it enables centralized, template-driven lifecycle management of Kubernetes clusters and services across on-prem, cloud, and hybrid environments. By providing a repeatable, secure, and standardized approach, k0rdent empowers teams to compose Internal Developer Platforms (IDPs) that support complex modern workloads, while ensuring consistency and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea behind this blog is to cover more details on the latest k0rdent release v0.3.0 which went out on the 30th of April 2025 and aims to achieve increased clarity for developers to identify what is going on in the cluster, helps provide more visibility for all different components, and allows self-management of the mothership cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re thrilled to announce the release of &lt;strong&gt;k0rdent v0.3.0&lt;/strong&gt;, now available across the&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/releases/tag/v0.3.0&#34;&gt; k0rdent Cluster Manager (kcm)&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/releases/tag/v0.3.0&#34;&gt; k0rdent Observability and FinOps (kof)&lt;/a&gt; components. This milestone brings significant enhancements focusing on observability, operational ease, and flexibility in infrastructure and service management.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Full documentation is available at:&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.k0rdent.io/v0.3.0&#34;&gt; docs.k0rdent.io/v0.3.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Highlights in v0.3.0&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The latest release brings advancements to multi-cluster Kubernetes management, with enhanced observability and operational improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Native Kubernetes events for observability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The release introduces native Kubernetes events emitted by core components:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cluster and service management controllers (kcm)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The kof-operator controller (kof)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These events offer transparency into system operations and support a new Cluster Deployment Dashboard for real-time visualization on the kof side.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Self-managed service templates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Service templates can now be defined and managed within the mothership cluster. This enhancement enables the following benefits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Template Logic isn’t exclusive to managed clusters anymore&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Faster iteration within a centralized environment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;GitOps-compliant declarative template management&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Helm chart integration with Flux sources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users can now install Helm charts using &lt;a href=&#34;https://fluxcd.io/flux/concepts/#sources&#34;&gt;Flux sources&lt;/a&gt; such as GitRepository, Bucket, and OCIRepository through service templates. This update:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simplifies integration with existing CI/CD pipelines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Supports enterprise-scale workflows&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enables standardized and version-controlled deployments&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dynamic infrastructure provider management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enhanced support for infrastructure provider management introduces greater flexibility in hybrid environments. This includes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Streamlined onboarding for new infrastructure providers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved lifecycle management capabilities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Readiness for hybrid and multi-cloud strategies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metrics and alerting enhancements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The release expands support for metrics and alerts collection across both mothership and regional kof storage clusters. Benefits include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved monitoring and fault detection&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced insight into resource utilization and performance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stability and bug fixes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release includes numerous improvements related to validation, performance, and bug resolution. Users can expect:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Smoother upgrades&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;More accurate resource handling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reduced system errors and improved reliability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/releases/tag/v0.3.0&#34;&gt;kcm v0.3.0 Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/releases/tag/v0.3.0&#34;&gt;kof v0.3.0 Release Notes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.k0rdent.io/v0.3.0/&#34;&gt;v0.3.0 Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking ahead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k0rdent v0.3.0 reinforces our mission to provide a robust, Kubernetes-native platform management framework. With enhanced observability, flexible service orchestration, and GitOps alignment, this release lays the groundwork for secure and scalable infrastructure operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We invite you to explore the release, engage with the project, and share your feedback via &lt;a href=&#34;http://slack.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;Slack&lt;/a&gt; or our&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent&#34;&gt; GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the k0rdent community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Platform engineers today face increasing demands—but they don’t have to tackle them alone. k0rdent is 100% open-source and community-driven, offering the flexibility, tools, and ecosystem needed to manage distributed infrastructure efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Built by an international team of passionate developers, k0rdent thrives on collaboration. We welcome contributions and ideas to expand and improve the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get Involved:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;⭐️Drop a star to support the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/k0rdent&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0rdent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; project&lt;br&gt;✅ Explore the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/community&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0rdent Community repo on GitHub&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;✅ Join the #k0rdent channel on &lt;a href=&#34;http://slack.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF Community Slack &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;(Sign up for CNCF Slack, then join #k0rdent)&lt;br&gt;✅ Sign up via our &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/EDwvAH11fsKmrar78&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Invitation Form&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to attend Team k0rdent’s regular Office Hours&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be part of the movement—let’s build the future of Kubernetes-native infrastructure together!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我的&lt;p&gt;中，https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/02/02/24/introducing-k0rdent-design-deploy-and-manage-manage-manage-manage-kubernetes----------------------- kubernetes-基于基于的-Idps/“&gt;上一个博客&lt;/a&gt;我写了一个详细的platept &lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt; eases platport &lt;/eases platport &lt;/stals &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于那些不了解的人，&lt;a href =“ https://k0rdent.io/”&gt; k0rdent &lt;/a&gt;是一个kubernetes-native分布式集装箱管理环境（DCME），旨在帮助平台工程师以大规模管理基础设施。基于Kubernetes的成熟度，稳定性和广泛采用，K0rdent利用社区驱动的标准来最大程度地降低采用风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;充当“超级控制平面”，它可以在本地，云和混合环境中启用Kubernetes群集和服务的集中模板驱动的生命周期管理。通过提供可重复，安全和标准化的方法，K0rdent授权团队组成了内部开发人员平台（IDP），以支持复杂的现代工作负载，同时确保一致性和可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该博客背后的想法是要介绍2025年4月30日发布的最新K0rdent版本v0.3.0的更多详细信息，旨在使开发人员更加清晰地确定集群中发生的事情，有助于为所有不同的组件提供更多的可见性，并允许自我管理对母亲的自我管理。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re thrilled to announce the release of &lt;strong&gt;k0rdent v0.3.0&lt;/strong&gt;, now available across the&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/releases/tag/v0.3.0&#34;&gt; k0rdent Cluster Manager (kcm)&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/releases/tag/v0.3.0”&gt; k0rdent可观察性和Finops（KOF）&lt;/a&gt;组件。这个里程碑带来了重大的增强，重点是基础设施和服务管理中的可观察性，易于操作性和灵活性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完整文档可用：&lt;a href =“ https://docs.k0rdent.io/v0.3.0”&gt; docs.k0rdent.io/v0.3.0 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; v0.3.0 &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;中的关键亮点&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最新版本为多群体Kubernetes管理带来了进步，并具有增强的可观察性和运营改进。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;天然Kubernetes事件，可观察到&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该版本引入了由核心组件发出的天然kubernetes事件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;集群和服务管理控制器（KCM）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; KOF-操作器控制器（KOF）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些事件为系统操作提供了透明度，并支持在KOF侧实时可视化的新集群部署仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自我管理的服务模板&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在可以在母亲集群中定义和管理服务模板。这种增强能够带来以下好处：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;模板逻辑不再是托管群集的独特之处&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更快集中环境中的迭代&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;符合Gitops的声明模板管理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;与通量源的掌舵图集成&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户现在可以使用&lt;a href =“ https://fluxcd.io/flux/conectes/#sources”&gt;通量源&lt;/a&gt;（例如GitrePository，Bucket和Ocirepository）通过服务模板通过服务模板来安装HELM图表。此更新：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;简化与现有CI/CD管道的集成&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持企业规模的工作流&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;启用标准化和版本控制的部署&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;增强对基础设施提供商管理的支持在混合环境中引入了更大的灵活性。这包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;简化了新基础架构提供商的登机工作&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;改进的生命周期管理功能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;准备混合和多云策略&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;指标和提醒增强&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该版本扩大了对母舰和区域KOF存储群体的指标和警报收集的支持。好处包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;改进的监视和故障检测&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;增强了对资源利用和绩效的见解&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;稳定性和错误修复&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本包括与验证，性能和错误分辨率有关的许多改进。用户可以期望：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更平滑升级&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更准确的资源处理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;降低了系统错误并提高可靠性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;了解更多&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kcm/releases/tag/v0.3.0”&gt; kcm v0.3.0发行笔记&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/kof/releases/tag/v0.3.0”&gt; kof v0.3.0发行说明&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://docs.k0rdent.io/v0.3.0/”&gt; v0.3.0文档&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;向前看&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; k0rdent v0.3.0加强了我们提供强大的kubernetes-native平台管理框架的使命。该版本具有增强的可观察性，灵活的服务编排和Gitops对齐方式，为安全可扩展的基础设施操作奠定了基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们邀请您探索发行版，与项目互动，并通过&lt;a href =“ http://slack.cncf.io/”&gt; slack &lt;/a&gt;或我们的&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;加入K0rdent社区&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;平台工程师如今面临着越来越多的需求，但他们不必独自解决。 K0rdent是100％开源D社区驱动的，提供有效管理分布式基础架构所需的灵活性，工具和生态系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由国际热情开发人员团队建立的K0rdent在协作方面蓬勃发展。我们欢迎贡献和想法扩展和改进项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;参与：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;⭐️Dropa星可支持&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/k0rdent/k0rdent”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k0rdent &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; project &lt;br&gt; project &lt;br&gt;✅ github &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;✅&lt;&lt;a href =“ http:/ http://slack.cncf.io/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; cncf community slack&gt; &lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://forms.gle/edwvah11fskmrar78”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;社区邀请表格&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;参加K0rdent团队的常规办公时间&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;成为运动的一部分 -  LET的建立Kubernetes-Native基础设施的未来！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A milestone for lightweight Kubernetes: k0s joins CNCF sandbox】轻量级Kubernetes的里程碑：K0S加入CNCF沙箱</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/20/a-milestone-for-lightweight-kubernetes-k0s-joins-cncf-sandbox/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mirantis.com/blog/a-milestone-for-lightweight-kubernetes-k0s-joins-cncf-sandbox/&#34;&gt;Mirantis blog&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;by Prithvi Raj&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;2160&#34; height=&#34;1216&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70.webp&#34; alt=&#34;k0s image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-132041&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70.webp 2160w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-1024x576.webp 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-768x432.webp 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-900x507.webp 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-1800x1013.webp 1800w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-355x200.webp 355w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-711x400.webp 711w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 2160px) 100vw, 2160px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce that&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://k0sproject.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;k0s&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, our lightweight, zero dependencies, and fully open-source Kubernetes distribution, has officially joined the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) as a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Sandbox project&lt;/strong&gt;! This is a significant milestone in our journey, and we couldn’t be more excited about what lies ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CNCF is the home for the most innovative cloud-native projects, and being part of this community reinforces our commitment to advancing Kubernetes usability and adoption for everyone. Joining the CNCF Sandbox program provides us with an incredible opportunity to collaborate with the community, gain valuable feedback, and scale our efforts to make Kubernetes more accessible and efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is k0s?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k0s was designed to be a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;zero-friction Kubernetes distribution&lt;/strong&gt;, catering to the needs of developers, operators, and edge computing enthusiasts. Here’s what makes k0s stand out:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightweight and Minimal&lt;/strong&gt;: A single binary that encapsulates all necessary components, making installation and maintenance effortless.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fully Open Source&lt;/strong&gt;: Built with transparency and a focus on community-driven innovation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optimized for Data Center to Edge Use Cases&lt;/strong&gt;: With a compact footprint and high efficiency, can be used in centralized data centers while also being a perfect fit for edge and resource-constrained environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified Management&lt;/strong&gt;: Reduced complexity while maintaining full Kubernetes functionality.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From developers spinning up clusters on their laptops, to centralized large scale production clusters, to operators managing resource constrained AI inference engines at the edge, k0s has proven itself as a versatile and reliable solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why CNCF Sandbox Matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CNCF Sandbox is an entry point for early-stage projects that show promise in the cloud-native ecosystem. It offers:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Support&lt;/strong&gt;: Access to a broad and engaged community of developers and users.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visibility&lt;/strong&gt;: Greater exposure to end users, contributors, and organizations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: A chance to work closely with other CNCF projects, fostering interoperability and innovation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By becoming a CNCF Sandbox project, k0s is poised to gain invaluable feedback and contributions that will help us refine and expand our capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What This Means for k0s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Joining the CNCF paves a way for better:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transparency&lt;/strong&gt;: Reinforcing our open governance and commitment to community-led development.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Innovation&lt;/strong&gt;: Continuing to push boundaries to make Kubernetes accessible in new and exciting ways.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;: Working alongside other CNCF projects and members to advance the cloud-native ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This milestone marks the beginning of an exciting new chapter, where the k0s community and contributors can work together to shape the future of Kubernetes at the edge and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the Journey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We want to express our heartfelt gratitude to everyone who has contributed to and supported k0s thus far. This achievement wouldn’t have been possible without you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to k0s, now is the perfect time to get involved! Here’s how you can join the journey:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try k0s&lt;/strong&gt;: Download and get started with k0s &lt;a href=&#34;https://k0sproject.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://k0sproject.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;here&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contribute&lt;/strong&gt;: Check out our GitHub repository and join the community discussions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spread the Word&lt;/strong&gt;: Share your experiences with k0s and help us grow the community.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re excited about the road ahead and look forward to collaborating with the CNCF community to make Kubernetes simpler, lighter, and more powerful for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for being part of our story!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初发表在&lt;a href =“ https://www.mirantis.com/blog/a-milestone-for-lightweight-kubernetes-k0s-k0s-koins-koins-joins-cncf-sandbox/-&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;2160&#34; height=&#34;1216&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70.webp&#34; alt=&#34;k0s image&#34; class =“ wp-image-132041” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/205/filters-quality70.webp 2160w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-300x169.webp 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-1024x576.webp 1024W，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-768x432.webp 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-quality70-quality70-900x507.webp 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/2025/2025/20111113.1013.703.703.703.703.70-113 https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-355x200.webp 355w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/filters-quality70-711x400.webp 711W“ sizes =” auto，（最大宽度：2160px）100vw，2160px“ referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce that &lt;a href=&#34;https://k0sproject.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;k0s&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, our lightweight, zero dependencies, and fully open-source Kubernetes distribution, has officially joined the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) as a &lt;strong&gt;Sandbox项目&lt;/strong&gt;！这是我们旅程中一个重要的里程碑，我们对未来的情况并不感到兴奋。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CNCF是最具创新性的云本地项目的家园，成为该社区的一部分，加强了我们致力于促进每个人的可用性和采用的承诺。加入CNCF沙箱计划为我们提供了与社区合作，获得宝贵的反馈并扩展我们为使Kubernetes更加易于访问和高效的努力的难以置信的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是k0s？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; k0s被设计为&lt;strong&gt;零摩擦分销&lt;/strong&gt;，满足了开发人员，运营商和边缘计算爱好者的需求。这是使K0脱颖而出的原因：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;轻巧且最小&lt;/strong&gt;：一种封装所有必要组件的单个二进制文件，使安装和维护毫不费力。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;完全开源的&lt;/strong&gt;：以透明度和关注社区驱动创新为基础。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;针对数据中心进行优化到边缘用例&lt;/strong&gt;：具有紧凑的足迹和高效率，可以在集中式数据中心中使用，同时也非常适合边缘和资源受限的环境。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简化的管理&lt;/strong&gt;：降低复杂性，同时保持完整的kubernetes功能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来自DevelopeRS将笔记本电脑上的簇旋转到集中大规模生产群集，运营商管理资源受限的AI推理引擎的运营商，K0S已证明自己是一种通用和可靠的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么cncf沙盒很重要&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CNCF沙盒是早期项目的切入点，这些项目在云本地生态系统中显示出希望。它提供：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;社区支持&lt;/strong&gt;：访问一个广泛而参与的开发人员和用户的社区。&lt;/​​li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可见性&lt;/strong&gt;：最终用户，贡献者和组织的接触更多。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;协作机会&lt;/strong&gt;：与其他CNCF项目紧密合作的机会，促进互操作性和创新。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过成为CNCF沙盒项目，K0S准备获得宝贵的反馈和贡献，以帮助我们完善和扩大我们的能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;这对k0s &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;加入CNCF铺平了一种更好的方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;透明度&lt;/strong&gt;：加强我们对社区主导发展的公开治理和承诺。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;创新&lt;/strong&gt;：继续推动界限以使Kubernetes以新颖而令人兴奋的方式访问。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;合作&lt;/strong&gt;：与其他CNCF项目和成员一起推进云本地生态系统。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个里程碑标志着令人兴奋的新章节的开始，K0S社区和贡献者可以共同努力，以塑造边缘及以后的Kubernetes的未来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;加入旅程&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们想对迄今为止为K0做出贡献和支持的每个人表示衷心的感谢。没有您，这一成就是不可能的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您是K0的新手，那么现在是参与的最佳时机！您可以加入旅程：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;尝试K0S &lt;/strong&gt;：下载并开始使用K0S &lt;a href =“ https://k0sproject.io/” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noreferrer noopener”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a a href = &lt;a href =“ NOOPENER“&gt; &lt;u&gt;此处&lt;/u&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;贡献&lt;/strong&gt;：查看我们的GitHub存储库并加入社区讨论。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;传播这个词&lt;/strong&gt;：与K0分享您的经验并帮助我们发展社区。&lt;/​​li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们对未来的道路感到兴奋，并期待与CNCF社区合作，使Kubernetes更简单，更轻，更强大。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;感谢您成为我们故事的一部分！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Linkerd 2.18: Battlescars, lessons learned, and preliminary Windows support】宣布Linkerd 2.18：BattlesCars，学习的课程和初步的Windows支持</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/09/announcing-linkerd-2-18-battlescars-lessons-learned-and-preliminary-windows-support/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We’re happy to announce the release of Linkerd 2.18. The theme of this release is &lt;em&gt;battlescars&lt;/em&gt;: we’ve&amp;nbsp; added features and updated functionality to reduce operational pain in response to real life, hard-won lessons we’ve learned with our customers who have pushed the limits of what Linkerd (and Kubernetes itself!) can do. This release also introduces an experimental build of the proxy for Windows environments, an exciting new area for Linkerd.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Infrastructure software means nothing if it is not reliable. Linkerd has now had over 9 years of continuous improvement and evolution, and our goal is to build a service mesh that our users can rely on for 100 years. Linkerd 2.18 release is the second major version since the &lt;a href=&#34;https://buoyant.io/blog/linkerd-forever&#34;&gt;announcement of Buoyant’s profitability, and Linkerd’s sustainability, last October&lt;/a&gt; and continues our laser focus on &lt;em&gt;operational simplicity—&lt;/em&gt;delivering the notoriously complex service mesh feature set in a way that is manageable by human beings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Battlescars&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release includes three significant changes based on our experience helping our customers run Linkerd at the boundaries of scale: protocol declarations, GitOps-compatible multicluster, and changes to Gateway API support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protocol declarations&lt;/strong&gt;. Since the very beginnings of Linkerd we have followed what is essentially the Hippocratic oath: if you add Linkerd to a functioning Kubernetes application, the application should continue functioning! This obvious-sounding statement is tremendously difficult to accomplish, but is key to Linkerd’s reputation for simplicity. A foundational feature here has been &lt;em&gt;protocol detection&lt;/em&gt;: rather than requiring the user to configure the protocols used by applications, Linkerd will automatically determine them just by looking at the data passed through the proxy. This allows you to “drop in” Linkerd without configuration and have your application continue to work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the majority of cases, protocol detection just works. But in extreme situations, it can make things more complicated. One particularly egregious issue is that if the cluster is under extreme load, the application may not send data in time for protocol detection to happen! Linkerd will fall back to treating the connection as raw TCP data, and HTTP-specific features will suddenly be disabled for that connection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To avoid this unpredictable behavior, Linkerd 2.18 will now optionally read the protocol for a port from the &lt;em&gt;appProto&lt;/em&gt; field on Kubernetes Service objects. When this field is specified, Linkerd will not perform protocol detection and instead just use the configured protocol. There are some interesting implementation details under the hood (to improve efficiency, Linkerd transparently upgrades HTTP/1.1 connections to HTTP/2 ones in between client and server proxies; and we make use of this to transit protocol information between proxies) but the net result is that avoiding protocol declaration for a Service is as easy as configuring the appProtocol field:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: v1&#xA;kind: Service&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: myService&#xA;spec:&#xA;  ports:&#xA;  - name: myPort&#xA;    port: 8090&#xA;    protocol: tcp&#xA;    appProtocol: http&#xA;    targetPort: 8090&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve also added a host of metrics to capture Linkerd’s protocol detection behavior, so as to make diagnosing future issues even easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitOps-compatible multicluster linking. &lt;/strong&gt;Linkerd’s multicluster capabilities allow applications to communicate between Kubernetes clusters in a way that is secure, even across the open Internet, and fully transparent to the application. Linkerd first introduced multicluster connectivity with the release of Linkerd 2.8 in 2020, allowing adopters to enable a full range of multicluster options including multi-cloud and hybrid cloud deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At that point in time, multicluster adoption in the Kubernetes ecosystem was largely ad-hoc, with small numbers of “pet” clusters. Today, multicluster adoption is significantly different. Linkerd adopters sometimes run Linkerd on hundreds or thousands of clusters, and will typically manage their infrastructure via GitOps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Linkerd 2.14, we took a first step to supporting new multicluster patterns by introducing &lt;a href=&#34;https://linkerd.io/2/tasks/pod-to-pod-multicluster/&#34;&gt;pod-to-pod multicluster&lt;/a&gt; for platforms with flat networks. In Linkerd 2.17, we introduced federated services, a new model for services that span many clusters. In Linkerd 2.18, we’ve further improved multicluster by allowing the creation of all Link resources in a declarative fashion, making it fully GitOps-compatible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gateway API decoupling.&lt;/strong&gt; Since the release of Linkerd 2.12 in 2022, Linkerd has been leading the charge in using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway-api.sigs.k8s.io/&#34;&gt;Gateway API&lt;/a&gt; as a core configuration mechanism. With the 2.14 release, Linkerd became the first service mesh to achieve conformance with the Gateway API &lt;em&gt;mesh&lt;/em&gt; profile.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our initial approach here was “batteries included”: since most adopters did not have the Gateway API types, Linkwes would bundle them by default. As the Gateway API itself matures and as adoption of the Gateway API spreads across more projects, this approach has started to cause friction as &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; projects have started installing, or requiring, specific versions of the Gateway API types.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Linkerd 2.18 will be the last release that installs Gateway API types by default. In this release, we’ve bumped the installed versions of these types; we’ve added support for Gateway API version 1.2.1, the latest available; and we’ve improved our documentation with recommendations for how users should &lt;a href=&#34;https://linkerd.io/2-edge/features/gateway-api/#managing-the-gateway-api&#34;&gt;manage the Gateway API&lt;/a&gt; across Linkerd and other projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Experimental Windows build&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 2.18 release ships with an experimental build of the proxy for Windows machines. This is a critical first step in our path to full Window support. If you are interested in running Linkerd in Windows environments—please reach out!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Other fun stuff&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 2.18 release also fixes a smattering of smaller issues. Federated services now propagate metadata dynamically as the set of underlying services change over time. Multicluster service labels and annotations can now be filtered, to avoid sharing cluster-specific metadata (e.g. from tools like ArgoCD). And proxy CPU usage can now be configured in terms of the number of available cores on the machine, easing certain types of resource configurations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Getting your hands on Linkerd 2.18&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the next few days, we will publish the official stable release package of Buoyant Enterprise for Linkerd, BEL 2.18.0, as well as a comprehensive changelog and upgrade guidance for existing Linkerd users. BEL is the enterprise distribution of Linkerd. It is free for anyone to download and use in non-production environments, and free for companies with fewer than 50 employees to run in production. BEL is the distribution of Linkerd that we run ourselves. You can &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.buoyant.io/&#34;&gt;get started with BEL in under five minutes&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们很乐意宣布发布Linkerd 2.18。该版本的主题是&lt;em&gt; battlescars &lt;/em&gt;：我们添加了功能和更新功能，以减少对现实生活的操作疼痛，我们已经与客户了解到的客户所学到的硬击课程，他们推动了Linkerd（和Kubernetes本身！）可以做到的限制。该版本还引入了Windows Environments代理的实验性构建，这是一个令人兴奋的Linkerd。&lt;/p&gt;的新领域。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基础架构软件如果不可靠，则无关紧要。 Linkerd现在已经有9年以上的持续改进和演变，我们的目标是建立一个服务网，我们的用户可以依靠100年。 Linkerd 2.18发行版是第二个主要版本以来是自&lt;a href =“ https://buoyant.io/blog/linkerd-forever”&gt;宣布《浮力盈利能力》和Linkerd的可持续性，以及去年10月的可持续性&lt;/a&gt;，并延续了我们的激光对人类的工作&lt;em&gt; simperational nistation &lt;em&gt; emementials nistimational-emess nistimational-emess nistimentime n is a in emess aw/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/生物。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; battlescars &lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本包括基于我们的经验，可以帮助客户在规模的边界运行Linkerd：协议声明，与Gitops兼容的多群集以及对Gateway API支持的更改。&lt;/p&gt;更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;协议声明&lt;/strong&gt;。自从Linkerd的开始时，我们遵循了基本上是希波克拉底宣誓的内容：如果将Linkerd添加到功能的Kubernetes应用程序中，则该应用程序应继续运行！这种明显的声明很难完成，但这是Linkerd以简单性而闻名的关键。此处的基本功能是&lt;em&gt;协议检测&lt;/em&gt;：而不是要求用户配置应用程序使用的协议，而是只能通过查看通过代理传递的数据来自动确定它们。这使您可以在不配置的情况下“插入” Linkerd，并使您的应用程序继续工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在大多数情况下，协议检测只是有效的。但是在极端情况下，它可以使事情变得更加复杂。一个特别令人难忘的问题是，如果集群处于极端负载下，则该应用程序可能不会及时发送数据以进行协议检测！ Linkerd将落后于将连接视为RAW TCP数据，而该连接的HTTP特定功能将突然被禁用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了避免这种不可预测的行为，Linkerd 2.18现在将选择从kubernetes服务对象上的&lt;em&gt; appproto &lt;/em&gt;字段读取端口的协议。指定此字段时，Linkerd将不会执行协议检测，而只需使用已配置的协议即可。引擎盖下有一些有趣的实现详细信息（为了提高效率，Linkerd透明地升级了http/1.1连接到客户端和服务器代理之间的HTTP/2；而我们和我们的连接；利用它来在代理之间传输协议信息），但净结果是避免服务的协议声明与配置AppProtocol字段一样容易：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：v1&#xA;善良：服务&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：MyService&#xA;规格：&#xA;  端口：&#xA;   - 名称：Myport&#xA;    端口：8090&#xA;    协议：TCP&#xA;    AppProtocol：http&#xA;    TargetPort：8090&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还添加了许多指标来捕获Linkerd的协议检测行为，以使诊断更容易诊断。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Gitops兼容的多簇链接。 &lt;/strong&gt; Linkerd的多簇功能允许应用程序以安全的方式在Kubernetes群集之间进行通信，即使在开放的Internet上也可以完全透明。 Linkerd首先引入了多簇连接性，并在2020年发行了Linkerd 2.8，允许采用者启用一系列多群集选项，包括多云和混合云部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在那个时间点，Kubernetes生态系统中的多簇采用在很大程度上是临时的，其中少量“ PET”簇。如今，多群集的采用率显着差异。 Linkerd采用者有时会在数百或数千个集群上运行Linkerd，通常会通过Gitops管理其基础架构。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Linkerd 2.14中，我们迈出了第一步，通过引入&lt;a href =“ https://linkerd.io/2/tasks/pod-te-pod-te-pod-pod-multicluster/”&gt; pod-to-to-to-pod-pod-pod multicluster &lt;/a&gt;用于具有平坦网络的平台的平台，以支持新的多群集模式。在Linkerd 2.17中，我们引入了Federated Services，这是一种跨越许多集群的服务的新模型。在Linkerd 2.18中，我们通过允许以声明性的方式创建所有链接资源，从而进一步改善了多群集，使其完全兼容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;网关API解耦。&lt;/strong&gt;自2022年Linkerd 2.12发布以来，Linkerd一直在使用&lt;a href =“ https://gateway-api.sig.sigs.k8s.io/”&gt; Gateway API &lt;/a&gt;作为核心配置机制。使用2.14版本，Linkerd成为了第一个与Gateway API &lt;em&gt;网格配置符合的服务网格。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们最初的方法是“包括电池”：由于大多数采用者没有网关API类型，因此linkwes默认情况下会捆绑它们。随着网关API本身的成熟并采用网关API在更多项目中传播时，这种方法已开始引起摩擦，因为&lt;em&gt;其他项目已经开始安装或需要Gateway API类型的特定版本。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Linkerd 2.18将是默认安装网关API类型的最后一个版本。在此版本中，我们碰到了这些类型的安装版本。我们添加了对Gateway API版本1.2.1的支持，最新的可用；我们通过建议用户应如何&lt;a href =“ https://linkerd.io/2-edge/fea提出建议，我们改进了文档。tures/gateway-api/＃管理the-gateway-api”&gt;管理网关api &lt;/a&gt;遍布Linkerd和其他项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;实验窗口构建&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2.18释放船，具有实验性的Windows机器代理。这是我们进行全窗户支持的道路中的关键第一步。如果您有兴趣在Windows环境中运行Linkerd，请伸出援手！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;其他有趣的东西&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2.18版本还解决了大量较小问题。现在，随着基础服务的一组随着时间的变化，联邦服务现在动态地传播元数据。现在可以过滤多簇服务标签和注释，以避免共享特定于群集的元数据（例如，来自诸如argoCD之类的工具）。现在可以根据机器上可用的内核数来配置代理CPU的使用，从而简化了某些类型的资源配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;启动您的链接器2.18 &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在接下来的几天中，我们将发布针对BEL 2.18.0 Linkerd的浮力企业的官方稳定发行套件，以及针对现有Linkerd用户的全面更改和升级指南。 BEL是Linkerd的企业发行。任何人都可以在非生产环境中下载和使用，并且可以免费使用不到50名员工的公司来生产。 BEL是我们自己运行的Linkerd的分布。您可以&lt;a href =“ https://docs.buoyant.io/”&gt;在五分钟以下与BEL一起开始&lt;/a&gt;！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tea &amp; Peaches: KubeCon + CloudNativeCon London Recap, Atlanta Sneak-Peek】茶与桃子：库贝孔 + Cloudnativecon伦敦回顾，亚特兰大偷偷摸摸</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/09/tea-peaches-kubecon-cloudnativecon-london-recap-atlanta-sneak-peek/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 in London&lt;/a&gt; was nothing short of historic. As the biggest KubeCon to date — with 12,418 attendees, including 46% first-timers — it was a moment of celebration, reflection, and connection for the cloud native community. As we now look ahead to the next gathering in Atlanta this November, we’re taking a moment to look back on the energy and impact of London — and look forward with excitement and an opportunity to always build on our learnings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reflecting on KubeCon London&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just the numbers for the London event speak volumes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;12,418 attendees&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2,947 CFP submissions (with an acceptance rate of just 8%)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;36% of accepted talks were from end users&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;24 keynote sessions, 241 breakout sessions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;26% gender minority speakers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;96 projects represented in the Project Pavilion&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXe8VQm7EHTv7NOkmOFvU541j7QkzHrySjqRhYizNVgrC9gBI37zSXVr9txojYfdjoXjjxoEfNNwooZ34gWRp5nxyfI5RkykYGdD3r_v2QPFhLq7UklvsfevDgsDIIc-8qxck0X_Ow?key=I_nTVXQQJ3-6trlRe-UowOzu&#34; alt=&#34;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 recap graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the scale, it was the quality of the content and the diversity of voices that stood out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Faseela K, a co-chair in London, shared her excitement for the response from attendees:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Overall, the attendees’ feedback on the sessions was great. Looking at the ratings for each talk, we had an average score of almost 9 (excluding unrated sessions).”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Based on previous feedback, the keynotes in London were structured in a different way than past events. Rather than thematic days, each day hosted a mix of talks that gave everyone a reason to stay engaged every day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In particular, Kasper noticed the hard work the co-chairs and program committees had put into building a more diverse lineup across not only speakers but also topics. “It was also exciting to see how the increased focus on end user talks and observability resonated. OpenTelemetry was &lt;em&gt;everywhere&lt;/em&gt;!”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Joseph Sandoval, another co-chair, saw a pattern beyond the topics at this year’s flagship European event:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“KubeCon London reminded me how powerful our shared experiences are. Talks that resonated most weren’t just about wins — they shared real struggles, lessons, and unknowns. That authenticity is what creates real value.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the community looks forward to the next North American event this autumn, Kasper looks back on his experience as a co-chair coming to close after the London event:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“It’s been an amazing experience serving the community. Reviewing nearly 3,000 CFPs is no small task, but we strive for fairness, diversity, and balance. I’ve learned so much from this role — especially from our incredible program committee and track chairs. It’s bittersweet to say goodbye, but finishing my co-chair journey in London, with my family by my side, was the perfect end. I’m incredibly excited for Abby Bangser to step in. She’s going to be fantastic.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking Forward to KubeCon Atlanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the community turns its eyes to &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America&lt;/a&gt; from November 10–13, 2025 in Atlanta it is important to continue the trend of always striving to community feedback.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Joseph sees Atlanta as an opportunity to continue the trend towards deeper learning through not only successes, but also challenges:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“One of our big learnings is to keep evolving how we connect with the audience. We’ll continue to look for talks that aren’t just technical deep-dives, but also highlight the hard parts—what’s been learned, what’s still unknown.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improving the CFP Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One common point of confusion in London was track alignment in the CFP process. Abby explains how the co-chairs are addressing this for Atlanta:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We saw many great proposals submitted under the wrong tracks. To help with this, we’re suggesting &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/cfp/#need-help-choosing-a-track&#34;&gt;example projects or TAGs&lt;/a&gt; to help speakers self-select more appropriate tracks. And for those that continue to be misplaced we will encourage reviewers to recommend better-fit tracks. This will allow speaker stories to truly shine in the right space.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But regardless of the track, Abby emphasizes that all talk proposals should strive to connect with the community:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“As potential speakers, you need to think about the full story. Real-world experiences including both the wins &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; the ongoing unknowns. You don’t need to have a perfect ending — honesty and lessons learned are powerful.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Behind the Scenes: CFP and Selection Transparency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With an event of this scale it is important to lean on experts around the world to help identify the best topics for the event. As Faseela explains:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“As co-chairs we often get questions about how to get a talk accepted or how the program committee is formed. It’s important to highlight that the co-chairs &lt;em&gt;do not&lt;/em&gt; decide talk acceptance alone.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In fact, there is a large, dedicated program committee, made up of community members who help review, score, and shape the schedule. The process is collective, thorough, and fair — but also competitive. Not getting accepted doesn’t mean your talk wasn’t great and you can reach out to the CNCF for feedback from the review process to learn how to improve for the next event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Helpful reading:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/08/19/inside-the-numbers-the-kubecon-cloudnativecon-selection-process-for-north-america-2024/&#34;&gt;Inside the Numbers: KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Selection Process (NA 2024)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2021/03/08/a-look-inside-the-kubecon-cloudnativecon-schedule-selection-process/&#34;&gt;A Look Inside the KubeCon Schedule Selection Process (2021)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2018/05/29/get-your-kubecon-talk-accepted/&#34;&gt;Get your KubeCon Talk Accepted (2018)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, a CFP doesn’t need to be only used for a single event! If your talk doesn’t make it in, consider submitting to KubeCrash or other community-led events. Also, we have the Day 0 – KubeCon co-located events and we encourage you to take a look at &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/cncf-hosted-co-located-events-overview/&#34;&gt;CNCF-hosted Co-located Events Overview | LF Events&lt;/a&gt; and see if your talk proposal fits for one of these events. We highly recommend submitting the talk for both KubeCon and any of the co-located events and the CNCF events team will make sure the talk is accepted for the right event.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anticipated Trends for Atlanta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for what topics might stand out in November, Joseph had this to say:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“AI, platform engineering, and observability continue to be strong themes. We expect even more innovation and insight around these areas.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Thoughts: See You in Atlanta!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The KubeCon community is growing, evolving, and becoming more inclusive and insightful with every event. The success of London was built on years of learning and iteration — and Atlanta will be no different.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever thought about submitting a talk, now is the time. Whether you’re a first-time speaker, a seasoned contributor, or someone in between, &lt;strong&gt;your story matters&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;📣 &lt;strong&gt;CFP for KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America in Atlanta closes Tuesday, May 27, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/cfp/&#34;&gt;Submit your talk&lt;/a&gt;, share your experience, and help shape the future of cloud native.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can’t wait to see you in Atlanta, November 10–13!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe/”&gt; kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025在伦敦举行的欧洲&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;简而言之。作为迄今为止最大的库贝康（Kubecon），有12,418名与会者，包括46％的成员，这是庆祝，反思和云土著社区联系的时刻。现在，当我们今年11月展望下一次在亚特兰大举行的聚会时，我们将花点时间回顾伦敦的能量和影响 - 并以兴奋和机会始终基于我们的学习。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;反思kubecon伦敦&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;只是伦敦活动的数字说​​话：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 12,418名与会者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 2,947 CFP提交（仅接受8％）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 36％的接受会谈来自最终用户&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 24个主题演讲，241个突破会议&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 26％的性别少数派发言人&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;项目馆中代表的96个项目&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxe8vqm7ehtv7nokmofvu541j7qkzhrysjqrhyiznvgrc9gbrc9gbi37zsxvr9t xojyfdjoxjjjjxoefnnnwooz34gwrp5nxyfi5rkykygdd3r_v2qpfhlq7uklvsfsfdgsdiic-8qxck0x_ow？ alt =“ Kubecon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 recap Graphic” referrerpolicy =“ no-toferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;超出规模，是内容的质量和声音的多样性引人注目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Faseela K是伦敦的联合主席，他对与会者的回应分享了她的兴奋：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“总的来说，与会者对会议的反馈很棒。查看每次演讲的评分，我们的平均得分接近9（不包括未列出的会议）。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基于以前的反馈，伦敦的主题演讲的结构与过去的事件不同。而不是主题日子，每天举办一系列会谈，使每个人每天都有一个订婚的理由。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;特别是，卡斯珀（Kasper）注意到共同主席和计划委员会为在演讲者和主题上建立更多样化的阵容所做的辛勤工作。 “看到如何增加对最终用户谈话和可观察性的关注的关注点也令人兴奋。opentelemetry无处不在&lt;/em&gt;！” &lt;/p&gt;！&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一位联合主席约瑟夫·桑多瓦尔（Joseph Sandoval）在今年的旗舰欧洲活动中看到了一个超出主题的模式：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“库贝康伦敦提醒我我们的共同经历有多强大。引起共鸣的谈话不仅仅是胜利 - 他们分享了真正的挣扎，课程和未知数。这种真实性是创造真实价值的原因。” &lt;/p&gt;。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然社区期待今年秋天的下一个北美活动，但卡斯珀回顾了他作为伦敦活动结束后联合主席的经历：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“为社区服务是一次了不起的经历。NG将近3,000个CFP并不是一件小事，但是我们努力建立公平，多样性和平衡。我从这个角色中学到了很多东西，尤其是从我们令人难以置信的计划委员会和田径主持人那里学到了很多东西。说再见是苦乐参半，但是与我的家人在伦敦结束我在伦敦的联合主席之旅是完美的结局。我为艾比·班瑟（Abby Bangser）介入而感到非常兴奋。她将变得很棒。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;期待库贝康亚特兰大&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;社区将目光转向&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-rorth-america/”&gt; kubecon + kubecon + cloubnativecon北美&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; 2025年11月10日至11月10日，在2025年11月10日至11月10日，在Atlanta中，它一直在始终保持趋势。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;约瑟夫认为亚特兰大是一个机会，不仅要通过成功，而且还挑战了更深入学习的趋势：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们的最大学习者之一就是不断发展我们如何与观众建立联系。我们将继续寻找不仅是技术深处的演讲，而且还强调了艰难的部分 - 已经学到了什么，仍然未知的内容。” &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;伦敦混乱的一个共同点是CFP过程中的轨道对准。艾比（Abby）解释了联合主席是如何解决亚特兰大的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We saw many great proposals submitted under the wrong tracks. To help with this, we’re suggesting &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/cfp/#need-help-choosing-a-track&#34;&gt;example projects or TAGs&lt;/a&gt; to help speakers self-select more appropriate轨道。对于那些继续放错的人，我们会鼓励审稿人推荐更好的曲目。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，无论曲目如何，艾比都强调，所有谈话建议都应努力与社区建立联系：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“作为潜在的演讲者，您需要思考完整的故事。现实世界中的经历包括Wins &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;和&lt;/em&gt;持续的未知数。您不需要拥有完美的结局 - 诚实和经验教训是有力的。” &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;幕后：CFP和选择透明度&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此规模的事件中，重要的是要依靠世界各地的专家，以帮助确定该活动的最佳主题。如Faseela所述：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“作为联合主席，我们经常会收到有关如何接受演讲或如何组建演讲的问题。重要的是要强调联合主席&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;单独决定接受谈话。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;实际上，有一个庞大的专门计划委员会，由社区成员组成，他们有助于审查，得分和塑造时间表。该过程是集体，彻底和公平的，但也具有竞争力。不getting被接受并不意味着您的演讲不是很好，您可以与CNCF接触以获取审核过程的反馈，以了解如何在下一个活动中进行改进。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有用的阅读：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/2024/08/19/inside-theide-the-numbers-the-numbers-the-number-the-number-the-number-the-number--kloudnativecon-selection-process-process-for-north-north-america-america-2024/&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2021/03/08/a-look-inside-the-kubecon-cloudnativecon-schedule-selection-selection-process/”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2018/05/05/29/get-your-kubecon-talk-accepted/”&gt;获得您的kubecon谈话（2018）&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，CFP不需要用于单个事件！如果您的演讲没有参加，请考虑服从Kubecrash或其他社区主导的活动。另外，我们有第0天 - 库贝孔共同定位的事件，我们鼓励您查看&lt;a href =“ https：//events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-merica/co-located-co.-located-events/cncf-host-co-co-co-co-loced-event-cocered-coperated-copered-coc.---------------- LF事件&lt;/a&gt;看看您的谈话建议是否适合其中一项事件。我们强烈建议您向Kubecon和任何共同确定的活动提交演讲，而CNCF活动团队将确保对合适的活动接受演讲。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;亚特兰大的预期趋势&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;至于11月可能脱颖而出的话题，约瑟夫说：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“ AI，平台工程和可观察性仍然是强大的主题。我们期望这些领域的创新和见解更多。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;最终想法：在亚特兰大见！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;库贝康社区正在发展，不断发展，并且在每个活动中变得更具包容性和洞察力。伦敦的成功是建立在多年学习和迭代的基础上的 - 亚特兰大也不会有什么不同。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您曾经考虑过提交演讲，那么现在是时候了。无论您是首次演讲者，经验丰富的贡献者还是中间的人，&lt;strong&gt;您的故事很重要&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kubecon + Cloudnativecon北美北美的北美北美关闭，2025年5月27日，星期二&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;a href =“ https:///events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-cloudnativecon-north-north-north-mamerica/cloge/cloge/cloge/clogn-cloge- &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;云本地。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们迫不及待想在11月10日至13日在亚特兰大见！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamlining application deployment on Kubernetes at RBC Capital Markets: A journey with FluxCD】简化了RBC Capital Markets Kubernetes上的应用程序部署：与FluxCD的旅程</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/22/streamlining-application-deployment-on-kubernetes-at-rbc-capital-markets-a-journey-with-fluxcd/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As we learned from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/02/18/royal-bank-of-canadas-cloud-evolution/&#34;&gt;the first blog&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;in our series, RBC has taken a holistic approach on our cloud journey, as it enables technologies across our enterprise. In today’s post, we’re going to share how Capital Markets has integrated Kubernetes and FluxCD into our technology stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the fast-paced world of capital markets, agility, reliability, and scalability are paramount. At RBC Capital Markets, we are constantly evolving our technology stack to meet the needs of our clients. One of the key enablers of this evolution has been our adoption of Kubernetes for application deployment. In this blog post, we’ll take you through our journey of deploying applications on Kubernetes, with a particular focus on how we leverage &lt;strong&gt;FluxCD&lt;/strong&gt; to manage our platform and user applications as tenants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The need for Kubernetes in capital markets&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Capital markets operate in a highly dynamic environment where milliseconds can make a difference. Our applications need to be highly available, scalable, and resilient to failures. Kubernetes, with its capabilities, is an industry standard for managing containerized applications at scale. It allows us to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scale applications dynamically&lt;/strong&gt; based on market demand.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensure high availability&lt;/strong&gt; with self-healing capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roll out updates seamlessly&lt;/strong&gt; with zero downtime.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optimize resource utilization&lt;/strong&gt; across our infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, managing Kubernetes at scale, especially in a multi-tenant environment like ours, comes with its own set of challenges. This is where &lt;strong&gt;FluxCD&lt;/strong&gt; comes into play.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Introducing FluxCD: GitOps for Kubernetes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FluxCD is a GitOps tool that helps us automate the deployment and management of applications on Kubernetes. It operates on the principle of &lt;strong&gt;declarative infrastructure as code&lt;/strong&gt;, where the desired state of our applications and infrastructure is defined in Open Container Initiative (OCI) repositories. FluxCD continuously monitors these repositories and ensures that the actual state of the cluster matches the desired state. It allows us to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automate deployments&lt;/strong&gt; across multiple environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enforce consistency&lt;/strong&gt; by using OCI as the single source of truth.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplify rollbacks&lt;/strong&gt; by reverting to previous OCI version.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable self-service for tenants&lt;/strong&gt; while maintaining strict governance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our deployment architecture&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We operate across multiple teams (e.g., trading desks, risk management teams, equities application team), &amp;nbsp;where each of them deploy and manage their own applications on our Kubernetes platform. Here’s how we’ve structured our deployment pipeline using FluxCD:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Platform deployment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The platform layer includes all the shared services and infrastructure components that are required to run our applications. This includes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingress controllers&lt;/strong&gt; for routing traffic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring and logging&lt;/strong&gt; tools like Prometheus, Loki, and Grafana.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cert management&lt;/strong&gt; and network configurations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Custom resource definitions (CRDs)&lt;/strong&gt; for tenant-specific configurations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We use a dedicated OCI repository to define the desired state of our platform. FluxCD monitors this repository and applies any changes to the Kubernetes cluster automatically. This ensures that our platform is always up-to-date and consistent across all environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;Tenant application deployment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each tenant has its own OCI repository where they define the desired state of their applications. These repositories include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes manifests&lt;/strong&gt; (Deployments, Services, ConfigMaps, etc.).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Helm charts&lt;/strong&gt; for packaging applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environment-specific configurations&lt;/strong&gt; (e.g., dev, qa, production).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FluxCD is configured to monitor these tenant repositories and deploy applications to their respective namespaces in the Kubernetes cluster. This allows tenants to manage their applications independently while adhering to the platform’s governance policies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;Multi-tenant isolation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To ensure isolation between tenants, we use Kubernetes namespaces and role-based access control (RBAC). Each tenant is assigned a dedicated namespace where they can deploy and manage their applications. FluxCD enforces RBAC policies to ensure that tenants can only modify resources within their own namespaces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;Continuous Delivery Pipeline&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FluxCD integrates seamlessly with our CI/CD (Continuous Integration/Continuous Dployment) pipeline. When a tenant pushes changes to their Git repository, FluxCD automatically picks up the changes and deploys them to the appropriate environment. This enables us to achieve continuous delivery with minimal manual intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Benefits of using FluxCD at RBC Capital Markets&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The improvements we have seen in our deployment process are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Faster time-to-market&lt;/strong&gt;: Automated deployments reduce the time it takes to roll out new features and updates.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved reliability&lt;/strong&gt;: GitOps ensures that our deployments are consistent and reproducible, reducing the risk of errors.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;: Tenants can manage their applications independently, while platform teams focus on maintaining the underlying infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Better governance&lt;/strong&gt;: Git and OCI serves as an audit trail, allowing us to track changes and enforce compliance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Challenges and lessons learned&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While FluxCD has been a great fit for our use case, we’ve also encountered some challenges along the way:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managing large Repositories&lt;/strong&gt;: As the number of tenants and applications grow, managing large Git repositories can become cumbersome. We’ve addressed this by breaking down repositories into smaller, more manageable components.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sensitive Information&lt;/strong&gt;: Managing information requires careful consideration. We’ve integrated FluxCD and external management tools like HasiCorp Vault to improve processing of information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Onboarding tenants&lt;/strong&gt;: Educating tenants on GitOps practices and Kubernetes concepts has been an ongoing effort. We’ve invested in training and documentation to help tenants get up to speed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we continue to scale our Kubernetes platform, we’re exploring new ways to enhance our deployment process. Some of the areas we’re focusing on include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced GitOps patterns&lt;/strong&gt;: Implementing canary deployments, blue-green deployments, and other advanced deployment strategies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy enforcement&lt;/strong&gt;: Using tools like Open Policy Agent (OPA) to enforce policies across tenants.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observability&lt;/strong&gt;: Enhancing our monitoring and alerting capabilities to provide better visibility into the health of our applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a highly competitive environment, we will continue to innovate and are excited to see how these technologies evolve.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;正如我们从&lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/02/02/18/royal-bank-canadas-cloud-evolution/”&gt;我们系列中的第一个博客&lt;/a&gt;，RBC在我们的云之旅中采取了整个跨越我们的范围的技术。在今天的帖子中，我们将分享资本市场如何将Kubernetes和FluxCD整合到我们的技术堆栈中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在快节奏的资本市场世界中，敏捷性，可靠性和可伸缩性至关重要。在加拿大皇家银行资本市场（RBC Capital Markets），我们不断发展我们的技术堆栈以满足客户的需求。这种进化的主要推动者之一是我们采用了Kubernetes进行申请部署。在这篇博客文章中，我们将带您进行在Kubernetes上部署应用程序的旅程，特别关注我们如何利用&lt;strong&gt; fluxcd &lt;/strong&gt;将我们的平台和用户应用程序作为租户管理。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对资本市场中的库伯纳特的需求&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;资本市场在高度动态的环境中运作，毫秒可以有所作为。我们的应用程序需要高度可用，可扩展性且有弹性的失败。 Kubernetes具有其功能，是规模管理集装箱应用程序的行业标准。它允许我们：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;根据市场需求动态&lt;/strong&gt;规模应用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;确保具有自我修复功能的高可用性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在零停机时间内无缝进行更新。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;优化资源利用率&lt;/strong&gt;在我们的基础架构中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，按大规模管理Kubernetes，尤其是在像我们这样的多租户环境中，都面临着自己的挑战。这是&lt;strong&gt; fluxcd &lt;/strong&gt;发挥作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;介绍FluxCD：kubernetes的gitops &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; FluxCD是一种gitops工具，可帮助我们自动化Kubernetes应用程序的部署和管理。它以&lt;strong&gt;声明性基础结构为代码&lt;/strong&gt;的原理运行，在开放容器倡议（OCI）存储库中定义了我们的应用程序和基础架构的所需状态。 FluxCD不断监视这些存储库，并确保集群的实际状态与所需状态匹配。它允许我们：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自动部署&lt;/strong&gt;在多个环境中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;通过使用OCI作为真理的单一来源来执行一致性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;通过恢复到先前的OCI版本来简化回滚&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在维持严格的治理的同时为租户提供自助服务。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的部署体系结构&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们跨多个团队（例如，交易桌，风险管理团队，股票应用团队）运营，在我们的Kubernetes Platf上部署和管理自己的申请ORM。这是我们使用FluxCD构建部署管道的方式：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 1。 &lt;strong&gt;平台部署&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该平台层包括运行我们应用程序所需的所有共享服务和基础架构组件。这包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;入口控制器&lt;/strong&gt;用于路由流量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;监视和记录&lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt; Prometheus，Loki和Grafana等工具。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; cert管理&lt;/strong&gt;和网络配置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自定义资源定义（CRD）&lt;/strong&gt;用于特定于租户的配置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们使用专用的OCI存储库来定义平台的所需状态。 FluxCD监视此存储库，并将任何更改自动应用于Kubernetes群集。这样可以确保我们的平台在所有环境中始终是最新和一致的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2。 &lt;strong&gt;租户应用程序部署&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个租户都有自己的OCI存储库，在其中定义了其应用程序的所需状态。这些存储库包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kubernetes表现出&lt;/strong&gt;（部署，服务，配置等）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Helm图表&lt;/strong&gt;包装应用程序。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;特定环境的配置&lt;/strong&gt;（例如Dev，QA，生产）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; FluxCD配置为监视这些租户存储库并将应用程序部署到Kubernetes群集中的各自名称空间。这允许租户在遵守平台的治理政策时独立管理其申请。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 3。 &lt;strong&gt;多租户隔离&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了确保租户之间的隔离，我们使用Kubernetes名称空间和基于角色的访问控制（RBAC）。每个租户都被分配一个专用的名称空间，他们可以在其中部署和管理其应用程序。 FluxCD强制执行RBAC策略，以确保租户只能在其自己的名称空间中修改资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 4。 &lt;strong&gt;连续交付管道&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; fluxCD与我们的CI/CD（连续集成/连续失业）管道无缝集成。当租户推动更改其GIT存储库时，FluxCD会自动拾取更改并将其部署到适当的环境中。这使我们能够通过最少的手动干预实现连续交付。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在RBC资本市场使用FluxCD的好处&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们在部署过程中看到的改进是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;更快的上市时间&lt;/strong&gt;：自动部署减少了推出新功能和更新所需的时间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提高可靠性&lt;/strong&gt;：Gitops确保我们的部署一致且可重复，从而降低了错误的风险。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;增强协作&lt;/strong&gt;：租户可以独立管理其应用程序，而PLATFORM团队专注于维护基础架构。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;更好的治理&lt;/strong&gt;：git和oci充当审计跟踪，使我们能够跟踪变更并执行合规性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;挑战和经验教训&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管FluxCD非常适合我们的用例，但我们在此过程中也遇到了一些挑战：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;管理大型存储库&lt;/strong&gt;：随着租户和应用的数量的增加，管理大型GIT存储库可能会变得繁琐。我们通过将存储库分解为较小，更可管理的组件来解决这一问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;敏感信息&lt;/strong&gt;：管理信息需要仔细考虑。我们已经集成了FluxCD和外部管理工具，例如Hasicorp Vault，以改善信息的处理。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;入职租户&lt;/strong&gt;：对租户进行有关Gitops实践和Kubernetes概念的教育一直是一项持续的努力。我们已经投资了培训和文档，以帮助租户提高速度。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;向前看&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着我们继续扩展我们的Kubernetes平台，我们正在探索增强部署过程的新方法。我们关注的一些领域包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;高级Gitops模式&lt;/strong&gt;：实施金丝雀部署，蓝绿色部署和其他高级部署策略。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;政策执行&lt;/strong&gt;：使用诸如Open Policy Agent（OPA）之类的工具来执行租户的政策。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;：增强我们的监控和警报功能，以更好地了解我们应用程序的健康。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在竞争激烈的环境中，我们将继续创新，并很高兴看到这些技术如何发展。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to install and run Minikube with Rootless Podman on ARM-based MacBooks】如何在基于ARM的MacBook上安装和运行Minikube</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/13/how-to-install-and-run-minikube-with-rootless-podman-on-arm-based-macbooks/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/&#34;&gt;minikube&lt;/a&gt; provides a local Kubernetes cluster on macOS, Linux, and Windows. minikube’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/concepts/principles/&#34;&gt;primary goals&lt;/a&gt; are to be the best tool for &lt;strong&gt;local Kubernetes application development&lt;/strong&gt; and to support all Kubernetes features that fit into that environment. It runs as a container, inside a VM, and on Linux, it can also be deployed directly, i.e., bare-metal. The container-based and VM-based deployments for either operating system have multiple choices. You can see the entire list of options on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/drivers/&#34;&gt;minikube Drivers documentation page&lt;/a&gt;. In this post, I’ll show you how to install and run Minikube with Podman on an ARM-based MacBook. &lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt; that the Podman driver is still in the &lt;em&gt;experimental&lt;/em&gt; stage at the time of writing this blog post.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Installing Podman&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because I’m using Podman, having &lt;a href=&#34;https://podman.io/&#34;&gt;Podman&lt;/a&gt; installed and a Podman machine running on your Mac is a prerequisite. Thanks to &lt;a href=&#34;https://brew.sh/&#34;&gt;Homebrew&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;em&gt;The Missing Package Manager for macOS&lt;/em&gt;), installing Podman (and minikube) is easier than ever before. A brew install podman will do:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % brew install podman&#xA;==&amp;gt; Downloading https://ghcr.io/v2/homebrew/core/podman/manifests/5.4.0&#xA;Already downloaded: /Users/gvenzl/Library/Caches/Homebrew/downloads/ec2ed8ba7b7cc27d27dc15f5ac0c4661b7ffb9d5debdcdafa267a209cc0081e3--podman-5.4.0.bottle_manifest.json&#xA;==&amp;gt; Fetching podman&#xA;==&amp;gt; Downloading https://ghcr.io/v2/homebrew/core/podman/blobs/sha256:8000fe73e511908388ca85e95fdddcb69bca121ef920aaf922fac46e8167afaf&#xA;####################################################################################################################################################### 100.0%&#xA;==&amp;gt; Pouring podman--5.4.0.arm64_sonoma.bottle.tar.gz&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;==&amp;gt; Caveats&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order to run containers locally, podman depends on a Linux kernel. One can be started manually using `podman machine` from this package. To start a podman VM automatically at login, also install the cask “podman-desktop.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;zsh completions have been installed to:&#xA;  /opt/homebrew/share/zsh/site-functions&#xA;==&amp;gt; Summary&#xA;🍺  /opt/homebrew/Cellar/podman/5.4.0: 201 files, 78.3MB&#xA;==&amp;gt; Running `brew cleanup podman`...&#xA;Disable this behaviour by setting HOMEBREW_NO_INSTALL_CLEANUP.&#xA;Hide these hints with HOMEBREW_NO_ENV_HINTS (see `man brew`).&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, a Podman machine needs to be created and started. Podman machine is essentially a tiny VM running on your Mac with a Podman environment inside it. The machine can be initialized with the podman machine init command and started with the podman machine start command. The init command takes additional parameters that specify, among others, CPUs, memory and the VM disk size assigned to the VM. Pick some values that are appropriate for your Laptop (for me, I decided on 4 CPUs, 4GB RAM and 25GB disk size) and issue the following command:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % podman machine init --cpus 4 --memory 4096 --disk-size 25&#xA;Looking up Podman Machine image at quay.io/podman/machine-os:5.4 to create VM&#xA;Getting image source signatures&#xA;Copying blob a5202b5e26ab done   |&#xA;Copying config 44136fa355 done   |&#xA;Writing manifest to image destination&#xA;a5202b5e26abdb846baed95761c47a42c5d49529752fa6fba45ea7a5ea046b52&#xA;Extracting compressed file: podman-machine-default-arm64.raw: done&#xA;Machine init complete&#xA;To start your machine run:&#xA; &#xA;    podman machine start&#xA; &#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Starting Podman machine&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To start the machine, as the output of the podman machine init command tells you, issue the podman machine start command. You must run this command once every time you start your Mac unless you use something like &lt;a href=&#34;https://podman-desktop.io/&#34;&gt;Podman Desktop&lt;/a&gt; instead. Podman machine can either run &lt;em&gt;rootful&lt;/em&gt; (with root permissions) or &lt;em&gt;rootless&lt;/em&gt; (the default). I recommend always running with &lt;em&gt;rootless&lt;/em&gt; first unless you have a really good reason not to. Why? Because of basic security. If you run &lt;em&gt;rootful&lt;/em&gt;, your containers (and minikube environment) will run with root privileges and although that might not be a big deal with your Mac’s Podman machine VM, it may be in production:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % podman machine start&#xA;Starting machine &#34;podman-machine-default&#34;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This machine is currently configured &lt;strong&gt;in&lt;/strong&gt; rootless mode. If your containers require root permissions (e.g. ports &amp;lt; 1024), or &lt;strong&gt;if&lt;/strong&gt; you run into compatibility issues with non-podman clients, you can switch using the following command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;podman machine set --rootful&#xA; &#xA;API forwarding listening on: /var/folders/t_/jtt4g5455pn3cbmxcjj4nszw0000gn/T/podman/podman-machine-default-api.sock&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The system helper service is not installed; the default Docker API socket address can’t be used by podman. If you would like to install it, run the following commands:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;        sudo /opt/homebrew/Cellar/podman/5.4.0/bin/podman-mac-helper install&#xA;        podman machine stop; podman machine start&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can still connect Docker API clients by setting DOCKER_HOST using thefollowing command &lt;strong&gt;in&lt;/strong&gt; your terminal session:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;        export DOCKER_HOST=&#39;unix:///var/folders/t_/jtt4g5455pn3cbmxcjj4nszw0000gn/T/podman/podman-machine-default-api.sock&#39;&#xA; &#xA;Machine &#34;podman-machine-default&#34; started successfully&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, you can inquire about the state of your Podman machine with podman machine ls:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % podman machine ls&#xA;NAME                 VM TYPE CREATED     LAST UP        CPUS    MEMORY  DISK SIZE&#xA;podman-machine-default*  applehv 32 seconds ago  Currently running  4       4GiB    25GiB&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Installing minikube&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just like Podman, minikube is also available via Homebrew. Just run brew install minikube:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % brew install minikube&#xA;==&amp;gt; Downloading https://formulae.brew.sh/api/formula.jws.json&#xA;==&amp;gt; Downloading https://formulae.brew.sh/api/cask.jws.json&#xA;==&amp;gt; Downloading https://ghcr.io/v2/homebrew/core/minikube/manifests/1.35.0&#xA;Already downloaded: /Users/gvenzl/Library/Caches/Homebrew/downloads/d45c630cc9dec65c97d897010d979d5c0c105ab7c4d983e27f33ee86a7ff62aa--minikube-1.35.0.bottle_manifest.json&#xA;==&amp;gt; Fetching minikube&#xA;==&amp;gt; Downloading https://ghcr.io/v2/homebrew/core/minikube/blobs/sha256:5736711e2&#xA;Already downloaded: /Users/gvenzl/Library/Caches/Homebrew/downloads/28a4e66e37ea4fae2794d9f8156d07f283ecc40d27cc6a4fbba9edb260e5158f--minikube--1.35.0.arm64_sonoma.bottle.tar.gz&#xA;==&amp;gt; Pouring minikube--1.35.0.arm64_sonoma.bottle.tar.gz&#xA;==&amp;gt; Caveats&#xA;zsh completions have been installed to:&#xA;  /opt/homebrew/share/zsh/site-functions&#xA;==&amp;gt; Summary&#xA;🍺  /opt/homebrew/Cellar/minikube/1.35.0: 10 files, 118.2MB&#xA;==&amp;gt; Running `brew cleanup minikube`...&#xA;Disable this behaviour by setting HOMEBREW_NO_INSTALL_CLEANUP.&#xA;Hide these hints with HOMEBREW_NO_ENV_HINTS (see `man brew`).&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Starting minikube&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before starting the minikube environment, ensure that you have a Podman machine &lt;strong&gt;running&lt;/strong&gt;.The first step is to tell minikube that you are using a &lt;em&gt;rootless&lt;/em&gt; Podman machine, which is done via minikube config set rootless true. You will not see any output from that command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % minikube config set rootless true&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second step is to start minikube via:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt; minikube start --driver=podman --container-runtime=containerd&#xA;&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % minikube start --driver=podman --container-runtime=containerd&#xA;😄  minikube v1.35.0 on Darwin 15.3.1 (arm64)&#xA;    ▪ MINIKUBE_ROOTLESS=true&#xA;✨  Using the podman (experimental) driver based on user configuration&#xA;📌  Using rootless Podman driver&#xA;👍  Starting &#34;minikube&#34; primary control-plane node in &#34;minikube&#34; cluster&#xA;🚜  Pulling base image v0.0.46 ...&#xA;💾  Downloading Kubernetes v1.32.0 preload ...&#xA;    &amp;gt; preloaded-images-k8s-v18-v1...:  357.10 MiB / 357.10 MiB  100.00% 18.54 M&#xA;    &amp;gt; gcr.io/k8s-minikube/kicbase...:  452.84 MiB / 452.84 MiB  100.00% 23.24 M&#xA;E0305 18:03:24.209927   24330 cache.go:222] Error downloading kic artifacts:  not yet implemented, see issue #8426&#xA;🔥  Creating podman container (CPUs=2, Memory=3846MB) ...&#xA;📦  Preparing Kubernetes v1.32.0 on containerd 1.7.24 ...&#xA;    ▪ Generating certificates and keys ...&#xA;    ▪ Booting up control plane ...&#xA;    ▪ Configuring RBAC rules ...&#xA;🔗  Configuring CNI (Container Networking Interface) ...&#xA;🔎  Verifying Kubernetes components...&#xA;    ▪ Using image gcr.io/k8s-minikube/storage-provisioner:v5&#xA;🌟  Enabled addons: storage-provisioner, default-storageclass&#xA;🏄  Done! kubectl is now configured to use &#34;minikube&#34; cluster and &#34;default&#34; namespace by default&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; if you were to run the minikube start command without Podman machine running, you will see this error:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % minikube start --driver=podman --container-runtime=cri-o&#xA;😄  minikube v1.35.0 on Darwin 14.7.1 (arm64)&#xA;✨  Using the podman (experimental) driver based on user configuration&#xA; &#xA;💣  Exiting due to PROVIDER_PODMAN_NOT_RUNNING: &#34;podman version --format &amp;lt;no value&amp;gt;&#34; exit status 125: Cannot connect to Podman. Please verify your connection to the Linux system using `podman system connection list`, or try `podman machine init` and `podman machine start` to manage a new Linux VM&#xA;Error: unable to connect to Podman socket: failed to connect: dial tcp 127.0.0.1:58608: connect: connection refused&#xA;📘  Documentation: https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/drivers/podman/&#xA; &#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Using minikube&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With minikube installed, you are now ready to go. Here are a couple of useful commands:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To stop minikube, use: minikube stop&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To restart the existing minikube environment, use: minikube start&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To pause Kubernetes without impacting deployed apps, use: minikube pause&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To unpause a paused instance, use: minikube unpause&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To interact with minikube using kubectl:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you don’t have kubectl installed, use: minikube kubectl –, for example, minikube kubectl — get po -A to get all pods&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You may want to create a shortcut for minikube kubectl by creating an alias: alias kubectl=”minikube kubectl –“&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you have kubectl installed, minikube will have configured kubectl to speak to the local cluster. You can see that actually in the last line of the minikube start … command output above&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To get the Kubernetes Dashboard up and running, use: minikube dashboard, the dashboard will be opened automatically in your default browser&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Running your app on minikube&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/start&#34;&gt;minikube Get Started!&lt;/a&gt; page lists a handy demo app to deploy on your cluster, see section 4) Deploy applications. To test your minikube installation, you can spin up the echo-server application. Remember, you can shortcut minikube kubectl but for completeness, I’m using the full syntax.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Create a sample deployment and expose it on port 8080:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;minikube kubectl -- create deployment hello-minikube --image=kicbase/echo-server:1.0&#xA;minikube kubectl -- expose deployment hello-minikube --type=NodePort --port=8080&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It may take a moment for the deployment to deploy but eventually, it will show up when you run minikube kubectl — get services hello-minikube:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % minikube kubectl -- get services hello-minikube&#xA;NAME         TYPE   CLUSTER-IP  EXTERNAL-IP   PORT(S)      AGE&#xA;hello-minikube   NodePort   10.104.20.158   &amp;lt;none&amp;gt;    8080:31532/TCP   9s&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ %&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The app is now exposed &lt;em&gt;inside&lt;/em&gt; the cluster via port 8080. To make it reachable to the outside world use, i.e., straight from your Mac, use port forwarding. For example, to forward the app to port 7081, use: minikube kubectl — port-forward service/hello-minikube 7080:8080&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac ~ % minikube kubectl -- port-forward service/hello-minikube 7080:8080&#xA;Forwarding from 127.0.0.1:7080 -&amp;gt; 8080&#xA;Forwarding from [::1]:7080 -&amp;gt; 8080&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now access the app at &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:7080/&#34;&gt;http://localhost:7080/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdvgTKGEv-qPtD6wcz2huxBXotqvz803wUTi33nUf1I9nXuiG8r1zTF71m8IAU6XOH8VXvSjwrRWpb-2G1eBgxQog7rJ8JTAoRFe8neWGF-sAoLzJr6vlwhp76EC4RjLKj809mpog?key=7Yozzami6Jnx3cytq1NCSx9X&#34; alt=&#34;The web interface of the hello-minikube deployment.&#34; title=&#34;The web interface of the hello-minikube deployment.&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/”&gt; Minikube &lt;/a&gt;在MacOS，Linux和Windows上提供了本地的Kubernetes群集。 Minikube的&lt;a href =“ https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/docs/conepts/principles/”&gt;主要目标&lt;/a&gt;是&lt;strong&gt; local Kubernetes应用程序开发的最佳工具&lt;/strong&gt;，并支持适合所有Kubernetes功能，以适应该环境。它作为容器，在VM内部和Linux上运行，也可以直接部署，即裸机。两个操作系统的基于容器和基于VM的部署都有多种选择。您可以在&lt;a href =“ https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/drivers/” &lt;a href =上查看整个选项列表。在这篇文章中，我将向您展示如何在基于ARM的MacBook上与Podman一起安装和运行Minikube。 &lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;撰写此博客文章时，Podman驱动程序仍处于&lt;em&gt;实验&lt;/em&gt;阶段。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;安装Podman &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因为我正在使用podman，所以安装了&lt;a href =“ https://podman.io/”&gt; podman &lt;/a&gt;已安装，并且在Mac上运行的Podman机器是先决条件。感谢&lt;a href =“ https://brew.sh/”&gt; homebrew &lt;/a&gt;（&lt;em&gt; MacOS &lt;/em&gt;的缺少软件包管理器&lt;/em&gt;），安装Podman（和Minikube）比以往任何时候都容易。酿造安装Podman会做：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％brew brew install podman&#xA;==&gt;下载https://ghcr.io/v2/homebrew/core/podman/manifests/5.4.0&#xA;已经下载了：/users/gvenzl/library/caches/homebrew/downloads/ec2ed8ba7b7cc27d27d27d27dc15f5ac0c4661b7ffb9d5debdcdafa267a209cc0081cc0081e3-cc0081e3-podman-podman-5.4.0.bottle_bottle_manifest.json.jjson&#xA;==&gt;提取Podman&#xA;==&gt;下载https://ghcr.io/v2/homebrew/core/podman/podman/blobs/sha256:8000fe73e5119083885e95fdddcb69bca12121ef921ef920aaf92222fac46e81678167167afaf&#xA;######### ######################### 100.0％&#xA;==&gt;浇注Podman  -  5.4.0.arm64_sonoma.bottle.tar.gz&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ==&gt;警告&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了本地运行容器，Podman取决于Linux内核。可以从此软件包中使用“ Podman Machine”手动启动。要在登录时自动启动Podman VM，还要安装Cask“ Podman-Desktop”。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ZSH完成已安装到：&#xA;  /opt/homebrew/share/zsh/站点函数&#xA;==&gt;摘要&#xA;🍺/opt/homebrew/cellar/podman/5.4.0：201文件，78.3MB&#xA;==&gt;运行`brew Clearup podman` ...&#xA;通过设置homebrew_no_install_cleanup来禁用此行为。&#xA;用homebrew_no_env_hints隐藏这些提示（请参阅“ Man Brew”）。&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，需要创建并启动探针机。 Podman Machine本质上是在您的Mac上运行的一个微小的VM，其中内部有一个Podman环境。该机器可以用Podman Machine init命令初始化，然后从Podman Machine S开始TART命令。 INIT命令采用其他参数，除其他参数外，包括CPU，内存和分配给VM的VM磁盘大小。选择适合您笔记本电脑的一些值（对我来说，我决定使用4个CPU，4GB RAM和25GB磁盘尺寸），并发出以下命令：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％podman Machine init-cpus 4-memory 4096-Disk-size 25&#xA;在quay.io/podman/machine-os:5.4查找Podman Machine Image以创建VM&#xA;获取图像源签名&#xA;复制Blob A5202B5E26AB完成|&#xA;复制配置44136FA355完成|&#xA;写入图像目的地&#xA;A5202B5E26ABDB846BAED95761C47A42C5D49529752FA6FBA45EA7A5EA7A5EA046B52&#xA;提取压缩文件：podman-machine-default-arm64.raw：完成&#xA;机器启动完成&#xA;开始运行机器：&#xA; &#xA;    Podman Machine开始&#xA; &#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;启动podman Machine &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;启动机器，因为Podman Machine Init命令的输出告诉您，请发出Podman Machine Start命令。每次启动Mac时，都必须运行此命令，除非您使用&lt;a href =“ https://podman-desktop.io/”&gt; podman桌面&lt;/a&gt;而不是。 Podman Machine可以运行&lt;em&gt; ruitful &lt;/em&gt;（带有根本权限）或&lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; root &lt;/em&gt;（默认）。我建议您始终使用&lt;em&gt; rootless &lt;/em&gt;首先运行，除非您有一个很好的理由不这样做。为什么？由于基本安全性。如果您运行&lt;em&gt; ruitful &lt;/em&gt;，则您的容器（和Minikube环境）将具有根特权，尽管这可能与您的Mac的Podman Machine VM无关，但它可能正在生产中：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％podman机器开始&#xA;启动机器“ Podman-Machine-Default”&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，该机器在&lt;/strong&gt;无根模式下配置&lt;strong&gt;。如果您的容器需要根本权限（例如端口&lt;1024）或&lt;strong&gt;如果&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;您会遇到与非销售客户端的兼容性问题，则可以使用以下命令进行切换：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; podman Machine Set-rototful&#xA; &#xA;api转发侦听：/var/folders/t_/jtt4g54555pn3cbmxcjj4nszw000000gn/t/podman/podman/podman-machine-machine-default-api.sock&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;未安装系统助手服务； Podman无法使用默认的Docker API套接字地址。如果您想安装它，请运行以下命令：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;        Podman Machine Stop; Podman Machine开始&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您仍然可以使用theFollowing命令&lt;strong&gt;在&lt;/strong&gt;您的终端会话中设置Docker_host来连接Docker API客户端：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; export docker_host =&#39;unix：///var/folders/t_/t_/jtt4g54555pn3cbmxcjjjj4nszw0000000000000000 glo&#xA; &#xA;机器 ”Podman-Machine-Default成功开始&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后但并非最不重要的一点是，您可以使用Podman Machine LS询问Podman Machine的状态：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％podman Machine ls&#xA;名称VM类型创建的最后一个CPU内存磁盘大小&#xA;Podman-Machine-Default* AppleHV 32秒前运行4 4GiB 25GIB&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-teading”&gt;安装Minikube &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;就像Podman一样，Minikube也可以通过Homebrew提供。只需运行酿造安装Minikube：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％brew brew instalm&#xA;==&gt;下载https://formulae.brew.sh/api/formula.jws.json&#xA;==&gt;下载https://formulae.brew.sh/api/cask.jws.json&#xA;==&gt;下载https://ghcr.io/v2/homebrew/core/minikube/manifests/1.35.0&#xA;已经下载了：/users/gvenzl/library/caches/homebrew/downloads/D45C630CC9DEC65C97D897010D979D979D5C105B7C4D983E27C4D983E27F3EE86E7.86A7FF6A7FF6A2AAA-MINIKUBE-MINIKUBE-MANEF.JESTON.JESTON.JESTON&#xA;==&gt;提取Minikube&#xA;==&gt;下载https://ghcr.io/v2/homebrew/core/minikube/blobs/sha256:5736711e2&#xA;已经下载了：/users/gvenzl/library/caches/homebrew/downloads/28a4e66e37EA4FAE2794D9F8156D07F283ECC40D227CC6A4FBBA9EDBBA9EDBBBA9EDB260E5158F-MINIKUBE&#xA;==&gt;倒入Minikube-1.35.0.arm64_sonoma.bottle.tar.gz&#xA;==&gt;警告&#xA;ZSH完成已安装到：&#xA;  /opt/homebrew/share/zsh/站点函数&#xA;==&gt;摘要&#xA;🍺/opt/homebrew/cellar/minikube/1.35.0：10个文件，118.2MB&#xA;==&gt;运行`brew Clearup minikube` ...&#xA;通过设置homebrew_no_install_cleanup来禁用此行为。&#xA;用homebrew_no_env_hints隐藏这些提示（请参阅“ Man Brew”）。&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;启动minikube &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在开始Minikube环境之前，请确保您拥有Podman Machine &lt;strong&gt;运行&lt;/strong&gt;。第一步是告诉Minikube您使用的是&lt;em&gt; rootless &lt;/em&gt; podman Machine，该机器是通过Minikube Config set sere neless true完成的。您将看不到该命令的任何输出：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt;&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％minikube配置集无根真&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第二步是通过：&lt;/p&gt;启动Minikube&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;态&#xA;&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％minikube start -driver = podman -container-runtime = containerd&#xA;tarwin 15.3.1（ARM64）上的Minikube V1.35.0&#xA;    ▪Minikube_rootless= true&#xA;✨使用基于用户配置的Podman（实验）驱动程序&#xA;📌使用无根的Podman驱动程序&#xA;👍在“ Minikube”群集中启动“ Minikube”主要控制平面节点&#xA;🚜拉动基本图像v0.0.46 ...&#xA;💾下载kubernetes v1.32.0预付...&#xA;    &gt;预加载-Images-K8S-V18-V1 ...：357.10 MIB / 357.10 MIB 100。00％18.54 m&#xA;    &gt; gcr.io/k8s-minikube/kicbase ...：452.84 MIB/452.84 MIB 100.00％23.24 m&#xA;E0305 18：03：24.209927 24330 CACHE.GO：222]错误下载KIC文物：尚未实施，请参阅第8426页&#xA;🔥创建Podman容器（CPU = 2，内存= 3846MB）...&#xA;📦在容器上准备Kubernetes v1.32.0 1.7.24 ...&#xA;    ▪生成证书和密钥...&#xA;    ▪启动控制平面...&#xA;    ▪配置RBAC规则...&#xA;🔗配置CNI（容器网络接口）...&#xA;🔎验证kubernetes组件...&#xA;    ▪使用Image gcr.io/k8s-minikube/storage-proviseer：v5&#xA;🌟启用插件：storage-provisioner，默认storageclass&#xA;🏄完成！ Kubectl现在配置为使用“ Minikube”群集和“默认”名称空间&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;如果您要运行Minikube start命令而没有Podman机器运行，您将看到此错误：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％minikube start -driver = podman -container-runtime = cri-o&#xA;tarwin 14.7.1（ARM64）上的Minikube V1.35.0&#xA;✨使用基于用户配置的Podman（实验）驱动程序&#xA; &#xA;💣由于Provider_podman_not_running离开而退出：“ podman版本 -  format &lt;no value&gt;”退出状态125：无法连接到Podman。请使用“ Podman System Connection List”验证您与Linux系统的连接&#xA;错误：无法连接到Podman插座：无法连接：拨号TCP 127.0.0.1：58608：连接：连接拒绝&#xA;📘文档：https：//minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/drivers/podman/&#xA; &#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;使用Minikube &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;安装了Minikube，您现在就可以去了。这是几个有用的命令：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;停止Minikube，使用：Minikube Stop &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要重新启动现有的Minikube环境，请使用：Minikube Start &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要暂停Kubernetes而不会影响部署的应用程序，请使用：Minikube暂停&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要解开暂停的实例，使用：Minikube Unauthe &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用kubectl与Minikube互动：&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果您没有安装Kubectl，请使用：Minikube Kubectl  - 例如，Minikube Kubectl  - 获取PO -A获取所有豆荚&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;您可能想通过创建一个别名为Minikube Kubectl创建一个快捷方式：Alias Kubectl =“ Minikube Kubectl  - “ &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果您安装了Kubectl，Minikube将配置Kubectl与本地群集交谈。您可以看到，实际上在Minikube启动的最后一行中……命令输出&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要使Kubernetes仪表板启动并运行，请使用：Minikube仪表板，仪表板将在您的默认浏览器&lt;/li&gt;中自动打开&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;在Minikube上运行您的应用&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https：//minikube.sIgs.k8s.io/docs/start&#34;&gt; minikube开始！&lt;/a&gt;页面列出了一个方便的演示应用程序，可以在您的群集上部署，请参见第4节）部署应用程序。要测试您的Minikube安装，您可以旋转Echo-Server应用程序。请记住，请记住，请记住，您可以使用完整的Minikube Kububectl，我可以使用完整的Syntax。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建样本部署并将其暴露在端口8080：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt;&#xA;Minikube kubectl-创建部署hello minikube -image = kicbase/echo-server：1.0&#xA;Minikube kubectl-露出部署hello minikube -type = nodeport -port = 8080&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;部署可能需要片刻，但是最终，当您运行Minikube Kubectl时会显示出来 - 获取服务Hello Minikube：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％minikube kubectl-获取服务hello minikube&#xA;名称类型类型群集IP外部IP端口年龄&#xA;Hello-Minikube NodePort 10.104.20.158 &lt;none&gt; 8080：31532/TCP 9S&#xA;gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，该应用程序通过端口8080暴露在&lt;/em&gt;内部&lt;/em&gt;。为了使其可与外界使用，即直接从Mac直接使用，请使用端口转发。例如，要将应用程序转发到端口7081，请使用：Minikube Kubectl  -  Port-Forward Service/Hello-Minikube 7080：8080 &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; gvenzl@gvenzl-mac〜％minikube kubectl-port-forward服务/hello minikube 7080：8080&#xA;从127.0.0.1：7080-转发 - &gt; 8080&#xA;从[:: 1]：7080-&gt; 8080转发&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您现在可以在&lt;a href =“ http：// localhost：7080/”&gt; http：// localhost：7080/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;访问该应用程序。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdvgtkgev-qptd6wcz2huxbxotqvz803wuti3wuti3wuti33nuf1i9nxuig1i9nxuig8r1ztf71 m8iau6xoh8vxvsjwrrwpb-2g1ebgxqog7rj8jtaorfe8newgf-saolzjr6vl6vlwhl6vlwhp76ec4rjlkj809mpog？ alt =“ Hello-Minikube部署的Web接口。” title =“ Hello-Minikube部署的Web接口。” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Kyverno Release 1.14!】宣布kyverno版本1.14！</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/14/announcing-kyverno-release-1-14/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeaaup8DoNKjLMrEe3VlUbZfNOHPpdv9x024rgVAMQS8PiPJg5qneBeXVb8RQxqZwkdb1Jed1DM8e-A3yKmWAl2lADGBm6s3jMh2dmso6jcsaWXpfDL7kLJvm44juQtMu7bltwRyA?key=bNwTikwb7q2PD8Ue5oV9IKjA&#34; alt=&#34;Kyverno release 1.14.0&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two new specialized policy types: ValidatingPolicy and ImageValidatingPolicy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Streamlined validation with improved CEL support and performance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced supply chain security with dedicated image verification&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Policy exceptions now support CEL expressions for fine-grained control&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CLI improvements for shift-left validation of any JSON payload&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Community milestone: 744 changes with 60+ contributors (40 first-time!)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce the release of Kyverno 1.14.0, marking a significant milestone in our journey to make policy management in Kubernetes more modular, streamlined, and powerful. This release introduces two new policy types – &lt;em&gt;ValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;ImageValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; – that represent our vision for the future of policy management in Kubernetes environments and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why New Policy Types?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno’s evolution has led to a proliferation of overlapping rule types (&lt;em&gt;validate.pattern&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;validate.cel&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;validate.deny&lt;/em&gt;, etc.) within the &lt;em&gt;ClusterPolicy&lt;/em&gt; CRD, creating unnecessary complexity for users. Meanwhile, Kubernetes has introduced its own &lt;em&gt;ValidatingAdmissionPolicies&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;MutatingAdmissionPolicies&lt;/em&gt; using CEL expressions, presenting an opportunity for closer alignment. The new policy types address these challenges by migrating each rule type into its own dedicated CRD. This modular approach streamlines the user experience, standardizes on CEL for better Kubernetes compatibility, simplifies maintenance for the project, and provides a clearer, more focused way to define policies according to their specific functions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;New Policy Types: A Modular Approach&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.14.0 begins a new chapter for Kyverno with the introduction of specialized policy types that separate concerns and confusion about validation checks being written in various patterns by providing a more focused approach to functionality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;ValidatingPolicy: Streamlined Validation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new &lt;em&gt;ValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; Custom Resource Definition (CRD) simplifies how you write validation rules by centralizing all validation logic into a dedicated resource type. This approach offers several advantages:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified structure&lt;/strong&gt;: A clean, focused structure that makes policies easier to write and understand&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CEL-first approach&lt;/strong&gt;: ValidatingPolicy uses CEL (Common Expression Language) as the primary validation method, aligning with Kubernetes’ own trajectory for policy management&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Native compatibility&lt;/strong&gt;: Works seamlessly with Kubernetes ValidatingAdmissionPolicy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved performance&lt;/strong&gt;: Optimized for faster validation checks with reduced overhead&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is an example of validating deployment replicas (ensuring deployments don’t exceed a maximum replica count).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Previous &lt;em&gt;ClusterPolicy&lt;/em&gt; approach:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&#xA;kind: ClusterPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: check-deployment-replicas&#xA;spec:&#xA;  validationFailureAction: Enforce&#xA;  rules:&#xA;    - name: check-replicas&#xA;      match:&#xA;        resources:&#xA;          kinds:&#xA;            - Deployment&#xA;      validate:&#xA;        message: “The number of replicas must not exceed 5”&#xA;        pattern:&#xA;          spec:&#xA;            replicas: “&amp;lt;= 5&#34;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New &lt;em&gt;ValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; approach:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: policies.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: ValidatingPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: check-deployment-replicas&#xA;spec:&#xA;  validations:&#xA;    - expression: &#34;object.spec.replicas &amp;lt;= 5&#34;&#xA;      message: &#34;The number of replicas must not exceed 5&#34;&#xA;  matchConstraints:&#xA;    resourceRules:&#xA;      - apiGroups: [&#34;apps&#34;]&#xA;        apiVersions: [&#34;v1&#34;]&#xA;        resources: [&#34;deployments&#34;]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;ValidatingAdmissionPolicy Generation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release enhances policy flexibility with the ability to automatically generate Kubernetes &lt;em&gt;ValidatingAdmissionPolicies&lt;/em&gt; from &lt;em&gt;ValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt;, enabling validations to be performed directly by the Kubernetes API server rather than the Kyverno admission controller. This capability improves performance and resilience by leveraging native Kubernetes validation while maintaining the rich feature set and ease of use provided by Kyverno. Read more about &lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/policy-types/validating-policy/#autogen&#34;&gt;auto-generating ValidatingAdmissionPolicy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Comparison with ValidatingAdmissionPolicy&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feature&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;K8s ValidatingAdmissionPolicy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyverno ValidatingPolicy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Enforcement&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Admission&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Admission, Background, Pipelines, …&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Payloads&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kubernetes, Any JSON or YAML&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Distribution&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kubernetes API server&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Helm, CLI, Web Service, API, SDK&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;CEL Library&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Basic&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Extended&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Bindings&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Manual&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Automatic&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Auto-generation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⛔&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Pod Controllers, ValidatingAdmissionPolicy&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;External Data&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⛔&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kubernetes resources or API calls&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Caching&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⛔&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Global Context, image verification results&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Background scans&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⛔&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Periodic, On policy creation or updates&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Exceptions&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⛔&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Fine-grained exclusions&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Reporting&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⛔&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Policy WG Reports, Policy Reporter, etcd offload&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Testing&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;⛔&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kyverno CLI (unit), Chainsaw (e2e)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more details on ValidatingPolicy, check the official document &lt;a href=&#34;https://main--kyverno.netlify.app/docs/policy-types/validating-policy/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;ImageValidatingPolicy: Advanced Supply Chain Security&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;ImageValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; is a dedicated policy type that focuses exclusively on container image verification, significantly enhancing software supply chain security capabilities. By decoupling the image verification rule from &lt;em&gt;ClusterPolicy&lt;/em&gt; into its own CRD, it provides a more modular and streamlined approach to image security. This policy type can also extract images from any JSON payload, allowing for comprehensive and flexible image verification.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Key features include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comprehensive Image Verification&lt;/strong&gt;: Verify signatures, Software Bill of Materials (SBOMs), attestations, and other artifacts to ensure the integrity and authenticity of container images.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible Matching&lt;/strong&gt;: Match images using glob patterns or powerful CEL expressions, providing versatility in defining verification criteria.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced CEL Functions&lt;/strong&gt;: Leverages specialized CEL functions for verifying image signatures and attestations, making complex validation logic easier to implement.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following &lt;em&gt;ImageValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; verifies that all container images from &lt;em&gt;ghcr.io&lt;/em&gt; meet strict supply chain security requirements before pods are created, ensuring all images are properly signed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: policies.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: ImageValidatingPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: ivpol-sample&#xA;spec:&#xA;  webhookConfiguration:&#xA;    timeoutSeconds: 20&#xA;  failurePolicy: Ignore&#xA;  validationActions:&#xA;    - Deny&#xA;  matchConstraints:&#xA;    resourceRules:&#xA;      - apiGroups: [“”]&#xA;        apiVersions: [“v1&#34;]&#xA;        operations: [“CREATE”]&#xA;        resources: [“pods”]&#xA;  matchImageReferences:&#xA;    - glob: ghcr.io/*&#xA;  attestors:&#xA;    - name: notary&#xA;      notary:&#xA;        certs:&#xA;          value: |-&#xA;            -----BEGIN CERTIFICATE-----&#xA;            …&#xA;            …&#xA;            -----END CERTIFICATE-----&#xA;  attestations:&#xA;    - name: sbom&#xA;      referrer:&#xA;        type: sbom/cyclone-dx&#xA;  validations:&#xA;    - expression: &amp;gt;-&#xA;        images.containers.map(image, verifyImageSignatures(image, [attestors.notary])).all(e, e &amp;gt; 0)&#xA;      message: failed to verify image with notary cert&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following policy enhances security posture by dynamically fetching Notary certificates from a ConfigMap:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: policies.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: ImageValidatingPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: check-images&#xA;spec:&#xA;  matchConstraints:&#xA;    resourceRules:&#xA;      - apiGroups: [“”]&#xA;        apiVersions: [“v1&#34;]&#xA;        operations: [“CREATE”]&#xA;        resources: [“pods”]&#xA;  variables:&#xA;    - name: cm&#xA;      expression: &amp;gt;-&#xA;        resource.Get(“v1”, “configmaps”, object.metadata.namespace, “keys”)&#xA;  matchImageReferences:&#xA;    - glob: ghcr.io/*&#xA;  attestors:&#xA;    - name: notary&#xA;      notary:&#xA;        certs:&#xA;          expression: variables.cm.data.certificate&#xA;   validations:&#xA;    - expression: &amp;gt;-&#xA;        images.containers.map(image, verifyImageSignatures(image, [attestors.notary])).all(e, e &amp;gt; 0)&#xA;      message: failed to verify image with notary cert&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more details of ImageValidatingPolicy, check the official document &lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/policy-types/image-validating-policy/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Other Features and Enhancements&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;CEL PolicyExceptions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.14.0 extends the powerful &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/exceptions/#policyexceptions-with-cel-expressions&#34;&gt;PolicyException&lt;/a&gt; feature to work seamlessly with the new policy types. This enhancement provides granular control over policy enforcement, allowing administrators to define specific exemptions from policy rules when needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Policy exceptions enable teams to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create targeted exemptions for specific workloads or resources&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Define precise conditions under which policies should not be applied&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Balance strict security controls with practical operational needs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support migration paths and special use cases&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, you can create an exception that excludes a specific deployment from an &lt;em&gt;ImageValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: policies.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: PolicyException&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: exclude-skipped-deployment&#xA;spec:&#xA;  policyRefs:&#xA;  - name: &#34;ivpol-report-background-sample&#34;&#xA;    kind: ImageValidatingPolicy&#xA;  matchConditions:&#xA;    - name: &#34;check-name&#34;&#xA;      expression: &#34;object.metadata.name == &#39;skipped-deployment&#39;&#34;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this example, the &lt;em&gt;PolicyException&lt;/em&gt; exempts any resource named “skipped-deployment” from the “ivpol-report-background-sample” &lt;em&gt;ImageValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt;. The &lt;em&gt;matchConditions&lt;/em&gt; field uses a CEL expression to precisely define when the exception applies, giving administrators fine-grained control over policy enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Advanced CEL Libraries&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.14.0 includes powerful CEL libraries that extend beyond standard Kubernetes capabilities. These libraries work seamlessly with new policy types while maintaining backward compatibility with established Kyverno features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are example signatures for each library, for a full list, please see &lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/policy-types/validating-policy/#kyverno-cel-libraries&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Resource Library&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Resource library retrieves Kubernetes resources for real-time validations against the current cluster state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;resource.Get(“v1”, “configmaps”, “default”, “my-config”)&#xA;resource.List(“apps/v1”, “deployments”, “default”).items&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;HTTP Library&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The HTTP library enables external API calls for integrating third-party validations into policy decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;http.Send(“GET”, “https://api.example.com/data”, {}).body&#xA;http.Post(&#34;https://audit.api/log&#34;, {&#34;kind&#34;: object.kind}, {&#34;Content-Type&#34;: &#34;application/json&#34;}).logged == true&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;User Library&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The User library includes functions like parseServiceAccount() to extract metadata from the user or service account that triggered the admission request. These expressions help enforce policies based on user identity, namespace association, or naming conventions of service accounts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;parseServiceAccount(request.userInfo.username)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;GlobalContext Library&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The GlobalContext library provides access to cached data that’s shared across multiple policies, improving performance by avoiding redundant API calls.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;globalcontext.Get(“gctxentry-apicall-correct”, “”) != 0&#xA;globalcontext.Get(“allowed-registries”, “”).registries.exists(r, image.registry == r):&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Image Library&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Image library parses container image references, enabling validation of image components like registry, repository, tag, and digest.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;image(“nginx:latest”).registry == “docker.io”&#xA;image(“ghcr.io/company/app:v1.2.3”).containsDigest()&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Image Data Library&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ImageData library enables deep inspection of container image metadata from OCI registries, including architecture, OS, layers, and manifest details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;image.GetMetadata(“nginx:1.21&#34;).config.architecture == “amd64”&#xA;image.GetMetadata(“my-image:latest”).manifest.layers.size() &amp;gt; 0&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;CLI &amp;amp; Reporting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.14.0 enhances the CLI experience by extending support for the new &lt;em&gt;ValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;ImageValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; types, making it easier to test and validate policies before applying them to your cluster. The CLI is beneficial for shift-left testing of policies during development or CI/CD pipelines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, you can validate a Dockerfile (represented as JSON) against security policies before building images. In the following &lt;em&gt;ValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; snippet, it uses CEL expressions to examine the Dockerfile structure and scans for prohibited commands like &lt;em&gt;curl&lt;/em&gt;. See full manifests &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/tree/v1.14.0/test/cli/test-validating-policy/json-check-dockerfile&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;validations:&#xA;  - message: “curl is not allowed”&#xA;    expression: &amp;gt;- &#xA;      !object.Stages.exists(s, &#xA;        s.Commands.exists(c, &#xA;          has(c.CmdLine) &amp;amp;&amp;amp; c.CmdLine.exists(cmd, string(cmd).contains(‘curl’))&#xA;        )&#xA;      )&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Complementing these CLI capabilities, Kyverno also integrates the new policy types with the &lt;em&gt;PolicyReport&lt;/em&gt; framework. While the CLI helps you validate resources during development, PolicyReports provide ongoing visibility into compliance status across your environment. These reports clearly identify which policy type generated the results (source: KyvernoImageValidatingPolicy), link to evaluated resources via owner references, and provide actionable messages for remediation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: wgpolicyk8s.io/v1alpha2&#xA;kind: PolicyReport&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  labels:&#xA;    app.kubernetes.io/managed-by: kyverno&#xA;  ownerReferences:&#xA;  - apiVersion: apps/v1&#xA;    kind: Deployment&#xA;    name: test-deployment&#xA;scope:&#xA;  apiVersion: apps/v1&#xA;  kind: Deployment&#xA;  name: test-deployment&#xA;results:&#xA;- message: failed to verify image with notary cert&#xA;  policy: ivpol-report-admission-sample&#xA;  result: fail&#xA;  scored: true&#xA;  source: KyvernoImageValidatingPolicy&#xA;...&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new policy types are also fully supported in Kyverno &lt;a href=&#34;https://playground.kyverno.io/next/#/&#34;&gt;Playground&lt;/a&gt;, allowing users to experiment with and test these policies in a web interface before deploying them to production environments. &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/policy-reporter&#34;&gt;Policy Reporter&lt;/a&gt; has also been enhanced to visualize and manage the specialized reports generated by these policy types, providing intuitive dashboards and alerts that help teams monitor image verification status and validation results across their clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Getting Started &amp;amp; Backward Compatibility&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Upgrading to Kyverno 1.14&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To upgrade to Kyverno 1.14, you can use Helm:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;helm repo update&#xA;helm upgrade kyverno kyverno/kyverno -n kyverno --version v1.14.0&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Backward Compatibility&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.14 maintains full backward compatibility with existing ClusterPolicy resources. You can continue using your current policies while gradually migrating to the new policy types as needed. The original ClusterPolicy type will continue to be supported, giving you time to evaluate and adopt the new specialized policy types at your own pace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Roadmap&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The introduction of &lt;em&gt;ValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;ImageValidatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; is just the beginning of our vision to make policy management in Kubernetes more modular, streamlined, and powerful. Looking ahead, we plan to complete the policy family with dedicated &lt;em&gt;MutatingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; for targeted resource modifications, &lt;em&gt;GeneratingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; for creating dependent resources, and &lt;em&gt;DeletingPolicy&lt;/em&gt; for controlled resource cleanup – each designed to excel at specific functions while maintaining a consistent user experience. This modular approach will simplify policy definition and management, reducing complexity while expanding capabilities. We’re also enhancing cross-cutting features, such as event generation, to provide detailed audit trails of policy actions and comprehensive metrics support, giving operators visibility into policy performance and effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.14.0 represents a significant evolution in Kubernetes policy management, offering more focused, efficient ways to implement policies. The new ValidatingPolicy and ImageValidatingPolicy types provide powerful capabilities while simplifying how users write and manage policies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this release cycle, there were &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/compare/release-1.13...v1.14.0&#34;&gt;744 changes&lt;/a&gt;, showcasing the extensive work and improvements made to the project. We are incredibly grateful to the over 60 contributors who participated in this release, with 40 of them being first-time contributors. This highlights the vibrant and growing community behind Kyverno, and we are thrilled to see such a collaborative effort. We extend our heartfelt thanks to everyone who contributed, and we encourage even more community involvement. Your contributions are vital to the continued success and evolution of Kyverno.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to see how the community leverages these new capabilities and welcome your feedback as we continue to enhance Kyverno’s policy management capabilities. For the complete list of changes, check out the release notes on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/releases/tag/v1.14.0&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;. Join us in shaping the future of policy management in Kubernetes!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxeaaup8donkjlmree3vlubzfnohppdv9x024rgvamqs8pipjg5qnebexv B8RQXQZWKDB1JED1DM8E-A3YKMWAL2LADGBM6S3JMH2DMSO6JCSAWXPFDL7KLJVM44JUQTMU7BLTWRYA？ alt =“ Kyverno版本1.14.0” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; tl; dr &lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;两种新的专业策略类型：验证和imageValidatingPolicy &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过改进的CEL支持和性能的简化验证&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用专用图像验证增强的供应链安全&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;政策例外现在支持细粒度控制的CEL表达&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; CLI改进用于任何JSON有效载荷左右验证&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;社区里程碑：744个变化，有60多个贡献者（40个初次！）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴地宣布发布Kyverno 1.14.0，这标志着我们在Kubernetes的政策管理过程中的旅程中的一个重要里程碑，更模块化，精简和强大。此版本介绍了两种新的策略类型 -  &lt;em&gt;验证policypolicy &lt;/em&gt;和&lt;em&gt; imageValidatingPolicy &lt;/em&gt;  - 代表了我们对Kubernetes环境中策略管理未来的愿景。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;为什么新策略类型？&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyverno的进化导致重叠规则类型的扩散（&lt;em&gt; validate.pattern &lt;/em&gt;，&lt;em&gt; validate.cel.cel.cel &lt;/em&gt;，&lt;em&gt; validate.deny &lt;/em&gt;等）在&lt;em&gt; clusterpolicy &lt;/em&gt; crd中，创造了不必要的复杂性。同时，Kubernetes使用CEL表达式引入了自己的&lt;em&gt; vallatingAdmissionpolicies &lt;/em&gt;和&lt;em&gt; mutatingAdmissionpolicies &lt;/em&gt;，为紧密的对齐提供了机会。新的政策类型通过将每个规则类型迁移到自己的专用CRD中来解决这些挑战。这种模块化方法简化了用户体验，在CEL上标准化以提高kubernetes的兼容性，简化了项目的维护，并提供了一种更清晰，更专注的方式，以根据其特定功能定义策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H1 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;新策略类型：模块化方法&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyverno 1.14.0通过引入专门的政策类型开始了kyverno的新章节，通过为验证检查以各种模式编写，通过提供更为专注的功能方法。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;“验证”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;新的&lt;em&gt;验证Policy &lt;/em&gt;自定义资源定义（CRD）通过将所有验证逻辑集中到专用的资源类型中，简化了如何编写验证规则。这种方法提供了几个优点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简化的结构&lt;/strong&gt;：一种干净，集中的结构，使策略更容易编写和理解&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; cel-first第一应用蟑螂&lt;/strong&gt;：验证policy使用CEL（通用表达语言）作为主要验证方法，与Kubernetes自己的策略管理轨迹保持一致&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;本地兼容性&lt;/strong&gt;：与Kubernetes验证adaDaiddricePolicy &lt;/li&gt;无缝地工作&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;改进的性能&lt;/strong&gt;：通过减少开销的更快验证进行优化&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是验证部署复制品的一个示例（确保部署不超过最大副本计数）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上一个&lt;em&gt; clusterpolicy &lt;/em&gt;方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：kyverno.io/v1&#xA;种类：群集&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  姓名：检查部门重复&#xA;规格：&#xA;  验证：强制性：执行&#xA;  规则：&#xA;     - 名称：校验重复&#xA;      匹配：&#xA;        资源：&#xA;          种类：&#xA;             - 部署&#xA;      证实：&#xA;        消息：“复制品的数量不得超过5”&#xA;        图案：&#xA;          规格：&#xA;            副本：“ &lt;= 5”&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; new &lt;em&gt;验证policy &lt;/em&gt;方法：&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：palicies.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;善良：验证物理&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  姓名：检查部门重复&#xA;规格：&#xA;  验证：&#xA;     - 表达式：“ object.spec.replicas &lt;= 5”&#xA;      消息：“复制品的数量不得超过5”&#xA;  Matchconstraints：&#xA;    资源：&#xA;      -Apigroups：[“应用程序”]&#xA;        apiversions：[“ V1”]&#xA;        资源：[“部署”]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;验证addaiddermission-policypolicy &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本通过自动生成Kubernetes &lt;em&gt; validatingAdmissionPolicies &lt;/em&gt;从&lt;em&gt; validatingPolicy &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; validatingAdmissionpolicies &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt;，可以直接由Kubernetes API服务器执行验证，而不是kyverno Admessive Contersions。这种能力通过利用本地Kubernetes验证来提高性能和韧性，同时保持Kyverno提供的丰富功能集和易用性。阅读有关&lt;a href =“ https://main.kyverno.io.io/docs/policy-types/validating-policy/#autogen”&gt; auto-generating validativatingAddissionAdmissionPolicyPolicyPolicyPolicyPolicyPolicy &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与验证的addaidpolicy &lt;/p&gt;进行比较&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-table”&gt; &lt;table class =“ has-fixed-layout”&gt; &lt;tbody&gt; &lt;ttry&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;strong&gt;功能&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k8s varrivationadmissionAdmissionPolicy &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;验证policy &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;执行&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;录取&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;入学，背景，管道，…&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;有偿yaml &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;发行&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; kubernetes api server &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; helm，cli，web服务，api，api，sdk &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;ttd&gt; cel library &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;基本&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;扩展&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt; bindings &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt;手动&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;自动验证advisingAdmissionPolicy &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;外部数据&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; kubernEtes Resources或API调用&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;缓存&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt;全局上下文，图像验证结果&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;背景扫描&lt;/td&gt;更新&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;异常offload &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;tr&gt; &lt;td&gt;测试&lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;td&gt; kyverno cli（单位），Chainsaw（E2e）&lt;/td&gt; &lt;/td&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tr&gt; &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/tbody&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;/table&gt; &lt;/figig&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关验证的更多详细信息，请查看官方文档&lt;a href =“ https://main---- kyverno.netlify.app/docs/policy-types/validating-policy/-policy-policy/”&gt;在这里&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; ImageValidatingPolicy &lt;/em&gt;是一种专用的策略类型，专门针对容器图像验证，可显着增强软件供应链安全性功能。通过将图像验证规则从&lt;em&gt; clusterpolicy &lt;/em&gt;中解散到自己的CRD中，它为图像安全性提供了更模块化和简化的方法。此策略类型还可以从任何JSON有效载荷中提取图像，从而允许全面且灵活的图像验证。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;关键功能包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;全面的图像验证&lt;/strong&gt;：验证签名，软件材料清单（SBOM），证明和其他工件，以确保容器图像的完整性和真实性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;灵活匹配&lt;/strong&gt;：使用球形图案或强大的CEL表达式匹配图像，在定义验证标准方面提供多功能性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;增强CEL功能&lt;/strong&gt;：利用专门的CEL功能来验证图像签名和证明，使复杂的验证逻辑更易于实现。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下&lt;em&gt; imageValidatingPolicy &lt;/em&gt;验证所有容器图像来自&lt;em&gt; ghcr.io &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; ghcr.io &lt;/em&gt;符合严格的供应链安全要求，以确保正确签名所有图像。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：palicies.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;种类：图像validatingPolicy&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：IVPOL样本&#xA;规格：&#xA;  webhookconfiguration：&#xA;    超时路要数：20&#xA;  失败物理：忽略&#xA;  验证措施：&#xA;    - 否定&#xA;  Matchconstraints：&#xA;    资源：&#xA;      -Apigroups：[“”]&#xA;        apiversions：[“ V1”]&#xA;        操作：[“创建”]&#xA;        资源：[“豆荚”]&#xA;  Matchimagreeferences：&#xA;    -Glob：ghcr.io/*&#xA;  认证者：&#xA;     - 名称：公证人&#xA;      公证人：&#xA;        证书：&#xA;          价值：|  - &#xA;            -----开始证书--------------&#xA;            …&#xA;            …&#xA;            -----结束证书---------------&#xA;  证明：&#xA;     - 名称：SBOM&#xA;      推荐人：&#xA;        类型：SBOM/Cyclone-DX&#xA;  验证：&#xA;     - 表达：&gt;  - &#xA;        images.containers.map（图像，verifyImagesignatures（图像，[adtestors.notary]））。所有（e，e&gt; 0）&#xA;      消息：无法使用ify图像带公证证书&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下策略通过从configmap中动态获取公证证书来增强安全姿势：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：palicies.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;种类：图像validatingPolicy&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：检查图像&#xA;规格：&#xA;  Matchconstraints：&#xA;    资源：&#xA;      -Apigroups：[“”]&#xA;        apiversions：[“ V1”]&#xA;        操作：[“创建”]&#xA;        资源：[“豆荚”]&#xA;  变量：&#xA;     - 名称：CM&#xA;      表达：&gt;  - &#xA;        resource.get（“ v1”，“ configmaps”，object.metadata.namespace，“键”）&#xA;  Matchimagreeferences：&#xA;    -Glob：ghcr.io/*&#xA;  认证者：&#xA;     - 名称：公证人&#xA;      公证人：&#xA;        证书：&#xA;          表达式：variables.cm.data.certificate&#xA;   验证：&#xA;     - 表达：&gt;  - &#xA;        images.containers.map（图像，verifyImagesignatures（图像，[adtestors.notary]））。所有（e，e&gt; 0）&#xA;      消息：无法使用公证证书验证图像&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关ImageValidatingPolicy的更多详细信息，请检查官方文档&lt;a href =“ https://main.kyverno.io.io/docs/policy-types/image-validating-policy/-policy-policy/&gt;在这里&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;其他功能和增强&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; cel PolicyExceptions &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyverno 1.14.0扩展了功能强大的&lt;a href =“ https://kyverno.io/docs/docs/expections/#policyexpections/#policyexpections-with-cel-expressions”&gt; PolicyExections&gt; PolicyException &lt;/a&gt;功能&lt;/a&gt;与新的策略类型无缝地工作。这种增强提供了对政策执法的颗粒状控制，使管理员可以在需要时定义特定的豁免。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;策略例外使团队能够：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;为特定的工作量或资源创建有针对性的豁免&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;定义不应应用政策的精确条件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;平衡严格的安全控制与实际操作需求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持迁移路径和特殊用例&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，您可以创建一个异常，将特定部署排除在&lt;em&gt; imageValidatingPolicy &lt;/em&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;中&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：palicies.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;善：策略评估&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  姓名：排除销售的部署&#xA;规格：&#xA;  PolicyRefs：&#xA;   - 名称：“ ivpol-report-background-sample”&#xA;    种类：图像validatingPolicy&#xA;  火柴条件：&#xA;     - 名称：“ check-name”&#xA;      表达式：“ object.metadata.name ==&#39;跳过部署&#39;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此示例中，&lt;em&gt; policy Exception &lt;/em&gt;将任何名为“跳过部门”的资源豁免了“ IVPOL-RENPORT-BACKROCK-STAME” &lt;em&gt; ImageValidatingPolicy &lt;/em&gt;。 &lt;em&gt; MatchConditions &lt;/em&gt;字段使用CEL表达式精确定义了何时适用该异常，从而使管理员对策略执行进行细粒度的控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;高级cel库&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyverno 1.14.0包括强大的cel库超出标准的Kubernetes功能。这些图书馆无缝地与新的政策类型一起工作，同时保持与已建立的kyverno功能的向后兼容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是每个库的示例签名，有关完整列表，请参阅&lt;a href =“ https://main.kyverno.io.io/docs/policy-types/validating-policy/#kyverno-celverno-cel-cel-cel-cel-cel-cel-cel-libraries”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;资源库&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;资源库检索针对当前群集状态的实时验证的Kubernetes资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;resource.list（“ apps/v1”，“部署”，“默认”）。项目&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; http库&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; HTTP库启用外部API呼吁将第三方验证集成到策略决策中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; http.send（“ get”，“ https：//api.example.com/data”，{}）。&#xA;http.post（“ https：//audit.api/log”，{“n式”：object.kind}，{“ content-type”：“ application/json”}）。&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;用户库&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户库包括parseserviceaccount（）之类的功能，以从触发入学请求的用户或服务帐户中提取元数据。这些表达式有助于基于用户身份，命名空间关联或服务帐户命名的策略执行策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; parseserviceaccount（request.userinfo.username）&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; globalContext库&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; GlobalContext库提供了对多个策略共享的缓存数据的访问，从而通过避免冗余API调用来提高性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;globalContext.get（“允许Registries”，“”）.registries.exists（r，image.Registry == r）：&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;图像库&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;图像库解析了容器图像参考，启用诸如注册表，存储库，标签和摘要之类的图像组件的验证。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; image（“ nginx：最新”）。注册表==“ docker.io”&#xA;图像（“ ghcr.io/company/app:v1.2.3”）。containsDigest（）&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-teading”&gt;图像数据库&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Imagedata库可以深入检查OCI注册表中的容器图像元数据，包括体系结构，OS，层和清单细节。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; image.getMetadata（“ nginx：1.21”）。config.architecture ==“ amd64”&#xA;image.getMetAdata（“ my-image：最新”）。subtest.layers.size（）&gt; 0&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; cli＆Reporting &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyverno 1.14.0通过扩展对新的&lt;em&gt; validatingpolicy &lt;/em&gt;和&lt;em&gt; im的支持来增强CLI体验AgeValidatingPolicy &lt;/em&gt;类型，在将其应用于群集之前，可以更容易测试和验证策略。 CLI对在开发或CI/CD管道期间的策略左右测试是有益的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，您可以在构建图像之前针对安全策略验证Dockerfile（表示为JSON）。在以下&lt;em&gt;验证绘制片段中，它使用cel表达式检查dockerfile结构并扫描是否诸如curl &lt;/em&gt;之类的禁止命令。请参阅完整清单&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/kyverno/tree/v1.14.0/test/cli/test-validating-policy/json-check-dockerfile”&gt;在这里&lt;/a&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt;验证：&#xA;   - 消息：“不允许卷发”&#xA;    表达：&gt;  -  &#xA;      ！object.stages.exists（S， &#xA;        s.commands.sists（c， &#xA;          具有（c.cmdline）&amp;&amp; c.cmdline.exists（cmd，string（cmd）.contains（&#39;curl’））&#xA;        ）&#xA;      ）&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;补充这些CLI功能，Kyverno还将新的政策类型与&lt;em&gt; Policy Reporport &lt;/em&gt;框架集成在一起。尽管CLI可以帮助您在开发过程中验证资源，但政策报告可在环境中持续了解合规性状态。这些报告清楚地确定了哪种策略类型生成了结果（来源：KyvernoimageValidatingPolicy），通过所有者参考链接到评估资源的链接，并提供可行的消息进行补救。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：wgpolicyk8s.io/v1alpha2&#xA;善：政策报告&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  标签：&#xA;    app.kubernetes.io/managed-by：kyverno&#xA;  所有者报道：&#xA;  -Apiversion：应用程序/V1&#xA;    类型：部署&#xA;    姓名：测试人员&#xA;范围：&#xA;  apiversion：应用程序/V1&#xA;  类型：部署&#xA;  姓名：测试人员&#xA;结果：&#xA; - 消息：未能使用公证证书验证图像&#xA;  策略：IVPOL-报告 - 入选样本&#xA;  结果：失败&#xA;  得分：是的&#xA;  资料来源：kyvernoimageValidatingPolicy&#xA;...&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyverno &lt;a href =“ https://playground.kyverno.io.io/next/#/”&gt; Playground &lt;/a&gt;，在将用户允许用户在将它们部署到生产环境之前，允许用户在网络界面中尝试并测试这些策略。 &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kyverno/policy-reporter”&gt;策略记者&lt;/a&gt;也已得到增强，以可视化和管理这些策略类型生成的专业报告，从而提供直观的仪表板和警报，并提供帮助团队监控图像验证状态和验证结果的结果。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;入门和向后兼容&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;升级到kyverno 1.14 &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要升级到kyverno 1.14，您可以使用头盔：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; helm repo更新&#xA;Helm升级kyverno kyverno/kyverno -n kyverno-version v1.14.0&#xA;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-tearing”&gt;向后兼容性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyverno 1.14保持全部向后的补偿具有现有的群集资源的含义。您可以根据需要逐渐迁移到新的策略类型时继续使用当前的策略。原始的群集类型将继续得到支持，使您有时间以自己的节奏评估和采用新的专业政策类型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H1 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;路线图&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;引入&lt;em&gt;验证policypolicy &lt;/em&gt;和&lt;em&gt; imageValidatingPolicy &lt;/em&gt;只是我们愿景的开始，即使Kubernetes中的策略管理更加模块化，简化和强大。展望未来，我们计划使用专用&lt;em&gt;突变的政策&lt;/em&gt;进行目标资源修改，&lt;em&gt;生成&lt;/em&gt;用于创建依赖资源，而&lt;em&gt; deletingpolicy &lt;/em&gt;用于受控资源清理 - 每种都旨在在特定功能上表现出一致的功能，同时保持一致的用户体验。这种模块化方法将简化策略定义和管理，从而降低复杂性，同时扩大功能。我们还在增强跨切割功能，例如活动生成，以提供有关政策行动和全面指标支持的详细审核之路，从而使操作员可见政策绩效和有效性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;结论&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kyverno 1.14.0代表了Kubernetes政策管理的重大发展，提供了更加专注，有效的实施政策的方法。新的验证物质和ImageValidatingPolicy类型提供了强大的功能，同时简化了用户的编写和管理策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此发行周期中，有&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/kyverno/compare/release-1.1.13...v1.14.0”&gt; 744更改&lt;/a&gt;，展示了对项目进行的广泛工作和改进。我们非常感谢参加此版本的60多名贡献者，其中40位是首次贡献者。这突出了Kyverno背后充满活力和不断增长的社区，我们很高兴看到如此合作的努力。我们衷心感谢所有贡献的人，我们鼓励更多的社区参与。您的贡献对于kyverno的持续成功和演变至关重要。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，我们很高兴看到社区如何利用这些新功能，并随着我们继续增强Kyverno的政策管理能力，欢迎您的反馈。有关更改的完整列表，请查看&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/kyverno/ReleaSes/tag/v1.14.0”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt;的发行说明。加入我们，塑造Kubernetes政策管理的未来！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>