<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://cloudys-rsshub-ab061133bcab.herokuapp.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 Co-Located Event Deep Dive: Observability Day】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon北美2024年共同置换活动深度潜水：可观察日</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/19/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2024-co-located-event-deep-dive-observability-day-2/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1746&#34; height=&#34;294&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Observability Day North America 2025 Graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-146181&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1.jpg 1746w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-300x51.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-1024x172.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-768x129.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-900x152.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-600x101.jpg 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-1200x202.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1746px) 100vw, 1746px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/observability-day/?ajs_aid=b4cbcea8-db3a-48a5-b9ca-81b8469a1e6a&#34;&gt;Observability Day&lt;/a&gt; traces its roots back to KubeCon Europe 2022 in Valencia, where we hosted FluentCon, a co-located event dedicated exclusively to the Fluentd and Fluent Bit projects. The gathering was a success, and the feedback we received from the community made it clear that we could serve the broader observability space at KubeCon in an even bigger way. To make that happen, we expanded our focus and invited other CNCF projects to join.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just a few months later, at KubeCon US 2022, we introduced Open Observability Day, bringing together maintainers and community members from projects such as Jaeger, Fluentd, Thanos, Prometheus, and OpenTelemetry. The response was overwhelmingly positive, and it quickly became clear that this effort needed to evolve into something more formal and structured. Working closely with the CNCF, that vision became reality—and Observability Day was officially born&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you want attendees to get out of this event?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We want attendees to know that Observability Day is a community-driven gathering where practitioners, end users, and project maintainers come together to shape the future of observability. It’s not just about one tool or project, it’s about learning from each other, sharing best practices, and exploring how the CNCF ecosystem works together to solve real-world challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re new to observability or deeply involved in projects like Prometheus, Fluent Bit, Jaeger, Thanos, or OpenTelemetry, you’ll leave with practical insights, valuable connections, and a clearer picture of where the space is heading. Most importantly, this is your chance to directly engage with the people building the tools you use every day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is new and different this year?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What’s new this year is the breadth and depth of community-driven content. Observability Day 2025 puts CNCF projects front and center, with maintainers and practitioners sharing the latest updates and lessons learned. You’ll find talks that go beyond theory—covering real-world scaling challenges, cost-efficient monitoring strategies, and new frontiers like AI observability&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s also a stronger emphasis on OpenTelemetry in action, from rapid adoption patterns to advanced use cases in telco, mobile, and enterprise systems. Panels and lightning talks bring diverse voices together, giving space for emerging projects and honest conversations about what works (and what doesn’t) in production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, this year’s event is designed to help the community connect the dots across projects, learn from real experiences, and shape the future of observability together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will the day look like?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Observability Day is a full-day community gathering focused on CNCF observability projects and real-world practices. The program starts with opening remarks and project updates, then moves into a mix of deep-dive talks, case studies, and panels covering everything from scaling OpenTelemetry to tackling cost, performance, and AI observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, sessions highlight practical lessons from end users and contributors, followed by interactive panels and lightning talks that showcase emerging ideas. The day closes with reflections from the community, leaving attendees with fresh insights and new connections to carry forward.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should I do any homework first?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Attendees don’t need to do heavy prep, but a little groundwork can make the experience more valuable. We recommend:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reviewing the CNCF observability landscape – get familiar with projects like Prometheus, Fluent Bit, Jaeger, Thanos, and OpenTelemetry, since many sessions dive deep into these.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bringing real questions or challenges – the panels and community discussions are a great place to get practical advice directly from maintainers and practitioners.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Exploring OpenTelemetry basics – since many talks highlight OTel adoption and use cases, having a baseline understanding will help you follow along more easily.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Skimming the agenda – choose in advance which talks align most with your work, so you don’t miss the ones that matter most to you.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, come ready to connect, share experiences, and learn from the community—that’s where the real value of the day comes from.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet your community!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At its core, Observability Day is about community and collaboration. It’s the one place where maintainers, practitioners, and end users can come together to learn from each other, share honest lessons from the field, and influence the future of CNCF observability projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re coming for the technical depth, the project updates, or simply to connect with others who share your challenges, this event is built to give you both practical takeaways and meaningful connections. We’re excited to see how the conversations and ideas from this day ripple out into the wider community&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We hope you join us at &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/observability-day/?ajs_aid=b4cbcea8-db3a-48a5-b9ca-81b8469a1e6a&#34;&gt;Observability Day&lt;/a&gt; this year!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1746&#34; height=&#34;294&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Observability Day North America 2025 Graphic&#34; class =“ wp-image-146181” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1.jpg 1746w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-300x51.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-1024x172.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-768x129.jpg 768w，https://wwwww.cncf.io/wp.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/2025/2025/09/image-1900-1-1-159.p.159.p.j159.jp.jj159.jpr https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1-600x101.jpg 600w，https://wwwwwww.cncf.io/wp.io/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/209/image-1200x202.jppe （最大宽度：1746px）100VW，1746px“ reverrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-merica/co-located-events/observibents/observibality-day/?ajs_aid=b4cbcbcea8-cbcbcea8-db3a-48a5-b9ca-81B81B81B81B81B81B81B81B81B81B81B81B81B81B816AAA到瓦伦西亚（Valencia）的库贝康欧洲（Kubecon Europe），我们在那里举办了Fluentcon，这是一个专门针对Fluentd and Fluent Bit项目的共同地点的活动。聚会取得了成功，我们从社区那里收到的反馈明确表示，我们可以以更大的方式为库贝孔提供更广泛的可观察性空间。为了实现这一目标，我们扩大了重点，并邀请其他CNCF项目加入。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;几个月后，在美国2022年的Kubecon，我们引入了开放性观察日，将Jaeger，Fluentd，Thanos，Prometheus和Opentelemetry等项目的维护者和社区成员汇集在一起​​。反应绝大多数是积极的，很快就清楚地表明，这种努力需要发展成为更正式和结构化的事情。与CNCF紧密合作，该愿景变成了现实，可观察到的日子正式出生&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您希望与会者摆脱此活动？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们希望与会者知道可观察日是一个社区驱动的聚会，从业者，最终用户和项目维护者聚集在一起以塑造可观察性的未来。这不仅与一个工具或项目有关，还与彼此学习，共享最佳实践以及探索CNCF生态系统如何共同努力解决现实世界中的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是不熟悉的可观察性，还是深深地参与Prometheus，Fluent Bit，Jaeger，Thanos或Opentelemetry等项目，您都将带有实用的见解，有价值的连接以及更清晰的空间前进方向。最重要的是，这是您直接与建立您每天使用的工具的人们直接互动的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;今年有什么新鲜事物？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年的新功能是社区驱动内容的广度和深度。可观察到第202天5将CNCF项目放在首位和中心，维护人员和从业人员分享了最新的更新和经验教训。您会发现超越理论的演讲 - 跨越现实世界的扩展挑战，成本效益的监视策略以及AI可观察性&lt;/p&gt;等新边界&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在行动中，从快速采用模式到电信，移动和企业系统中的高级用例也更加强调Opentelemetry。面板和闪电谈话将各种各样的声音聚集在一起，为新兴项目提供了空间，并就生产中有效的（以及什么无效）的诚实对话。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;简而言之，今年的活动旨在帮助社区跨项目连接点，从真实的经验中学习并塑造可观察性的未来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;这一天会是什么样？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可观察日是一个全天的社区聚会，专注于CNCF可观察性项目和现实世界实践。该计划从开幕式和项目更新开始，然后融入深度潜水对话，案例研究以及涵盖从缩放OpentElemetry到解决成本，性能和AI可观察性的所有内容的组合。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下午，会议突出了最终用户和贡献者的实用课程，其次是交互式面板和闪电谈话，展示新兴的想法。这一天通过社区的思考而结束，让与会者提供新的见解和新的联系以实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我应该先做任何家庭作业吗？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与会者无需进行重度准备，但是一点基础可以使体验更有价值。我们建议：&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;审查CNCF可观察性景观 - 熟悉Prometheus，Fluent Bit，Jaeger，Thanos和Opentelemetry等项目，因为许多会议深入研究了这些。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;带来真正的问题或挑战 - 小组讨论是直接从维护者和从业者那里获得实用建议的好地方。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;探索OpenTelemetry基础知识 - 由于许多谈话突出了Otel的采用和用例，因此具有基线理解将有助于您更轻松地遵循。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;浏览议程 - 提前选择与您的工作相符，因此您不会错过对您最重要的事情。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最重要的是，准备联系，分享经验和向社区学习 - 这是一天的真正价值来自。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;与您的社区见面！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以其核心，可观察日是关于社区和协作的。这是维护者，从业者和最终用户可以互相学习，分享诚实的课程并影响CNCF可观察性P的未来的地方ROjects。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是要进行技术深度，项目更新，还是只是与分享您挑战的其他人建立联系，该活动都是为了为您提供实际的要点和有意义的联系。我们很高兴看到这一天的对话和想法如何融入更广泛的社区&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们希望您通过&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-north-merica/co-located-events/observents/observents/observibity-day/？今年！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon India 2025: A Transformative Experience in Hyderabad】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon印度2025年：海得拉巴的变革经验</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/19/kubecon-cloudnativecon-india-2025-a-transformative-experience-in-hyderabad/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;My journey from Sri Lanka to India’s premier cloud-native conference&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; height=&#34;437&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon India Graphic&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-147543&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1.jpg 720w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1-300x182.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1-330x200.jpg 330w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1-659x400.jpg 659w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Dream Come True: The Dan Kohn Scholarship&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m thrilled to share my incredible experience at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon India 2025 in Hyderabad, made possible through the prestigious Dan Kohn Scholarship from the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My heartfelt gratitude goes to Kanchana Wickremasinghe, Audra Montenegro, and Wendi West from CNCF for selecting me from the KCD Organizer digest, and special thanks to Kemila De Silva for nominating me. This opportunity opened doors to an unforgettable learning and networking experience that will shape my cloud-native journey for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reuniting with Fellow Sri Lankan Cloud Native Leaders&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most exciting aspects of this trip was meeting my fellow KCD organizers and CNCF ambassadors Kemila De Silva and Chamod Shehanka Perera. These amazing individuals traveled to Hyderabad to speak on the first day of KubeCon, representing the vibrant Sri Lankan cloud-native community on an international stage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 1: Keynotes, Connections, and Big Announcements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our first day began with the essential conference ritual of collecting our badges and heading to the keynote hall. The energy was palpable, with thousands of cloud-native enthusiasts gathered under one roof.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Brief but Memorable Encounter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After the keynotes, we had the privilege of meeting Chris, the CTO of Cloud Infrastructure at CNCF. Despite his hectic schedule, he graciously took a minute to speak with us, a testament to the inclusive, welcoming nature of the CNCF community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; height=&#34;540&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Selfie image with Chris A.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-147544&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2.jpg 720w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2-267x200.jpg 267w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2-533x400.jpg 533w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exciting News: KubeCon 2026 Mumbai&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the initial keynotes, we received thrilling news: KubeCon 2026 is coming to Mumbai in July! This announcement was met with thunderous applause and signals the growing importance of India in the global cloud native ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Solution Showcase: Unexpected Sri Lankan Connections&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Solution Showcase proved to be a treasure trove of discoveries. We were delighted to meet two fellow Sri Lankans making their mark in the cloud-native world:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; height=&#34;1280&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Fellow Sri Lankan selfie&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-147545&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1.jpg 720w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1-169x300.jpg 169w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1-576x1024.jpg 576w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1-113x200.jpg 113w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1-225x400.jpg 225w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploring Cutting-Edge Observability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The showcase floor buzzed with innovative technologies. We dove deep into new observability solutions, exploring offerings from:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Middleware&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Grafana Labs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ClickHouse&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each interaction provided valuable insights into the evolving landscape of cloud-native monitoring and observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Solving Real-World Problems: AWS EKS Discussion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most practical benefits of attending KubeCon was the opportunity to discuss real challenges with experts. I had an invaluable conversation with the AWS EKS team in India regarding an EKS cluster upgrade issue I was facing. They provided their team’s contact information but also demonstrated EKS Auto Mode, showcasing how to fully automate managed clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building Partnerships: Grafana Labs Connection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A particularly exciting conversation was with Ana Vrsalovic, Developer Programs Specialist at Grafana Labs. I shared details about KCD Sri Lanka, scheduled for October 26th, and she graciously promised support for our future events. These partnerships are crucial for strengthening the global cloud-native community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Deep Dives and Learning Sessions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;gRPC Lightning Talk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Hall 3, I attended “Essential Resources for gRPC Development” by Kannan Jayaprakasam. This lightning talk provided valuable insights into the updated features of gRPC, enhancing my understanding of this critical communication protocol.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infrastructure Knowledge Graphs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hall 1 hosted “To Succeed in Platform Engineering, Build Infrastructure Knowledge Graphs” by Safeer. This session opened new perspectives on platform engineering approaches and the importance of visualizing infrastructure relationships.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Taste of Hyderabad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The authentic Hyderabadi lunch was a delightful cultural experience, offering delicious local flavors that perfectly complemented the day’s technical sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dockerfiles vs Buildpacks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Back in Hall 3, Ram Iyengar (who previously spoke at our KCD Sri Lanka 2023) presented “Dockerfiles vs Buildpacks: What’s The Cloud Native Way?” This session was particularly engaging, as it demonstrated how to transform applications into containers with ease.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sri Lankan Spotlight: Community Leadership Talk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The day’s highlight was Kemila’s and Chamod’s presentation: “Lessons from Running a CNCF Community: Mistakes, Wins, and Growth.” They shared the incredible journey of KCD Sri Lanka, from its inception to its current success, and revealed the upcoming KCD Sri Lanka date: October 26th.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Day 2: Deeper Connections and Advanced Topics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Morning Rituals and Networking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Day two began with breakfast at HICC, followed by inspiring keynotes and the perfect accompaniment, authentic Indian chai with biscuits. These small moments of cultural immersion added richness to the technical conference experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video Interviews and Community Building&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We conducted several video interviews with members of the Indian CNCF community and tech experts, focusing on promoting KCD Sri Lanka. These conversations strengthened cross-border community connections and built anticipation for our October event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Machine Learning Meets Cloud Native&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I attended “Bridging Big Data and Machine Learning Ecosystems: A Cloud Native Approach Using Kubeflow” by Johnu George &amp;amp; Shiv Jha. This session provided valuable insights into the intersection of ML and cloud-native technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cast AI Deep Dive&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meeting Kunal from Cast AI led to an informative demonstration of their platform’s capabilities. His colleague walked us through Cast AI’s functionality, answering our questions and clarifying how their solution addresses real-world Kubernetes cost optimization challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Golden Kubestronaut Wisdom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another enriching encounter was with Sajeeva, a Golden Kubestronaut. Our knowledge-sharing session was invaluable, providing insights from someone who has achieved the highest level of Kubernetes expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reflections: An Unforgettable Experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the conference drew to a close, I found myself already missing the energy, learning opportunities, and connections that made KubeCon + CloudNativeCon India 2025 so special.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gratitude and Recognition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My humble gratitude goes to the organizers of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Hyderabad and the entire CNCF team for orchestrating a massive event with more than 4000 participants. The seamless execution and inclusive atmosphere made this experience truly unforgettable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking Forward: KCD Sri Lanka 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I return to Sri Lanka, I carry with me not just technical knowledge and new connections, but also renewed enthusiasm for our local community. KCD Sri Lanka is coming on October 26th at BMICH, Colombo, and I extend a humble invitation to everyone interested in Kubernetes and CNCF technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This KubeCon experience reinforced my belief in the power of community, the importance of knowledge sharing, and the incredible potential of cloud-native technologies to transform how we build and deploy applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;blob:https://www.cncf.io/d16cf053-0005-4757-ad97-6b5444177d48&#34; style=&#34;&#34; alt=&#34;Collage Graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Join us at KCD Sri Lanka 2025 on October 26th at BMICH, Colombo. Let’s continue building the cloud-native community together!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blog Link:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@kaveeshag/kubecon-cloudnativecon-india-2025-a-transformative-experience-in-hyderabad-d77e7def7ced&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon India 2025: A Transformative Experience&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Video:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtube.com/shorts/joc7WyER8L4&#34;&gt;https://youtube.com/shorts/joc7WyER8L4&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;我从斯里兰卡到印度的首屈一指的云本地会议的旅程&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; height=&#34;437&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon印度图形“ class =” wp-image-147543“ srcset =” https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1.jpg 720w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1-300x182.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1-330x200.jpg 330w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-1-659x400.jpg 659w“ sizes =” sizes =“ auto，（max-width：720px）100vw，100vw，720px“ referrerpolicy =”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;梦想成真：丹·科恩奖学金&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我很高兴分享我在海得拉巴的Kubecon + Cloudnativecon India 2025年的不可思议的经历，这是通过云机构计算基金会（CNCF）的享有声望的Dan Kohn奖学金。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我衷心感谢CNCF的Kanchana Wickremasinghe，Audra Montenegro和Wendi West，从KCD组织者Digest中选择了我，并特别感谢Kemila de Silva提名我。这个机会为难忘的学习和网络经验打开了大门，这将影响我未来几年的云原始旅程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;与Sri Lankan Cloud本地领导人团聚&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这次旅行最令人兴奋的方面之一是与我的KCD组织者和CNCF大使Kemila de Silva和Chamod Shehanka Perera会面。这些了不起的人前往海得拉巴，在库贝孔的第一天讲话，代表着充满活力的斯里兰卡云土地社区，在国际舞台上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第1天：主题，连接和大公告&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的第一天始于收集徽章并前往主题演讲厅的基本会议仪式。能量很明显，成千上万的云源发烧友聚集在一个屋顶下。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;短暂但令人难忘的相遇&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主题演讲之后，我们有特权与CNCF的Chris CTO会见Chris。尽管他的日程安排忙碌，但他花了一分钟的时间与我们交谈，这证明了CNCF社区的包容性，热情的性质。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; height=&#34;540&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Selfie image with Chris A.&#34; class =“ wp-image-147544” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2.jpg 720w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2-300x225.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2-267x200.jpg 267w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-4-2-533x400.jpg 533W“ sizes =” sizes =“ auto，（max-width：720px）100vw，100vw，720px“ weverrerpolicy&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;令人兴奋的新闻：库贝肯2026孟买&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在最初的主题演讲中，我们收到了令人兴奋的新闻：Kubecon 2026将于7月来到孟买！该公告受到了雷鸣般的掌声，并表示印度在全球云本地生态系统中的重要性日益严重。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;解决方案展示：意外的Sri Lankan连接&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;解决方案展示柜被证明是发现的宝库。我们很高兴认识两个斯里兰卡人在云国世界中留下自己的印记：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; height=&#34;1280&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Fellow Sri Lankan selfie&#34; class =“ wp-image-147545” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1.jpg 720w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1-169x300.jpg 169w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1-576x1024.jpg 576w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-5-1-113x200.jpg 113w，https://www.cncf.io/wp.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/225/2025/225/5-5-154.jp254.jp254.jpp25400.jpp25400.jpp5xpp5xpp5xpp5xpp5x5400.jp尺寸=“ auto，（最大宽度：720px）100VW，720px” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;探索尖端可观察性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;展示地板上嗡嗡作响的创新技术。我们深入研究了新的可观察性解决方案，探索了以下方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;中间件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Grafana Labs &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Clickhouse &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每种互动都为云本地监测和可观察性的不断发展的景观提供了宝贵的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;解决现实世界问题：AWS EKS讨论&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;参加Kubecon的最实际好处之一是与专家讨论真正的挑战的机会。我与印度的AWS EKS团队进行了无价的对话，讨论了我面临的EKS集群升级问题。他们提供了团队的联系信息，但还展示了EKS自动模式，展示了如何完全自动化托管群集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;建立合作伙伴关系：Grafana Labs Connection &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与Grafana Labs的开发人员计划专家Ana Vrsalovic进行了一次特别令人兴奋的对话。我分享了计划于10月26日举行的KCD斯里兰卡的详细信息，她慷慨地承诺支持我们未来的活动。这些伙伴关系对于加强全球云本地社区至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;技术深度潜水和学习课程&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; grpc Lightning Talk &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在第3厅，我参加了Kannan Jayaprakasam的“ GRPC开发基本资源”。这次闪电谈话为GRPC的更新功能提供了宝贵的见解，从而增强了我对这种关键交流协议的理解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;基础架构知识图&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Hall 1主持了“在平台工程中取得成功，建立基础架构知识图”。该会议为平台工程方法开辟了新的观点以及可视化基础架构关系的重要性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;海得拉巴的味道&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正宗的海得拉巴午餐是一种令人愉快的文化体验，提供了完美补充当天技术会议的美味当地风味。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; dockerfiles vs buildpacks &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;回到3厅，Ram Iyengar（以前在我们的KCD Sri Lanka 2023上讲话）介绍了“ Dockerfiles vs Buildpacks：什么是Cloud Native方式？”本届会议特别引人入胜，因为它演示了如何轻松地将应用程序转换为容器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;斯里兰卡的聚光灯：社区领导力谈话&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当天的亮点是凯米拉（Kemila）和查索德（Chamod）的演讲：“经营CNCF社区的教训：错误，胜利和成长。”他们分享了KCD斯里兰卡的令人难以置信的旅程，从成立到目前的成功，并透露了即将到来的KCD Sri Lanka日期：10月26日。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第2天：更深的连接和高级主题&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;早晨的仪式和网络&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第二天从HICC开始了早餐，随后是鼓舞人心的主题演讲和完美的伴奏，正宗的印度柴和饼干。这些文化沉浸的一小部分为技术会议的经验增添了丰富性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;视频访谈和社区建设&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们对印度CNCF社区和技术专家的成员进行了几次视频访谈，重点是促进KCD Sri Lanka。这些对话加强了跨境社区的联系，并为我们的十月活动建立了期望。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;机器学习遇到云本地&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我参加了Johnu George＆Shiv Jha的“桥接大数据和机器学习生态系统：使用KubeFlow的云本机方法”。本届会议为ML和云原生技术的交集提供了宝贵的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;铸造AI深水&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与Cast AI的Kunal会面，导致了其平台能力的信息。他的同事带领我们完成了AI的功能，回答了我们的问题，并澄清了他们的解决方案如何解决现实世界中的Kubernetes成本优化挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;金色kubestronaut智慧&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一个丰富的遭遇是与金kubestronaut的萨吉瓦（Sajeeva）。我们的知识共享会议是无价的，从获得最高水平的Kubernetes专业知识的人提供了见解。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;反思：难忘的体验&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;会议结束时，我发现自己已经缺少使Kubecon + Cloudnativecon I的能量，学习机会和联系NDIA 2025如此特殊。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;感激和认可&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我谦虚的感激之情，感谢Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Hyderabad的组织者和整个CNCF团队，为与4000多名参与者一起精心策划了一场大规模的活动。无缝的执行和包容性的氛围使这种经历确实令人难忘。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;期待：KCD Sri Lanka 2025 &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我返回斯里兰卡时，我不仅随身携带技术知识和新的联系，而且还为我们的当地社区带来了热情。 KCD斯里兰卡将于10月26日在科伦坡的BMICH上市，我向对Kubernetes和CNCF Technologies感兴趣的每个人致以谦虚的邀请。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种库贝康的经验加强了我对社区力量，知识共享的重要性以及云本地技术改变我们如何构建和部署应用程序的难以置信的潜力的信念。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ blob：https：//www.cncf.io/d16cf053-0005-4757-4757-AD97-AD97-6B5444444177D48”斯里兰卡2025年10月26日在科伦坡的BMICH。让我们继续一起建立云本地社区！&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;博客链接：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https：//medium.comny@kaveeshag/@kaveeshag/kaveeshag/kaveeshag/kubecon-cloudnativecon-india-india-india-2025-2025-a-a-a-a-a-epperience-transience-transience-transience-intrienfation-in-hyderabad-hyderabad-d77e7e7e7e7e7e7e7e7e7defecn;经验&lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简短视频：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://youtube.com/shorts.com/shorts/joc7wyer8l4”&gt; https://youtube.com/youtube.com/shortbe.com/shorts/joc7wyer8l4l4l4l4l4l4 &lt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Kubernetes (K8s) Troubleshooting Techniques – Part 2】顶级Kubernetes（K8S）故障排除技术 - 第2部分</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/19/top-kubernetes-k8s-troubleshooting-techniques-part-2/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In Part 1 of our series, we explored essential Kubernetes troubleshooting techniques that help DevOps engineers diagnose and resolve common cluster and application issues effectively. However, Kubernetes environments are complex, and there’s always more to uncover.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this Part 2, we’ll dive deeper into additional troubleshooting strategies, covering advanced techniques and real-world scenarios that can save you time and prevent downtime. Whether you’re dealing with persistent pod failures, network issues, or cluster misconfigurations, these tips will equip you with the knowledge to tackle Kubernetes challenges with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Troubleshooting Storage: Resolving PVC Pending Errors&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;PersistentVolumeClaim (PVC) Pending&lt;/em&gt; status is a common storage issue in Kubernetes, preventing applications from accessing persistent data. This typically results from misconfigured storage classes, missing volume provisioners, or insufficient available storage in the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 1: Inspecting PV and PVC Status&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Start by listing all Persistent Volumes (PVs) and Persistent Volume Claims (PVCs) across all namespaces. This command provides an overview of their status, access modes, capacity, and whether they are bound:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get pv,pvc --all-namespaces&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 2: Troubleshooting Mounting Issues&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To further investigate an unbound PVC stuck in the &lt;em&gt;Pending&lt;/em&gt; state, use the following command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe pvc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check the &lt;strong&gt;Events&lt;/strong&gt; section at the bottom of the output. It often reveals the root cause, such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No matching&lt;code&gt; PersistentVolume &lt;/code&gt;available&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Storage class mismatch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Insufficient capacity&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Missing provisioned&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 3: Verifying Storage Classes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Incorrect or non-existent storage classes are a common culprit. List all available storage classes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get storageclass&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, describe a specific one to inspect details like the provisioner and parameters:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe storageclass&amp;nbsp;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ensure that your PVC references a valid, correctly configured storage class. If the specified provisioner does not exist or is misspelled, the volume will fail to provision.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 4: Common Mistakes and Resolution&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Suppose you’ve defined a PVC that references a storage class named &lt;code&gt;fast-ssd&lt;/code&gt;, but it’s failing to provision. Run:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe pvc my-data-pvc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You might see an error like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;Warning&amp;nbsp; ProvisioningFailed&amp;nbsp; 3m&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; persistentvolume-controller&amp;nbsp;&#xA;&#xA;storageclass.storage.k8s.io &#34;fast-ssd&#34; not found&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, list all available storage classes to confirm:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get storageclass&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If &lt;code&gt;fast-ssd&lt;/code&gt; is missing, but &lt;code&gt;gp2&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;standard&lt;/code&gt; exists, update your PVC to use a valid class.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;7. Using Event and Audit Logs: Deep System Analysis&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes provides two powerful tools for debugging: events and audit logs. These help you track what happened, when it happened, and why, giving you a timeline of system activities for root cause analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 1: Understanding Kubernetes Events&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Events in Kubernetes record what’s happening inside the cluster. You can list events across all namespaces and sort them by their creation time to see the most recent activity at the bottom. This helps correlate issues with recent system behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For a more comprehensive understanding of how Kubernetes handles logs across nodes and clusters, check out our complete guide to &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/kubernetes-logging/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes logging&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For View all events sorted by time:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get events --all-namespaces &#xA;--sort-by=&#39;.metadata.creationTimestamp&#39;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To filter events that occurred after a specific time:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get events &#xA;--field-selector=&#39;lastTimestamp&amp;gt;2023-10-01T10:00:00Z&#39;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To view only warning-type events (which often indicate potential problems):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get events --field-selector type=Warning&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also monitor events in real-time using the&lt;code&gt; --watch&lt;/code&gt; flag. This is helpful when you’re actively troubleshooting and want to immediately observe what happens after deploying or modifying resources:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get events --watch&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re investigating a specific pod, deployment, or service, you can filter events to focus only on that object. For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get events --field-selector &lt;a href=&#34;http://involvedobject.name/&#34;&gt;involvedObject.name&lt;/a&gt;=my-pod&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In case you’re dealing with pods not getting scheduled, you can filter events with a reason set to “FailedScheduling.” This will show why Kubernetes couldn’t place the pod on a node, such as due to insufficient resources or affinity conflicts:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get events --field-selector reason=FailedScheduling&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 2: Using Audit Logs for In-Depth Troubleshooting&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While events help you understand what’s happening, audit logs let you see &lt;strong&gt;who did what&lt;/strong&gt; at the API level essential for security investigations or when tracking administrative actions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Audit logs are not enabled by default. To enable them, you must configure an audit policy. Here’s a sample audit policy configuration that captures detailed logs for core resources like pods, services, deployments, etc.:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: audit.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: Policy&#xA;&#xA;rules:&#xA;&#xA;- level: RequestResponse&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resources:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- group: &#34;&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resources: [&#34;pods&#34;, &#34;services&#34;]&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- group: &#34;apps&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resources: [&#34;deployments&#34;, &#34;replicasets&#34;]&#xA;&#xA;- level: Request&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resources:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- group: &#34;&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resources: [&#34;configmaps&#34;, &#34;secrets&#34;]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once configured, audit logs can help you track down issues like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;{&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;kind&#34;: &#34;Event&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;apiVersion&#34;: &#34;audit.k8s.io/v1&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;level&#34;: &#34;RequestResponse&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;auditID&#34;: &#34;4d2c8b7a-f3e1-4b2a-9c8d-1e3f5a7b9c2d&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;stage&#34;: &#34;ResponseComplete&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;requestURI&#34;: &#34;/api/v1/namespaces/production/pods/web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;verb&#34;: &#34;delete&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;user&#34;: {&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;username&#34;: &#34;admin@company.com&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;groups&#34;: [&#34;system:authenticated&#34;]&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;},&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;sourceIPs&#34;: [&#34;192.168.1.100&#34;],&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;userAgent&#34;: &#34;kubectl/v1.28.0&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;objectRef&#34;: {&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;resource&#34;: &#34;pods&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;namespace&#34;: &#34;production&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;name&#34;: &#34;web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;},&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;responseStatus&#34;: {&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;code&#34;: 200&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;},&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;requestReceivedTimestamp&#34;: &#34;2024-01-15T10:30:00.000Z&#34;,&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&#34;stageTimestamp&#34;: &#34;2024-01-15T10:30:00.123Z&#34;&#xA;&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once audit logging is enabled, logs will show important details such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which user made the API request&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;From which IP address&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The HTTP verb used (e.g., GET, POST, DELETE)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The resource affected (e.g., pod, deployment)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The timestamp of the action&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Whether the request succeeded&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example:&lt;/strong&gt; An audit log might show that a pod was deleted at a specific time, by a specific admin user, from a certain IP address. This level of transparency is crucial when diagnosing problems caused by accidental or unauthorized changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;8. Using Kubernetes Dashboard and Visual Tools&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While command-line tools like &lt;code&gt;kubectl&lt;/code&gt; offer powerful ways to inspect your Kubernetes cluster, visual tools simplify cluster management, especially when identifying patterns across metrics, logs, and events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 1: Kubernetes Dashboard Overview&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Kubernetes Dashboard is a web-based user interface that lets you manage cluster resources visually. It provides detailed insights into deployments, resource usage, logs, and events, making it easier to diagnose issues without needing to run multiple CLI commands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, the Dashboard is not installed in production environments due to security concerns. However, it can be manually deployed as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Deploy the Dashboard: Run the following command to apply the recommended configuration:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/kubernetes/dashboard/v2.7.0/aio/deploy/recommended.yaml&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Create a service account for access.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl create serviceaccount dashboard-admin -n kubernetes-dashboard&#xA;&#xA;kubectl create clusterrolebinding dashboard-admin --clusterrole=cluster-admin --serviceaccount=kubernetes-dashboard:dashboard-admin&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;Generate Access Token:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl create token dashboard-admin -n kubernetes-dashboard&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once deployed, the Dashboard allows you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Monitor CPU and memory usage over time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Visualize event timelines&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Explore relationships between Kubernetes resources&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Stream application logs directly in your browser&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example Use Case:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Suppose your application experiences intermittent failures. The Dashboard may show that CPU usage spikes align with these failures, and the events log shows that pods are being OOMKilled. This kind of pattern is easier to identify visually than by reading raw CLI logs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;9. Implementing Health Checks and Probes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Health checks in Kubernetes function similarly to routine medical checkups, helping to detect issues early and ensuring everything is functioning as expected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes uses &lt;em&gt;probes&lt;/em&gt; to monitor the health and availability of your application containers. These probes enable the cluster to detect issues and take automated actions, such as restarting containers or stopping traffic routing, when necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Understanding Readiness and Liveness Probes&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes provides three types of probes, each serving a specific role in maintaining container health:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Liveness Probe: Checks if the container is still running. If it fails repeatedly, Kubernetes restarts the container.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Readiness Probe: Checks if the container is ready to accept traffic. If this fails, the container is temporarily removed from the service endpoints.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Startup Probe: Provides containers with additional time to complete their startup logic before other probes begin. This is useful for applications with longer boot times.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example: Configuring All Three Probes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below is a configuration example that combines all three types of probes in a single deployment:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: apps/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: Deployment&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: web-application&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;replicas: 3&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;selector:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;matchLabels:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;app: web-application&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;template:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;labels:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;app: web-application&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;containers:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- name: web-app&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;image: my-app:v1.2.3&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ports:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- containerPort: 8080&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;# Startup probe - gives the app time to initialize&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;startupProbe:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;httpGet:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;path: /health/startup&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 8080&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;initialDelaySeconds: 10&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;periodSeconds: 5&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;timeoutSeconds: 3&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;failureThreshold: 30&amp;nbsp; # 30 * 5 = 150 seconds to start&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;successThreshold: 1&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;# Liveness probe - restarts container if unhealthy&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;livenessProbe:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;httpGet:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;path: /health/live&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 8080&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;initialDelaySeconds: 30&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;periodSeconds: 10&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;timeoutSeconds: 5&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;failureThreshold: 3&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;successThreshold: 1&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;# Readiness probe - removes from service if not ready&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;readinessProbe:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;httpGet:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;path: /health/ready&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 8080&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;initialDelaySeconds: 5&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;periodSeconds: 5&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;timeoutSeconds: 3&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;failureThreshold: 3&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;successThreshold: 1&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resources:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;requests:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: &#34;256Mi&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: &#34;250m&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;limits:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: &#34;512Mi&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: &#34;500m&#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How These Probes Work Together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Startup Probe: This is checked first. It runs every 5 seconds, allowing up to 150 seconds for the application to complete startup tasks such as initializing databases or loading configurations. During this time, other probes are paused.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Liveness Probe: Once the startup probe succeeds, the liveness probe takes over. It ensures the container remains healthy. If the check fails three times in a row, Kubernetes automatically restarts the container.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Readiness Probe: This ensures the container is prepared to handle incoming traffic. If the check fails (e.g., due to a temporary database outage), Kubernetes temporarily removes the pod from the load balancer without restarting it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;10. Advanced Debugging Techniques&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While standard Kubernetes debugging methods handle many day-to-day issues, there are times when more advanced techniques are needed, especially for diagnosing complex performance bottlenecks, unexpected &lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/what-is-application-performance-monitoring/&#34;&gt;application behavior&lt;/a&gt;, or deep network-level problems that basic tools can’t resolve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 1: Using Ephemeral Containers for Live Debugging&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ephemeral containers are a powerful way to troubleshoot live applications without restarting pods or altering their state. They allow you to temporarily inject a debugging container into a running pod, ideal for production debugging where uptime is critical.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, to initiate a basic debugging container within a live pod:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl debug -it --image=busybox --target=&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To include specific debugging tools (like bash, curl, dig), use an image like Ubuntu:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl debug database-pod -it --image=ubuntu --target=postgres -- bash&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Practical Example: Network Issue Investigation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine your web application is facing intermittent connectivity issues. You can attach a debugging container with networking tools like &lt;code&gt;netshoot&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl debug web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz -it --image=nicolaka/netshoot --target=web-app&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Inside the debugging container, we can now check network connectivity:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;ping database-service&#xA;&#xA;nslookup database-service&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Inside the debugging container, you can perform several diagnostics:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check service connectivity&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;ping database-service&#xA;&#xA;nslookup database-service&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test open ports&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;telnet database-service 5432&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspect networking interfaces&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;ip addr show&#xA;&#xA;ss -tuln&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Validate DNS resolution&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;dig database-service.default.svc.cluster.local&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitor network traffic&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;tcpdump -i any port 5432&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspect running processes&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;ps aux&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And examine the file system:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;ls -la /app/&#xA;&#xA;cat /app/config.yaml&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This kind of live environment debugging allows for pinpointing issues that might only occur under real production conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 2: Leveraging &lt;code&gt;kubectl debug&lt;/code&gt; for Broader Scenarios&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The kubectl debug command also supports more advanced operations beyond ephemeral containers:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a full debug copy of a pod&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl debug web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz --copy-to=web-app-debug --image=ubuntu --set-image=web-app=ubuntu -- sleep 1d&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also create a new pod with the same configuration but a different image:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl exec -it web-app-debug -- bash&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debug at the node level&lt;/strong&gt;: You can launch a privileged pod on a node to investigate node-level issues:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl debug node/worker-node-1 -it --image=ubuntu&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Inside the privileged container, you can access the host’s filesystem and services:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;chroot /host bash&#xA;&#xA;systemctl status kubelet&#xA;&#xA;journalctl -u kubelet -f&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add profiling containers for performance analysis&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;If you’re looking into CPU profiling or memory leaks, a container with Go or another profiling tool can help:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl debug web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz -it --image=golang:1.21 --target=web-app&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why These Techniques Matter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Advanced debugging isn’t just about having extra commands; it’s about having flexibility to access low-level details without affecting production workloads. With ephemeral containers, node-level access, and full pod duplication, you can troubleshoot virtually any problem live and in context, minimizing guesswork and downtime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Effectively troubleshooting Kubernetes relies on knowing when and how to apply the right debugging approach. Tools like &lt;code&gt;kubectl&lt;/code&gt;, events, and audit logs are crucial for day-to-day debugging. However, combining these with a dedicated &lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/kubernetes-observability/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes observability&lt;/a&gt; platform can enhance visibility, &lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/how-to-reduce-mttr/&#34;&gt;reduce MTTR&lt;/a&gt; (mean time to resolution), and ensure smoother operations across your Kubernetes environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我们系列的第1部分中，我们探索了必不可少的Kubernetes故障排除技术，以帮助DevOps工程师有效地诊断和解决常见集群和应用程序问题。但是，Kubernetes环境很复杂，而且总是有更多的东西可以发现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本第2部分中，我们将更深入地研究其他故障排除策略，涵盖高级技术和现实情况，这些方案可以节省您的时间并防止停机时间。无论您是处理持续的POD故障，网络问题还是集群错误的配置，这些技巧都将使您能够充满信心地应对Kubernetes挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; persistentvolumeclaim（PVC）待处理&lt;/em&gt;状态是Kubernetes中常见的存储问题，可防止应用程序访问持久数据。这通常是由错误配置的存储类，缺少的卷提供者或集群中可用的存储不足引起的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤1：检查PV和PVC状态&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先列出所有命名空间中的所有持久卷（PVS）和持久卷声明（PVC）。此命令概述了其状态，访问模式，容量以及它们是否被绑定：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取PV，pvc-all-namespaces &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤2：故障排除安装问题&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要进一步调查卡在&lt;em&gt;待处理状态中的未结合的PVC，请使用以下命令：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述pvc &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;检查输出底部的&lt;strong&gt;事件&lt;/strong&gt;部分。它通常会揭示根本原因，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;无匹配&lt;code&gt; persistentvolume &lt;/code&gt;可用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;存储类不匹配&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;容量不足&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;缺少配置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-teading”&gt;步骤3：验证存储类&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不正确或不存在的存储类是常见的罪魁祸首。列出所有可用的存储类：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取storageclass &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，描述一个特定的，以检查诸如供应者和参数之类的详细信息：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述storageclass &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确保您的PVC引用有效，正确配置的存储类。如果指定的供应商不存在或拼写错误，则该卷将无法提供。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤4：常见错误和解决方案&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设您已经定义了一个PVC，该PVC引用了一个名为&lt;code&gt; fast-SSD &lt;/code&gt;的存储类，但无法提供。运行：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述pvc my-data-pvc &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可能会SEe错误：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt;警告provisioningfailed 3m &#xA;&#xA;Storageclass.storage.k8s.io“ fast-ssd”找不到&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，列出所有可用存储类以确认：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取storageclass &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果&lt;code&gt; fast-ssd &lt;/code&gt;缺少，但是&lt;code&gt; gp2 &lt;/code&gt;或&lt;code&gt;标准&lt;/code&gt;存在，请更新您的PVC以使用有效的类。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt; 7。使用事件和审核日志：深度系统分析&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes提供了两种强大的调试工具：事件和审核日志。这些可以帮助您跟踪发生的事情，发生的事情以及为什么为您提供用于根本原因分析的系统活动的时间表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-teading”&gt;步骤1：了解Kubernetes事件&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubernetes中的事件记录了集群中发生的事情。您可以列出所有命名空间中的事件，然后按其创建时间对其进行排序，以查看底部的最新活动。这有助于将问题与最近的系统行为相关联。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;以更全面地了解Kubernetes如何处理节点和群集的日志，请查看我们的完整指南&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://middleware.io/blog/blog/kubernetes-logging/&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查看所有事件按时间排序：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取事件 -  all-namespaces &#xA;-sort-by =&#39;。metadata.creationtimestamp&#39;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要过滤特定时间后发生的事件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取事件 &#xA;-field-selector =&#39;LastTimestamp&gt; 2023-10-01T10：00：00Z&#39;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仅查看警告类型事件（通常表明潜在问题）：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您还可以使用&lt;code&gt; -watch &lt;/code&gt; flag实时监视事件。当您积极故障排除并想立即观察部署或修改资源后发生的事情时，这将很有帮助：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取事件-Watch &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您正在调查特定的POD，部署或服务，则可以过滤事件以专注于该对象。例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取事件-Field-selector &lt;a href =“ http://involvedobject.name/”&gt; comenedobject.name &lt;/a&gt; = my-pod = my-pod &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您要处理未安排的豆荚，则可以过滤事件，其原因是“失败的scheduling”。这将说明为什么Kubernetes无法将POD放在节点上，例如由于资源或亲和力冲突不足而引起的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤2：使用审核日志进行深入故障排除&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;事件有助于您了解正在发生的事情，但审核日志让您看到&lt;strong&gt;谁在安全调查或跟踪管理行动时在API级别上做了什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认情况下未启用审核日志。要启用它们，您必须配置审核策略。这是示例审核策略配置，可捕获核心资源（例如POD，服务，部署等）的详细日志：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：audit.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;善：政策&#xA;&#xA;规则：&#xA;&#xA; - 级别：requestResponse&#xA;&#xA;  资源：&#xA;&#xA;  - 团体： ””&#xA;&#xA;    资源：[“ PODS”，“服务”]&#xA;&#xA;   - 组：“应用程序”&#xA;&#xA;    资源：[“部署”，“ replicaset”]&#xA;&#xA; - 级别：请求&#xA;&#xA;  资源：&#xA;&#xA;  - 团体： ””&#xA;&#xA;    资源：[“ configmaps”，“ secrets”] &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦配置，审核日志就可以帮助您跟踪以下问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; {&#xA;&#xA;  “ ank”：“ event”，&#xA;&#xA;  “ apiversion”：“ audit.k8s.io/v1”，&#xA;&#xA;  “等级”：“ requestResponse”，&#xA;&#xA;  “ AUDITID”：“ 4D2C8B7A-F3E1-4B2A-9C8D-1E3F5A7B9C2D”，&#xA;&#xA;  “阶段”：“回应完整”，&#xA;&#xA;  “ requesturi”：“/api/v1/namespaces/production/pods/web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz”，&#xA;&#xA;  “动词”：“删除”，&#xA;&#xA;  “用户”：{&#xA;&#xA;    “用户名”：“ admin@company.com”，&#xA;&#xA;    “组”：[“系统：身份验证”]&#xA;&#xA;  }，，&#xA;&#xA;  “ sourceips”：[“ 192.168.1.100”]，&#xA;&#xA;  “ useragent”：“ kubectl/v1.28.0”，&#xA;&#xA;  “ ObjectRef”：{&#xA;&#xA;    “资源”：“ pods”，&#xA;&#xA;    “名称空间”：“生产”，&#xA;&#xA;    “名称”：“ Web-App-7D4B8C9F-XYZ”&#xA;&#xA;  }，，&#xA;&#xA;  “ ResponseStatus”：{&#xA;&#xA;    “代码”：200&#xA;&#xA;  }，，&#xA;&#xA;  “ requestReceivedTimestamp”：“ 2024-01-15T10：30：00.000Z”，&#xA;&#xA;  “ Stagetimestamp”：“ 2024-01-15T10：30：00.123Z”&#xA;&#xA;} &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;启用了审核记录后，日志将显示重要的详细信息，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;哪个用户提出API请求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;从哪个IP地址&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用的HTTP动词（例如，获取，发布，删除）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;受影响的资源（例如，POD，部署）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;动作的时间戳&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;请求是否成功&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;示例：&lt;/strong&gt;审核日志可能表明，特定的管理员用户从特定的IP地址在特定时间删除了POD。当诊断出由意外或未经授权的变化引起的问题时，这种透明度至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 8。使用kubernetes仪表板和视觉工具&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然命令行工具（例如&lt;code&gt; kubectl &lt;/code&gt;）提供了检查kubernetes群集的强大方法，但视觉工具简化了群集管理，特别是在识别跨指标，日志和事件的模式时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;步骤1：kubernetes仪表板概述&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubernetes仪表板是基于Web的用户界面，可让您视觉管理集群资源。它为部署，资源使用情况，日志和事件提供了详细的见解，使诊断问题更容易，而无需运行多个CLI命令。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认情况下，由于安全问题，仪表板未安装在生产环境中。但是，可以手动部署如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。部署仪表板：运行以下命令以应用建议的配置：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl apply -f https：//raw.githubusercercontent.com/kubernetes/dashboard/dashboard/v2.7.0/aio/aio/deploy/deploy/recommend.yaml &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 2。为访问创建服务帐户。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;kubectl创建clusterrolebinding仪表板-admin -clusterrole = cluster-admin -serviceaccount = kubernetes-dashboard：dashboard-admin &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 3。 &lt;strong&gt;生成访问令牌：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl创建令牌仪表板 -  admin -n kubernetes-dashboard &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;部署后，仪表板允许您：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;随着时间的推移，监视CPU和内存使用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可视化事件时间表&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;探索Kubernetes资源之间的关系&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;流应用程序直接在您的浏览器中登录&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;示例用例：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设您的应用程序经历间歇性失败。仪表板可能表明CPU用法与这些故障相一致，事件日志显示Pods正在被填充。这种模式比阅读原始CLI日志更容易在视觉上识别。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 9。实施健康检查和探针&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubernetes中的健康检查与常规医疗检查相似，有助于尽早检测问题并确保一切正常运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes使用&lt;em&gt;探针&lt;/em&gt;来监视应用程序容器的健康和可用性。这些探针使集群能够检测问题并采取自动操作，例如重新启动容器或停止流量路由。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;了解准备和livesens探针&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes提供了三种类型的探针，每种探针在维持容器健康方面起着特定的作用：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; LIVISE探测：检查容器是否仍在运行。如果反复失败，kubernetes会重新启动容器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;准备就绪探测：检查容器是否准备好接受流量。如果失败了，则将容器暂时从服务中删除端点。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;启动探针：为容器提供额外的时间来完成其他探针开始之前完成其启动逻辑。这对于启动时间较长的应用很有用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;示例：配置所有三个探针&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下面是一个配置示例，将所有三种类型的探针组合在单个部署中：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：apps/v1&#xA;&#xA;类型：部署&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：Web应用程序&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  复制品：3&#xA;&#xA;  选择器：&#xA;&#xA;    MatchLabels：&#xA;&#xA;      应用：Web应用程序&#xA;&#xA;  模板：&#xA;&#xA;    元数据：&#xA;&#xA;      标签：&#xA;&#xA;        应用：Web应用程序&#xA;&#xA;    规格：&#xA;&#xA;      容器：&#xA;&#xA;       - 名称：Web-App&#xA;&#xA;        图像：my-app：v1.2.3&#xA;&#xA;        端口：&#xA;&#xA;         - 集装箱：8080&#xA;&#xA;        ＃启动探测器 - 给应用程序有时间初始化&#xA;&#xA;        startupprobe：&#xA;&#xA;          httpget：&#xA;&#xA;            路径： /健康 /启动&#xA;&#xA;            端口：8080&#xA;&#xA;          InitiaDelayseconds：10&#xA;&#xA;          时期：5&#xA;&#xA;          超时路要数：3&#xA;&#xA;          FailureThreshold：30＃30 * 5 = 150秒开始&#xA;&#xA;          SuccessThreshold：1&#xA;&#xA;        ＃LIVISE探测 - 如果不健康，重新启动容器&#xA;&#xA;        LIVENICE PROPBE：&#xA;&#xA;          httpget：&#xA;&#xA;            路径： /Health /Live&#xA;&#xA;            端口：8080&#xA;&#xA;          InitiaDelayseconds：30&#xA;&#xA;          周期：10&#xA;&#xA;          超时路要数：5&#xA;&#xA;          失败：3&#xA;&#xA;          SuccessThreshold：1&#xA;&#xA;        ＃准备探测器 - 如果没有准备就绪，将从服务中删除&#xA;&#xA;        REACHINCESPROBE：&#xA;&#xA;和NBSP;         httpget：&#xA;&#xA;            路径： /健康 /准备就绪&#xA;&#xA;            端口：8080&#xA;&#xA;          InitiaDelayseconds：5&#xA;&#xA;          时期：5&#xA;&#xA;          超时路要数：3&#xA;&#xA;          失败：3&#xA;&#xA;          SuccessThreshold：1&#xA;&#xA;        资源：&#xA;&#xA;          请求：&#xA;&#xA;            内存：“ 256mi”&#xA;&#xA;            CPU：“ 250m”&#xA;&#xA;          限制：&#xA;&#xA;            内存：“ 512mi”&#xA;&#xA;            CPU：“ 500m” &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;这些探针如何一起工作&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;启动探针：首先检查。它每5秒运行一次，最多可让应用程序完成启动任务，例如初始化数据库或加载配置。在此期间，其他探针被暂停。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; LIVISE探测器：一旦启动探测成功，Livices探测就会接管。它确保容器保持健康。如果支票连续三次失败，则Kubernetes会自动重新启动容器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;准备就绪探测：这确保容器准备处理传入的流量。如果支票失败（例如，由于临时数据库中断），Kubernetes会暂时从负载平衡器中删除POD而不重新启动。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 10。高级调试技术&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然标准的Kubernetes调试方法处理了许多日常问题，但有时需要更多的高级技术，尤其是用于诊断复杂的性能瓶颈，而出乎意料的&lt;a href =” https://middleware.io/blog/blog/what-s-performation-performation-performance-performance-monoritoring/ bactor note note note note note nockity bach opplance &lt;/copplation-peclove &lt;/quest &lt;/&gt; covery &lt;/&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤1：使用短暂的容器进行实时调试&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;短暂的容器是无需重新启动豆荚或更改其状态的实时应用程序的有力方法。它们允许您暂时将调试容器注入运行的吊舱中，非常适合运行时间的生产调试。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，在实时POD中启动基本调试容器：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl debug -it-image = busybox -targET = &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;包括特定的调试工具（例如bash，curl，dig），使用ubuntu之类的图像：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl debug debug数据库pod -it -image = ubuntu -target = postgres-bash &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想象您的Web应用程序正面临间歇性连接问题。您可以使用&lt;code&gt; NetShoot &lt;/code&gt;的网络工具附加调试容器：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl debug web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz -it  -  image = nicolaka/netshoot-target-target = web-app &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在调试容器中，我们现在可以检查网络连接：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ping database-service&#xA;&#xA;NSlookup数据库服务&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在调试容器中，您可以执行多个诊断：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;检查服务连接&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ping database-service&#xA;&#xA;NSlookup数据库服务&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;测试打开端口&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; telnet数据库服务5432 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;检查网络接口&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ip addr show&#xA;&#xA;SS -Tuln &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;验证DNS分辨率&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; dig database-service.default.svc.cluster.local.local &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;监视网络流量&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; tcpdump -i任何端口5432 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;检查运行过程&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ps aux &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;并检查文件系统：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; ls -la /app /&#xA;&#xA;cat/app/config.yaml&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种实时环境调试允许查明仅在实际生产条件下发生的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;步骤2：利用&lt;code&gt; kubectl debug &lt;/code&gt;更广泛的方案&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubectl调试命令还支持超过短暂容器以外的更高级操作：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;创建POD &lt;/strong&gt;的完整调试副本：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl debug web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz --copy-to=web-app-debug --image=ubuntu --set-image=web-app=ubuntu -- sleep 1d&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您还可以创建一个具有相同配置的新吊舱，但图像不同：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl exec -it web-app-debug-bash &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在节点级别进行调试&lt;/strong&gt;：您可以在节点上启动特权POD来调查节点级问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl debug node/worker-node-1 -it-image = ubuntu &lt;/code &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在特权容器中，您可以访问主机的文件系统和服务：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; chroot /host bash&#xA;&#xA;SystemCTL状态库布尔特&#xA;&#xA;journalctl -u kubelet -f &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;添加分析容器以进行性能分析&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;br&gt;如果您正在研究CPU分析或内存泄漏，带有GO或其他分析工具的容器可以帮助：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl debug web-app-7d4b8c9f-xyz -it  -  image = golang = golang：1.21 -target = web-app &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么这些技术重要&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;高级调试不仅仅是要有额外的命令；这是关于灵活访问低级细节而不会影响生产工作量的灵活性。使用短暂的容器，节点级访问和完整的POD重复，您可以实时解决任何问题，并在上​​下文中最小化猜测和停机时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ wp-block-neading”&gt;结论&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有效地故障排除Kubernetes依赖于知道何时以及如何应用正确的调试方法。 &lt;Code&gt; Kubectl &lt;/code&gt;，事件和审核日志等工具对于日常调试至关重要。但是，将它们与专用的&lt;a href =“ https://middleware.io/blog/kubernetes-observability/”&gt; kubernetes可观察性&lt;/a&gt;平台可以提高可见度，&lt;a href =“分辨率），并确保在您的Kubernetes环境中进行更光滑的操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2025 Co-Located Event Deep Dive: KyvernoCon】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon北美2025年共同介绍的活动深度潜水：kyvernocon</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/15/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2025-co-located-event-deep-dive-kyvernocon/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1746&#34; height=&#34;294&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-06-at-1.37.18-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;KyvernoCon North American 2025&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-146176&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-06-at-1.37.18-PM.jpg 1746w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-06-at-1.37.18-PM-300x51.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-06-at-1.37.18-PM-1024x172.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-06-at-1.37.18-PM-768x129.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-06-at-1.37.18-PM-900x152.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-06-at-1.37.18-PM-600x101.jpg 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-06-at-1.37.18-PM-1200x202.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1746px) 100vw, 1746px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the very first &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/kyvernocon/?ajs_aid=b4cbcea8-db3a-48a5-b9ca-81b8469a1e6a&#34;&gt;KyvernoCon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;! While Kyverno has been part of the CNCF since November 2020, and has had a strong presence at past KubeCon events through policy as code focused talks, maintainer sessions, and community meetups, this is the first time our community is gathering under one roof for a dedicated event.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes has become the standard for cloud native and AI/ML workloads, and large organizations need to automate security and compliance. Hence, there is a critical need and growing awareness for policy as code. Over the past few years, Kyverno has matured significantly, becoming the most widely adopted CNCF policy engine. As we work towards becoming a graduated project and are continuing to incorporate new capabilities like CEL-based policies and a growing set of integrations across the ecosystem, the timing felt right to create a space where users, contributors, and platform teams can learn, share, and shape the future of policy as code together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who will get the most out of attending this event?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KyvernoCon is designed for anyone building or running Kubernetes platforms, but especially valuable for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Organizations running Kubernetes at scale and for mission critical software, who are looking for unified governance across clusters, pipelines, and cloud.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Platform engineers and SREs who want to leverage policy as code into day-to-day workflows for automated and secure delivery practices, cost savings, and a better overall developer experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Security and compliance teams looking for practical ways to enforce standards and reduce risk.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developers and operators who want to understand how policy can improve reliability and speed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Adopters, contributors, and open-source enthusiasts eager to collaborate and shape Kyverno’s next chapter.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Leaders and decision-makers curious about why policy as code has become a must-have in modern platform engineering and software delivery.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you touch Kubernetes in any way and care about doing it securely, sustainably, and at scale, you’ll get value out of spending the day with us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is new with Kyverno this year?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This inaugural edition is especially exciting because of the timing: Kyverno was born and raised in Kubernetes, but has now expanded beyond Kubernetes into a unified policy engine that can be used at any layer of the stack, inside and outside of clusters. Other solutions that attempted to do the same, have failed or stagnated because of high complexity and lack of scalability.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyerno 1.15 just unified policy types like &lt;strong&gt;ValidatingPolicy&lt;/strong&gt; with expanded CEL support, and added powerful CLI and shift-left features. This is a game changer, as now Kubernetes style policies can be used universally!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KyvernoCon attendees will be among the first to see how these new capabilities are shaping real-world platform engineering practices. The event will also showcase community case studies, highlighting how organizations across industries are solving compliance, supply chain security, and reliability challenges at scale with Kyverno.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, KyvernoCon 2025 is the community’s first chance to come together, share lessons, and chart the future of policy as code in the CNCF ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will the day look like?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KyvernoCon is a halfday, community-driven event. The morning will be filled with deep-dive talks, demos, and case studies highlighting how policies are transforming software delivery at scale. The initial response to our CFP was excellent and we’re grateful to our program committee for reviewing so many talks in detail helping us create a diverse track offering something for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sessions will feature practical case studies and stories from end users and other ecosystem partners, interactive discussions that connect Kyverno to the wider CNCF landscape, and forward-looking conversations about where policy as code is headed, ensuring attendees leave with both immediate takeaways and a vision of what’s possible next.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, our team will be on-hand during the event and throughout KubeCon as we deliver additional technical sessions, project updates, and contributor insights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should I do any homework first?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No heavy preparation is required to feel at home at KyvernoCon. To ensure you get the most out of the experience we encourage folks to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Explore the agenda. We have talks for all levels so be sure to add them to your Shed schedule and calendar.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Consider learning about the Kyverno basics – review the documentation or try out a simple policy for context.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Think about your own challenges – bring questions about compliance, developer experience, or supply chain security and be ready to raise your hand to ask questions during Q&amp;amp;A.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Engage with our team on Slack or GitHub – say hello to the community ahead of time; it makes in-person conversations even better!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Above all, come ready to connect, share, and learn. KyvernoCon is built around collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Find your community!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KyvernoCon is more than just a conference — it’s a milestone for our community! For the first time, contributors, adopters, and curious newcomers will have a dedicated space to meet, exchange ideas, and influence the future of policy as code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re looking for practical takeaways, inspiration from peers, or ways to get more involved in open source, KyvernoCon is the best place to start. We’re excited to see the community come together and can’t wait for the conversations, connections, and collaborations that will spark here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A special note from the chairs&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re looking forward to &lt;strong&gt;seeing the policy as code conversation elevated across KubeCon&lt;/strong&gt;. Our team will be at the Kyverno booth in the Project Pavillion to discuss your use cases in depth. As the creators of Kyverno, we will also be present at the Nirmata booth (1430??) for discussions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Policy as Code has become essential for platform engineering success, and it’s exciting to see it recognized alongside other core CNCF technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re also eager to connect with the broader community in Atlanta, learn from other projects, and explore how Kyverno can continue to integrate across the ecosystem—from GitOps and supply chain security to observability and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We hope to &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/kyvernocon/?ajs_aid=b4cbcea8-db3a-48a5-b9ca-81b8469a1e6a&#34;&gt;see you there&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dexoding =“ async” width =“ 1746” height =“ 294” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-06-AT-1.37.18-pm.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-06-AT-1.37.18.18-pm.jpg 1746w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-06-AT-1.37.18-pm-300x51.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-06-AT-1.37.18-PM-1024X172.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-06-AT-1.37.18-PM-768X1299.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-06-AT-1.37.18-PM-900X152.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-06-AT-1.37.18-pm-600x101.jpg 600w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-06-AT-1.37.18-PM-1200X202.JPG 1200W 1200W 1200W“ sizes =” size =“ auto referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是第一个&lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/kyvernocon/?ajs_aid = b4cbcea8 = b4cbcea8-db3a-48a5-b9ca-b9ca-81b81b81b81b84469a1e1e1e1e1everl虽然Kyverno自2020年11月以来一直是CNCF的一部分，并且在过去的库贝康（Kubecon）事件中，作为集中的谈判，维护者会议和社区聚会，在过去的库贝康活动中有很强的影响力，但这是我们的社区第一次在一个屋顶下聚集在一个专门的活动下。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes已成为云本地和AI/ML工作负载的标准，大型组织需要自动化安全性和合规性。因此，对政策作为代码的迫切需求和越来越多的意识。在过去的几年中，Kyverno已经大量成熟，成为最广泛采用的CNCF政策引擎。随着我们努力成为一个毕业的项目，并继续纳入整个生态系统中基于CEL的政策和越来越多的集成的新功能，因此时机感觉到创建一个空间的正时，用户，贡献者和平台团队可以一起学习，共享并将其作为代码的未来塑造为代码。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;谁会最大程度地参加此活动？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyvernocon专为建造或运行Kubernetes平台的任何人而设计，但对于：&lt;/p&gt;特别有价值：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;组织规模运行Kubernetes和Mission Critister Software，他们正在跨簇，管道和云的统一治理。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;想要将政策作为代码的平台工程师和SRES纳入日常工作流程，以进行自动和安全的交付实践，节省成本以及更好的整体开发人员体验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;安全和合规团队正在寻找实用方法来执行标准并降低风险。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;开发人员和经营者nt了解政策如何提高可靠性和速度。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;采用者，贡献者和开源爱好者渴望合作并塑造Kyverno的下一章。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;领导者和决策者对为什么作为代码成为现代平台工程和软件交付的必备政策感到好奇。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您以任何方式触摸kubernetes，并且要安全地，可持续和大规模地进行操作，那么您将从与我们度过的一天中获得价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;今年的kyverno是什么？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于时间安排，这个就职版尤其令人兴奋：Kyverno在Kubernetes中出生和长大，但现在已经将Kubernetes超越Kubernetes扩展到统一的政策引擎中，可以在堆栈的任何一层，内部和外部使用集群。试图做同样的其他解决方案由于高复杂性和缺乏可扩展性而失败或停滞。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyerno 1.15只是统一的策略类型，例如&lt;strong&gt;验证policypolicy &lt;/strong&gt;具有扩展的CEL支持，并添加了强大的CLI和Shift-Left功能。这是一个改变游戏规则的人，因为现在可以普遍使用Kubernetes风格政策！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyvernocon的与会者将成为第一个看到这些新功能如何塑造现实世界平台工程实践的人之一。该活动还将展示社区案例研究，强调各行业的组织如何解决合规性，供应链安全和可靠性挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;简而言之，Kyvernocon 2025是社区中的第一个机会，分享课程并将政策的未来描绘为CNCF生态系统中的代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;一天会是什么样？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyvernocon是一个半天，社区驱动的活动。早晨将充满深度潜水，演示和案例研究，这些案例研究强调了政策如何大规模转换软件的交付。对我们CFP的最初回应非常出色，我们感谢计划委员会详细审查这么多演讲，以帮助我们创建一段多样的曲目，为每个人提供一些东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;会议将以最终用户和其他生态系统合作伙伴的实践案例研究和故事为特色，这些讨论将kyverno连接到更广阔的CNCF景观，以及有关政策作为代码的前进位置的前瞻性对话，以确保与会者立即离开，以及下一步可能的愿景。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，我们的团队将在活动期间和整个Kubecon在整个过程中进行。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我应该先做任何家庭作业吗？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Kyvernocon不需要大量准备工作。为了确保您充分利用我们鼓励的经验人们到：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;探索议程。我们对各个级别进行了谈判，因此请务必将它们添加到您的棚时间表和日历中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;考虑学习kyverno基础知识 - 查看文档或尝试以下情况的简单政策。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;考虑一下您自己的挑战 - 提出有关合规性，开发人员经验或供应链安全的问题，并准备举手在问答期间提出问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在Slack或Github上与我们的团队互动 - 提前向社区打招呼；它使面对面的对话变得更好！&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最重要的是，准备连接，共享和学习。 kyvernocon建立在协作中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;找到您的社区！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kyvernocon不仅仅是一次会议，这是我们社区的里程碑！首次，贡献者，采用者和好奇的新移民将有一个专门的空间来满足，交换思想和影响政策的未来，作为代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是在寻找实用的外卖，同行的灵感还是让更多参与开源的方法，Kyvernocon都是最好的起点。我们很高兴看到社区聚在一起，迫不及待地想在这里引发的对话，联系和合作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们期待&lt;strong&gt;看到该政策随着Kubecon的代码对话而提高&lt;/strong&gt;。我们的团队将在Pavillion项目的Kyverno展位上进行深入讨论您的用例。作为Kyverno的创建者，我们还将在Nirmata Booth（1430 ??）出席讨论。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;策略作为代码对平台工程的成功至关重要，令人兴奋地看到它与其他核心CNCF技术一起认可。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还渴望与亚特兰大的更广泛的社区联系，从其他项目中学习，并探索如何从gitops和供应链安全到可观察性及以后的生态系统中继续整合kyverno。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们希望&lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-north-merica/co-located-events/kyvernocon/kyvernocon/?ajs_aid=b4cbcbcea8-db3a-48a-48a5b9a-48a5-b9ca-81b81b81b81b81b8166aa &lt;/e &lt;/e &lt;/e &lt;/e &lt;/e &lt;/&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2025 Co-Located Event Deep Dive: OpenTofu Day】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon北美2025年共同介绍的活动深度潜水：Opentofu Day</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/12/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2025-co-located-event-deep-dive-opentofu-day/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1746&#34; height=&#34;322&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-05-at-4.46.42-PM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;OpenTofu Day North America&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-146086&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-05-at-4.46.42-PM.jpg 1746w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-05-at-4.46.42-PM-300x55.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-05-at-4.46.42-PM-1024x189.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-05-at-4.46.42-PM-768x142.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-05-at-4.46.42-PM-900x166.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-05-at-4.46.42-PM-600x111.jpg 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-05-at-4.46.42-PM-1200x221.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1746px) 100vw, 1746px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/opentofu-day/?ajs_aid=b4cbcea8-db3a-48a5-b9ca-81b8469a1e6a&#34;&gt;OpenTofu Day&lt;/a&gt; is the best place to connect with the OpenTofu community. It’s a fantastic place to talk shop with other infrastructure or platform engineers, trade stories, discuss best practices, and maybe even hire / be hired. OpenTofu is the open source continuation of Hashicorp® Terraform™. The very first of these events was in 2024 at KubeCon in Paris. It was an incredible place to start!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who will get the most out of attending this event?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OpenTofu Day schedule is built around the assumption that the audience has prior experience with OpenTofu, Terraform, or other infrastructure as code. Having this experience is not required to attend, but it will definitely help to get the most out of the event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As such, it is best for DevOps engineers, platform engineers, and infrastructure leadership, especially for those looking to migrate from Terraform in 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is new and different this year?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year we focus less on what it took to get the project off the ground, and more on what is in store for the community, and sharing community experiences with the project in production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will the day look like?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The event kicks off with a summary of the progress of the project, new features, growth, and new additions to the core team. Then we have the devs expand on that with a live panel, followed by community members sharing their experiences and learned lessons with the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should I do any homework first?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It would be best if you have already downloaded and used OpenTofu. What’s more, if you migrated from Terraform. Second to that, it would be great if attendees started planning for a migration, and have questions related to it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thanks to the community!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A big thank you to &lt;a href=&#34;http://env0.com/&#34;&gt;Env0&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://gruntwork.io/&#34;&gt;Gruntwork&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://harness.io/&#34;&gt;Harness&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://scalr.com/&#34;&gt;Scalr&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://spacelift.io/&#34;&gt;Spacelift&lt;/a&gt;, the over 180 individuals that have committed code to the project, and the over 1,000 that have contributed ideas, votes, and comments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-09-05-AT-4.46.46.42-pm.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-09-05-AT-4.46.46.42-pm.jpg 1746w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-05-AT-4.46.42-pm-300x55.jpg 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-05-AT-4.46.42-PM-1024X189.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-05-AT-4.46.42-PM-768X142.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-05-AT-4.46.42-PM-900X166.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-05-AT-4.46.42-PM-600X111.JPG 600W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-05-AT-4.46.42-PM-1200X221.JPG 1200W 1200W 1200W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-merica/co-located-events/opentofu-day/?ajs_aid=b4cbcbcea8-cbcbcea8-db3a-48a-48a5-b9ca-81b81b81b81b8166 aa ap to op to op op与Opentofu社区建立联系。这是与其他基础设施或平台工程师，贸易故事，讨论最佳实践甚至雇用 /被雇用的绝佳场所。 Opentofu是Hashicorp®Terraform™的开源延续。这些事件中的第一个是在2024年在巴黎的库贝孔（Kubecon）。这是一个不可思议的起点！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;谁会最大程度地参加此活动？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Opentofu日计划是围绕以下假设，即观众以前具有Opentofu，Terraform或其他基础架构作为代码的经验。拥有这种经验并不需要参加，但肯定会有助于充分利用活动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，这是最适合DevOps工程师，平台工程师和基础设施的领导，特别是对于那些希望从Terraform迁移的人。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;今年有什么新鲜事物？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年，我们不再关注将项目脱离地面所需的内容，而更多地关注社区的商品，并与该项目分享生产项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;这一天会是什么样？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;活动开始了项目的进度，新功能，增长和核心团队的新成员。然后，我们将开发人员通过现场小组进行扩展，然后社区成员分享他们的经验并与该项目学习课程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我应该先做任何家庭作业吗？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您已经下载并使用了Opentofu，那将是最好的。更重要的是，如果您从Terraform迁移。其次，如果与会者开始计划移民并有与之相关的问题，那将是很棒的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;感谢社区！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;非常感谢&lt;a href =“ http://env0.com/”&gt; env0 &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ http://gruntwork.io/”&gt; gruntwork &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ href =” href =“ http://scalr.com/”&gt; scalr &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ http://spacelift.io/”&gt; spacelift &lt;/a&gt;，超过180个人已向项目承诺代码的人，以及超过1,000多个有助于想法，投票，投票，评论和评论。 &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Kubernetes (K8s) Troubleshooting Techniques – Part 1】顶级Kubernetes（K8S）故障排除技术 - 第1部分</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/12/top-kubernetes-k8s-troubleshooting-techniques-part-1/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Middleware&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;blog by &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/authors/keval/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Keval Bhogayata&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, covering the &lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/kubernetes-troubleshooting-techniques/&#34;&gt;top 10 Kubernetes Troubleshooting Techniques&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Regardless of its popularity, there can be times where even the most seasoned DevOps engineers must troubleshoot Kubernetes. While it excels at handling containerised applications at scale, it can present unique troubleshooting challenges.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll explore the top 10 Kubernetes troubleshooting techniques that every &lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/what-is-devops/&#34;&gt;DevOps&lt;/a&gt; engineer should master. These K8s troubleshooting tips come from real-world scenarios, showing how to solve common and critical Kubernetes issues quickly and reliably.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Fixing CrashLoopBackOff Errors in Pods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most common and frustrating issues in Kubernetes is when a pod repeatedly crashes during restarts; a situation known as the CrashLoopBackOff error. This occurs when a container fails to start correctly, and Kubernetes continually attempts to restart it, resulting in a loop of failures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 1: List All Pods&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first step in debugging this error is to get a high-level overview of all pods running in your namespace. You can do this with the following command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get pods&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will show the status, restart count, and age of each pod. Pods with a status that &lt;code&gt;CrashLoopBackOff&lt;/code&gt; clearly indicates an issue requiring immediate attention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 2: Describe the Affected Pod&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve identified the problematic pod, use the &lt;code&gt;describe&lt;/code&gt; command to inspect its internal details:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe pod&amp;nbsp;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This provides configuration information, recent events, and messages that might indicate the reason for the crash. Pay special attention to the &lt;strong&gt;Events&lt;/strong&gt; section, which can help pinpoint issues such as failed image pulls, missing configuration, or permission errors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 3: Review Container Logs&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logs are essential for understanding what went wrong inside a container. Use the following command to access a pod’s logs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl logs&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the pod fails before producing logs, you might find the logs are empty. In such cases, use the&lt;code&gt; --previous&lt;/code&gt; Flag to inspect the logs from the last failed container instance. This often reveals the root cause, especially if the container exited before any meaningful activity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’re trying to debug pods in real-time, don’t miss our detailed guide on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/kubectl-logs-tail/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;tailing logs with kubectl&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, which walks you through using &lt;/em&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;em&gt;-tail, -f&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and more advanced flags for live troubleshooting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example Scenario&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s walk through a practical example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.Run &lt;code&gt;kubectl get pods&lt;/code&gt; and observe the output:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get pods&#xA;&#xA;my-webapp-pod &amp;nbsp; 0/1 &amp;nbsp; CrashLoopBackOff &amp;nbsp; 5 (2m ago)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The pod &lt;code&gt;my-webapp-pod&lt;/code&gt; is crashing repeatedly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. Try describing the pod:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe pod my-webapp-pod&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If this yields no helpful insight, the issue might be within the container logs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. Check the logs of the previous instance:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl logs my-webapp-pod --previous:&#xA;&#xA;Error: DATABASE_URL environment variable is not set&#xA;&#xA;Process exiting with code 1&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The logs show that the &lt;code&gt;DATABASE_URL&lt;/code&gt; Environment variable was missing. This explains why the container failed. The application inside expected a configuration that wasn’t provided.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CrashLoopBackOff errors often result from misconfigurations such as missing environment variables, incorrect commands, or failed dependencies. By systematically inspecting pods, describing their events, and reviewing logs (including those from previous container instances), you can efficiently identify and resolve the underlying cause.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Kubernetes Troubleshooting Deployment Failures: ImagePullBackOff&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When Kubernetes cannot pull a container image due to authentication issues or an incorrect image name, it triggers an &lt;code&gt;ImagePullBackOff&lt;/code&gt; error.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 1: Identify Problematic Deployments&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Start by checking the status of your deployments:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get deployments&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This command displays all deployments and their replica counts. Pay close attention to the &lt;strong&gt;READY&lt;/strong&gt; column. For example, a “0/3” status means that none of the pods are starting successfully, suggesting an issue at the pod level rather than with the application itself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For deeper insight, run the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe deployment&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This provides detailed deployment data, including the pod template, conditions, and recent events. You may see messages like “ReplicaSet failed to create pods,” which can indicate underlying issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 2: Monitor Rollout Status and History&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To track a deployment rollout in real time:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl rollout status deployment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is useful when monitoring deployments during &lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/what-is-a-ci-cd-pipeline/&#34;&gt;CI/CD pipeline&lt;/a&gt; runs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To view the deployment history:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl rollout history deployment&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use this to identify which revision introduced the issue and compare it with previous working versions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 3: Investigate the Root Cause of ImagePullBackOff&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s list the pods and spot the error:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get pods&#xA;&#xA;my-app-7d4b8c8f-xyz &amp;nbsp; 0/1 &amp;nbsp; ImagePullBackOff &amp;nbsp; 0 &amp;nbsp; 2m&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, inspect the failing pod:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe pod my-app-7d4b8c8f-xyz&#xA;&#xA;Failed to pull image &#34;private-registry.com/my-app:v1.2.3&#34;:&#xA;&#xA;Error response from daemon: pull access denied for private-registry.com/my-app&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This indicates that Kubernetes cannot access the private container registry due to missing or invalid credentials.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 4: Fixing the ImagePullBackOff Using Secrets&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To resolve this, create a Kubernetes Secret to store your private registry credentials securely:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl create secret docker-registry my-registry-secret \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--docker-server=private-registry.com \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--docker-username=myuser \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--docker-password=mypassword \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--docker-email=my@email.com&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, patch your deployment to reference the secret:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl patch deployment my-app -p &#39;{&#34;spec&#34;:{&#34;template&#34;:{&#34;spec&#34;:{&#34;imagePullSecrets&#34;:[{&#34;name&#34;:&#34;my-registry-secret&#34;}]}}}}&#39;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once patched, Kubernetes will re-trigger the deployment using the correct credentials. You can monitor the new rollout using:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl rollout status deployment my-app&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Kubernetes Troubleshooting: Fixing NotReady Node Errors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another frequently faced error is the &lt;code&gt;NotReady&lt;/code&gt; status on a node, which blocks pod scheduling and disrupts workloads. If the kubelet on the node cannot communicate with the server or the node fails health checks, the &lt;code&gt;NotReady&lt;/code&gt; status appears, preventing pods from being scheduled, which often leads to application downtime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step1: Checking Node Status&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, check the status of all nodes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get nodes -o wide&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This command lists all cluster nodes, showing their status, container runtime, IP addresses, and OS details. The &lt;code&gt;-o wide&lt;/code&gt; flag gives additional context, helping identify node-level issues such as OS mismatches or node location patterns (e.g., subnet-specific failures).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Inspecting Node Conditions and Issues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use the following command to get a detailed view of a node’s resource capacity and health:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe node | grep -A 5 &#34;Capacity\|Allocatable&#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will show whether the node’s allocatable resources are within limits or are being over-utilized.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, let’s say you have a node showing a &lt;code&gt;NotReady&lt;/code&gt; status:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get nodesworker-node-1 &amp;nbsp; NotReady &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5d &amp;nbsp; v1.28.0&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 3: To investigate further&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe node worker-node-1&#xA;&#xA;Conditions:&#xA;&#xA;Type &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Status&amp;nbsp; LastHeartbeatTime &amp;nbsp; LastTransitionTime &amp;nbsp; Reason &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Message&#xA;&#xA;DiskPressure &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; True&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Mon, 01 Jan 2024&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Mon, 01 Jan 2024 &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &#xA;KubeletHasDiskPressure kubelet has disk pressure&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fixing Disk Pressure Issues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this case, the node is reporting disk pressure typically because the partitions or logs have consumed excessive space.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To resolve this, clear out system logs using:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;sudo journalctl --vacuum-time=3d&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will remove logs older than 3 days and free up disk space, helping the kubelet return the node to a &lt;code&gt;Ready&lt;/code&gt; state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Diagnosing Service and Networking Problems: The Pending Error&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When services or pods are stuck in a &lt;code&gt;Pending&lt;/code&gt; state, Kubernetes troubleshooting becomes essential. This often indicates a selector mismatch, networking misconfiguration, or issues with DNS resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Service connectivity problems are among the most frustrating issues in Kubernetes. Start by listing all services to verify their configuration:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get services --all-namespaces&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This command returns service types and network details, including IP addresses and ports.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 1: Verifying services&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To identify if a service lacks matching pods, use the following command to list endpoints:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get endpoints&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If an endpoint is empty, it means no pods match the service’s selector, which is commonly the root cause of connection failures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can further inspect the service configuration to verify the labels used to locate pods:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe service&amp;nbsp;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Compare the selector labels in the service with the actual labels on your pods to ensure they align.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 2: Inspecting DNS Issues In The Cluster&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If there’s a communication failure between microservices that causes the &lt;code&gt;Pending&lt;/code&gt; state, DNS resolution might be the culprit. You can run the following commands from within a pod:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;nslookup my-service&#xA;&#xA;nslookup my-service.d&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the DNS name does not resolve to an IP address, there’s likely an issue with the cluster’s DNS configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing HTTP Connectivity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To ensure that the service is responding correctly, test its endpoint with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;wget -qO- my-service:80/health&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the request fails, it could indicate a problem with the service configuration, network policies, or incorrect pod selectors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;5. Kubernetes Troubleshooting High Resource Usage: Solving OOMKilled Errors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Monitoring resources is a crucial part of Kubernetes troubleshooting, enabling the maintenance of healthy clusters and ensuring optimal application performance. When a container exceeds its allocated memory limit, Kubernetes forcefully terminates it, resulting in the infamous &lt;code&gt;OOMKilled&lt;/code&gt; error. This can cause pod evictions, application downtime, or severe performance degradation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 1: Checking Resource Usage&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To identify memory-intensive nodes and pods:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl top nodes&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This command provides real-time resource usage across nodes. If a node is using over 80% of its memory, it may be at risk of triggering OOMKilled errors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also view pod-level resource usage and sort by CPU or memory:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl top pods --all-namespaces --sort-by=cpu&#xA;&#xA;kubectl top pods --all-namespaces --sort-by=memory&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These commands help you pinpoint the most resource-hungry pods in the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Track OOMKilled and other errors in real-time with Middleware’s &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.middleware.io/agent-installation/kubernetes/kubernetes-agent&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;K8 agent&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Investigating Resource Quotas, Limits, And Autoscaling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understanding and monitoring resource limits is essential. To check quotas across all namespaces:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe quota --all-namespaces&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/memory-leaks/&#34;&gt;Memory leaks&lt;/a&gt; often appear as a gradual increase in memory usage over time. You can monitor a pod’s live memory consumption every 5 seconds using:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;watch -n 5 &#39;kubectl top pod memory-hungry-app&#39;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This helps you spot memory leaks or gradually increase memory usage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Avoid memory issues before they crash your pod. See how to detect them early via &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/kubernetes-monitoring/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3: Checking Pod Resource Requests and Limits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If pods lack memory limits, they can consume excessive resources, potentially affecting other workloads. To inspect resource requests and limits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl describe pod memory-hungry-app | grep -A 10 &#34;Requests\|Limits&#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a useful Kubernetes troubleshooting trick to identify which pods lack proper memory restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Step 4: Mitigating Resource-Related Issues&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To prevent OOMKilled errors and automatically balance resource usage, you can set up Horizontal Pod Autoscaling (HPA).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pro Tip: Use autoscaling to manage resource spikes. For example, to autoscale a deployment based on 70% CPU usage:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl autoscale deployment my-app --cpu-percent=70 --min=2 --max=10&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can verify if &lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/what-is-autoscaling/&#34;&gt;autoscaling&lt;/a&gt; is active and functioning correctly:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get hpa&#xA;&#xA;kubectl describe hpa my-app&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Proactively managing resource limits and enabling autoscaling helps prevent OOMKilled errors and ensures smoother application performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Using Monitoring and Tracing Tools&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While built-in tools like &lt;code&gt;kubectl &lt;/code&gt;are essential for initial debugging, they can fall short when dealing with complex, distributed systems. This is where third-party observability platforms come into play. Middleware, for instance, offers a comprehensive observability solution that provides deeper visibility into your Kubernetes clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初发表在&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://middleware.io/”&gt; href =“ https://middleware.io/blog/authors/keval/”&gt; &lt;em&gt; keval bhogayata &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，涵盖&lt;a a href =“ https:///middleware.io oio of技术&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论其受欢迎程度如何，甚至可能是经验丰富的DevOps工程师也必须对Kubernetes进行故障排除。尽管它可以大规模处理容器化应用程序，但它可以提出独特的故障排除挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将探索每个&lt;a href =“ https://middleware.io/blog/what what what-is-is-devops/”&gt; devops &lt;/a&gt;工程师都应该掌握的十大kubernetes故障排除技术。这些K8的故障排除技巧来自现实世界中的情况，显示了如何快速，可靠地解决常见和关键的Kubernetes问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。修复Pods中的CrashloopBackoff错误&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubernetes中最常见和最令人沮丧的问题之一是，当豆荚重新启动过程中反复撞车时；一种称为crashloopbackoff错误的情况。当容器无法正确启动时，就会发生这种情况，而Kubernetes不断尝试重新启动它，从而导致故障循环。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;步骤1：列出所有POD &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;调试此错误的第一步是获得在您的名称空间中运行的所有POD的高级概述。您可以使用以下命令来执行此操作：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl get pods &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这将显示每个POD的状态，重新启动计数和年龄。具有&lt;code&gt; crashloopbackoff &lt;/code&gt;状态的POD清楚地表明了需要立即注意的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-teading”&gt;步骤2：描述受影响的POD &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确定了有问题的POD后，请使用&lt;code&gt; Dricesd &lt;/code&gt;命令检查其内部详细信息：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述pod &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这提供了配置信息，最新事件和消息，这些信息可能表明崩溃的原因。请特别注意&lt;strong&gt;事件&lt;/strong&gt;部分，这可以帮助查明问题，例如失败图像拉力，缺失配置或许可错误。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-teading”&gt;步骤3：查看容器日志&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;日志对于了解容器内出了什么问题至关重要。使用以下命令访问POD的日志：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl logs &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果POD在生成日志之前失败，则可能会发现日志是空的。在这种情况下，请使用&lt;code&gt;  - 预览&lt;/code&gt;标志来检查最后一个失败的容器实例的日志。这通常揭示了根本原因，尤其是在容器E时在任何有意义的活动之前进行X。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;如果您想实时调试豆荚，请不要错过有关&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://middleware.io/blog/blog/kubectl-logs-tail/”&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;用kubectl &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; -f &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;em&gt;，以及实时故障排除的更多高级标志。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;示例方案&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们浏览一个实践示例：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 1. run &lt;code&gt; kubectl获取豆荚&lt;/code&gt;并观察输出：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取豆荚&#xA;&#xA;my-webapp-pod 0/1 crashloopbackoff 5（2m前）&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; pod &lt;code&gt; my-webapp-pod &lt;/code&gt;正在反复崩溃。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2。尝试描述豆荚：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述pod my-webapp-pod &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果这不会产生有用的见解，则问题可能在容器日志中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 3。检查上一个实例的日志：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;&#xA;&#xA;错误：database_url环境变量未设置&#xA;&#xA;使用代码1 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;退出过程&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;日志显示&lt;code&gt; database_url &lt;/code&gt;不含环境变量。这解释了为什么容器失败。内部的应用程序预期未提供的配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; crashloopbackoff错误通常是由于缺失的环境变量，错误命令或失败依赖关系而引起的。通过系统地检查POD，描述其事件并审查日志（包括以前的容器实例的日志），您可以有效地识别和解决根本原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 2。 Kubernetes故障排除部署故障：ImagePullBackoff &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当Kubernetes由于身份验证问题或不正确的图像名称而无法拉出容器映像时，它会触发&lt;code&gt; imagepullbackoff &lt;/code&gt;错误。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤1：识别有问题的部署&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先检查部署的状态：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取部署&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此命令显示所有部署及其副本计数。密切注意&lt;strong&gt; Ready &lt;/strong&gt;列。例如，“ 0/3”状态意味着没有一个POD成功启动，暗示了POD级别的问题，而不是使用应用程序本身。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，要进行更深入的见解，请运行以下内容：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述部署&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这提供了详细的部署数据，包括POD模板，条件和最近的事件。您可能会看到诸如“ Replicaset无法创建POD”之类的消息，这些消息可能表明潜在的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤2：监视显示状态和历史记录&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; traCK实时部署推出：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl推出状态部署&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在监视&lt;a href =“ https://middleware.io/blog/what-is-a-ci-cd-pipeline/”&gt; ci/cd Pipeline &lt;/a&gt;运行时，这很有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查看部署历史记录：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl推出历史记录部署&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用它来确定哪个修订引入了问题并将其与以前的工作版本进行比较。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们列出豆荚并发现错误：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取豆荚&#xA;&#xA;my-app-7d4b8c8f-xyz 0/1 imagepullbackoff 0 2m &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，检查失败的POD：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述pod my-app-7d4b8f-xyz&#xA;&#xA;未能拉动图像“ private-Registry.com/my-app:v1.2.3”：&#xA;&#xA;守护程序的错误响应：private-Registry.com/my-app&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这表明Kubernetes由于缺失或无效的凭据而无法访问私人容器注册表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;步骤4：使用Secrets &lt;/h4&gt;修复ImagePullBackoff&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要解决此问题，请创建一个kubernetes秘密，以安全地存储您的私人注册表：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;  -docker-server = private-Registry.com \&#xA;&#xA;  -docker-username = myuser \&#xA;&#xA;  -docker-password = myPassword \&#xA;&#xA;  -docker-email=my@email.com &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，修补您的部署以引用秘密：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl patch部署my-app -p&#39;{“ spec”：{“ template”：{“ spec”：{“ imagepullSecrets”：[imagepullSecrets&#39;：[{“ name” name&#39;：“”：&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦修补，Kubernetes将使用正确的凭据重新触发部署。您可以使用：&lt;/p&gt;监视新的推出&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl推出状态部署my-app &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 3。 kubernetes故障排除：修复未准备就绪的节点错误&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一个经常面对的错误是节点上的&lt;code&gt;未准备就绪&lt;/code&gt;状态，它阻止了POD调度并破坏工作负载。如果节点上的kubelet无法与服务器通信或节点失败健康检查，则会出现&lt;code&gt;未准备就绪&lt;/code&gt;状态，防止POD被安排，这通常会导致应用程序停机时间。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; step1：检查节点状态&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，检查所有节点的状态：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl get nodes -o wide &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此命令列出了所有群集节点，显示其状态，容器运行时，IP地址和OS详细信息。 t他&lt;code&gt; -o wide &lt;/code&gt;标志给出了其他上下文，帮助识别节点级问题，例如OS不匹配或节点位置模式（例如，子网特定故障）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;步骤2：检查节点条件和问题&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用以下命令获取节点资源能力和健康的详细视图：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述节点| GREP -A 5“容量\ |分配” &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这将显示节点的可分配资源在限制范围内还是被过度使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，假设您有一个节点显示&lt;code&gt; notready &lt;/code&gt;状态：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl get nodesworker-node-1未准备就绪5D v1.28.0 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;步骤3：要进一步研究&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述节点worker node-1&#xA;&#xA;状况：&#xA;&#xA;键入状态lastheartbeattime lastTransitionTime原因消息&#xA;&#xA;DISKPRESSURE TRUE MON，2024年1月1日星期一，2024年1月1日     &#xA;kubelethasdiskpressure kubelet具有磁盘压力&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;固定磁盘压力问题&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这种情况下，节点通常报告磁盘压力通常是因为分区或日志消耗了过多的空间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要解决此问题，请使用：&lt;/p&gt;清除系统日志&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这将删除超过3天的日志并释放磁盘空间，帮助Kubelet将节点返回&lt;code&gt; Ready &lt;/code&gt;状态。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 4。诊断服务和网络问题：待处理错误&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当服务或豆荚陷入&lt;code&gt;等待&lt;/code&gt;状态时，Kubernetes故障排除将变得至关重要。这通常表明选择器不匹配，网络配置错误或DNS分辨率问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;服务连通性问题是Kubernetes中最令人沮丧的问题之一。首先列出所有服务以验证其配置：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取服务 -  all-namespaces &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此命令返回服务类型和网络详细信息，包括IP地址和端口。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤1：验证服务&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要识别服务是否缺乏匹配的POD，请使用以下命令列出端点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取端点&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果端点为空，则意味着没有豆荚匹配服务的选择器，这通常是连接故障的根本原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以进一步检查服务配置，以验证过去的标签找到豆荚：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述服务&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将服务中的选择标签与豆荚上的实际标签进行比较，以确保它们对齐。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤2：检查群集中的DNS问题&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果微服务在导致&lt;code&gt;待处理&lt;/code&gt;状态之间存在通信失败，则DNS分辨率可能是罪魁祸首。您可以从吊舱内运行以下命令：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; nslookup my-service&#xA;&#xA;nslookup my-service.d &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果DNS名称无法解析为IP地址，则群集的DNS配置可能存在问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;测试HTTP连接&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要确保服务正确响应，请测试其端点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果请求失败，则可以指示服务配置，网络策略或不正确的POD选择器的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; 5。 kubernetes故障排除高资源用法：求解oomkilled错误&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;监视资源是Kubernetes故障排除的关键部分，可以维护健康群集并确保最佳的应用程序性能。当一个容器超过其分配的内存限制时，Kubernetes会强行终止它，从而导致臭名昭著的&lt;code&gt; oomkilled &lt;/code&gt;错误。这可能会导致POD驱逐，应用停机时间或严重的性能降解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤1：检查资源使用&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;识别内存密集的节点和豆荚：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl top节点&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此命令提供跨节点的实时资源使用情况。如果一个节点使用其内存的80％以上，则可能有触发OOMKILD错误的风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您还可以查看POD级资源使用情况，并通过CPU或内存进行排序：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;kubectl顶部豆荚 -  all-namespaces -sort-by = memory &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些命令可帮助您查明集群中最渴望资源的豆荚。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;与中间件的&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://docs.middleware.io/agent-installation/agent-installation/kubernetes/kubernetes-agentes-agentes-agent”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解和监视资源限制至关重要。在所有名称空间上检查配额：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述配额 -  all-namespaces &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://middleware.io/blog/memory-leaks/”&gt;内存泄漏&lt;/a&gt;通常会随着时间的推移逐渐增加内存使用情况。您可以监视豆荚的李VE每5秒使用记忆消耗：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这可以帮助您发现内存泄漏或逐渐增加内存使用量。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;避免记忆问题在撞车之前。 See how to detect them early via &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/blog/kubernetes-monitoring/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果POD缺乏内存限制，它们可能会消耗过多的资源，并可能影响其他工作量。检查资源请求和限制：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl描述pod memory-hungry-app | grep -a 10“请求\ |限制” &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一个有用的Kubernetes故障排除技巧，可以识别哪些POD缺乏适当的内存限制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;步骤4：减轻与资源相关的问题&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了防止OOMKILD错误并自动平衡资源使用情况，您可以设置水平吊舱自动化（HPA）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;专业提示：使用自动升级来管理资源尖峰。例如，根据70％CPU使用自动进行部署：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl autoscale部署my-app -cpu-perment = 70 -min = 2 -max = 10 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以验证&lt;a href =“ https://middleware.io/blog/what-is-autoscaling/”&gt; autoscaling &lt;/a&gt;处于活动状态并正常工作：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl获取HPA&#xA;&#xA;Kubectl描述HPA My-App &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主动管理资源限制并启用自动化有助于防止错误的错误并确保应用程序性能更顺畅。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;使用监视和跟踪工具&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当内置工具（例如&lt;code&gt; kubectl &lt;/code&gt;）对于初始调试至关重要时，它们在处理复杂的，分布式系统时可能会缺乏。这是第三方可观察性平台发挥作用的地方。例如，中间件提供了一种全面的可观察性解决方案，可为您的Kubernetes群集提供更深的可见性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2025 Co-located Event Deep Dive: Istio Day】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon北美2025年共同介绍的活动深度潜水：Istio Day</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/09/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2025-co-located-event-deep-dive-istio-day/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;November 10, 2025&lt;br&gt;Atlanta, Georgia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;205&#34; height=&#34;67&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/Istio-Day-NA_2023_Logos_Istio-Day-Logo-Color.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Istio Day North America&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-117642&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/istio-day/&#34;&gt;Istio Day&lt;/a&gt; is the biannual community event for the industry’s most widely adopted and feature rich service mesh, where attendees will find lessons learned from running Istio in production, the latest updates on Istio’s ambient mode developments, and the opportunity to meet and learn from maintainers across the Istio ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will be the fourth Istio Day.&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2023/istio-at-kubecon-eu/&#34;&gt; The first Istio Day&lt;/a&gt; was co-located with KubeCon Europe 2023, in Amsterdam. This colocated event replaces ServiceMeshCon, which was first held in 2019, before Istio was a CNCF project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who will get the most out of attending this event?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Everyone from newcomers to seasoned professionals will benefit from this event. Whether you’re just starting with Istio or have extensive experience, you’ll gain new insights, discover emerging trends, and have the opportunity to engage directly with industry experts and fellow practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is new and different this year?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, we’ve curated a selection of topics that provide fresh and diverse perspectives on Istio. The event features new voices, emerging technologies, and real-world use cases that reflect the latest industry trends, offering attendees valuable insights they won’t find elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will the day look like?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The event will begin with a welcome from the chairs, followed by a series of technical sessions covering various aspects of Istio, including case studies, new features, and practical recipes. Throughout the event, there will be dedicated breaks for coffee and networking, giving attendees the chance to connect with speakers and fellow practitioners. The event will conclude with closing remarks summarizing key takeaways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should I do any homework first?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Attendees are encouraged to familiarize themselves with the basics of Istio and review the schedule to identify sessions of interest. Reading recent blog posts or documentation updates can also provide valuable context for the discussions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Find your community!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio Day is more than just a conference; it’s a community gathering that fosters collaboration and innovation. We encourage attendees to actively participate, ask questions, and share their experiences to make the most of this opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to see how the community has embraced service mesh technologies and to learn from the diverse set of sessions and speakers at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon. The opportunity to network with peers and discuss the future of cloud-native technologies is something we highly anticipate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/register/?utm_source=www&amp;amp;utm_medium=homepage&amp;amp;utm_campaign=10608228-KubeCon-NA-2025&amp;amp;utm_content=hero&amp;amp;ajs_aid=b4cbcea8-db3a-48a5-b9ca-81b8469a1e6a&amp;amp;__hstc=60185074.8e4b51df8090e8cfa91e680bb9f547c3.1753120388630.1757099605228.1757114301600.188&amp;amp;__hssc=60185074.4.1757114301600&amp;amp;__hsfp=1387625814&#34;&gt;Don’t forget to register&lt;/a&gt; for KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; 2025年11月10日&lt;br&gt;乔治亚州亚特兰大&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 205” height =“ 67” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/istio-day-na_2023_istio-day-day-loogos_istio-day-logo-color.svg”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-north-america/co-located-events/istio-day/&gt; istio day&gt;&gt; istio day&gt;” ISTIO的环境模式发展，以及向ISTIO生态系统中的维护者见面和学习的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这将是第四天。这个共凝结的事件取代了ISTIO是CNCF项目之前于2019年首次举行的ServiceMeshcon。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;谁会最大程度地参加此活动？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从新移民到经验丰富的专业人士的每个人都将受益于这一活动。无论您是从ISTIO开始还是有丰富的经验，都可以获得新的见解，发现新兴趋势，并有机会直接与行业专家和其他从业人员互动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;今年有什么新鲜事物？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年，我们策划了一系列主题，这些主题为ISTIO提供了新鲜而多样的观点。该活动以新的声音，新兴技术和现实世界中的用例以反映最新行业趋势，为与会者提供了他们在其他地方找不到的宝贵见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;这一天会是什么样？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该活动将从椅子的欢迎开始，然后是一系列技术会议，涵盖了ISTIO的各个方面，包括案例研究，新功能和实际食谱。在整个活动期间，将有专门的休息时间用于咖啡和网络，这使与会者有机会与演讲者和同事们建立联系。该活动将以总结关键要点的结束评论来结束。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我应该先做任何家庭作业吗？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;鼓励与会者熟悉ISTIO的基础知识，并审查时间表以确定感兴趣的会议。阅读最近的博客文章或文档更新也可以为讨论提供宝贵的背景。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;找到您的社区！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; istio day不仅仅是会议。这是一个促进合作和创新的社区聚会。我们鼓励与会者积极参与ipate，提出问题并分享他们的经验以充分利用这一机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴看到社区如何接受服务网络技术，并从Kubecon + Cloudnativecon的各种会议和演讲者中学习。我们非常期待与同行建立联系并讨论云本地技术的未来的机会。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/gregister/?utm_source=www&amp;utm_medium = homeium = homepage&amp;utm_campaign = 1060608228-kubecon-kubecon-na-na-20222 emandtent = BBENTINT = BBENTINT =BBENTINTINTICTINTINT。 4CBCEA8-DB3A-48A5-B9CA-81B8469A1E6A＆__ HSTC = 60185074.8E4B51DF8090E8CFA91E680BBBBB9F547C3.17531203 88630.1757099605228.1757114301600.188＆__ HSSC = 60185074.4.4.1757114301600＆__ HSFP = 1387625814“&gt;忘记注册&lt;/a&gt; kubecon + Cloudnativecon北美2025年。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Combatting Sophisticated Cybersecurity Threats with AI】用AI对抗复杂的网络安全威胁</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/08/combatting-sophisticated-cybersecurity-threats-with-ai/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As AI continues to evolve, businesses are rapidly integrating it into their operations. But with this growth comes an urgent need to prioritise cybersecurity because ignoring security risks in an AI-driven landscape can leave businesses vulnerable to sophisticated threats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity isn’t about relying on a single tool but rather building layered defences. A strategic combination of firewalls, encryption, and advanced threat detection systems can significantly reduce cyber risks while ensuring your organisation runs smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When security is effectively managed, uncertainty is reduced, and your organisation can operate with confidence, allowing you to focus on what truly matters: &lt;strong&gt;scaling your business, driving innovation, and staying ahead of the competition.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores key cybersecurity tools and how they work together to build a robust security strategy. Whether you’re looking to enhance your existing defences or implement new solutions, these insights will help you strengthen your organisation’s security posture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smarter, faster, and more dangerous&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity is no longer just an IT concern, but rather a boardroom priority. With AI-driven cyber threats no longer limited to generic phishing emails or outdated malware, today’s attacks are smarter, more precise, and alarmingly convincing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2023, &lt;a href=&#34;https://darktrace.com/cyber-ai&#34;&gt;Darktrace reported a staggering 135%&lt;/a&gt; increase in social engineering attacks. These aren’t just your average phishing attempts – they’re highly targeted, AI-generated, and built to exploit human trust. Tools like wormGPT and FraudGPT are being used by attackers to create realistic, personalised, and highly deceptive campaigns that can slip past traditional security filters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen emails that perfectly mimic legitimate correspondence, right down to the sender’s domain and writing style, designed to fool recipients into clicking malicious links. I know many of us have encountered that moment when something about an email just doesn’t feel right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s no longer enough to rely on human intuition or traditional security measures. We need AI-powered defences that evolve as fast as the threats themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intrusion Detection Systems (IDS) as your early warning system&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An Intrusion Detection System (IDS) is a non-negotiable part of modern cybersecurity. Without it, you’re leaving your organisation vulnerable to stealthy threats that can infiltrate and wreak havoc before you even realise it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many companies only discover data breaches after significant damage has already been done, which is a costly and entirely preventable situation. An IDS helps to detect suspicious behaviour in real time, allowing teams to respond before threats escalate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For organisations that don’t self-host and have no on-premise networks or physical servers to monitor, Cloud-Native IDS solutions provided by AWS, Azure, and Google Cloud, or third-party security vendors are the alternative. Some examples of Cloud-Native IDS solutions include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;AWS GuardDuty – Monitors AWS accounts, workloads, and network traffic for threats.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Defender for Cloud – Provides security alerts for Azure-based infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Google Cloud IDS – Detects malicious activity within Google Cloud environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CrowdStrike Falcon &amp;amp; Palo Alto Prisma Cloud – Offer cloud-specific IDS capabilities for SaaS and multi-cloud environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, for SaaS security and API monitoring solutions, there are Cloud Access Security Brokers (CASB) like Microsoft Defender CASB and Netskope, which play a crucial role in identifying and flagging suspicious activity in fully remote and hybrid environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These tools maintain a comprehensive audit trail of user actions across an organisation, enabling IT security teams to investigate and respond to potential breaches.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, CASBs are particularly effective in hybrid and remote work environments, offering full visibility into user activity, from logins to file transfers and other movements within the network. Example architecture:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1280&#34; height=&#34;794&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-146065&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image.jpg 1280w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-300x186.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1024x635.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-768x476.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-900x558.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-322x200.jpg 322w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-645x400.jpg 645w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image caption: A visual representation of how a Wi-Fi connection can serve as an entry point for cyber threats, while log data is securely transmitted to Microsoft Cloud App Security, which is a Microsoft Defender (CASB)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OAuth applications have become a prime target for cybercriminals. They exploit users’ trust, tricking them into granting access to corporate credentials, often without a second thought. Many organisations rely on OAuth to log into websites using their company Google accounts, for example. Once access is granted, these apps can tap into everything from employee Google Calendars and LinkedIn accounts to project management tools, GitHub repositories, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By leveraging AI and machine learning, CASBs can also monitor which OAuth apps are genuinely authorised within the organisation, giving IT security teams the power to set policies that automatically block risky access attempts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond just access control, CASBs also add another layer of security to cloud storage which makes them an essential defence mechanism in today’s digital workplace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choosing the right IDS approach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A seemingly harmless Flash Player update began spreading across corporate networks in Russia and Ukraine in 2017. Employees thought they were simply installing routine software, unknowingly opening the gates to one of the most disruptive ransomware attacks of the year: BadRabbit ransomware attack. Within a few hours, critical files were encrypted, operations stopped, and businesses faced a difficult choice: pay a ransom of 0.05 Bitcoin (BTC) per infected device (283 USD equivalent), or lose their data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The attack was devastating because it was highly sophisticated and slipped past traditional security measures. Signature-based detection systems failed to flag it and the malware hadn’t been seen before, so it didn’t match any known threat signatures. By the time security teams realised what was happening, the damage was done.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What if there had been another layer of defence that could have detected the unusual behaviour? Today, traditional IDS falls short because cyber threats are more dynamic than ever. Attackers constantly evolve their tactics, exploiting zero-day vulnerabilities and using AI-driven methods to bypass defences.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Relying solely on signature-based IDS is like trying to catch a criminal using only a database of known suspects which may be effective for repeat offenders, but useless against a new threat.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anomaly-based IDS, on the other hand, acts like an intelligent detective, identifying suspicious patterns and behaviour. It can catch new and unknown attacks but requires ongoing fine-tuning to reduce false positives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each method has its strengths and limitations, which is why enterprises can no longer afford to rely on just one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future-proofing your security with a hybrid approach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A hybrid IDS combines the precision of signature-based detection with the adaptability of anomaly-based analysis, offering a more robust security posture. Here’s how organisations can determine the right balance:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A signature-based IDS is best suited for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Organisations with well-documented threats like malware and phishing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Security teams that rely on predefined threat intelligence due to limited resources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Networks with relatively predictable traffic patterns.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An anomaly-based IDS is more effective when:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Operating in industries with high-value data, such as finance, healthcare, or government.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Security teams have the expertise to fine-tune and manage evolving detection rules.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Managing hybrid or cloud infrastructures with complex and dynamic network activity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For modern enterprises, security must be both precise and adaptive and a hybrid IDS ensures that both known and emerging threats are addressed while also improving operational efficiency. Key advantages include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Proactive risk management – Real-time detection of both signature-based threats and anomalous activities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Adaptive security for hybrid environments – Reduces attack surfaces across multi-cloud and on-premises networks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Regulatory compliance – Enhances security visibility to meet standards like GDPR, ISO 27001, and NIST.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved SOC efficiency – Reduces false positives, allowing security teams to focus on real threats.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;BadRabbit was a wake-up call, but it won’t be the last. Cybercriminals are constantly refining their techniques, and organisations that fail to adapt will always be playing catch-up. A hybrid IDS isn’t just a smart investment, but an essential step in staying ahead of the next inevitable attack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introducing an Intrusion Prevention System (IPS) to complement your IDS as a proactive defence&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While an IDS alerts you to potential threats, an IPS takes it a step further by proactively blocking threats before they can infiltrate your network.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Equally, with the integration of machine learning capabilities to enhance security observability, organisations are empowered to detect both known and unknown risks when both security systems complement and work together. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;751&#34; height=&#34;464&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-09-at-17.04.50.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-146748&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-09-at-17.04.50.jpg 751w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-09-at-17.04.50-300x185.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-09-at-17.04.50-324x200.jpg 324w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Screenshot-2025-09-09-at-17.04.50-647x400.jpg 647w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 751px) 100vw, 751px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image caption: IDS and IPS working together to enhance network security. Source: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/document?doi=ddcb13f5dc671786b6fef5aa1fc4cc0285c4c79d&amp;amp;repid=rep1&amp;amp;type=pdf&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intrusion Detection System (IDS) &amp;amp; Intrusion Prevention System (IPS): Case Study&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One great example of an organisation that uses both IDS and IPS effectively is Omada Health. They are a provider of digital healthcare solutions and they initially used a log-based IDS but found it inadequate due to the growing complexity of threats and stringent healthcare regulations. To enhance security, they adopted Threat Stack, a host-based IPS that examined running processes and system calls for more actionable insights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the combination of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.f5.com/products/distributed-cloud-services&#34;&gt;Threat Stack’s Cloud Security Platform and managed cybersecurity services&lt;/a&gt;, Omada Health gained real-time intrusion detection and proactive threat prevention. The IPS automatically blocked threats as they were detected, while the IDS flagged potential risks. This dual approach allowed Omada Health to respond faster to security incidents, protecting sensitive healthcare data and ensuring compliance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The integration also improved operational efficiency. The security team no longer had to sift through low-priority alerts, saving two to four hours of analysis time per day. This blend of IDS and IPS provided a comprehensive, AI-powered security solution, enhancing both detection and prevention capabilities while streamlining security operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This story illustrates how an organisation achieved a well-rounded security solution while boosting their operational efficiency. Here’s an overview of how IDS and IPS work well together:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Detection vs. prevention:&lt;/strong&gt; The IDS, whether signature-based or anomaly-based, monitors network traffic and system behaviour to identify threats. However, it doesn’t take action on its own. The IPS takes immediate action to block or mitigate detected threats, such as stopping malicious traffic or quarantining compromised systems.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved response time: &lt;/strong&gt;In the event of a detection, an IPS can respond faster than a purely manual security response, which might take time to assess and act. This makes it particularly useful for blocking attacks in real time, enhancing the overall efficiency of the hybrid IDS system.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimising damage:&lt;/strong&gt; While the IDS provides alerts, the IPS stops attacks from spreading, minimising potential damage. For example, if the IDS detects unusual behaviour, such as a ransomware attack beginning to encrypt files, the IPS can prevent it from executing or spreading further.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leveraging Cloud-Native Endpoint Security for fully-remote or hybrid organisational setups&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If each device in your network is a potential entry point for attackers, wouldn’t you want to secure every single one? For fully remote and cloud-based businesses, traditional endpoint security isn’t enough. You’d need a Cloud-Native approach that scales without adding complexity or friction. Here’s how Cloud-Native Endpoint Security can enhance your network’s security:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1280&#34; height=&#34;794&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;An example of a cloud-based solution for Endpoint Security and management that offers a unified approach through a SaaS model. Source: Endpoint Central&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-146066&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image.jpg 1280w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-300x186.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-1024x635.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-768x476.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-900x558.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-322x200.jpg 322w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-645x400.jpg 645w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image caption: An example of a cloud-based solution for Endpoint Security and management that offers a unified approach through a SaaS model. Source: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.manageengine.com/products/desktop-central/help/cloud-architecture.html#ecserver&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Endpoint Central&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI plays a crucial role in distinguishing modern Endpoint protection from traditional solutions. It enables advanced protection by using models trained on vast amounts of data to predict threats accurately, particularly when enhancing defences against sophisticated attacks like fileless threats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One standout solution is CrowdStrike Falcon. This tool is a Cloud-Native Endpoint Security platform designed for speed, efficiency, and AI-driven protection. Unlike traditional security tools, Falcon doesn’t require constant signature updates, on-premise management infrastructure, or complex integrations that slow down operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead, it leverages machine learning to analyse files, network traffic, and user behaviour, detecting and stopping threats before they cause harm.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The WannaCry ransomware attack in May 2017 disrupted businesses globally by exploiting a Windows vulnerability (MS17-010), known as EternalBlue, to spread and encrypt files, demanding ransom in Bitcoin.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In response, CrowdStrike Falcon was deployed to identify WannaCry’s unusual behaviour through machine learning, flagging its deviation from normal patterns. Falcon automatically isolated infected endpoints, preventing further spread, and helped organisations apply the MS17-010 patch to mitigate the vulnerability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, deep learning algorithms in endpoint security now detect advanced threats, like polymorphic malware, which evades traditional detection methods by constantly changing its signature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Behaviour Analytics (UBA)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No matter how well-vetted your employees are, intentional or accidental insider threats remain an ongoing risk. Even a well-meaning employee might download unapproved software that appears harmless but ends up introducing malware into the organisation. A more serious scenario is when a departing employee with access to sensitive intellectual property takes that data to a competitor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional security measures like firewalls and Endpoint protection aren’t always equipped to detect these behaviours, especially as phishing tactics and scams become increasingly sophisticated, so this is where User Behaviour Analytics (UBA) becomes a critical layer of defence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The strength of UBA lies in its focus on insider threats. It excels in this area with its subtle, undercover-like approach to monitoring user behaviour within the organisation. It not only looks for obvious red flags, it also establishes a baseline of normal activity i.e. which files employees access, how often they log in, where they typically work from, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;UBA also detects subtle deviations that might go unnoticed, like accessing sensitive data at odd hours or logging in from unusual locations. It identifies these anomalies before they escalate, offering tailored security based on your organisation’s unique patterns.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Splunk UBA stands out as a promising solution, as it provides a range of detection models that have comprehensive security insights and advanced analytics:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Streaming models: &lt;/strong&gt;Process events in real-time, assessing the impact of each event within a short period (e.g., 24 hours).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Batch models: &lt;/strong&gt;Analyse longer time windows i.e. 30 days to detect anomalies and trends using historical data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A powerful example of AI and UBA together in action is DarkTrace. DarkTrace detected an active cyberattack on an energy grid just hours after its deployment. By monitoring around 5,000 devices, the AI grouped them based on behavioural similarities and quickly identified an anomaly that indicated a potential threat.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;UBA’s ability to leverage AI and machine learning for real-time threat detection makes it a crucial tool in identifying insider threats and maintaining the security of an organisation’s IT infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security is about layering, not luck&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A unified, multi-layered approach to cybersecurity, combining IDS, IPS, UBA, and Endpoint Security, creates a dynamic, adaptable defence system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each tool enhances the other, forming a self-learning security network that shares insights to improve detection and response. AI-powered systems take this a step further, evolving to outsmart attackers, safeguard critical data, and stay ahead of emerging threats.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Implementing AI in cybersecurity requires thoughtful investment in technology, training, and infrastructure, but the long-term benefits are clear: improved threat detection, prevention, and response, securing your organisation’s assets and reputation. To stay ahead of evolving threats, ensure your security systems evolve with technological advancements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着AI的不断发展，企业正在迅速将其整合到他们的运营中。但是随着这种增长，迫切需要优先考虑网络安全，因为无视AI驱动的景观中的安全风险可能会使企业容易受到复杂威胁的影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;网络安全不是要依靠单个工具，而是要构建分层防御。防火墙，加密和高级威胁检测系统的战略组合可以显着降低网络风险，同时确保您的组织运行顺利。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当安全有效地管理安全性时，不确定性会减少，您的组织可以充满信心地运作，使您可以专注于真正重要的事情：&lt;strong&gt;扩展业务，推动创新并保持竞争领先地位。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了关键的网络安全工具以及它们如何共同努力以建立强大的安全策略。无论您是想增强现有防御措施还是实施新解决方案，这些见解都将帮助您加强组织的安全姿势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;更聪明，更快，更危险&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;网络安全不再只是IT关注，而是董事会优先事项。由于AI驱动的网络威胁不再限于通用的网络钓鱼电子邮件或过时的恶意软件，因此今天的攻击更加聪明，更精确且令人震惊。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在2023年，&lt;a href =“ https://darktrace.com/cyber-ai”&gt; DarkTrace报告了惊人的135％&lt;/a&gt;社会工程攻击的增加。这些不仅是您的平均网络钓鱼尝试 - 它们是高度针对性，AI生成的，并且是为了利用人类信任而建立的。攻击者正在使用诸如Wormgpt和欺诈的工具来创建现实，个性化和高度欺骗性的活动，这些活动可以滑过传统的安全过滤器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我已经看到了完美模仿合法通信的电子邮件，直到发件人的域和写作风格，旨在欺骗接收者单击恶意链接。我知道我们中的许多人遇到了那一刻，关于电子邮件的事情感觉不正确。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这已经不足以依靠人类的直觉或传统的安全措施。我们需要AI驱动的防御能力，这些防御能力与威胁本身一样快。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;入侵检测系统（IDS）作为您的预警系统&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;入侵检测系统（IDS）是现代网络安全的不可谈判的一部分。没有它，您的组织很容易受到隐秘威胁，这些威胁甚至可能在意识到它之前渗透和破坏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多公司仅在造成重大损害后才发现数据泄露，这是一种昂贵且完全可预防的情况。 IDS有助于实时检测可疑行为，使团队在威胁升级之前做出响应。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;没有自我主持人且没有可监视的本地网络或物理服务器的组织，AWS，Azure和Google Cloud提供的云本地IDS解决方案或第三方安全供应商是替代方案。云本地IDS解决方案的一些示例包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; AWS GuardDuty  - 监视威胁的AWS帐户，工作量和网络流量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Microsoft Defender for Cloud  - 为基于Azure的基础结构提供安全警报。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Google Cloud ID  - 检测Google Cloud Environments中的恶意活动。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; CrowdStrike Falcon＆Palo Alto Prisma Cloud  - 为SaaS和Multi-Cloud环境提供特定于云的IDS功能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一方面，对于SaaS安全和API监视解决方案，有云访问安全经纪人（CASB），例如Microsoft Defender Casb和Netskope，它们在识别和标记完全遥远和混合环境中的可疑活动中起着至关重要的作用。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些工具维持了整个组织中用户行动的全面审计，使IT安全团队能够调查并应对潜在的违规行为。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，CASB在混合和远程工作环境中特别有效，可全面了解用户活动，从登录到网络中的文件传输和其他动作。示例体系结构：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 1280” height =“ 794” src =“ https：//www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/uploads/2555/2025/09/image.image.image.image.jpg” class =“ wp-image-146065” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image.jpg 1280W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-300x186.jpg 300W，https://www.cncf.io/wp.io/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/20255/2025/209/image-1024x635.jpgpg55.jppgpg5.jppg5.jppgpg5.jppgpg5 and https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-768x476.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-900x558.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-322x200.jpg 322w，https://www.cncf.io/wp.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/255/2025/2025/209/image-image-image-image-1445.jpg45.jpg45.jpg&#39;&#39; （最大宽度：1280px）100VW，1280px“ reverrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;图像标题：Wi-Fi连接如何作为网络威胁的切入点的视觉表示，而日志数据则牢固地传输到Microsoft Cloud App App Security，这是Microsoft Defender（CASB）&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; oauth应用已成为网络犯罪分子的主要目标。他们利用用户的信任，欺骗他们授予对公司凭据的访问，通常没有再考虑。例如，许多组织依靠Oauth使用其公司Google帐户登录网站。授予访问后，这些应用程序可以利用从员工Google日历和LinkedIn帐户到项目管理工具，GitHub存储库等的所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过利用AI和机器学习，CASB还可以监视组织内真正授权的OAuth应用程序，使其安全团队有权设定自动阻止风险访问尝试的策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了访问控制之外，Casbs还为云存储添加了另一层安全性，这使它们成为当今数字工作场所的重要防御机制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;选择正确的IDS方法&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;看似无害的Flash Player更新开始在2017年开始在俄罗斯和乌克兰的公司网络上传播。员工认为他们只是在安装例行软件，在不知不觉中将大门打开了今年最具破坏性的勒索软件攻击之一：Badrabbit Bitbit Ransomware攻击。在几个小时内，关键文件被加密，停止操作，并且企业面临一个困难的选择：每个受感染的设备（283 USD同等用途）支付0.05比特币（BTC）的赎金，或丢失其数据。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这次攻击是毁灭性的，因为它是高度复杂且经过传统的安全措施。基于签名的检测系统未能标记它，并且以前从未见过恶意软件，因此它与任何已知的威胁签名不符。到安全团队意识到发生了什么时，损坏已造成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果有另一层防御能够检测到异常行为怎么办？如今，传统ID不足，因为网络威胁比以往任何时候都更具动态性。攻击者不断发展他们的战术，利用零日漏洞，并使用AI驱动的方法绕过防御。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仅依靠基于签名的ID就像试图使用已知犯罪嫌疑人的数据库捕获犯罪分子，这些嫌疑人可能对重复犯罪者有效，但对新威胁无用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;另一方面，&lt;p&gt;基于异常的ID像智能侦探一样，识别可疑模式和行为。它可能会捕获新的和未知的攻击，但需要进行持续的微调以减少误报。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每种方法都有其优势和局限性，这就是为什么企业不再能够仅依靠一个。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;通过混合方法&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;来防止您的安全性&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;混合IDS结合了基于签名的检测的精度和基于异常的分析的适应性，提供了更强大的安全姿势。这是组织如何确定正确平衡的方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基于签名的ID最适合：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;具有据可查的组织，例如恶意软件和网络钓鱼。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;由于资源有限而依靠预定义威胁情报的安全团队。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;具有相对可预测的流量模式的网络。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当以下情况下，基于异常的ID更有效：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在WI行业运营高价值数据，例如财务，医疗保健或政府。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;安全团队具有微调和管理不断发展的检测规则的专业知识。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用复杂且动态的网络活动管理混合或云基础架构。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于现代企业，安全必须既精确又适应性，并且混合ID可以确保对已知和新兴威胁的解决，同时也提高了运营效率。关键优势包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;主动风险管理 - 实时检测基于签名的威胁和异常活动。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;混合环境的自适应安全性 - 减少多云和本地网络的攻击表面。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;监管合规性 - 提高安全性可见性，以满足GDPR，ISO 27001和NIST等标准。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;提高了SOC效率 - 降低误报，使安全团队专注于真正的威胁。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Badrabbit是一个警钟，但这不是最后一个。网络犯罪分子一直在不断完善其技术，而未能适应的组织将始终在追赶。混合ID不仅是一项明智的投资，而且是在下一次不可避免的攻击之前的重要一步。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;引入入侵预防系统（IPS）以将您的ID作为主动防御&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;补充&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然IDS会提醒您对潜在威胁的提醒，但IPS通过主动阻止威胁在渗透您的网络之前将其更进一步。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同样，随着机器学习能力的集成以增强安全性可观察性，当安全系统均补充和共同工作时，组织有权检测已知和未知风险。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 751” height =“ 464” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-09-AT-17.04.50.50.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-09-AT-17.04.50.50.50.jpg 751W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-AT-17.04.504.50-300x185.jpg 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-2025-09-09-09-AT-17.04.50-50-324x200.jpg 324W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/screenshot-2025-09-09-09-09-AT-17.04.50-504.50-647x400.jpg 647w 647W 647W“ sizes =” size =“ auto referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;图像标题：IDS和IP共同努力增强网络安全性。资料来源：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://citeseerx.ist.ist.psu.edu/document?doi = ddcb13f5dc671786b6b6fef5aaaa1fc41fc4c4cc0285c49dc79d时间入侵预防系统（IPS）：案例研究&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用两个ID的组织的一个很好的例子S和IP有效的是Omada健康。他们是数字医疗解决方案的提供商，最初使用基于日志的ID，但由于威胁和严格的医疗保健法规的复杂性日益严重，因此发现它不足。为了提高安全性，他们采用了基于主机的IPS的威胁堆栈，该堆栈检查了运行过程和系统要求提供更多可行的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结合了&lt;a href =“ https://www.f5.com/products/distributed-cloud-services”&gt; theatn stack stack的云安全平台和托管网络安全服务&lt;/a&gt;，OMADA Health获得了实时入侵检测和主动威胁预防。 IPS在检测到时会自动阻止威胁，而IDS则标记了潜在风险。这种双重方法使Omada Health可以更快地应对安全事件，保护敏感的医疗保健数据并确保合规。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;集成也提高了运营效率。安全团队不再需要筛选低优先级的警报，每天节省了两到四个小时的分析时间。这种ID和IP的混合物提供了一种全面的，AI驱动的安全解决方案，在简化安全操作的同时增强了检测和预防功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个故事说明了组织如何在提高其运营效率的同时实现全面的安全解决方案。这是ID和IP如何一起工作的概述：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;检测与预防：&lt;/strong&gt; ID，无论是基于签名还是基于异常的ID，监视网络流量和系统行为以识别威胁。但是，它不会自行采取行动。 IPS立即采取行动来阻止或减轻检测到的威胁，例如停止恶意流量或隔离损害系统。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;改善了响应时间：&lt;/strong&gt;在检测时，IPS可以比纯粹的手动安全响应更快，这可能需要时间来评估和采取行动。这使得它对于实时阻止攻击特别有用，从而提高了混合IDS系统的整体效率。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;最小化损害：&lt;/strong&gt; IDS提供警报时，IPS阻止攻击扩散，从而最大程度地减少潜在的损害。例如，如果IDS检测到异常行为，例如勒索软件攻击开始加密文件，则IPS可以防止其执行或进一步传播。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;利用云原状端点安全性用于全身或混合组织设置&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的网络中的每个设备都是攻击者的潜在切入点，您是否想保护每个设备？对于完全遥远和基于云的业务，传统的端点安全是不​​够的。您需要一种云原状方法，可以扩展而不会增加复杂性或摩擦。以下是云原始端点安全性可以增强您的网络的安全性：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1280&#34; height=&#34;794&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;An example of a cloud-based solution for Endpoint Security and management通过SaaS模型提供了统一的方法：端点中央“ class” =“ WP-Image-146066” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/09/image.jpg 1280w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-300x186.jpg 300W，https://www.cncf.io/wp.io/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/20255/2025/209/image-1024x635.jpgpg55.jppgpg5.jppg5.jppgpg5.jppgpg5 and https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-768x476.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-900x558.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/image-322x200.jpg 322w，https://www.cncf.io/wp.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/255/2025/2025/209/image-image-image-image-1445.jpg45.jpg45.jpg&#39;&#39; （最大宽度：1280px）100VW，1280px“ reverrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;图像标题：用于端点安全和管理的基于云的解决方案的示例，该解决方案通过SaaS模型提供了统一的方法。来源：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.manageengine.com/products/desktop-central/help/help/cloud-architecture.htmll#ecserver”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; AI在区分现代端点保护与传统解决方案方面起着至关重要的作用。它可以通过使用对大量数据训练的模型来准确预测威胁，尤其是在增强防御攻击之类的复杂攻击（如无归档威胁）时，可以实现高级保护。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个出色的解决方案是Crowdstrike Falcon。该工具是云端端点安全平台，旨在速度，效率和AI驱动保护。与传统的安全工具不同，Falcon不需要持续的签名更新，本地管理基础架构或复杂的集成，以减慢操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;相反，它利用机器学习分析文件，网络流量和用户行为，在造成危害之前检测和停止威胁。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2017年5月，WannaCry勒索软件攻击通过利用Windows漏洞（MS17-010）（称为EternalBlue）来散布和加密文件，从而在全球范围内破坏了企业，要求在比特币中赎金。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了响应，CrowdStrike Falcon被部署以通过机器学习来识别WannaCry的异常行为，并标记其与正常模式的偏差。猎鹰会自动隔离感染的端点，防止进一步扩散，并帮助组织应用MS17-010补丁以减轻漏洞。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，端点安全中的深度学习算法现在检测到高级威胁，例如多态性恶意软件，该威胁通过不断更改其签名来逃避传统的检测方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;用户行为分析（UBA）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不管您的EM多么很好故意或意外的内部威胁是持续的风险。即使是善意的员工也可能下载未批准的软件，该软件似乎无害，但最终将恶意软件引入了组织。一个更严重的情况是，当访问敏感知识产权的离开员工将数据带给竞争对手时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;诸如防火墙和端点保护之类的传统安全措施并不总是能够检测这些行为的能力，尤其是随着网络钓鱼策略和骗局变得越来越复杂，因此这是用户行为分析（UBA）成为防御的关键层的地方。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; UBA的优势在于它的重点是内幕威胁。它在该领域以其微妙的，类似卧底的方法来监视组织内部的用户行为。它不仅寻找明显的危险信号，还建立了正常活动的基准，即文件访问员工访问，登录的频率，通常从何处工作等等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; uba还检测到可能不会引起注意的微妙偏差，例如在奇数小时访问敏感数据或从异常位置登录。它在这些异常升级之前确定了这些异常，并根据您组织的独特模式提供量身定制的安全性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Splunk UBA是一个有前途的解决方案，因为它提供了具有全面安全见解和高级分析的一系列检测模型：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;流媒体模型：&lt;/strong&gt;实时过程事件，评估每个事件在短时间内的影响（例如24小时）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;批处理模型：&lt;/strong&gt;分析更长的时间窗口，即使用历史数据检测异常和趋势的30天。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; AI和UBA一起进行的一个有力的例子是DarkTrace。 DarkTrace在部署后仅数小时就在电网上检测到了一个主动网络攻击。通过监视约5,000个设备，AI根据行为相似性将它们分组，并迅速确定了一种表明潜在威胁的异常。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; UBA利用AI和机器学习进行实时威胁检测的能力使其成为识别内部威胁和维护组织IT基础架构的安全性的至关重要工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一种统一的，多层的网络安全方法，结合ID，IPS，UBA和端点安全性，创建了动态，适应性的防御系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个工具都会增强另一个工具，形成一个自学习的安全网络，该网络共享洞察力以改善检测和响应。 AI驱动的系统将这一步骤进一步发展，发展为超车攻击者，保护关键数据，并保持领先于新兴威胁。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在网络安全方面实施AI需要对技术，培训和基础设施进行周到的投资，但是长期福利是明确的：改善威胁检测，预防和响应，确保组织的资产和声誉。要保持不断发展的威胁，请确保您的安全系统通过技术进步而发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Considerations when doing AI on Kubernetes】在Kubernetes上进行AI时的考虑</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/05/considerations-when-doing-ai-on-kubernetes/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As more teams start weaving generative AI (GenAI) into their apps and workflows, Kubernetes naturally comes up as the go-to platform. It’s a tried-and-tested solution for managing containerized workloads, but AI workloads are a different beast.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a rundown of what you should think about—and which tools can help—when running AI workloads in cloud-native environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;GenAI Workloads Need Event-Driven Infrastructure&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GenAI features often hinge on user prompts, streaming data, or background jobs. That means you need infrastructure that’s reactive, scalable, and lean.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://knative.dev/docs/concepts/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knative Serving&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Great for HTTP-based GenAI services (like LLM APIs). It automatically scales up when requests come in, and scales to zero when they don’t. Perfect for saving money on GPU-bound workloads.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://keda.sh/docs/2.11/concepts/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEDA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Adds event-driven autoscaling based on external sources like Kafka, RabbitMQ, or Prometheus. It complements Knative by widening the scope of what can trigger scaling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Together, they give you a nimble setup that reacts fast and keeps infra costs manageable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Things to consider when serving LLMs in Cloud-Native Environments&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud-native tooling provides robust building blocks to tackle the considerations below. The key is integrating scalable serving, observability, and DevOps best practices into your AI stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autoscaling Sensitivity&lt;/strong&gt;: Traffic to LLMs can spike unpredictably. Autoscalers must be finely tuned with custom metrics.&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://keda.sh/docs/2.11/concepts/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KEDA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Great for event-based scaling—think queue lengths or custom metrics like token usage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://knative.dev/docs/concepts/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knative Serving&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Scales based on actual HTTP traffic, and goes to zero when idle—perfect for APIs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/workloads/autoscaling/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;VPA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Helps tune your pods’ CPU and memory requests automatically.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kubeflow.org/docs/external-add-ons/kserve/introduction/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KServe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Built with ML in mind, it supports scaling on things like inference throughput or request count.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observability &amp;amp; Debugging&lt;/strong&gt;: GenAI behaviors are opaque. You need metrics, traces, and feedback to understand what’s working.&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/concepts/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: The go-to for collecting logs, metrics, and traces all in one.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/introduction/overview/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prometheus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: System monitoring and alerting toolset.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prompt and Model Drift&lt;/strong&gt;: Just like model drift, prompts can become stale or produce inconsistent outputs.&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/evidentlyai/evidently&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evidently AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Great for keeping tabs on prompt or input drift with real-time monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/langfuse/langfuse&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Langfuse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; / PromptLayer&lt;/strong&gt;: Track how prompts perform and evolve—like analytics for your LLM calls.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/protectai/llm-guard&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LLMGuard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Adds guardrails around your outputs to keep them on track and safe.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resource Intensity&lt;/strong&gt;: Consider smart scheduling to avoid resource waste. LLMs are GPU-hungry and memory-heavy.&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Karpenter or Cluster Autoscaler&lt;/strong&gt;: Automatic node provisioning (like GPU-powered ones) when your workloads need them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kubeflow.org/docs/components/pipelines/concepts/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubeflow Pipelines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Deploying scalable ML workflows using containers on kubernetes based systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kueue.sigs.k8s.io/docs/concepts/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kueue&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;:&amp;nbsp; It manages queues for batch jobs, especially when resources are tight. Need four GPUs for one big job? Kueue would ensure all resources are in place before the workload starts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/tasks/manage-gpus/scheduling-gpus/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes GPU Scheduling (Device Plugins)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: You can fine-tune pod placement using labels and selectors. It will let you request specific specific sources using selectors and tolerations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;MLDevOps is Growing Up: It’s Not Just About Models Anymore&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With GenAI, it’s not just about models anymore. We’re now managing prompts, routing, evaluation loops—and all of it needs version control, observability, and automation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PromptOps- Prompts as Versioned Artifacts: &lt;/strong&gt;Treat prompts like you treat code. Use Gitops tools like Argo CD to manage prompt templates. Deploy and validate with Ci/CD tools like Argo workflows and monitor using prometheus and/or grafana. You can utilize KServe to dynamically serve versioned prompts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shadow Deployments for GenAI: &lt;/strong&gt;Deploy new prompts or models in the background, monitor behavior, then roll out by using Istio, Knative(handles requests route and scale) and KServe(which is built on Knative and adds model lifecycle and inference management)&amp;nbsp; that helps with Traffic routing, traffic splitting and shadow support.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation Pipelines- Automate Model and Prompt Testing: &lt;/strong&gt;Keep quality high with continuous evaluation. Utilize MLflow/Weights and biases to log prompts and model changes. Also, Kubeflow pipelines to manage ML-native workflows.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Final Thoughts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Running AI on Kubernetes isn’t just possible, it’s powerful. With the right tools, you can treat prompts, models, and GenAI services just like any other production-grade software component. But doing so requires a mindset shift: prompts aren’t just strings, they’re assets. And evaluations aren’t just test scripts, they’re pipelines. Lean into the cloud-native ecosystem and let your AI workflows evolve alongside your infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着越来越多的团队开始将生成AI（Genai）编织到他们的应用程序和工作流程中，Kubernetes自然会成为首选平台。这是用于管理容器化工作负载的尝试和测试的解决方案，但是AI工作负载是另一种野兽。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是您应该考虑的内容以及在云本地环境中运行AI工作负载时的想法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; genai工作负载需要事件驱动的基础架构&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; genai特征通常在用户提示，流数据或背景作业上取决于。这意味着您需要反应性，可扩展和瘦的基础架构。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://knative.dev/docs/concepts/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; knative serving &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：非常适合基于HTTP的Genai Services（例如LLM APIS）。当请求进来时，它会自动缩放，并在不提出时将其缩放为零。非常适合在GPU结合工作量上节省资金。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://keda.sh/docs/2.11/concepts/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; keda &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：添加了基于Kafka，Rabbitmq或Prometheus（例如Kafka，Rabbitmq或Prometheus）的外部来源的Event-event-drive驱动自动式化。它通过扩大可以触发缩放的范围的范围来补充Knative。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一起，它们为您提供了一个敏捷的设置，可以快速反应并保持中产阶级成本可管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol start =“ 2” class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;在云本地环境中服务LLM时要考虑的事情&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云本地工具提供了可靠的构建块，以应对以下注意事项。关键是将可扩展的服务，可观察性和DevOps的最佳实践集成到您的AI堆栈中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自动敏感性&lt;/strong&gt;：llms的流量可能无法预测。必须用自定义指标对自动制剂进行精心调整。&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://keda.sh/docs/2.11/concepts/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; keda &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：非常适合基于事件的缩放量表 - 思考队列长度或诸如图形用法之类的自定义指标。&lt;/li&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://knative.dev/docs/concepts/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; knative serving &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：基于实际http流量的缩放量表&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kubernetes.io/docs/conectes/workloads/workloads/autoscaling/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; vpa &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：帮助调整Pods的CPU和内存请求。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.kubeflow.org/docs/external-add-ons/kserve/introduction/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kserve &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：使用ML构建，它可以牢记ML，它支持诸如contription taky taky taby taky taby taby taby taby taby taby contput或请求。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/lie&gt; &lt;/&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可观察性和调试性&lt;/strong&gt;：Genai行为不透明。您需要指标，跟踪和反馈来了解有效的方法。&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://opentelemetry.io/docs/concepts/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; opentelemetry &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：收集日志，指标和指标和痕迹全部。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://prometheus.io/docs/introduction/overview/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Prometheus &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：系统监视和警报工具集。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提示和模型漂移&lt;/strong&gt;：就像模型漂移一样，提示也可能变成陈旧或产生不一致的输出。&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/evideshiai/evidesly&#39;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;显然是ai &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：非常适合通过实时监控来保持及时或输入漂移的标签。&lt;/li&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/langfuse/langfuse”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; langfuse &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;/stressLayer &lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt;：跟踪提示的性能和进化方式 - 类似于LLM呼叫的分析。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/protectai/llm-guard”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; llmguard &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：在您的输出周围添加护栏，以使其保持正轨和安全。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;资源强度&lt;/strong&gt;：考虑智能调度以避免资源浪费。 LLMS是渴望GPU的人和记忆力繁多的。&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; karpenter或cluster Autoscaler &lt;/strong&gt;：当您的工作负载需要时，自动节点配置（如gpu驱动的节点）。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.kubeflow.org/docs/components/pipelines/pipelines/concepts/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kubeflow Pipelines &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：使用Kubernetes基于Kubernetes上的容器在Kubernetes上使用容器来部署可扩展的ML Workflows。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kueue.sigs.k8s.io/docs/concepts/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kueue &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：它管理批处理工作的排队，尤其是当资源紧张时。需要四个GPU才能做一份大工作吗？ Kueue将在工作负载开始之前确保所有资源已到位。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kubernetes.io/docs/tasks/manage-gpus/scheduling-gpus/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kubernetes gpu Scheduling（设备插件）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：您可以使用Babels and Persectors进行填充POD POD。它将让您使用选择器和公差请求特定的特定来源。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol start =“ 3” class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; Mldevops正在成长：不仅与模型有关&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与Genai一起，不仅仅是模型。我们现在正在管理提示，路由，评估循环 - 所有它都需要版本控制，可观察性和自动化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提示 - 提示为版本的工件：&lt;/strong&gt;像对待代码一样处理提示。使用诸如Argo CD之类的Gitops工具来管理及时模板。使用Prometheus和/或Grafana使用CI/CD工具（例如Argo Workfrows）进行部署和验证。您可以利用Kserve动态服务于版本的提示。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; genai的阴影部署：&lt;/strong&gt;在后台部署新提示或模型，监视行为，然后使用istio，knative（手柄请求路线和规模）和kserve推出（构建在knative上，并添加模型生命周期和生命周期型生命周期和模型推理管理），有助于交通路由，流量分裂和阴影支持。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;评估管道 - 自动化模型和及时测试：&lt;/strong&gt;通过连续评估保持高质量。利用MLFLOW/权重和偏见来日志提示和模型更改。另外，KubeFlow管道管理ML本地工作流程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;最终思想&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在kubernetes上运行AI不仅有可能，而且很强大。使用正确的工具，您可以像其他任何生产级软件组件一样处理提示，模型和Genai服务。但是这样做需要改变心态：提示不仅是字符串，它们是资产。评估不仅是测试脚本，而且是管道。倾斜到云本地生态系统，让您的AI工作流与基础架构一起发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Debug Trap: Why Smart Engineers Waste Hours on Trivial Problems】调试陷阱：为什么智能工程师浪费小时数小时</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/09/04/the-debug-trap-why-smart-engineers-waste-hours-on-trivial-problems/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Last month, I watched three senior engineers burn four hours debugging a “mysterious” Kubernetes issue that turned out to be a kubectl version upgrade. The same week, another team spent an entire night hunting phantom load balancer bugs when a certificate rotation had broken mobile clients with certificate pinning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These aren’t stories about incompetent engineers. These are stories about brilliant people falling into the same cognitive trap that catches everyone: diving deep instead of looking broad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Question Nobody Asks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what happened with the kubectl disaster. The symptoms looked serious: cron jobs failing, secrets not updating across namespaces, image pulls crashing left and right. Classic distributed systems chaos, right?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team immediately went into full forensic mode. Pod logs. RBAC permissions. Service account configurations. Network policies. Container registry connectivity. They even started questioning whether someone had compromised their infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Four hours later, an exhausted engineer finally asked the obvious question: “Wait, did we change anything recently?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One git log later, they found their smoking gun: a kubectl version bump from earlier that day. The new version handled secret types differently. Five minutes to roll back, problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The brutal truth? They spent 240 minutes debugging something that took 5 minutes to fix, all because they forgot to ask a 10-second question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Change Principle (It’s Not Rocket Science)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Production systems don’t just randomly decide to break on Tuesday afternoon. Something always changes first. Always.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The change usually falls into one of four buckets:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Code: deployments, feature flags, that “quick fix” someone pushed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Infrastructure: server upgrades, network changes, scaling operations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Configuration: environment variables, that toggle, you flipped “just to test”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Traffic: load spikes, geographic shifts, bot attacks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you accept this reality, debugging becomes less about technical wizardry and more about detective work. Good detectives don’t start by analyzing the murder weapon—they start with “who was here when it happened?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Revert Rebellion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s where I lose most engineers: your first instinct shouldn’t be to understand the problem. It should be to undo whatever caused it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This goes against everything we’re taught. Engineers love understanding root causes. We want to learn, to fix things properly, to write post-mortems that impress people with our technical depth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But production users don’t care about your learning journey. They care about working software.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The certificate pinning incident I mentioned? Operations had rotated SSL certificates overnight. The mobile app couldn’t connect because it was checking for the old certificate fingerprint. Web browsers worked fine because they don’t do certificate pinning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The “proper” debugging approach: dive into TLS handshake logs, analyze certificate validation failures, and understand the cryptographic details of pinning implementations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first-principle approach: “What changed? Oh, certificates. Let’s roll back.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One took six hours. The other took six minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Exotic Bug Fallacy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every engineer has a favorite theory about why their system is broken. Usually, it involves something impressive-sounding:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“It might be a race condition in our distributed cache.” “Could be a memory leak in the JVM garbage collector.” “I bet it’s that new Kubernetes version causing networking issues.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s the uncomfortable truth: 95% of production issues are caused by boring, obvious changes that you made recently. The remaining 5% are caused by boring, obvious changes that someone else made recently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your code is almost certainly the problem. Your recent deployment is almost certainly the problem. That configuration change you made this morning is almost certainly the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Exotic platform bugs make great conference talks, but they’re terrible debugging hypotheses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Debug Stack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When something breaks, work through this hierarchy:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What did I deploy recently?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What infrastructure changed?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What configuration changed?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What external dependencies changed?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is there a platform bug?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most issues resolve at level 1 or 2. If you’re investigating level 5 before exhausting levels 1-4, you’re debugging in hard mode for no reason.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Meta Problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After years of watching engineers debug in circles, I realized the real problem isn’t technical complexity. It changes visibility.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When production breaks, teams shouldn’t have to play “did anyone deploy anything?” detective. They shouldn’t have to dig through multiple repositories, chat histories, and change management systems to build a timeline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This insight sparked our current product, which has unified change management as a core principle that captures everything: &lt;em&gt;code, infrastructure, and configuration&lt;/em&gt; in one timeline. When alerts fire, the ‘what changed?’ question has an immediate answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next time your production system decides to have a bad day, resist every instinct to dive deep. Take a breath. Ask the right question: “What changed?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then fix it first, and understand it later.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your users will thank you. Your sleep schedule will thank you. And your ego might take a small hit, but that’s probably good for you anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;上个月，我看着三位高级工程师燃烧了四个小时，调试了一个“神秘的”库伯内特问题，结果证明是Kubectl版本的升级。同一周，当证书轮换折断的移动客户端时，另一个团队整夜狩猎幻影负载均衡器错误。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些不是关于无能的工程师的故事。这些故事是关于聪明的人陷入抓住每个人的认知陷阱的故事：深入深处而不是看起来很广泛。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;没有人问&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;的问题&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是Kubectl灾难发生的事情。症状看上去很严重：Cron作业失败，秘密不会在命名空间上更新，图像左右拉动。经典分布式系统混乱，对吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;团队立即进入完整的法医模式。 POD日志。 RBAC许可。服务帐户配置。网络政策。容器注册表连接。他们甚至开始质疑某人是否妥协了他们的基础设施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;四个小时后，一位疲惫的工程师终于问了一个明显的问题：“等等，我们最近更改了什么吗？” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;稍后，他们发现了吸烟枪：那天早些时候的kubectl版本。新版本处理秘密类型的处理方式不同。五分钟回头，解决问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;残酷的真相？他们花了240分钟调试一些需要5分钟的时间来修复的东西，这一切都是因为他们忘了提出10秒的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;变化原理（不是火箭科学）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;生产系统不仅决定在星期二下午随机休息。某事总是首先改变。总是。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更改通常落入四个存储桶之一：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;代码：部署，功能标志，“快速修复”某人推了&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;基础架构：服务器升级，网络更改，缩放操作&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;配置：环境变量，切换，您翻转“只是测试” &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;流量：负载尖峰，地理班次，机器人攻击&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦您接受了这一现实，调试就会变得越来越涉及技术巫术，而更多地涉及侦探工作。好的侦探不是从分析谋杀武器开始的，他们从“发生的时候在这里？” &lt;/p&gt;开始&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;恢复叛乱&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是我失去大多数工程师的地方：您的第一个本能不应该理解问题。应该撤消任何造成的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这违背了我们所教的一切。工程师喜欢理解根本原因。我们想学习，正确修复事情，写验尸，以我们的技术深度打动人们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是生产用户不在乎您的学习旅程。他们关心工作软件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我提到的证书固定事件？运营已旋转了SSL证书过夜。移动应用无法连接，因为它正在检查旧的证书指纹。 Web浏览器工作正常，因为它们没有固定证书。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“正确”调试方法：潜入TLS握手日志，分析证书验证失败并了解固定实现的加密细节。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第一原理方法：“什么变化了？哦，证书。让我们回滚。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个小时花了六个小时。另一个花了六分钟。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个工程师都有一个喜欢的理论，说明为什么他们的系统被打破了。通常，它涉及一些令人印象深刻的东西：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“这可能是我们分布式缓存中的种族条件。” “可能是JVM垃圾收集器中的记忆泄漏。” “我敢打赌，这是新的kubernetes版本引起了网络问题。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是令人不安的事实：95％的生产问题是由于您最近做出的无聊，明显的变化而引起的。其余的5％是由于最近有人做出的无聊，明显的变化引起的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您的代码几乎可以肯定是问题所在。您最近的部署几乎可以肯定是问题所在。您今天早上进行的这种配置更改几乎可以肯定是问题所在。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;异国情调的平台错误进行了很棒的会议演讲，但它们是可怕的调试假设。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; debug stack &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当某件事破裂时，通过此层次结构进行工作：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我最近部署了什么？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;哪些基础架构发生了变化？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;哪种配置更改？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;哪些外部依赖性发生了变化？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;是否有平台错误？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大多数问题在第1级或2级解决。如果您在耗尽1-4级之前正在调查5级，则无缘无故地在硬模式下进行调试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;元问题&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;经过多年的观看工程师的调试，我意识到真正的问题不是技术复杂性。它改变了可见性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当生产中断时，团队不必玩“有人部署任何东西吗？”侦探。他们不必挖掘多个存储库，聊天历史记录和更改管理系统来构建时间表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种见解引发了我们当前的产品，该产品将统一的变更管理作为捕获所有内容的核心原则：&lt;em&gt;代码，基础架构和配置&lt;/em&gt;在一个时间轴中。当警报起火时，“什么变化？”问题立即得到答案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下次您的生产系统决定度过糟糕的一天时，可以抵制每一个本能深入研究。屏住呼吸。问正确的问题：“发生了什么变化？” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后首先修复并理解后来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您的用户会感谢您。您的睡眠时间表将感谢您。而且您的自我可能会受到很小的打击，但无论如何可能对您有好处。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>