<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://rsshub.rssforever.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 co-located event deep dive: Platform Engineering Day】KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 同期举办活动深入探讨：平台工程日</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/16/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2024-co-located-event-deep-dive-platform-engineering-day/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXf4P2KhN7jEKTmyfmu7p7xaXGHxoBRhkNgnJCuSFWm6osC8Zk8sb9Tickm9FwpdUq4VC_l97G7alcXwwcwmRMWGzVUw-Z486X9BB3a3tSkiW7vm_pR2yJBe5WdHcWMczsfAgGXWGH88tdmHsig_zBWfq5t-?key=YgCPyq-ufT8eEW7sXCYIxw&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Co-chairs: Paula Kennedy, Stacey Potter, Vijay Chintha&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;November 12, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Salt Lake City, Utah&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/platform-engineering-day/&#34;&gt;Platform Engineering Day&lt;/a&gt; focuses on solutions over tooling. We believe that Platform Engineering is a vital practice that helps organizations to increase their speed and efficiency of delivering software. The focus for the day will be to look at the challenges that teams are tackling and sharing use cases and advice from practitioners and consultants that will give attendees practical takeaways. This is the second time we’ve had a Platform Engineering Day; the first time was at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who will get the most out of attending this event?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This will be relevant for any engineers working in DevOps, Platform Teams, SRE teams or any team that is providing services or tooling to another team. There will also be key ideas and suggestions that will be useful for those working in infrastructure or operations teams, and for decision makers looking to understand how to solve bottlenecks within their organization caused by internal tech debt and platform sprawl.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is new and different this year?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have packed in even more amazing content than we had at Paris so it is going to be a fantastic day for learning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will the day look like?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The event is a full day, single track event that has a mixture of keynotes, lightning talks, breakout sessions and panels. We’ll kick off with an update from the CNCF Platforms Working Group (part of the TAG App delivery) and from then it will be an agenda packed with awesome stories.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Submitted by Paula Kennedy, who is looking forward to catching up with old friends and making new ones.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/register/&#34;&gt;Don’t forget to register&lt;/a&gt; for KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024.&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXf4P2KhN7jEKTmyfmu7p7xaXGHxoBRhkNgnJCuSFWm6osC8Zk8sb9Tickm9FwpdUq4VC_l97G7alcXwwcwmRMWGzVUw- Z486X9BB3a3tSkiW7vm_pR2yJBe5WdHcWMczsfAgGXWGH88tdmHsig_zBWfq5t-?key=YgCPyq-ufT8eEW7sXCYIxw&#34; alt=&#34;图片&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;联合主席：Paula Kennedy、Stacey Potter、Vijay Chintha&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2024 年 11 月 12 日&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;犹他州盐湖城&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co- located-events/platform-engineering-day/&#34;&gt;平台工程日&lt;/a&gt;重点关注解决方案超过工具。我们相信平台工程是帮助组织提高软件交付速度和效率的重要实践。当天的重点将是关注团队正在应对的挑战，并分享从业者和顾问的用例和建议，为与会者提供实用的收获。这是我们第二次举办平台工程日；第一次是在 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2024 上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;谁将从参加本次活动中获益最多？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这对于在 DevOps、平台团队、SRE 团队或任何向其他团队提供服务或工具的团队中工作的工程师都相关。此外，还将提供一些关键想法和建议，对于基础设施或运营团队的工作人员以及希望了解如何解决组织内因内部技术债务和平台扩张造成的瓶颈的决策者有用。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;今年有什么新的和不同的？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们提供了比巴黎更精彩的内容，因此这将是学习的美好一天。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;这一天会是什么样子？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该活动是一整天的单轨活动，包括主题演讲、闪电演讲、分组会议和小组讨论。我们将从 CNCF 平台工作组的更新（TAG 应用程序交付的一部分）开始，从那时起，这将是一个充满精彩故事的议程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;由 Paula Kennedy 提交，她期待与老朋友见面并结交新朋友。 &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/register/&#34;&gt;不要忘记注册&lt;/a&gt;参加 2024 年 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 北美大会。&lt;em &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Keep up with cloud native and Kubernetes security with the updated CKS certification】通过更新的 CKS 认证跟上云原生和 Kubernetes 安全的步伐</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/17/keep-up-with-cloud-native-and-kubernetes-security-with-the-updated-cks-certification/</link>
      <description>【&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cks/&#34;&gt;CKS&lt;/a&gt; exam updated on October 15, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native and Kubernetes adoption is accelerating&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud native technology adoption continues to increase across all enterprises, with most new applications being built on cloud native platforms and, in particular, being built on Kubernetes. This is largely driven by the increasing maturity and trust in Kubernetes as a core cloud native technology, the de facto standard for managing cloud native environments. According to the 2023 CNCF Annual survey, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/cncf-annual-survey-2023/&#34;&gt;84% of the cloud native communit&lt;/a&gt;y is using or evaluating Kubernetes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At CNCF, we’re seeing a significant increase in new members, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/people/ambassadors/&#34;&gt;cloud native ambassadors&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/&#34;&gt;Kubestronauts&lt;/a&gt; who have passed all Kubernetes certifications, indicating strong community support. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/06/06/the-voice-of-kubernetes-experts-report-2024-the-data-trends-driving-the-future-of-the-enterprise/&#34;&gt;Those who run applications on Kubernetes are&lt;/a&gt; trusting it more than ever to host mission critical elements, like databases, real-time analytics, and AI/ML workloads. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/06/06/the-voice-of-kubernetes-experts-report-2024-the-data-trends-driving-the-future-of-the-enterprise/&#34;&gt;In a recent survey &lt;/a&gt;of organizations that have already adopted Kubernetes, 80% report they are planning to build most of their new applications on cloud native. This means that their cloud native data platforms need to be able to provide enterprise-grade capabilities for these applications to run efficiently and securely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, adopting a cloud-native approach can introduce new challenges, including security and skills gaps. Practicing good cloud security protects organizations from a variety of risks that can have severe financial, operational, legal, and reputational consequences. Proper cloud security measures are essential to safeguarding data, maintaining compliance, and ensuring the continuity of business operations. In the 2023 Annual CNCF survey, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/cncf-annual-survey-2023&#34;&gt;40% of organizations&lt;/a&gt; reported security as the leading challenge, but 46% say lack of training is the biggest challenge facing organizations that have not started, or are just beginning, their cloud native journey&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security certifications are crucial&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF is committed to growing the community of specialists knowledgeable in Kubernetes security to enable continued growth across organization and industries. Certification is a key step in that process, allowing certified security specialists to quickly establish their credibility and value in the job market, and also allowing companies to more quickly hire high-quality teams to support their growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud security certifications like CKS and KCSA are especially important for Kubernetes professionals in the current digital landscape, where cloud environments must be secure to protect data and maintain business processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Value of the Certified Kubernetes Security Specialist (CKS)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cks/&#34;&gt;Certified Kubernetes Security Specialist (CKS) &lt;/a&gt;certification, created by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), in collaboration with &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/&#34;&gt;Linux Foundation Education&lt;/a&gt; and subject matter experts, is considered one of the most valuable certifications in the DevOps space because it’s a hands-on, performance-based certification exam that tests candidates’ knowledge of Kubernetes and cloud security in a simulated, real world environment. CKS certification also provides these benefits:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Validation of Demonstrated Expertise&lt;/strong&gt;: CKS certification proves that an individual has a deep understanding of Kubernetes security, including the ability to secure container-based applications and Kubernetes platforms during build, deployment, and runtime.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry Recognition:&lt;/strong&gt; As Kubernetes continues to be a leading platform for container orchestration, having a CKS certification is recognized by employers and peers as a mark of expertise in Kubernetes security, which is critical for roles involving cloud-native infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Career Advancement and Opportunities:&lt;/strong&gt; With the increasing importance of security in software development and operations, professionals with CKS certification are well-positioned for roles such as DevSecOps engineers, cloud security architects, and Kubernetes administrators, leading to better job opportunities and career growth.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Staying Current with Security Trends and &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evolving Threats&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; The CKS exam requires a solid understanding of the latest security tools and techniques for Kubernetes, helping professionals stay updated with evolving security challenges in the cloud-native space and are prepared to handle emerging risks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is changing in the CKS?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/cks-program-changes&#34;&gt;CKS exam was updated on October 15, 2024&lt;/a&gt;, to ensure that Certified Kubernetes Security Specialists have up-to-date skills and knowledge in securing Kubernetes and container-based applications. While the CKS domains (i.e. Cluster Setup, Cluster Hardening, etc.) will remain the same, there will be changes to competencies, including additions, deletions, and updated language, as well as adjustments to the percentage weight of some domains. These updates align with the latest developments in Kubernetes and cloud security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Achieving your&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cka/&#34;&gt;Certified Kubernetes Administrator (CKA)&lt;/a&gt; is a prerequisite to registering and taking your CKS exam, although your CKA certification does not have to be active.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CKS certification is especially valuable for those looking to specialize in the security aspects of Kubernetes&amp;nbsp; – a critical area as container adoption continues to grow. As Kubernetes continues to dominate as the platform of choice for managing cloud-native applications, staying current with the latest security practices is essential. The upcoming changes to the CKS exam confirm that certified CKS IT professionals possess the most relevant skills and knowledge to protect container-based applications and allow the professionals to validate their expertise, as well as&amp;nbsp;enhance their career prospects, contributing to the overall security and success of cloud-native initiatives across industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cks/&#34;&gt;CKS&lt;/a&gt; 考试于 2024 年 10 月 15 日更新&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云原生和 Kubernetes 的采用正在加速&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云原生技术在所有企业中的采用持续增加，大多数新应用程序都是在云原生平台上构建的，特别是在 Kubernetes 上构建的。这主要是由于 Kubernetes 作为核心云原生技术（管理云原生环境的事实上的标准）的成熟度和信任度不断提高而推动的。根据 2023 年 CNCF 年度调查，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/cncf-annual-survey-2023/&#34;&gt;84% 的云原生社区&lt;/a&gt;正在使用或评估 Kubernetes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 CNCF，我们看到新成员、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/people/ambassadors/&#34;&gt;云原生大使&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/&#34;&gt;Kubestronauts&lt;/a&gt; 通过了所有 Kubernetes 认证，表明社区的大力支持。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/06/06/the-voice-of-kubernetes-experts-report-2024-the-data-trends-driven-the-future-of -the-enterprise/&#34;&gt;那些在 Kubernetes 上运行应用程序的人&lt;/a&gt;比以往任何时候都更加信任它能够托管数据库、实时分析和 AI/ML 工作负载等关键任务元素。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/06/06/the-voice-of-kubernetes-experts-report-2024-the-data-trends-driven-the-future-of -the-enterprise/&#34;&gt;最近对已采用 Kubernetes 的组织进行的一项调查&lt;/a&gt;显示，80% 的组织表示他们计划在云原生上构建大部分新应用程序。这意味着他们的云原生数据平台需要能够提供企业级功能，以便这些应用程序高效、安全地运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，采用云原生方法可能会带来新的挑战，包括安全性和技能差距。实施良好的云安全性可以保护组织免受各种风险的影响，这些风险可能会造成严重的财务、运营、法律和声誉后果。适当的云安全措施对于保护数据、保持合规性和确保业务运营的连续性至关重要。在 2023 年 CNCF 年度调查中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/cncf-annual-survey-2023&#34;&gt;40% 的组织&lt;/a&gt;将安全性视为主要挑战，但 46 % 表示缺乏培训是尚未开始或刚刚开始云原生之旅的组织面临的最大挑战&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安全认证至关重要&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF 致力于发展精通 Kubernetes 安全的专家社区，以实现跨组织和行业的持续增长。认证是该过程中的关键步骤，使经过认证的安全专家能够快速建立目标继承人在就业市场上的信誉和价值，也让企业能够更快地聘请高素质团队来支持其发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;像 CKS 和 KCSA 这样的云安全认证对于当前数字环境中的 Kubernetes 专业人员尤其重要，因为云环境必须安全才能保护数据和维护业务流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;认证 Kubernetes 安全专家 (CKS) 的价值&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cks/&#34;&gt;认证 Kubernetes 安全专家 (CKS)&lt;/a&gt; 认证，由云原生计算基金会 (CNCF) 创建与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/&#34;&gt;Linux 基础教育&lt;/a&gt; 和主题专家合作，被认为是 DevOps 领域最有价值的认证之一，因为它是一门实践性的认证基于绩效的认证考试，测试考生在模拟的真实环境中对 Kubernetes 和云安全的了解。 CKS 认证还具有以下优势：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;验证所展示的专业知识&lt;/strong&gt;：CKS 认证证明个人对 Kubernetes 安全性有深入的了解，包括在构建、部署和运行时保护基于容器的应用程序和 Kubernetes 平台的能力。&lt; /里&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;行业认可&lt;/strong&gt;：由于 Kubernetes 仍然是容器编排的领先平台，拥有 CKS 认证被雇主和同行认可为 Kubernetes 安全专业知识的标志，这对于涉及相关角色的角色至关重要云原生基础设施。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;职业发展和机会：&lt;/strong&gt;随着安全性在软件开发和运营中的重要性日益增加，拥有 CKS 认证的专业人员非常适合担任 DevSecOps 工程师、云安全架构师和 Kubernetes 管理员等角色，带来更好的工作机会和职业发展。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;跟上安全趋势和不断变化的威胁&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;：&lt;/strong&gt;CKS 考试要求对 Kubernetes 的最新安全工具和技术有深入的了解，帮助专业人士及时了解云原生领域不断变化的安全挑战，并准备好应对新出现的风险。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CKS 发生了什么变化？ &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/cks-program-changes&#34;&gt;CKS 考试于 2024 年 10 月 15 日更新&lt;/a&gt;，以确保经过认证的 Kubernetes 安全专家具备以下能力：确保 Kubernetes 和基于容器的应用程序安全的最新技能和知识。虽然 CKS 域（即集群设置、集群强化等）将保持不变，但能力会发生变化，包括添加、删除等过时的语言，以及对某些域的百分比权重的调整。这些更新与 Kubernetes 和云安全的最新发展保持一致。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;获得&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cka/&#34;&gt;认证 Kubernetes 管理员 (CKA)&lt;/a&gt; 是注册和参加 CKS 考试的先决条件，不过您的 CKA 认证不必处于活动状态。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CKS 认证对于那些希望专注于 Kubernetes 安全方面的人来说尤其有价值——随着容器采用率的不断增长，这是一个关键领域。随着 Kubernetes 作为管理云原生应用程序的首选平台继续占据主导地位，保持最新的安全实践至关重要。 CKS 考试即将发生的变化证实，经过认证的 CKS IT 专业人员拥有保护基于容器的应用程序最相关的技能和知识，并允许专业人员验证他们的专业知识，并增强他们的职业前景，为整体安全和成功做出贡献跨行业的云原生计划。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Open collaboration to bring AI Gateway features to the Envoy community】开放合作将 AI Gateway 功能引入 Envoy 社区</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/18/open-collaboration-to-bring-ai-gateway-features-to-the-envoy-community/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/blog/tetrate-bloomberg-collaborating-on-envoy-ai-gateway/&#34;&gt;Tetrate’s blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The industry is embracing Generative AI functionality, and we need to evolve how we handle traffic on an industry-wide scale. Keeping AI traffic handling features exclusive to enterprise licenses is counterproductive to the industry’s needs. This approach limits incentives to a single commercial entity and its customers. Even single-company open-source initiatives do not promote open multi-company collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A shared challenge like this presents an opportunity for open collaboration to build the necessary features. We believe bringing together different use cases and requirements through open collaboration will lead to better solutions and accelerate innovation. The industry will benefit from diverse expertise and experiences by openly collaborating on software across companies and industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That is why Tetrate and Bloomberg have started an open collaboration to bring critical features for this new era of Gen AI integration. Collaborating openly in the Envoy community, bringing AI traffic handling features to Envoy, via Envoy Gateway and Envoy Proxy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;h-why-we-need-ai-traffic-handling-features&#34;&gt;Why we need AI traffic handling features&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What makes traffic to LLM models different from traditional API traffic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the surface it appears similar. Traffic comes from a client app that is making an API request, and this request has to get to the provider that hosts the LLM model.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, it is different. Managing LLM traffic from multiple apps, to multiple LLM providers, introduces new and different challenges where traditional API Gateway features fall short.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/envoy-ai-gateway-managing-traffic.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://tetrate.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/envoy-ai-gateway-managing-traffic.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-54803&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, traditional rate-limiting based on number of requests doesn’t work for controlling usage of LLM providers as they’re computationally complex services. To measure usage LLM providers tokenize the words in the request message and response message, and count the number of tokens used. This count gives a good approximation of the computational complexity and cost of serving the request.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond controlling usage of LLMs there are many more challenges relating to ease of integration and high-availability architectures. It’s no longer enough to just optimize for quality of service alone, adopters must consider costs of usage in real time. As adopters of Gen AI look for Gateway solutions to handle these challenges for their system, they often find the necessary features locked behind enterprise licenses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;h-three-key-mvp-features&#34;&gt;Three key MVP features&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s look at how handling AI traffic poses new challenges for Gateways. There are several features we discussed together with our collaborators at Bloomberg, and together we decided on three key features for the MVP:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Usage Limiting&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;– to control LLM usage based on word tokens&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unified API&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;– to simplify client integration with multiple LLM providers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upstream Authorization&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;– to configure Authorization to multiple upstream LLM providers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What other features are you looking for?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/get-in-touch/&#34;&gt;Get in touch&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;with us to share your use case and define the future of Envoy AI Gateway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are really excited about these features being part of Envoy. They will benefit those integrating with LLM providers and, ultimately, also Gateway users for general API request traffic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to AI Gateway features, we have chosen to collaborate and build within the CNCF Envoy project because we believe multi-company, open-source projects benefit the entire industry by enabling innovation without creating single vendor risk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;h-how-do-i-learn-more&#34;&gt;How do I learn more?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Via our Newsletter:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/join-our-mailing-list/&#34;&gt;Sign up to our mailing list to stay updated.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attend Online CNCF Panel Event:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;To learn more about integrating AI in the enterprise, attend the live CNCF-hosted event&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/events/details/cncf-cncf-online-programs-presents-cloud-native-live-enabling-ai-adoption-at-scale-the-ai-platform/&#34;&gt;“Enabling AI adoption at scale – The AI Platform with Envoy AI Gateway”&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;on October 17th with panelists from Tetrate and Bloomberg. You will be able to ask questions and interact with the panel live.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See a demo at Tetrate booth at KubeCon NA:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Visit Tetrate at booth #Q2 at KubeCon NA for a demo to see a demo and talk to engineers working on the AI traffic handling features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;has-text-align-center&#34;&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to service mesh, Tetrate has a bunch of free online courses&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetr8.io/academy&#34;&gt;available at Tetrate Academy&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;that will quickly get you up to speed with Istio and Envoy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are you using Kubernetes?&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/tetrate-enterprise-gateway-for-envoy/&#34;&gt;Tetrate Enterprise Gateway for Envoy (TEG)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;is the easiest way to get started with Envoy Gateway for production use cases. Get the power of Envoy Proxy in an easy-to-consume package managed by the Kubernetes Gateway API.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/tetrate-enterprise-gateway-for-envoy/&#34;&gt;Learn more ›&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/tetrate-istio-subscription/get-started/&#34;&gt;Getting started with Istio?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;If you’re looking for the surest way to get to production with Istio, check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetr8.io/tid&#34;&gt;Tetrate Istio Subscription&lt;/a&gt;. Tetrate Istio Subscription has everything you need to run Istio and Envoy in highly regulated and mission-critical production environments. It includes&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.tetrate.io/istio-distro/&#34;&gt;Tetrate Istio Distro&lt;/a&gt;, a 100% upstream distribution of Istio and Envoy that is FIPS-verified and FedRAMP ready. For teams requiring open source Istio and Envoy without proprietary vendor dependencies, Tetrate offers the ONLY 100% upstream Istio enterprise support offering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初发布于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/blog/tetrate-bloomberg-collaborating-on-envoy-ai-gateway/&#34;&gt;Tetrate 博客&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/嗯&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;行业正在拥抱生成式 AI 功能，我们需要改进在全行业范围内处理流量的方式。将人工智能流量处理功能保留为企业许可证独有，这与行业的需求适得其反。这种方法限制了对单个商业实体及其客户的激励。即使是单一公司的开源计划也无法促进开放的多公司协作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;像这样的共同挑战为开放协作提供了构建必要功能的机会。我们相信，通过开放协作将不同的用例和需求结合在一起将带来更好的解决方案并加速创新。通过跨公司和行业的软件公开合作，该行业将受益于多样化的专业知识和经验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是为什么 Tetrate 和 Bloomberg 开始开放合作，为 Gen AI 集成的新时代带来关键功能。在 Envoy 社区中公开合作，通过 Envoy 网关和 Envoy 代理为 Envoy 带来 AI 流量处理功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;h-why-we-need-ai-traffic-handling-features&#34;&gt;为什么我们需要人工智能流量处理功能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LLM 模型的流量与传统 API 流量有何不同？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;表面上看起来很相似。流量来自发出 API 请求的客户端应用，该请求必须到达托管 LLM 模型的提供商。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，情况有所不同。管理从多个应用程序到多个 LLM 提供商的 LLM 流量，会带来传统 API 网关功能无法满足的新的不同挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/envoy-ai-gateway-managing-traffic.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=“async”src=“https://tetrate.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/envoy-ai-gateway-managing-traffic.jpg”alt=“图像”class=“wp-image-” 54803&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，基于请求数量的传统速率限制无法控制 LLM 提供商的使用，因为它们是计算复杂的服务。为了衡量使用情况，LLM 提供商对请求消息和响应消息中的单词进行标记，并计算所使用的标记数量。该计数很好地近似了计算复杂性和服务请求的成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了控制 LLM 的使用之外，还存在许多与易于集成和高可用性架构相关的挑战。仅仅优化服务质量已经不够了，采用者必须实时考虑使用成本。当 Gen AI 的采用者寻找网关解决方案来应对其系统的这些挑战时，他们经常发现企业应用程序背后隐藏着必要的功能。香火。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;h- Three-key-mvp-features&#34;&gt;三个关键 MVP 功能&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，让我们看看处理人工智能流量如何给网关带来新的挑战。我们与 Bloomberg 的合作者一起讨论了几个功能，并共同确定了 MVP 的三个关键功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用限制&lt;/strong&gt; – 根据单词标记控制 LLM 使用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;统一 API&lt;/strong&gt; – 简化客户与多个 LLM 提供商的集成&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;上游授权&lt;/strong&gt; – 配置对多个上游 LLM 提供商的授权&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您还需要哪些其他功能？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/get-in-touch/&#34;&gt;联系&lt;/a&gt;与我们分享您的用例并定义 Envoy AI Gateway 的未来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们对这些功能成为 Envoy 的一部分感到非常兴奋。它们将使那些与 LLM 提供商集成的人受益，并最终使一般 API 请求流量的网关用户受益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 AI 网关功能方面，我们选择在 CNCF Envoy 项目内进行协作和构建，因为我们相信多公司开源项目可以通过实现创新而不会产生单一供应商风险，从而使整个行业受益。&lt;/p &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;h-how-do-i-learn-more&#34;&gt;我如何了解更多信息？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;通过我们的新闻通讯：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/join-our-mailing-list/&#34;&gt;注册我们的邮件列表以了解最新动态。&lt;/a &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;参加在线 CNCF 小组活动：&lt;/strong&gt;要了解有关在企业中集成 AI 的更多信息，请参加 CNCF 主办的现场活动&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/events/详细信息/cncf-cncf-online-programs-presents-cloud-native-live-enabling-ai-adoption-at-scale-the-ai-platform/&#34;&gt;“实现人工智能大规模采用——采用 Envoy AI Gateway 的人工智能平台”&lt;/a&gt; 10 月 17 日，与来自 Tetrate 和 Bloomberg 的小组成员一起。您将能够提出问题并与小组现场互动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在 KubeCon NA 的 Tetrate 展位观看演示&lt;/strong&gt;：访问 KubeCon NA 的 #Q2 展位的 Tetrate 进行演示，观看演示并与从事 AI 流量处理功能的工程师交谈。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;has-text-align-center&#34;&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您是服务网格新手，Tetrate 提供了一系列免费在线课程&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetr8.io/academy&#34;&gt;Tetrate Academy 提供&lt;/a&gt;，可帮助您快速入门与 Istio 和 Envoy 一起加速。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您是否使用 Kubernetes？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/tetrate-enterprise-gateway-for-envoy/&#34;&gt;Tetrate Enterprise Gateway for Envoy (TEG)&lt;/ a&gt; 是开始使用 Envoy Gateway 进行生产用例的最简单方法。在由 Kubernetes Gateway API 管理的易于使用的包中获取 Envoy Proxy 的强大功能。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/tetrate-enterprise-gateway-for-envoy/&#34;&gt;了解更多信息 ›&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tetrate.io/tetrate-istio-subscription/get-started/&#34;&gt;开始使用 Istio？&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;如果您正在寻找使用 Istio 进行生产的最可靠方法，请查看 &lt;a href=&#34;https://tetr8.io/tid&#34;&gt;Tetrate Istio 订阅&lt;/a&gt;。 Tetrate Istio 订阅拥有在高度监管和任务关键型生产环境中运行 Istio 和 Envoy 所需的一切。它包括 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.tetrate.io/istio-distro/&#34;&gt;Tetrate Istio Distro&lt;/a&gt;，这是 Istio 和 Envoy 的 100% 上游发行版，经过 FIPS 验证并支持 FedRAMP。对于需要开源 Istio 和 Envoy 而无需专有供应商依赖的团队，Tetrate 提供唯一 100% 上游 Istio 企业支持产品。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MicroK8s and ngrok: easy ingress at the edge】MicroK8s 和 ngrok：轻松进入边缘</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/16/microk8s-and-ngrok-easy-ingress-at-the-edge/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress&#34;&gt;ngrok’s blog&lt;/a&gt; by Mike Coleman&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/categories/kubernetes&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MicroK8s is a lightweight, efficient, and easy-to-use Kubernetes distribution that enables users to deploy and manage containerized applications. ngrok, on the other hand, provides a secure and scalable universal gateway that enables secure access to your workloads regardless of where they are hosted.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both MicroK8s and ngrok excel in the arena of edge computing. This blog post examines how leveraging MicroK8s alongside ngrok can simplify and accelerate edge computing use cases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-microk8s&#34;&gt;What is MicroK8s?&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress#what-is-microk8s&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MicroK8s is a lightweight Kubernetes distribution from Canonical. MicroK8s is&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://microk8s.io/docs/getting-started&#34;&gt;extremely simple to set up&lt;/a&gt;. According to the documentation, it can be up and running in as little as 60 seconds. Additionally, it’s optimized to run in low-resource environments requiring as little as 540MB RAM; however, 4G of RAM is recommended for running actual workloads. Because of its low overhead, MicroK8s is especially well suited to operating on edge compute devices, including point-of-sale systems, controllers, and lightweight hardware.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite its ability to run in low-resource environments, MicroK8s is a full-featured Kubernetes distribution. It provides several advanced features, such as GPU support, automated HA configurations, and strict confinement to provide additional isolation between workloads and the underlying resources they run on.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-ngrok&#34;&gt;What is ngrok?&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress#what-is-ngrok&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ngrok is a unified ingress platform that provides access to workloads running across a wide variety of infrastructure. By combining a lightweight agent with a powerful global network, ngrok makes it extremely easy to bring workloads online, including APIs, services, devices, and applications. With ngrok, you get a single platform that can replace multiple disjointed services, including reverse proxy, API gateway, firewall, and global load balancer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By automating and standardizing network access, ngrok simplifies providing edge access to edge computing workloads. Specific to MicroK8s ngrok features a&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/use-cases/kubernetes-operator&#34;&gt;Kubernetes operator&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;that can provide access to cluster-based workloads. The ngrok Kubernetes operator provides both a traditional&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/docs/using-ngrok-with/k8s/&#34;&gt;ingress controller&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;as well as a&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/introducing-support-for-kubernetes-gateway-api-in-ngrok-kubernetes-operator&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;gateway API&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;implementation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://cdn.prod.website-files.com/63ed707844acb1ccf1ccb700/66a2b81a6aad9e328dca1ed2_66a2b7d1319b4e379c15d50e_image1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MicroK8s and ngrok are powerful combinations for hosting and accessing edge-based workloads, but what makes those workloads challenging to manage?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;how-can-microk8s-and-ngrok-help-with-edge-computing&#34;&gt;How can MicroK8s and ngrok help with edge computing?&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress#how-can-microk8s-and-ngrok-help-with-edge-computing&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge computing presents several challenges, including managing and orchestrating distributed infrastructure, ensuring security and data privacy, and addressing variability in network connectivity and latency. Additionally, edge computing environments often require specialized hardware and software, which can be costly and difficult to maintain. Furthermore, edge applications require low-latency processing and real-time decision-making, making it essential to optimize performance and minimize downtime. Moreover, the edge ecosystem is highly fragmented, with diverse technologies and standards, making interoperability a significant challenge. Finally, edge computing also raises concerns about data management, including data processing, storage, and analytics, which must be addressed to unlock the full potential of edge computing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As mentioned before, MicroK8s is a full-featured, lightweight Kubernetes distribution. This combination allows MicroK8s to run on edge devices while handling intensive workloads such as AI inference and data analytics. By having MicroK8s deployed at the edge, latency can be greatly reduced. An additional benefit is reducing the unnecessary flow of data, which helps to provide additional layers of security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With MicroK8s handling the processing duties, ngrok can focus on managing access to the running workloads. In traditional environments, a mishmash of hardware and software provides access to running workloads. This results in a high amount of friction in deploying and managing access and security concerns.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://cdn.prod.website-files.com/63ed707844acb1ccf1ccb700/66a2b81a6aad9e328dca1ece_66a2b7ea52b9d03ca4b18832_image3.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ngrok provides a standardized platform that removes the complexity of providing access to edge-based workloads. ngrok standardizes connectivity into external networks hosting IoT devices without requiring support from partners or changes to their network configurations. ngrok does all this while working with any operating system or platform. Additionally, ngrok supports security policies to ensure compliance with necessary security requirements. Finally, ngrok’s global network helps guard against networking failures by providing multiple points of presence with automated failover.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://cdn.prod.website-files.com/63ed707844acb1ccf1ccb700/66a2b81a6aad9e328dca1ec6_66a2b7b4e12871762b0f29ef_image2.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-else-can-you-do-with-microk8s-and-ngrok&#34;&gt;What else can you do with MicroK8s and ngrok?&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress#what-else-can-you-do-with-microk8s-and-ngrok&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to edge computing, MicroK8s, ngrok, and the ngrok Kubernetes Operator can be combined to enable other use cases, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Secure access to development services for remote teams&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scalable and secure API gateways for cloud-native applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Secure exposure of services for testing and debugging purposes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, deploying and managing edge computing workloads can be challenging. However, by leveraging ngrok, our Kubernetes Operator, and MicroK8s these issues can be greatly reduced. Getting started is simple ngrok has a generous free tier (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dashboard.ngrok.com/signup&#34;&gt;sign up here&lt;/a&gt;!), and you can follow our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/docs/integrations/microk8s/k8s/&#34;&gt;ngrok and MicroK8s integration guide&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;to get started today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初由 Mike Coleman 发布在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress&#34;&gt;ngrok 的博客&lt;/a&gt;上&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/categories/kubernetes&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MicroK8s 是一个轻量级、高效且易于使用的 Kubernetes 发行版，使用户能够部署和管理容器化应用程序。另一方面，ngrok 提供了一个安全且可扩展的通用网关，可以安全地访问您的工作负载，无论它们托管在何处。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MicroK8s 和 ngrok 在边缘计算领域都表现出色。这篇博文探讨了如何利用 MicroK8s 和 ngrok 来简化和加速边缘计算用例。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-microk8s&#34;&gt;什么是 MicroK8s？&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress#what- is-microk8s&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MicroK8s 是 Canonical 推出的轻量级 Kubernetes 发行版。 MicroK8s &lt;a href=&#34;https://microk8s.io/docs/getting-started&#34;&gt;设置极其简单&lt;/a&gt;。根据文档，它可以在短短 60 秒内启动并运行。此外，它还经过优化，可在低资源环境中运行，只需 540MB RAM；但是，建议使用 4G RAM 来运行实际工作负载。由于开销较低，MicroK8s 特别适合在边缘计算设备上运行，包括销售点系统、控制器和轻量级硬件。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管 MicroK8s 能够在资源匮乏的环境中运行，但它是一个功能齐全的 Kubernetes 发行版。它提供了多种高级功能，例如 GPU 支持、自动化 HA 配置以及严格限制，以在工作负载与其运行的底层资源之间提供额外的隔离。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-ngrok&#34;&gt;什么是 ngrok？&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress#what- is-ngrok&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ngrok 是一个统一的入口平台，可提供对跨各种基础设施运行的工作负载的访问。通过将轻量级代理与强大的全球网络相结合，ngrok 使工作负载（包括 API、服务、设备和应用程序）在线变得极其容易。借助 ngrok，您可以获得一个可以替换多个脱节服务的单一平台，包括反向代理、API 网关、防火墙和全局负载均衡器。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过自动化和标准化网络访问，ngrok 简化了对边缘计算工作负载的边缘访问。特定于 MicroK8s 的 ngrok 具有 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/use-cases/kubernetes-operator&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 运算符&lt;/a&gt;，可以提供对基于集群的工作负载的访问。 ngrok Kubernetes Operator 提供传统的&lt;a href=&#34;https://ngrok.com/docs/using-ngrok-with/k8s/&#34;&gt;入口控制器&lt;/a&gt;以及&lt;a href=&#34;https: //ngrok.com/blog-post/introducing-support-for-kubernetes-gateway-api-in-ngrok-kubernetes-operator&#34;&gt;网关 API&lt;/a&gt; 实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://cdn.prod.website-files.com/63ed707844acb1ccf1ccb700/66a2b81a6aad9e328dca1ed2_66a2b7d1319b4e379c15d50e_image1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;无推荐人&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MicroK8s 和 ngrok 是托管和访问基于边缘的工作负载的强大组合，但是什么让这些工作负载难以管理？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;how-can-microk8s-and-ngrok-help-with-edge-computing&#34;&gt;MicroK8s 和 ngrok 如何帮助边缘计算？&lt;a href=&#34;https: //ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress#how-can-microk8s-and-ngrok-help-with-edge-computing&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;边缘计算带来了多项挑战，包括管理和编排分布式基础设施、确保安全和数据隐私，以及解决网络连接和延迟的可变性。此外，边缘计算环境通常需要专门的硬件和软件，这可能成本高昂且难以维护。此外，边缘应用程序需要低延迟处理和实时决策，因此优化性能和最大限度地减少停机时间至关重要。此外，边缘生态系统高度分散，技术和标准多种多样，使得互操作性成为重大挑战。最后，边缘计算还引起了人们对数据管理的担忧，包括数据处理、存储和分析，必须解决这些问题才能释放边缘计算的全部潜力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如前所述，MicroK8s 是一个功能齐全的轻量级 Kubernetes 发行版。这种组合允许 MicroK8 在边缘设备上运行，同时处理 AI 推理和数据分析等密集型工作负载。通过在边缘部署 MicroK8，可以大大减少延迟。另一个好处是减少不必要的数据流，这有助于提供额外的安全层。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过 MicroK8 处理处理任务，ngrok 可以专注于管理对正在运行的工作负载的访问。在传统环境中，硬件和软件的混合提供了对正在运行的工作负载的访问。这会导致部署和管理访问时出现大量摩擦和安全问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://cdn.prod.website-files.com/63ed707844acb1ccf1ccb700/66a2b81a6aad9e328dca1ece_66a2b7ea52b9d03ca4b18832_image3.png&#34; alt=&#34;图片&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;无推荐人&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ngrok 提供了一个标准化平台，消除了提供对基于边缘的工作负载的访问的复杂性。 ngrok 标准化了与托管 IoT 设备的外部网络的连接，无需合作伙伴的支持或更改其网络配置。 ngrok 在使用任何操作系统或平台时都可以完成所有这些工作。此外，ngrok 支持安全策略以确保合规性h 必要的安全要求。最后，ngrok 的全球网络通过提供具有自动故障转移功能的多个存在点来帮助防止网络故障。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://cdn.prod.website-files.com/63ed707844acb1ccf1ccb700/66a2b81a6aad9e328dca1ec6_66a2b7b4e12871762b0f29ef_image2.png&#34; alt=&#34;图片&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;无推荐人&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-else-can-you-do-with-microk8s-and-ngrok&#34;&gt;使用 MicroK8s 和 ngrok 还能做什么？&lt;a href=&#34;https: //ngrok.com/blog-post/microk8s-kubernetes-ingress#what-else-can-you-do-with-microk8s-and-ngrok&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了边缘计算之外，MicroK8s、ngrok 和 ngrok Kubernetes Operator 还可以组合起来以支持其他用例，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;远程团队安全地访问开发服务&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;适用于云原生应用的可扩展且安全的 API 网关&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;出于测试和调试目的安全公开服务&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终，部署和管理边缘计算工作负载可能具有挑战性。然而，通过利用 ngrok、我们的 Kubernetes Operator 和 MicroK8s，这些问题可以大大减少。入门很简单 ngrok 拥有丰富的免费套餐（&lt;a href=&#34;https://dashboard.ngrok.com/signup&#34;&gt;在此注册&lt;/a&gt;！），您可以关注我们的&lt;a href=&#34;https ://ngrok.com/docs/integrations/microk8s/k8s/&#34;&gt;ngrok 和 MicroK8s 集成指南&lt;/a&gt;立即开始。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tips for first-time visitors to Salt Lake City for #KubeCon + #CloudNativeCon】给首次访问盐湖城的游客 #KubeCon + #CloudNativeCon 的提示</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/18/tips-for-first-time-visitors-to-salt-lake-city-for-kubecon-cloudnativecon/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Community post by Dan Garfield&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the very first time, &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America&lt;/a&gt; is traveling to where I live! Hi, my name is Dan Garfield, I’m an Argo Maintainer for Codefresh and Octopus Deploy residing in Salt Lake City. I wanted to share some quick tips for how to get the most out of your trip to Salt Lake City, Utah.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Getting Around&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Salt Lake City has both a light rail and bus system for getting around town, as well as a regional train system called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rideuta.com/Rider-Tools/Schedules-and-Maps/750-FrontRunner&#34;&gt;Front Runner&lt;/a&gt; that runs north (Ogden) to south (Provo). You can take a short train ride from the SLC Airport to downtown, or just grab an Uber, Lyft, or Taxi. If you plan to stay near the convention I don’t recommend renting a car because you’ll have to pay for parking and SLC is small enough that it’s not really worth it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Weather&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;November is a wildcard in Utah, it could be 70-80 degrees or it could be snowing. It’s not uncommon for snow to start falling in SLC in late-October but these are usually quick storms that melt right away. Bring warm clothing options with closed shoes in case it’s cold and snowy the week of KubeCon.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Adventures&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Adventures in Town&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Salt Lake City is known for its proximity to amazing outdoor experiences. We’ll talk about the best things close to town but if you want to stay in town I recommend hiking &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.alltrails.com/trail/us/utah/ensign-peak-trail-and-overlook&#34;&gt;Ensign Peak&lt;/a&gt;, it’s a bit steep but at less than a mile it’s very doable and you’ll be rewarded with a view of the entire Salt Lake Valley. For something more robust I recommend doing the Bonneville Shoreline trail, the entire trail is hundreds of miles but you can start up off &lt;a href=&#34;https://maps.app.goo.gl/y4WiYJ6BPYhyJzNA9&#34;&gt;18th Ave&lt;/a&gt; and hike 9 miles to the Hoogle Zoo. There are plenty of places to rent mountain bikes if you’d rather ride and you can ride the same trail. Iif you’re an expert (this is black diamond) you can do the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mtbproject.com/trail/967440/bobsled-via-bonneville-shoreline-trail&#34;&gt;Bobsled trail&lt;/a&gt; off the same trail as above.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re staying on foot, just across the street from the convention center is the City Creek Mall which runs through the heart of downtown and is a nice place to walk. Next to that is the world-famous Temple Square where you can catch the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thetabernaclechoir.org/?lang=eng&#34;&gt;Tabernacle Choir at Temple Square&lt;/a&gt;, one of the largest and oldest choirs in the world. Also, there are several free museums – I recommend checking out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.familysearch.org/en/library/&#34;&gt;Family Search Library&lt;/a&gt; where you can get tons of information about your ancestors for free.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are plenty of bars and restaurants downtown and I’m hesitant to recommend any specific one because 10,000 KubeCon attendees would undoubtedly completely overrun any particular place. Soda shops like Thirst, Swig, Crema, Sips, Sodalicious, and others are Utah phenomena where you can get fancy soda. A dirty soda from these shops usually means Coca-Cola with flavorings added. They’re not my thing but they’re quite popular.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the week of KubeCon there will be lots of sporting events, the Delta Center is literally across the street from the convention center. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deltacenter.com/events/utah-jazz-vs-phoenix-suns/&#34;&gt;Jazz vs the Suns&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deltacenter.com/events/utah-jazz-vs-dallas-mavericks/&#34;&gt;Jazz vs the Mavericks&lt;/a&gt;, and Utah’s new and yet unnamed Hockey team will be playing the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deltacenter.com/events/utah-hockey-club-vs-carolina-hurricanes/&#34;&gt;Hurricanes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deltacenter.com/events/utah-hockey-club-vs-vegas-golden-knights/&#34;&gt;Knights&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are also opportunities for service, my team is planning to spend some time after the conference at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.churchofjesuschrist.org/share/welfare-square-cannery?lang=eng&#34;&gt;Cannery on Welfare &lt;/a&gt;Square which sends food and aid worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Day Trips After KubeCon&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lots of people have asked if they’re going to be able to Ski, while it is possible, currently, Park City is planning the earliest opening at November 22. If you don’t mind hiking backcountry like &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/mjasay/status/1776977573735760078/video/1&#34;&gt;Matt Asay&lt;/a&gt; you will be able to find snow but if you don’t normally ski backcountry I would heavily discourage doing so without a local guide as it can be quite dangerous.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond skiing, there are tons of day trips the weekend after KubeCon that are easily done with a rental car or in some cases with a tour bus. In no particular order:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;See the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antelope_Island_bison_herd&#34;&gt;Bison at Antelope Island&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Swim at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.utahcrater.com/&#34;&gt;Homestead crater&lt;/a&gt; – great in any weather.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;See what infinite nothing looks like at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.utah.com/destinations/natural-areas/bonneville-salt-flats/&#34;&gt;Bonneville Salt Flats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;There are lots of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.utah.com/articles/post/top-10-waterfall-hikes-in-utah/&#34;&gt;waterfalls&lt;/a&gt; to go see and hike.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do the infinite hikes up &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.visitsaltlake.com/listing/big-cottonwood-canyon/55175/&#34;&gt;Big&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.visitsaltlake.com/listing/little-cottonwood-canyon/55176/&#34;&gt;Little Cottonwood &lt;/a&gt;Canyons.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If there is snow, there are lots of snowshoeing&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.parkcitymountain.com/travel-guide/snowshoe-hikes-in-park-city.aspx&#34;&gt; opportunities in Park City&lt;/a&gt; and elsewhere.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Get a tour of &lt;a href=&#34;https://utaholympiclegacy.org/location/utah-olympic-park/&#34;&gt;Olympic Park&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While early November in Utah may fall between the peak summer and winter activities, there are still plenty of great experiences to enjoy. Whether you’re exploring Salt Lake City or taking a scenic drive south to Zion, Escalante, or Moab, this guide will help you discover a variety of exciting options to make the most of your time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;丹·加菲尔德 (Dan Garfield) 的社区帖子&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/&#34;&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 北美&lt;/a&gt;第一次来到我住的地方！大家好，我叫 Dan Garfield，是 Codefresh 和 Octopus Deploy 的 Argo 维护者，居住在盐湖城。我想分享一些关于如何充分享受犹他州盐湖城之旅的快速提示。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;出行&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;盐湖城拥有用于游览城镇的轻轨和巴士系统，以及名为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rideuta.com/Rider-Tools/Schedules-and- 的区域火车系统Maps/750-FrontRunner&#34;&gt;Front Runner&lt;/a&gt;，从北（奥格登）到南（普罗沃）。您可以乘坐短途火车从 SLC 机场前往市中心，或者乘坐 Uber、Lyft 或出租车。如果您打算住在会展中心附近，我不建议您租车，因为您需要支付停车费，而且 SLC 太小，不太值得。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;天气&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;11 月在犹他州是一个不确定的天气，可能是 70-80 度，也可能会下雪。 10 月下旬，SLC 开始下雪的情况并不罕见，但这些通常是很快就会融化的风暴。请携带保暖衣物和封闭式鞋子，以防 KubeCon 周寒冷多雪。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;冒险&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;城镇冒险&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;盐湖城以其邻近的令人惊叹的户外体验而闻名。我们将讨论城镇附近最好的事情，但如果您想留在城镇里，我建议徒步旅行 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.alltrails.com/trail/us/utah/ensign-peak-trail-and -overlook&#34;&gt;Ensign Peak&lt;/a&gt;，有点陡峭，但不到一英里，非常容易到达，您将欣赏到整个盐湖谷的景色。如果想体验更刺激的活动，我建议走邦纳维尔海岸线步道，整条步道长达数百英里，但您可以从 &lt;a href=&#34;https://maps.app.goo.gl/y4WiYJ6BPYhyJzNA9&#34;&gt;18 大道&lt;/a 出发&gt; 徒步 9 英里到达胡格尔动物园。如果您愿意骑行，有很多地方可以租用山地自行车，并且可以沿着同一条路线骑行。如果您是专家（这是黑钻石），您可以走&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mtbproject.com/trail/967440/bobsled-via-bonneville-shoreline-trail&#34;&gt;雪橇路线&lt;/ a&gt; 走与上面相同的路线。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您步行，会议中心对面就是 City Creek Mall，它贯穿市中心，是散步的好地方。旁边是世界著名的圣殿广场，您可以在那里观看&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thetabernaclechoir.org/?lang=eng&#34;&gt;圣殿广场的圣幕唱诗班&lt;/a&gt;，这是最大的圣殿唱诗班之一和世界上最古老的合唱团。此外，还有几个免费博物馆 - 我建议您查看 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.familysearch.org/en/library/&#34;&gt;家族搜索库&lt;/a&gt;，您可以在其中免费获取有关您祖先的大量信息。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;市中心有很多酒吧和餐馆，我不太愿意推荐任何一家特定的酒吧和餐馆，因为 10,000 名 KubeCon 与会者无疑会完全淹没任何特定的地方。 Thirst、Swig、Crema、Sips、Sodalicious 等汽水店是犹他州的一大特色，在这里您可以买到精美的汽水。这些商店里的脏苏打水通常意味着添加了调味料的可口可乐。它们不是我的菜，但它们很受欢迎。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 KubeCon 一周期间，将会有很多体育赛事，三角洲中心就在会议中心的街对面。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deltacenter.com/events/utah-jazz-vs-phoenix-suns/&#34;&gt;爵士队对阵太阳队&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deltacenter .com/events/utah-jazz-vs-dallas-mavericks/&#34;&gt;爵士队对阵小牛队&lt;/a&gt;，犹他州新的尚未命名的曲棍球队将参加&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deltacenter .com/events/utah-hockey-club-vs-carolina-hurricanes/&#34;&gt;飓风&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.deltacenter.com/events/utah-hockey-club-vs-维加斯-黄金骑士/&#34;&gt;骑士&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;还有服务机会，我的团队计划在会议结束后在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.churchofjesuschrist.org/share/welfare-square-cannery?lang=eng&#34; &gt;福利罐头厂&lt;/a&gt;广场，向世界各地运送食物和援助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;KubeCon 后的一日游&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;很多人都问他们是否可以滑雪，虽然这是可能的，但目前 Park City 计划最早于 11 月 22 日开放。如果您不介意像 &lt;a href= “https://x.com/mjasay/status/1776977573735760078/video/1&#34;&gt;Matt Asay&lt;/a&gt; 您将能够找到雪，但如果您通常不滑雪偏远地区，我强烈建议您在没有滑雪设备的情况下这样做当地导游，因为这可能非常危险。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了滑雪之外，KubeCon 结束后的周末还有大量的一日游，可以通过租车或在某些情况下乘坐旅游巴士轻松完成。排名不分先后：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;参观&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antelope_Island_bison_herd&#34;&gt;羚羊岛的野牛&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.utahcrater.com/&#34;&gt;Homestead 火山口&lt;/a&gt;游泳 - 任何天气都适合。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.utah.com/destinations/natural-areas/bonneville-salt-flats/&#34;&gt;博纳维尔盐滩&lt;/a&gt;看看无限虚无的样子&lt;/li &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;有很多&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.utah.com/articles/post/top-10-waterfall-hikes-in-utah/&#34;&gt;瀑布&lt;/a&gt;可供观赏和徒步.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;无限次攀登&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.visitsaltlake.com/listing/big-cottonwood-canyon/55175/&#34;&gt;大&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href=&#34;https:// www.visitsaltlake.com/listing/little-cottonwood-canyon/55176/&#34;&gt;小三叶杨&lt;/a&gt;峡谷。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果下雪，就会有很多在帕克城和其他地方&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.parkcitymountain.com/travel-guide/snowshoe-hikes-in-park-city.aspx&#34;&gt;体验雪鞋行走&lt;/a&gt;的机会。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;参观&lt;a href=&#34;https://utaholympiclegacy.org/location/utah-olympic-park/&#34;&gt;奥林匹克公园&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然犹他州十一月初可能处于夏季和冬季活动高峰期，但仍然有很多精彩的体验可供享受。无论您是探索盐湖城，还是驾车南下欣赏风景，前往锡安、埃斯卡兰特或摩押，本指南将帮助您发现各种令人兴奋的选择，充分利用您的时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Protection Working Group deep dive at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Salt Lake City】数据保护工作组在 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 盐湖城进行深入探讨</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/21/data-protection-working-group-deep-dive-at-kubecon-cloudnativecon-salt-lake-city/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Community post by Dave Smith-Uchida, Technical Leader, Veeam (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/dave-smith-uchida/&#34;&gt;Linkedin&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dsu-igeek&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data on Kubernetes is growing with databases, object stores, and other stateful applications moving to the platform. The Data Protection Working Group (DPWG) focuses on data availability and preservation for Kubernetes – including backup, restore, remote replication, and the facilitation and orchestration of these processes. At the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/1hovn&#34;&gt;Data Protection Working Group Deep Dive at Kubecon + CloudNativeCon Salt Lake City (Nov. 13, 2:30 PM)&lt;/a&gt;, Xing Yang,&amp;nbsp; Cloud Native Storage Tech Lead at Broadcom/VMware, and I will cover topics including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The need for Kubernetes data protection&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Deep Dive on Changed Block Tracking (CBT)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Deep Dive on Volume Group Snapshots&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Best Practices to Prepare Kubernetes Applications for Data Protection White Paper (new project)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The structure of the Data Protection Working Group&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to get involved with the Data Protection Working Group&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Need for Kubernetes Data Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes has evolved from its original mission as an orchestrator for stateless containers that uses external services for data storage into a platform that supports data storage and state within a Kubernetes cluster.&amp;nbsp; State can be stored in Persistent Volumes (PVs) but also in Kubernetes resources as native Kubernetes applications take advantage of the Kubernetes API server to store their working information.&amp;nbsp; The evolution of Kubernetes into a stateful platform has created a need to protect the data stored in Kubernetes against loss, corruption, and other threats such as ransomware attacks.&amp;nbsp; The Data Protection Working Group has published a white paper that outlines when you need data protection in Kubernetes.&amp;nbsp; We’ll cover the high points during the session at KubeCon, but in the meantime, we invite you to read the paper here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/blob/master/wg-data-protection/data-protection-workflows-white-paper.md&#34;&gt;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/blob/master/wg-data-protection/data-protection-workflows-white-paper.md&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep Dive on Changed Block Tracking (CBT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Data Protection Working Group has been working on adding CBT to Kubernetes and the Container Storage Interface (CSI). CBT improves the performance of backup and replication of large volumes by tracking the blocks that have been changed between two snapshots.&amp;nbsp; When a backup is performed, the backup system creates a volume snapshot and retrieves the list of blocks that have changed since the previous backup’s snapshot was taken and only copies those blocks. Many storage systems, both traditional and cloud-based, implement CBT, but the APIs are proprietary.&amp;nbsp; Since Kubernetes has already created standard APIs for allocating, attaching, snapshotting, and cloning volumes, adding CBT is the next step in standard APIs for storage systems. Veeam Kasten has been a leader in using proprietary CBT systems for Kubernetes data protection, and we’re proud to have been a participant in creating the Kubernetes CBT API, which is currently in beta with Kubernetes 1.32.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Changed Block Tracking KEP: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/enhancements/issues/3314&#34;&gt;https://github.com/kubernetes/enhancements/issues/3314&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep Dive on Volume Group Snapshots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Volume Group Snapshots are another Kubernetes enhancement that supports data protection.&amp;nbsp; When an application uses multiple volumes, taking a consistent snapshot of all of the volumes is important.&amp;nbsp; Taking snapshots one by one while the application is running may result in inconsistencies between the volumes, and may create a backup that will not be usable.&amp;nbsp; One way to get consistency is to quiesce the application and snapshot each volume it uses, but this can take considerable time and the application will be unavailable while in the quiesced state.&amp;nbsp; Volume Group Snapshots snapshot all of the volumes in the group together without needing to quiesce the application to achieve consistency. As with CBT, this is a feature offered by many storage systems, but only with proprietary APIs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Volume Group Snapshots KEP: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/enhancements/tree/master/keps/sig-storage/3476-volume-group-snapshot&#34;&gt;https://github.com/kubernetes/enhancements/tree/master/keps/sig-storage/3476-volume-group-snapshot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;White Paper: Best Practices to Prepare Kubernetes Applications for Data Protection&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A new project for the group is creating a white paper on Best Practices to Prepare Kubernetes Applications for Data Protection.&amp;nbsp; When working with data protection solutions like backup and restore, applications need to be structured so that the backup and restore process can make consistent backups and be restored to a working state. This is an ongoing project, and we invite everyone to join us and share their needs, experiences, and ideas for how to best prepare their applications for data protection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Structure of the Data Protection Working Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Data Protection Working Group consists of participants who use Kubernetes and&amp;nbsp;create applications, storage, and data protection solutions for the platform. We’re open to anyone who is interested in protecting their data on Kubernetes. Come join our session to exchange ideas, find out how to contribute and let us know what your needs are!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/blob/master/wg-data-protection/README.md&#34;&gt;Click here to learn more about the Kubernetes Data Protection Working Group.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come see us at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stop by Veeam’s booth (#K7) for in-person demonstrations of our Veeam Kasten data protection solution and talk to our subject matter experts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kanister&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kanister is an open source framework for data protection and management on Kubernetes.&amp;nbsp; It is a CNCF Sandbox project and can be found at:&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kanister.io/&#34;&gt;https://www.kanister.io/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Come see Xing and I at the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/1hovn&#34;&gt;Data Protection Working Group Deep Dive at Kubecon + CloudNativeCon Salt Lake City (Nov. 13, 2:30 PM)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Veeam 技术负责人 Dave Smith-Uchida 的社区帖子 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/dave-smith-uchida/&#34;&gt;Linkedin&lt;/a&gt;， &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dsu-igeek&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着数据库、对象存储和其他有状态应用程序迁移到该平台，Kubernetes 上的数据正在不断增长。数据保护工作组 (DPWG) 专注于 Kubernetes 的数据可用性和保存，包括备份、恢复、远程复制以及这些流程的促进和编排。在&lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/1hovn&#34;&gt;盐湖城 Kubecon + CloudNativeCon 数据保护工作组深入探讨（11 月 13 日下午 2:30）&lt;/a&gt;上，Xing Yang，云Broadcom/VMware 的本机存储技术主管，我将讨论的主题包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kubernetes 数据保护的需求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;深入探讨块更改跟踪 (CBT)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;深入研究卷组快照&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;准备 Kubernetes 应用程序以实现数据保护的最佳实践白皮书（新项目）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;数据保护工作组的结构&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如何参与数据保护工作组&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes 数据保护的需求&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 最初的使命是作为使用外部服务进行数据存储的无状态容器的编排器，现已发展成为支持 Kubernetes 集群内的数据存储和状态的平台。  状态可以存储在持久卷 (PV) 中，也可以存储在 Kubernetes 资源中，因为本机 Kubernetes 应用程序利用 Kubernetes API 服务器来存储其工作信息。  Kubernetes 发展成为有状态平台，需要保护 Kubernetes 中存储的数据免受丢失、损坏和其他威胁（例如勒索软件攻击）。  数据保护工作组发布了一份白皮书，概述了何时需要在 Kubernetes 中进行数据保护。  我们将在 KubeCon 会议期间介绍要点，但与此同时，我们邀请您阅读此处的论文：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/blob/master/wg-数据保护/data-protection-workflows-white-paper.md&#34;&gt;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/blob/master/wg-data-protection/data-protection-workflows-white-paper.md &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;深入探讨块更改跟踪 (CBT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据保护工作组一直致力于将 CBT 添加到 Kubernetes 和容器存储接口 (CSI)。 CBT 通过跟踪两个快照之间已更改的块来提高大卷备份和复制的性能。  执行备份时，备份系统会创建卷快照并检索自上次备份快照拍摄以来已更改的块列表，并且仅复制se 块。许多存储系统（无论是传统存储系统还是基于云的存储系统）都实现了 CBT，但 API 是专有的。  由于 Kubernetes 已经创建了用于分配、附加、快照和克隆卷的标准 API，因此添加 CBT 是存储系统标准 API 的下一步。 Veeam Kasten 一直是使用专有 CBT 系统进行 Kubernetes 数据保护的领导者，我们很荣幸能够参与创建 Kubernetes CBT API，该 API 目前在 Kubernetes 1.32 中处于测试阶段。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更改块跟踪 KEP：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/enhancements/issues/3314&#34;&gt;https://github.com/kubernetes/enhancements/issues/3314&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;深入了解卷组快照&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;卷组快照是另一个支持数据保护的 Kubernetes 增强功能。  当应用程序使用多个卷时，为所有卷拍摄一致的快照非常重要。  在应用程序运行时逐一拍摄快照可能会导致卷之间不一致，并可能创建无法使用的备份。  获得一致性的一种方法是停顿应用程序并为其使用的每个卷创建快照，但这可能需要相当长的时间，并且应用程序在停顿状态下将不可用。  卷组快照将组中的所有卷一起快照，无需停止应用程序即可实现一致性。与 CBT 一样，许多存储系统都提供此功能，但仅限于专有 API。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;卷组快照 KEP：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/enhancements/tree/master/keps/sig-storage/3476-volume-group-snapshot&#34;&gt;https://github。 com/kubernetes/enhancements/tree/master/keps/sig-storage/3476-volume-group-snapshot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;白皮书：准备 Kubernetes 应用程序进行数据保护的最佳实践&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该小组的一个新项目正在创建一份有关准备 Kubernetes 应用程序进行数据保护的最佳实践的白皮书。  当使用备份和恢复等数据保护解决方案时，需要对应用程序进行结构化，以便备份和恢复过程可以进行一致的备份并恢复到工作状态。这是一个正在进行的项目，我们邀请每个人加入我们，分享他们的需求、经验和想法，了解如何最好地准备他们的应用程序以实现数据保护。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据保护工作组的结构&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据保护工作组由使用 Kubernetes 并为该平台创建应用程序、存储和数据保护解决方案的参与者组成。我们向任何有兴趣保护 Kubernetes 数据的人开放。欢迎参加我们的会议，交流想法，了解如何做出贡献，并让我们知道您的需求！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/blob/master/wg-data-protection/README.md&#34;&gt;单击此处了解有关 Kubernetes 数据保护工作组的更多信息。&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;快来参加 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024！&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;前往 Veeam 展位 (#K7) 亲自演示我们的 Veeam Kasten 数据保护解决方案，并与我们的主题专家交谈。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;卡尼斯特&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kanister 是一个用于 Kubernetes 上数据保护和管理的开源框架。  它是一个 CNCF 沙箱项目，可以在以下位置找到：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kanister.io/&#34;&gt;https://www.kanister.io/&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来看看 Xing 和我在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://sched.co/1hovn&#34;&gt;盐湖城 Kubecon + CloudNativeCon 数据保护工作组深入探讨（11 月 13 日下午 2:30）&lt; /a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Prometheus 3.0 unveiled: highlights from PromCon Europe 2024】Prometheus 3.0 揭晓：PromCon Europe 2024 亮点</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/17/prometheus-3-0-unveiled-highlights-from-promcon-europe-2024/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Community post originally published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/prometheus-3-0-unveiled-highlights-from-promcon-europe-2024-1c5edca32c87&#34;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt; by Dotan Horovits&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/?source=post_page-----1c5edca32c87--------------------------------&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;ac25&#34;&gt;TL;DR Key updates:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Breaking Changes and OpenTelemetry Compatibility&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Facelift for Prometheus UI&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Remote Write 2.0 and Archive of OpenMetrics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;New Governance: Making Prometheus More Inclusive&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Native Histograms and Performance Improvements.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prometheus Ecosystem Updates: Thanos, Perses and More&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4693&#34;&gt;PromCon Europe 2024 just wrapped up in Berlin, and this year’s edition was a big one. Not just because the Prometheus community gathered in full force, but also because we got the long-anticipated&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;unveiling of Prometheus 3.0!&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The maintainers literally hit the ‘merge’ button for 3.0-Beta on stage!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d790&#34;&gt;For the occasion, I sat down with Julius Volz, the creator of Prometheus, for a walk through the major announcements and what they mean for the future of the Prometheus ecosystem. I’ll recap the highlights in this blog, and you can find the full fireside chat on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/openobservability/episodes/Prometheus-3-0-Unveiled-PromCon-Highlights-with-Julius-Volz---OpenObservability-Talks-S5E04-e2o0455&#34;&gt;the latest episode of OpenObservability Talks&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;wp-block-embed__wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; title=&#34;Prometheus 3.0 Unveiled: PromCon Highlights with Julius Volz&#34; width=&#34;500&#34; height=&#34;281&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iPUCU-78RD4?feature=oembed&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;60bc&#34;&gt;Major release: Breaking Changes and OpenTelemetry Compatibility&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7e5e&#34;&gt;Prometheus v2 has been around for almost 7 years, with no less than 54 minor releases. It was high time to bump that major release. Major versions are also the time that software usually has breaking changes, and Julius says this was indeed part of the reason for this major release. So should we expect things to break when we upgrade from 2.x to 3.0?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;a15c&#34;&gt;The good news, according to Julius, is that for most people, when they upgrade from 2.x to 3.0, nothing much will break. He said it was about getting rid of “old crafty stuff”, primarily removing deprecated experimental feature flags, so the majority of users should not experience any breaking changes. Don’t worry, Prometheus keeps its longstanding backwards-compatibility commitment to its users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;087f&#34;&gt;This major release is not just about incremental changes — it represents a shift in how Prometheus will be used moving forward. Julius explained that one of the major themes for v3.0 is OpenTelemetry (OTel) compatibility. This is not trivial, given&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:7233510791277142016&#34;&gt;different design principles employed by each project&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;around metric naming (dots or underscores? with or without units?) and encoding (UTF-8 now supported on Prometheus v3), pull vs. push mode, delta vs. cumulative temporality, and more. But there’s a clear upside to it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:7233510791277142016&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*5VfS9QqWV9Vm2Um355Ujcg.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Horovits post on the recent survey of the OpenTelemetry-Prometheus Working Group at the CNCF&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9d2d&#34;&gt;Prometheus has always been known for its robust metric collection, but with the move to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/p/83f85878e46a&#34;&gt;support native OpenTelemetry metrics&lt;/a&gt;, Prometheus maintainers want to position it as the go-to backend for OpenTelemetry. This is a strategic step to make Prometheus more interoperable and future-proof as OpenTelemetry continues to gain adoption across the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;a2bc&#34;&gt;A Facelift for Prometheus UI&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;fe67&#34;&gt;We also discussed the revamping of the&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Prometheus UI&lt;/em&gt;. While Prometheus has traditionally been loved for its backend performance and flexibility, the frontend has sometimes lagged behind. Julius walked us through how the new UI in 3.0, which he developed himself, will improve usability without sacrificing the core simplicity that Prometheus users value. It’s based on Mantine, a modern React component library, and achieves a slick and cleaner look.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;96c9&#34;&gt;The new Prometheus UI also offers new functionality, including a PromLens-style tree view, a better metrics explorer and an “Explain” tab. The revamped metrics explorer enables easy visual exploration of metrics and their labels, cardinality and more. The tree view was inspired by PromLens, a&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/fbede9b5cc9#4951&#34;&gt;PromQL query builder tool which was recently donated to Prometheus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;wp-block-embed__wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34; data-width=&#34;500&#34; data-dnt=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Just ported over the metrics and labels explorer from PromLens into the new &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/PrometheusIO?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;@PrometheusIO&lt;/a&gt; UI: &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.co/7jfDB6NdDt&#34;&gt;pic.twitter.com/7jfDB6NdDt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;— Julius Volz (@juliusvolz) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/juliusvolz/status/1830575287362339280?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;September 2, 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;0620&#34;&gt;To my question, Julius said that the Alertmanager UI is not being touched at the moment, and he’s not sure when that would happen. He did confirm that the goal is to adopt the same UI framework (currently it’s not even React-based) and look and feel, as the revamped Prometheus UI. For more on the new UI, check out&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://promlabs.com/blog/2024/09/11/a-look-at-the-new-prometheus-3-0-ui/&#34;&gt;Julius’s blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;2070&#34;&gt;Remote Write 2.0 and Archive of OpenMetrics&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;e4a8&#34;&gt;One of the standout features of Prometheus 3.0 is&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Write 2.0&lt;/strong&gt;. Remote Write format serves to transmit bulk metrics from Prometheus to analytics backends. Julius shared insights into how this new iteration of remote write enhances the way Prometheus handles long-term storage. Prometheus, by design, is all about short-term, high-performance metric collection. But the ecosystem has evolved to handle long-term storage solutions like Thanos, Cortex, and Mimir, which integrate with Prometheus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;58ad&#34;&gt;With Remote Write 2.0, the focus is on reliability and efficiency. It drastically reduces the chance of data loss during network outages or downtime and allows for better streaming of data to remote storage. This is a big leap forward for teams that rely on Prometheus for critical monitoring and need bulletproof data pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;af8f&#34;&gt;Also important is the exposition format, which defines how metrics are exposed by different components for scraping by Prometheus. A while back this format was spun off into its own project called OpenMetrics, in hope of making it into an independent standard. This hasn’t succeeded, and cluttered the Prometheus ecosystem. Now&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/openmetrics-is-archived-merged-into-prometheus-d555598d2d04&#34;&gt;OpenMetrics is officially archived and merged back into Prometheus&lt;/a&gt;, where it belongs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;6772&#34;&gt;Native Histograms and Performance Improvements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;39a3&#34;&gt;Another exciting feature coming with Prometheus 3.0 is&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/fbede9b5cc9#aa64&#34;&gt;the introduction of native histograms&lt;/a&gt;. This feature significantly enhances how Prometheus can handle high-cardinality data, making it easier to manage large data sets without sacrificing performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;cd87&#34;&gt;With v3.0, native histograms now support out-of-order ingestion, which addresses various scenarios brought up by OpenTelemetry, and more broadly by networking and similar disconnect and temporary gaps in metric data, a gap that that can now be filled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;51c2&#34;&gt;By natively supporting histograms, Prometheus 3.0 reduces the complexity of metric aggregation and makes queries faster and more efficient. It’s one of those under-the-hood improvements that might not make headlines, but it will have a big impact for users at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;b247&#34;&gt;Prometheus Ecosystem Updates: Thanos, Perses and More&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;0077&#34;&gt;We couldn’t talk about Prometheus without touching on the broader ecosystem. One important open source project in the Prometheus ecosystem is Thanos, which offers long-term scalable storage for Prometheus. Similar to Cortex and Mimir, Thanos is introducing native multi-tenancy support, enabling sending data from different tenants, and then tracking and controlling access to it by tenant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;dd9a&#34;&gt;Another interesting development in Thanos is distributed query execution, which improves query performance by pushing some of the processing down to leaf nodes, in a hub-and-spoke (or map-reduce) fashion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d7ca&#34;&gt;On the visualization side, one of the interesting developments coming out of PromCon this year was&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/unveiling-perses-the-gitops-friendly-metrics-visualization-tool-f05b5324d7da&#34;&gt;Perses project that recently joined the CNCF&lt;/a&gt;. Julius hinted that while Grafana has been the default for many, Perses is offering a lightweight, Prometheus-native dashboarding experience, with GitOps capabilities and foundational open source philosophy. Perses is still in its early days, but it’s worth keeping an eye on as it evolves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;4a56&#34;&gt;New Governance: Making Prometheus More Inclusive&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;528e&#34;&gt;As Prometheus continues to grow, the governance model has also undergone changes. We touched on the project’s shift to a more&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;formalized governance structure&lt;/strong&gt;, lowering the barrier to entry for people to get involved, and making it easier for contributors to reach key positions in the project and collaborate on the future of Prometheus. This move aligns with other CNCF projects that have embraced more structured, tiered, transparent governance models as they mature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;3065&#34;&gt;Julius pointed out that with Prometheus now being used by countless organizations, it was important to ensure that decisions about its direction are made inclusively. The new governance framework will offer more tiers and empower a broader community to get more responsibility, accountability and permissions, and ultimately influence the roadmap while maintaining the high standards that have made Prometheus a cornerstone of the observability space.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;1abd&#34;&gt;Looking Forward: The Future of Prometheus and the Ecosystem&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b285&#34;&gt;PromCon was full of updates, such as automatic reloading of the Prometheus configuration, Regex and query functionality, the new Service Discovery Manager, and the Agent mode reaching Stability, and we couldn’t cover it all here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9b0e&#34;&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus/prometheus/releases/tag/v3.0.0-beta.0&#34;&gt;3.0 Beta is out&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and you’re welcome to try it out and check the release notes. The Prometheus 3.0 GA release is expected towards KubeCon North America 2024 in November, according to the outcomes of the Prometheus maintainers’ DevSummit that followed PromCon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;cf7c&#34;&gt;As we wrapped up our discussion, Julius emphasized that while Prometheus 3.0 is a huge milestone, the work is far from over. The team is already looking ahead to what’s next, including improvements to scalability, deeper integrations with OpenTelemetry, and continued enhancements to the overall user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b468&#34;&gt;PromCon Europe 2024 was a reminder of just how far Prometheus has come. With the launch of Prometheus 3.0, the project is poised to remain a dominant force in the observability ecosystem for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;a74e&#34;&gt;Want to learn more? Check out the OpenObservability Talks episode:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/openobservability/episodes/Prometheus-3-0-Unveiled-PromCon-Highlights-with-Julius-Volz---OpenObservability-Talks-S5E04-e2o0455&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prometheus 3.0 Unveiled: PromCon Highlights with Julius Volz&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/episode/61Dt8RXY4S1zcMYX10XMMn?si=sk6-HuvLQSuOnk9EKNwjfQ&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;社区帖子最初发布于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/prometheus-3-0-unveiled-highlights-from-promcon-europe-2024-1c5edca32c87&#34;&gt;Medium&lt;/ a&gt; 作者：Dotan Horovits&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/?source=post_page-----1c5edca32c87------------- -------------------&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;ac25&#34;&gt;TL;DR 密钥更新：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;重大变更和 OpenTelemetry 兼容性&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prometheus UI 的改版&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;远程写入 2.0 和 OpenMetrics 存档&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;新治理：让 Prometheus 更具包容性&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;原生直方图和性能改进。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;普罗米修斯生态系统更新：Thanos、Perses 等&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4693&#34;&gt;PromCon Europe 2024 刚刚在柏林落下帷幕，今年的盛会非常盛大。不仅因为 Prometheus 社区全力聚集，还因为我们&lt;strong&gt;迎来了期待已久的 Prometheus 3.0！&lt;/strong&gt;维护人员在舞台上按下了 3.0-Beta 的“合并”按钮！&lt;/strong&gt; p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d790&#34;&gt;借此机会，我与 Prometheus 的创建者 Julius Volz 坐下来，一起了解了主要公告以及它们对 Prometheus 生态系统的未来意味着什么。我将回顾一下本博客中的重点内容，您可以在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/openobservability/episodes/Prometheus-3-0-Unveiled- 上找到完整的炉边聊天内容PromCon-Highlights-with-Julius-Volz---OpenObservability-Talks-S5E04-e2o0455&#34;&gt;OpenObservability 讲座的最新一集&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34; wp-block-embed__wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; title=&#34;Prometheus 3.0 揭晓：PromCon 亮点与 Julius Volz&#34; width=&#34;500&#34; height=&#34;281&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/iPUCU-78RD4?feature =oembed“frameborder =”0“允许=”剪贴板-写入; 画中画“referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”allowfullscreen =“” &gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;60bc&#34;&gt;主要版本：重大更改和 OpenTelemetry 兼容性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7e5e&#34;&gt;Prometheus v2 已经推出近 7 年了，至少有 54 个次要版本。是时候推出这个主要版本了。主要版本也是软件通常进行重大更改的时间，朱利叶斯表示这确实是此主要版本的部分原因。那么，当我们从 2.x 升级到 3.0 时，我们是否应该预期事情会发生变化呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;a15c&#34;&gt;Julius 认为，好消息是，对于大多数人来说，当他们从 2.x 升级到 3.0 时，不会有太大问题。他说这是为了摆脱“旧的狡猾的东西”，主要是删除已弃用的实验性功能标志，因此大多数用户不应该放弃经历任何重大变化。别担心，Prometheus 恪守其对用户的长期向后兼容性承诺。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;087f&#34;&gt;这个主要版本不仅仅是增量更改 - 它代表了 Prometheus 未来使用方式的转变。 Julius 解释说，v3.0 的主要主题之一是 OpenTelemetry (OTel) 兼容性。这并不是一件小事，因为&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:7233510791277142016&#34;&gt;每个项目在指标命名方面采用了不同的设计原则&lt;/a&gt;（点或下划线？带或不带单位？）和编码（Prometheus v3 现在支持 UTF-8）、拉模式与推模式、增量与累积时间性等等。但它有一个明显的好处。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:7233510791277142016&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34; https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*5VfS9QqWV9Vm2Um355Ujcg.png&#34; alt=&#34;图片&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-标题&#34;&gt;Horovits 发布了 CNCF OpenTelemetry-Prometheus 工作组最近的调查&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9d2d&#34;&gt;Prometheus 一直以其强大的指标收集而闻名，但现在已转向&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/p/83f85878e46a&#34;&gt;支持原生 OpenTelemetry 指标&lt;/a&gt; Prometheus 维护者希望将其定位为 OpenTelemetry 的首选后端。随着 OpenTelemetry 继续在整个行业得到采用，这是使 Prometheus 更具互操作性和面向未来的战略步骤。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;a2bc&#34;&gt;Prometheus UI 的改版&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;fe67&#34;&gt;我们还讨论了 Prometheus UI 的改进。&lt;em&gt;Prometheus UI&lt;/em&gt;。虽然 Prometheus 传统上因其后端性能和灵活性而受到喜爱，但前端有时会落后。 Julius 向我们介绍了他自己开发的 3.0 中的新 UI 如何在不牺牲 Prometheus 用户所看重的核心简单性的情况下提高可用性。它基于现代 React 组件库 Mantine，并实现了光滑、干净的外观。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;96c9&#34;&gt;新的 Prometheus UI 还提供了新功能，包括 PromLens 风格的树视图、更好的指标浏览器和“解释”选项卡。改进后的指标浏览器可以轻松地直观地探索指标及其标签、基数等。树视图的灵感来自于 PromLens，这是一款&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/fbede9b5cc9#4951&#34;&gt;PromQL 查询构建工具，最近捐赠给了 Prometheus&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;wp-block-embed__wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;twitter-tweet&#34; data-width=&#34;500&#34; data-dnt=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;p lang=&#34;en&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;刚刚将 PromLens 中的指标和标签资源管理器移植到新版本中&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/PrometheusIO?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;@PrometheusIO&lt;/a&gt; 用户界面：&lt;a href=&#34;https://t.co/7jfDB6NdDt&#34;&gt;pic.twitter.com/7jfDB6NdDt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;— Julius Volz (@juliusvolz) &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter. com/juliusvolz/status/1830575287362339280?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&#34;&gt;2024 年 9 月 2 日&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;0620&#34;&gt;对于我的问题，Julius 表示目前尚未触及 Alertmanager UI，而且他不确定何时会发生这种情况。他确实确认，目标是采用与改进后的 Prometheus UI 相同的 UI 框架（目前甚至不是基于 React 的）和外观。有关新用户界面的更多信息，请查看&lt;a href=&#34;https://promlabs.com/blog/2024/09/11/a-look-at-the-new-prometheus-3-0-ui/&#34;&gt;朱利叶斯的博客文章&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;2070&#34;&gt;远程写入 2.0 和 OpenMetrics 存档&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;e4a8&#34;&gt;Prometheus 3.0 的突出功能之一是&lt;strong&gt;远程写入 2.0&lt;/strong&gt;。远程写入格式用于将批量指标从 Prometheus 传输到分析后端。 Julius 分享了关于远程写入的新迭代如何增强 Prometheus 处理长期存储方式的见解。 Prometheus 在设计上就是致力于短期、高性能的指标收集。但生态系统已经发展到可以处理长期存储解决方案，例如与 Prometheus 集成的 Thanos、Cortex 和 Mimir。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;58ad&#34;&gt;远程写入 2.0 的重点是可靠性和效率。它大大降低了网络中断或停机期间数据丢失的可能性，并允许更好地将数据流式传输到远程存储。对于依赖 Prometheus 进行关键监控并需要防弹数据管道的团队来说，这是一个巨大的飞跃。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;af8f&#34;&gt;同样重要的是展示格式，它定义了不同组件如何公开指标以供 Prometheus 抓取。不久前，这种格式被分拆成自己的项目，名为 OpenMetrics，希望使其成为一个独立的标准。但这并没有成功，并且使 Prometheus 生态系统变得混乱。现在&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/openmetrics-is-archived-merged-into-prometheus-d555598d2d04&#34;&gt;OpenMetrics 已正式存档并合并回 Prometheus&lt;/a&gt;，它所属的地方。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;6772&#34;&gt;原生直方图和性能改进&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;39a3&#34;&gt;Prometheus 3.0 带来的另一个令人兴奋的功能是&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/fbede9b5cc9#aa64&#34;&gt;引入原生直方图&lt;/a&gt;。此功能显着增强了 Prometheus 处理高基数数据的能力，使得在不牺牲性能的情况下更轻松地管理大型数据集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;cd87&#34;&gt;在 v3.0 中，原生直方图现在支持无序摄取，这解决了 OpenTelemetry 带来的各种场景，更广泛地说是网络和指标数据中类似的断开连接和临时间隙（间隙）现在可以填充。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;51c2&#34;&gt;通过原生支持直方图，Prometheus 3.0 减少了指标聚合的复杂性并使查询更快、更高效。这是那些可能不会成为头条新闻的底层改进之一，但它将对大规模用户产生巨大影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;b247&#34;&gt;Prometheus 生态系统更新：Thanos、Perses 等&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;0077&#34;&gt;我们不能在不涉及更广泛的生态系统的情况下谈论 Prometheus。 Prometheus生态系统中一个重要的开源项目是Thanos，它为Prometheus提供长期可扩展的存储。与 Cortex 和 Mimir 类似，Thanos 引入了原生多租户支持，允许从不同租户发送数据，然后跟踪和控制租户对其的访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;dd9a&#34;&gt;Thanos 的另一个有趣的发展是分布式查询执行，它通过以中心辐射（或映射缩减）方式将一些处理下推到叶节点来提高查询性能。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d7ca&#34;&gt;在可视化方面，今年 PromCon 的一项有趣进展是&lt;a href=&#34;https://horovits.medium.com/unveiling-perses-the-gitops-friend- metrics-visualization-tool-f05b5324d7da&#34;&gt;最近加入 CNCF 的 Perses 项目&lt;/a&gt;。 Julius 暗示，虽然 Grafana 已成为许多人的默认选择，但 Perses 提供了轻量级、Prometheus 原生的仪表板体验，具有 GitOps 功能和基础开源理念。 Perses 仍处于早期阶段，但随着它的发展值得关注。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;4a56&#34;&gt;新治理：让 Prometheus 更具包容性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;528e&#34;&gt;随着 Prometheus 的不断发展，治理模型也发生了变化。我们谈到了该项目向更&lt;strong&gt;正式化的治理结构&lt;/strong&gt;的转变，降低了人们参与的门槛，并使贡献者更容易担任项目中的关键职位并就项目的未来进行协作普罗米修斯。这一举措与其他 CNCF 项目相一致，这些项目随着成熟而采用了更加结构化、分层、透明的治理模型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;3065&#34;&gt;Julius 指出，随着 Prometheus 现在被无数组织使用，确保有关其方向的决策具有包容性非常重要。新的治理框架将提供更多层级，并授权更广泛的社区获得更多责任、问责和权限，并最终影响路线图，同时保持使 Prometheus 成为可观测性领域基石的高标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;1abd&#34;&gt;展望未来：Prometheus 和生态系统的未来&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b285&#34;&gt;PromCon 充满了更新，例如自动重新加载 Prometheus 配置、正则表达式和查询功能、新的服务发现管理器以及达到稳定性的 Agent 模式，我们无法在此涵盖所有内容.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9b0e&#34;&gt;&lt;ahref=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus/prometheus/releases/tag/v3.0.0-beta.0&#34;&gt;3.0 Beta 版已发布&lt;/a&gt;，欢迎您试用并查看发行说明。根据 PromCon 后 Prometheus 维护者 DevSummit 的结果，Prometheus 3.0 GA 预计将于 11 月在 KubeCon North America 2024 发布。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;cf7c&#34;&gt;当我们结束讨论时，Julius 强调，虽然 Prometheus 3.0 是一个巨大的里程碑，但工作还远未结束。该团队已经在展望接下来的发展，包括可扩展性的改进、与 OpenTelemetry 的更深入集成以及整体用户体验的持续增强。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b468&#34;&gt;PromCon Europe 2024 提醒人们 Prometheus 已经走了多远。随着 Prometheus 3.0 的推出，该项目有望在未来几年内继续成为可观测性生态系统的主导力量。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;a74e&#34;&gt;想要了解更多信息吗？查看 OpenObservability Talks 剧集：&lt;a href=&#34;https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/show/openobservability/episodes/Prometheus-3-0-Unveiled-PromCon-Highlights-with-Julius-Volz--- OpenObservability-Talks-S5E04-e2o0455&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prometheus 3.0 揭晓：Julius Volz 的 PromCon 亮点&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/episode/61Dt8RXY4S1zcMYX10XMMn?si= sk6-HuvLQSuOnk9EKNwjfQ&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dilli Hai Dilwalon Ki】德里是恋人的天堂</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/21/dilli-hai-dilwalon-ki/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#dilli-hai-dilwalon-ki&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Translation: “Delhi is for the warm-hearted”)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Delhi guide by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/kunalstwt&#34;&gt;Kunal Kushwaha&lt;/a&gt;, Field CTO at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.civo.com/&#34;&gt;Civo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The capital city of India, Delhi, has roots that trace back thousands of years. Known as Indraprastha in ancient texts dating as far back as 400 BCE, it has been the center of various cultures and empires. There’s always something happening in Delhi, with a wide array of activities to experience. In this guide, I’ll share how you can make the most of your time when you visit during KubeCon India in December.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372558902-2e8e3f21-c601-4db3-bc64-f16fe58610cd.png?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTg5MDItMmU4ZTNmMjEtYzYwMS00ZGIzLWJjNjQtZjE2ZmU1ODYxMGNkLnBuZz9YLUFtei1BbGdvcml0aG09QVdTNC1ITUFDLVNIQTI1NiZYLUFtei1DcmVkZW50aWFsPUFLSUFWQ09EWUxTQTUzUFFLNFpBJTJGMjAyNDEwMjElMkZ1cy1lYXN0LTElMkZzMyUyRmF3czRfcmVxdWVzdCZYLUFtei1EYXRlPTIwMjQxMDIxVDEzMjgyNFomWC1BbXotRXhwaXJlcz0zMDAmWC1BbXotU2lnbmF0dXJlPWM5YTVmOWU3YTY1MzFhNzdlYjJlYmYxYWJiZDFlY2FlOGRhNDkyOTJlOTBkMTM3MTRjNGU0OTU3ZWEyNDMxMjImWC1BbXotU2lnbmVkSGVhZGVycz1ob3N0In0.3R2riecOUVfNpfwqX5S-Cgr-FWXZVSBeUlZ_LnVfyqg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372558902-2e8e3f21-c601-4db3-bc64-f16fe58610cd.png?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTg5MDItMmU4ZTNmMjEtYzYwMS00ZGIzLWJjNjQtZjE2ZmU1ODYxMGNkLnBuZz9YLUFtei1BbGdvcml0aG09QVdTNC1ITUFDLVNIQTI1NiZYLUFtei1DcmVkZW50aWFsPUFLSUFWQ09EWUxTQTUzUFFLNFpBJTJGMjAyNDEwMjElMkZ1cy1lYXN0LTElMkZzMyUyRmF3czRfcmVxdWVzdCZYLUFtei1EYXRlPTIwMjQxMDIxVDEzMjgyNFomWC1BbXotRXhwaXJlcz0zMDAmWC1BbXotU2lnbmF0dXJlPWM5YTVmOWU3YTY1MzFhNzdlYjJlYmYxYWJiZDFlY2FlOGRhNDkyOTJlOTBkMTM3MTRjNGU0OTU3ZWEyNDMxMjImWC1BbXotU2lnbmVkSGVhZGVycz1ob3N0In0.3R2riecOUVfNpfwqX5S-Cgr-FWXZVSBeUlZ_LnVfyqg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Weather&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#weather&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;In December, Delhi will be chilly with temperatures ranging from 22°C during the day to as low as 5°C at night. Pack a jacket and warm clothes. Rain is unlikely during this time, but it’s best to check the weather forecast closer to your travel date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Transportation&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#transportation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372560713-3e5b0d06-2ea8-44a4-91e4-9a33eaa79823.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NjA3MTMtM2U1YjBkMDYtMmVhOC00NGE0LTkxZTQtOWEzM2VhYTc5ODIzLmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT1iY2VkNDE3MGE1NGE0NTY0ZTRhYzhlMDM0ODIzMjliN2E0NjAxZDQ4MTZmZDBiMGU0Mjg2NDg5YTVmMTUwZjEzJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.fxIcO9ZpTdIp2HLZ6Tpj5pbqcTz0nJazS5ioO0IG0U8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372560713-3e5b0d06-2ea8-44a4-91e4-9a33eaa79823.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NjA3MTMtM2U1YjBkMDYtMmVhOC00NGE0LTkxZTQtOWEzM2VhYTc5ODIzLmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT1iY2VkNDE3MGE1NGE0NTY0ZTRhYzhlMDM0ODIzMjliN2E0NjAxZDQ4MTZmZDBiMGU0Mjg2NDg5YTVmMTUwZjEzJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.fxIcO9ZpTdIp2HLZ6Tpj5pbqcTz0nJazS5ioO0IG0U8&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Uber&lt;/strong&gt;: Uber is affordable, and you can pay by card. However, some drivers may ask you to cancel rides and pay them in cash. Avoid this by insisting on paying through the app to prevent being overcharged or scammed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Auto Rickshaws&lt;/strong&gt;: Another common form of transport. Compare the price offered by the rickshaw driver to what Uber suggests, as rickshaws only take cash unless booked via Uber.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Delhi Metro&lt;/strong&gt;: An efficient and affordable way to get around the city, with extensive coverage across Delhi and surrounding areas. It’s clean, reliable, and a great option to avoid traffic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Food and Shopping&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#food-and-shopping&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559536-d05757b7-3bb7-44ee-9573-77e7c370eff8.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk1MzYtZDA1NzU3YjctM2JiNy00NGVlLTk1NzMtNzdlN2MzNzBlZmY4LmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT0zNzMxYWY1Y2QzM2ZkZmIzN2NhNzg4NTE1MzYwOGQ3MWU0NjNjNjdlYzQ5NzNiODM2NGQyMmNlYmY3MzA0ZTkzJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.5d5WyLlUW7JU1Vai2we8UKi0r_9CL87VO2YzhMvW39Y&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559536-d05757b7-3bb7-44ee-9573-77e7c370eff8.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk1MzYtZDA1NzU3YjctM2JiNy00NGVlLTk1NzMtNzdlN2MzNzBlZmY4LmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT0zNzMxYWY1Y2QzM2ZkZmIzN2NhNzg4NTE1MzYwOGQ3MWU0NjNjNjdlYzQ5NzNiODM2NGQyMmNlYmY3MzA0ZTkzJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.5d5WyLlUW7JU1Vai2we8UKi0r_9CL87VO2YzhMvW39Y&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Local Shopping&lt;/strong&gt;: Vendors are everywhere in Delhi, and it’s wise to go with a local friend to avoid being overcharged. Lajpat Nagar is a great place for local shopping, but for fair prices and quality, I recommend sticking to malls. However, the hustle and bustle of Lajpat Nagar is worth experiencing, especially for delicious street food.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Malls&lt;/strong&gt;: Malls are a reliable way to shop for authentic Indian goods and enjoy good food:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ambience Mall, Gurgaon: Near the conference venue, it offers a wide range of shopping, food, and activities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;DLF Mall of India, Noida: India’s largest mall and my personal favorite for food and shopping.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Select Citywalk, Saket: Popular for nightlife and shopping. The DLF mall next door is excellent for restaurants.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Street Food&lt;/strong&gt;: While Delhi is famous for street food, it can be a hit or miss in terms of hygiene. I recommend sticking to trusted chains like Haldiram’s or Bikanervala for safe, authentic street food and sweets. Lajpat Nagar, Amar Colony, and Connaught Place also have good street food options if you’re feeling adventurous.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;32nd Milestone, Gurgaon&lt;/strong&gt;: A lively area with a variety of restaurants and bars, offering a great mix of cuisines and a vibrant atmosphere. It’s close to the conference venue and perfect for an evening out.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Things to Do in Delhi&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#things-to-do-in-delhi&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559742-93580717-b270-4756-9c5a-02892fe312ce.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk3NDItOTM1ODA3MTctYjI3MC00NzU2LTljNWEtMDI4OTJmZTMxMmNlLmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT1iMWUxMjFiZTQwMzk1ZTMzNWNlOGY5ZTQzYjBlNTk3OWZhYWQ2MjQyNjRiYzY3NTNjNmJmMDczMDE5ZTRiYjNlJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.ZrMYBPLLTZzCjTGId8CpQeRGsWh8n714-z8OIVVpeXQ&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559742-93580717-b270-4756-9c5a-02892fe312ce.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk3NDItOTM1ODA3MTctYjI3MC00NzU2LTljNWEtMDI4OTJmZTMxMmNlLmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT1iMWUxMjFiZTQwMzk1ZTMzNWNlOGY5ZTQzYjBlNTk3OWZhYWQ2MjQyNjRiYzY3NTNjNmJmMDczMDE5ZTRiYjNlJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.ZrMYBPLLTZzCjTGId8CpQeRGsWh8n714-z8OIVVpeXQ&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;India Gate&lt;/strong&gt;: A monumental war memorial built in honor of Indian soldiers, surrounded by beautiful lawns, making it a great spot for a peaceful evening stroll.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lotus Temple&lt;/strong&gt;: Known for its stunning flower-like shape, this temple is a peaceful place for meditation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Akshardham Temple&lt;/strong&gt;: A stunning modern temple complex showcasing India’s rich cultural heritage through intricate architecture, gardens, and a beautiful water show. It’s a must-visit for its grandeur and serenity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Red Fort&lt;/strong&gt;: A grand fortress from the Mughal era, offering a peek into Delhi’s historical significance. Though historically significant, Chandni Chowk can be very crowded, with a high risk of pickpocketing. The area is often dirty, and there’s not much to do beyond the local market. I recommend skipping it unless you have a specific reason to visit.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;National Museum&lt;/strong&gt;: A treasure trove of India’s art, history, and culture spanning millennia.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dilli Haat&lt;/strong&gt;: A market with traditional handicrafts and foods from various Indian states. A must-visit for authentic Indian souvenirs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Nightlife&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#nightlife&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559949-346f155d-1ee8-4d02-b73d-ebbe92c65b85.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk5NDktMzQ2ZjE1NWQtMWVlOC00ZDAyLWI3M2QtZWJiZTkyYzY1Yjg1LmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT0yZTVmZjQzZGUwOWZmM2RlM2ZmYzg4MGRiNzU1YWUyZmIyYTdlMDdhOGI2OTE0N2ZlM2VmMDhmZDgzZTJmZDdiJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.Ps4qIU8U3gFrr4WHoLvVMHHzDLkcP0x40j6OqUoDvs4&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559949-346f155d-1ee8-4d02-b73d-ebbe92c65b85.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk5NDktMzQ2ZjE1NWQtMWVlOC00ZDAyLWI3M2QtZWJiZTkyYzY1Yjg1LmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT0yZTVmZjQzZGUwOWZmM2RlM2ZmYzg4MGRiNzU1YWUyZmIyYTdlMDdhOGI2OTE0N2ZlM2VmMDhmZDgzZTJmZDdiJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.Ps4qIU8U3gFrr4WHoLvVMHHzDLkcP0x40j6OqUoDvs4&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connaught Place (CP)&lt;/strong&gt;: The best area for nightlife, filled with bars and restaurants, and safe with regular police patrols. It’s also close to many embassies, ensuring a professional and secure environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DLF CyberHub&lt;/strong&gt;: Located near the conference venue, CyberHub in Gurgaon is a great spot with numerous offices, restaurants, and bars. Clean and modern, it offers a variety of dining and entertainment options.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hauz Khas Social&lt;/strong&gt;: Popular but tends to attract a younger crowd. If you’re looking for a more professional vibe, stick to CP or CyberHub.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Important Tips&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#important-tips&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pollution&lt;/strong&gt;: Although it’s looking good right now, December is known for Delhi’s pollution after Diwali, so it’s advisable to bring face masks for protection. You will know for sure the air quality you can expect in December after Diwali, i.e. after 1st November, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety&lt;/strong&gt;: Delhi is generally a safe city, especially if you’re with others. Personally, I feel safer in Delhi than some other cities. Stick to the places I’ve recommended or ask trusted locals for advice. Avoid poorly lit alleys, particularly at night, and it’s always best to travel with someone.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Language&lt;/strong&gt;: Hindi is the most widely spoken language in Delhi, though most people also speak English. However, local vendors and Uber drivers may not be as fluent, so it’s helpful to use Google Translate or have someone with you who knows the language.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Delhi offers a diverse range of experiences, from some of the best food in the world to a rich cultural and historical landscape. Enjoy your visit to the city and make the most out of KubeCon India 2024! If you have any questions, feel free to message me on the CNCF Slack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See you there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#dilli-hai-dilwalon-ki&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;（翻译：“德里是热心人的地方”）&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;德里指南，作者：&lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/kunalstwt&#34;&gt;Kunal Kushwaha&lt;/a&gt;，现场首席技术官，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.civo.com /&#34;&gt;Civo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;印度首都德里的历史可以追溯到数千年前。在可追溯到公元前 400 年的古代文献中，它被称为 Indraprastha，一直是各种文化和帝国的中心。德里总是有活动发生，有各种各样的活动可供体验。在本指南中，我将分享您如何充分利用 12 月印度 KubeCon 期间参观的时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372558902-2e8e3f21-c601-4db3-bc64-f16fe58610cd.png?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9 ..3R2riecOUVfNpfwqX5S-Cgr-FWXZVSBeUlZ_LnVfyqg&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img 解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372558902-2e8e3f21- c601-4db3-bc64-f16fe58610cd.png?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9..3R2riecOUVfNpfwqX5S-Cgr-FWXZVSBeUlZ_LnVfyqg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;天气&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#weather&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;12 月，德里天气寒冷，气温在 22° 左右白天温度低至 5°C，夜间低至 5°C。带上夹克和保暖的衣服。这段时间不太可能下雨，但最好查看临近您旅行日期的天气预报。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separaTor 有-alpha-通道-不透明度&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;交通&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#transportation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3 &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372560713-3e5b0d06-2ea8-44a4-91e4-9a33eaa79823.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9 .eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80M jY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NjA3MTMtM2U1YjBkMDYtMmVhOC00NGE0LTkxZTQtoWEzM2VhYTc5ODIzLmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGl hbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM 9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT1iY2VkNDE3MGE1NGE0NTY0ZTRhYzhlMDM0ODIzMjliN2E0NjAxZDQ4MTZmZDBiMGU0Mjg2NDg5YTVmMTUwZjEzJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9 zdCJ9.fxIcO9ZpTdIp2HLZ6Tpj5pbqcTz0nJazS5ioO0IG0U8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img 解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372560713-3e5b0d06-2ea8- 44a4-91e4-9a33eaa79823.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsI mtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NjA3MTMtM2U1YjBkMDYtMmVhoC00NGE0LTkxZTQtoWEzM2VhYTc5ODIzLmp wZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1 BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M 0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT1iY2VkNDE3MGE1NGE0NTY0ZTRhYzhlMDM0ODIzMjliN2E0NjA xZDQ4MTZmZDBiMGU0Mjg2NDg5YTVmMTUwZjEzJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.fxIcO9ZpTdIp2HLZ6Tpj5pbqcTz0nJazS5ioO0IG0U8&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Uber&lt;/strong&gt;：Uber 价格实惠，而且您可以用卡付款。但是，有些司机可能会要求您取消行程并以现金支付。为了避免这种情况，请坚持通过应用付款，以防止被多收费或被骗。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;机动人力车&lt;/strong&gt;：另一种常见的交通工具。将人力车司机提供的价格与 Uber 建议的价格进行比较，因为除非通过 Uber 预订，否则人力车只接受现金。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;德里地铁&lt;/strong&gt;：一种高效且经济实惠的城市交通方式，覆盖范围广泛，覆盖德里及周边地区。它干净、可靠，是避免交通拥堵的绝佳选择。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;美食和购物&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#food-and-shopping&#34;&gt;&lt; /a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559536-d05757b7-3bb7-44ee-9573-77e7c370eff8.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCw icGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk1MzYtZDA1NzU3YjctM2JiNy00NGVlLTk1NzMtNzdlN2MzNzBlZmY4LmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbX otQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlg tQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT0zNzMxYWY1Y2QzM2ZkZmIzN2 NhNzg4NTE1MzYwOGQ3MWU0NjNjNjdlYzQ5NzNiODM2NGQyMmNlymY3MzA0ZTkzJlgtQ W16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.5d5WyLlUW7JU1Vai2we8UKi0r_9CL87VO2YzhMvW39Y&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img 解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/37255 9536-d05757b7-3bb7 -44ee-9573-77e7c370eff8.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtle SI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk1MzYtZDA1NzU3YjctM2JiNy00NGVlLTk1NzMtNzdlN2MzNzBlZmy4Lmp wZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd 3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT0zNzMxYWY1Y2QzM2ZkZmIzN2NHNzg4NTE1MzYwOGQ 3MWU0NjNjNjdlYzQ5NzNiODM2NGQyMmNlYmY3MzA0ZTkzJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.5d5WyLlUW7JU1Vai2we8UKi0r_9CL87VO2YzhMvW39Y&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;推荐人&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;本地购物&lt;/strong&gt;：德里到处都有供应商，明智的做法是与当地朋友一起去，以免被多收费。 Lajpat Nagar 是当地购物的好地方，但为了公平的价格和质量，我建议坚持去购物中心。不过，Lajpat Nagar 的喧嚣还是值得体验的，尤其是美味的街头小吃。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;购物中心&lt;/strong&gt;：购物中心是购买正宗印度商品和享受美食的可靠方式：&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;古尔冈 Ambience Mall：靠近会议场地，提供各种购物、美食和活动。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;DLF Mall of India，诺伊达：印度最大的购物中心，也是我个人最喜欢的美食和购物场所。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;选择 Saket Citywalk：这里是夜生活和购物的热门场所。隔壁的 DLF 购物中心非常适合餐馆。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;街头小吃&lt;/strong&gt;：虽然德里以街头小吃而闻名，但在卫生方面却可能参差不齐。我建议坚持去 Haldiram’s 或 Bikanervala 等值得信赖的连锁店购买安全、正宗的街头食品和糖果。如果您喜欢冒险，Lajpat Nagar、Amar Colony 和 Connaught Place 也有不错的街头美食选择。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;古尔冈第 32 座里程碑&lt;/strong&gt;：一个充满活力的地区，拥有各种餐厅和酒吧，提供各种美食和充满活力的氛围。距离会议已经很近了场地，非常适合晚上外出。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;在德里可以做的事情&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#things-to-do-在德里&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559742-93580717-b270-4756-9c5a-02892fe312ce.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9 .eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80M jY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk3NDITOTM1ODA3MTctYjI3MC00NzU2LTljNWEtMDI4OTJmZTMxMmNlLmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0 lbVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJ LGTQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT1iMWUxMjFiZTQwMzk1ZTMzNWNlOGY5ZTQzYjBlNTk3OWZhYWQ2MjQyNjRiYzY3NTNjNmJmMDczMDE5ZTRIYjNlJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlCNM9aG9zdC J9.ZrMYBPLLTZzCjTGId8CpQeRGsWh8n714-z8OIVVpeXQ&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img 解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559742-93580717- b270-4756-9c5a-02892fe312ce.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSI简单SI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk3NDITOTM1ODA3MTctYji3MC00NzU2LTljNWEtMDI4OTJmZTMxMmNlLmpwZWc _WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X 3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJ LGtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT1iMWUxMjFiZTQwMzk1ZTMzNWNlOGY5ZTQzYjBlNTk3OWZhYWQ2M jQyNjRiYzY3NTNjNmJmMDczMDE5ZTRiYjNlJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.ZrMYBPLLTZzCjTGId8CpQeRGsWh8n714-z8OIVVpeXQ&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;印度门&lt;/strong&gt;：为纪念印度士兵而建的纪念性战争纪念碑，周围环绕着美丽的草坪，是夜间宁静漫步的好去处。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;莲花寺&lt;/strong&gt;：这座寺庙以其令人惊叹的花朵形状而闻名，是一处宁静的冥想之地。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;阿克萨达姆神庙&lt;/strong&gt;：一座令人惊叹的现代寺庙建筑群，通过错综复杂的建筑、花园和美丽的水秀展示了印度丰富的文化遗产。这里的宏伟和宁静是必游之地。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;红堡&lt;/strong&gt;：莫卧儿时代的一座宏伟堡垒，让您一睹德里的历史意义。虽然月光集市具有重要的历史意义，但它却非常拥挤，扒窃的风险很高。该地区经常很脏，除了当地市场之外没有什么可做的。我建议您跳过它，除非您有特定的访问原因。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;全国博物馆&lt;/strong&gt;：印度数千年艺术、历史和文化的宝库。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dilli Haat&lt;/strong&gt;：一个市场，出售来自印度各邦的传统手工艺品和食品。购买正宗印度纪念品的必去之地。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;夜生活&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#nightlife&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3 &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559949-346f155d-1ee8-4d02-b73d-ebbe92c65b85.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9 .eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsImtleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk5NDktMzQ2ZjE1NWQtMWVlOC00ZDAyLWI3M2QtZWJiZTkyYzY1Yjg1LmpwZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT0yZTVmZjQzZGUwOWZmM2RlM2ZmYzg4MGRiNzU1YWUyZmIyYTdlMDdhOGI2OTE0N2ZlM2VmMDhmZDgzZTJmZDdiJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.Ps4qIU8U3gFrr4WHoLvVMHHzDLkcP0x40j6OqUoDvs4&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://private-user-images.githubusercontent.com/42698533/372559949-346f155d-1ee8- 4d02-b73d-ebbe92c65b85.jpeg?jwt=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9.eyJpc3MiOiJnaXRodWIuY29tIiwiYXVkIjoicmF3LmdpdGh1YnVzZXJjb250ZW50LmNvbSIsim tleSI6ImtleTUiLCJleHAiOjE3Mjk1MTc2MDQsIm5iZiI6MTcyOTUxNzMwNCwicGF0aCI6Ii80MjY5ODUzMy8zNzI1NTk5NDktMzQ2ZjE1NWQtMWVloC00ZDAyLWI3M2QtZWJiZTkyYzY1Yjg1Lmpw ZWc_WC1BbXotQWxnb3JpdGhtPUFXUzQtSE1BQy1TSEEyNTYmWC1BbXotQ3JlZGVudGlhbD1BS0lBVkNPRFlMU0E1M1BRSzRaQSUyRjIwMjQxMDIxJTJGdXMtZWFzdC0xJTJGczMlMkZhd3M 0X3JlcXVlc3QmWC1BbXotRGF0ZT0yMDI0MTAyMVQxMzI4MjRaJlgtQW16LUV4cGlyZXM9MzAwJlgtQW16LVNpZ25hdHVyZT0yZTVmZjQzZGUwOWZmM2RlM2ZmYzg4MGRiNzU1YWUyZmIy YTdlMDdhOGI2OTE0N2ZlM2VmMDhmZDgzZTJmZDdiJlgtQW16LVNpZ25lZEhlYWRlcnM9aG9zdCJ9.Ps4qIU8U3gFrr4WHoLvVMHHzDLkcP0x40j6OqUoDvs4&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;康诺特广场 (CP)&lt;/strong&gt;：最适合夜生活的区域，遍布酒吧和餐馆，而且安全，有定期警察巡逻。它还靠近许多大使馆，确保提供专业且安全的环境。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DLF Cyber​​Hub&lt;/strong&gt;：古尔冈的 Cyber​​Hub 位于会议场地附近，是一个拥有众多办公室、餐厅和酒吧的绝佳地点。干净而现代，提供各种餐饮和娱乐选择。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hauz Khas Social&lt;/strong&gt;：很受欢迎，但往往会吸引年轻人群。如果您正在寻找更专业的氛围，请选择 CP 或 Cyber​​Hub。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;重要提示&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kunal-kushwaha/blogs/blob/main/DELHI_GUIDE.md#important-tips&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;污染&lt;/strong&gt;：虽然现在看起来不错，但12月德里在排灯节后的污染是出了名的，所以建议带上口罩进行防护。您将确切地知道排灯节后 12 月（即 2024 年 11 月 1 日后）的空气质量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安全&lt;/strong&gt;：德里总体上是一个安全的城市，尤其是当您与他人在一起时。就我个人而言，我觉得德里比其他一些城市更安全。坚持去我推荐的地方或向值得信赖的当地人寻求建议。避免进入光线不足的小巷，尤其是在晚上，最好有人结伴出行。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;语言&lt;/strong&gt;：印地语是德里使用最广泛的语言，但大多数人也会说英语。不过，当地供应商和 Uber 司机可能不会那么流利，因此使用 Google 翻译或有懂该语言的人陪伴会很有帮助。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;德里提供多种多样的体验，从世界上最好的美食到丰富的文化和历史景观。祝您游览这座城市愉快，并充分利用 KubeCon India 2024！如果您有任何疑问，请随时在 CNCF Slack 上给我留言。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;再见！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes CI/CD pipeline with Jenkins and Devtron】Kubernetes CI/CD 管道与 Jenkins 和 Devtron</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/17/kubernetes-ci-cd-pipeline-with-jenkins-and-devtron/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-ci-cd-pipeline-with-jenkins-and-devtron/&#34;&gt;Devtron’s blog&lt;/a&gt; by Bhushan Nemade&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt;: Build a powerful Kubernetes CI/CD pipeline using Jenkins and Devtron. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/what-is-jenkins-a-quick-guide-for-ci-cd-with-jenkins/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;previous blog on Jenkins&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we already covered how to set up a Jenkins pipeline, and the pros and cons of Jenkins for CI/CD pipelines for Kubernetes environments. In this blog, we will dive deep into potential challenges that can be faced if Continuous Deployments (CD) are managed through Jenkins. We will also take a look at how we can execute robust Continuous Deployments in complex Kubernetes environments keeping Jenkins for Continuous Integration (CI) and integrating Jenkins with Devtron for complete CI/CD experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;continuous-deployment-pipelines-with-jenkins&#34;&gt;Continuous Deployment Pipelines with Jenkins&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We recommend avoiding Jenkins for Continuous Deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins was originally designed for Continuous Integration (CI). Still, with the level of flexibility, Jenkins has been used for Continuous Deployments. It comes with multiple Jenkins plugins that can be integrated within the pipelines to execute Continuous Deployments through Jenkins. The CD pipelines through Jenkins can be managed in two ways:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrating as a Stage into Jenkins CI Pipeline&lt;/strong&gt;: With this approach, you can add a new stage to your existing build pipeline which will execute deployment to the Kubernetes environments. Typically, you will have to write your custom scripts to apply the configurations on the target environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Setting a Dedicated Jenkins Agent&lt;/strong&gt;: Configure a separate Jenkins agent on your target Kubernetes environment. This agent will be responsible for executing deployments to target environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;disadvantages-of-jenkins-for-continous-deployments-cd-on-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Disadvantages of Jenkins for Continous Deployments (CD) on Kubernetes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even though Jenkins has been used widely for Continuous Integration (CI) and Continuous Deployment (CD), there are certain pitfalls where you would not want to use Jenkins. Here are some of the disadvantages of Jenkins for Continuous Deployment on Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;extensive-scripting&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extensive Scripting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins pipelines are executed through groovy scripts, when it comes to deploying applications/services to multiple environments it becomes tedious and error-prone to write and manage these scripts. Additionally, there is a learning curve to understand Groovy and write those scripts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;complex-configurations&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Complex&amp;nbsp;Configurations&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Managing crucial configurations through Jenkins scripts poses risks of misconfigurations and potential leaks of sensitive information. It also makes it challenging to audit and track configuration changes effectively. It heavily relies on plugins, and managing a large number of plugins can become challenging as they need to be frequently updated to avoid compatibility issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;security-issues&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Issues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Jenkins, every process/step gets handled through a Jenkins pipeline which is in the form of a script and as the scale increases it becomes more complex to manage those scripts and might impose human errors. Additionally, Jenkins has a complicated permission and access control system, especially when working with large teams. Managing fine-grained access control across multiple teams and projects is not as straightforward as in some other modern Continuous Deployment (CD) tools like ArgoCD or Devtron. Since Jenkins relies heavily on third-party plugins, it can introduce security vulnerabilities, especially if plugins are not regularly updated, and managing the complex web of plugins itself is a big challenge. Here are some references to previous zero-day vulnerabilities in Jenkins because of the vast web of plugin ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jenkins.io/security/advisory/2024-01-24/?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://www.jenkins.io/security/advisory/2024-01-24/&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.trendmicro.com/en_in/research/24/c/cve-2024-23897.html?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://www.trendmicro.com/en_in/research/24/c/cve-2024-23897.html&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/jenkins-discloses-dozens-of-zero-day-bugs-in-multiple-plugins/?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/jenkins-discloses-dozens-of-zero-day-bugs-in-multiple-plugins/&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://nordicdefender.com/blog/critical-jenkins-vulnerability-cve-2024-23897?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://nordicdefender.com/blog/critical-jenkins-vulnerability-cve-2024-23897&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;lack-of-production-capabilities&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of Production Capabilities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins was originally designed for Continuous Integration (CI), but it has been extended to continuous deployment with some hacks and plugins. Even with custom scripts and plugins, it lacks built-in production capabilities which are highly important for a stable production pipeline such as policy-driven pipelines, approval workflows, prod configuration protection, DR mechanisms, configuration drifts, release management, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;absence-of-production-grade-capabilities&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Absence&amp;nbsp;of Production-Grade Capabilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins was originally designed for Continuous Integration, but it has limitations in deployment capabilities. It lacks built-in approval workflows and gates for production deployments, as well as native support for advanced deployment strategies like canary releases or blue-green deployments. Jenkins also lacks to provide visibility and rollback capabilities for production deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;maintenance-overhead&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintenance Overhead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Executing CI/CD pipeline operations using Jenkins is handled by multiple plugins and extensive scripts. These plugins and pipelines need to be verified from time to time to make sure that the current version is supported. With time and scale, this becomes a tedious process and an overhead work to keep everything up to date. Additionally, Jenkins can become resource-intensive, especially in larger setups with multiple pipelines and concurrent builds. It often requires dedicated servers and frequent performance tuning as performance degrades over time because of concurrent builds and jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;lack-of-advanced-deployment-strategies&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of Advanced Deployment Strategies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins doesn’t natively support advanced deployment strategies such as canary releases, blue-green deployments, or rolling updates. Achieving these requires custom scripting or integrating third-party tools.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;no-native-monitoring-or-observability&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Native Monitoring or Observability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins does not come with advanced monitoring, logging, or observability features out of the box. To gain insight into deployment health or performance, you need to integrate external monitoring tools and create your custom dashboard in maybe Grafana. For your workloads deployed on Kubernetes, you can’t see the real-time status of the workloads, if it is deployed or in a pending state, which again is one of the important aspects of any continuous deployment which is available in modern continuous deployment (CD) tools like ArgoCD or Devtron.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;not-native-to-kubernetes&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not Native to Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins is not designed specifically for Kubernetes, so managing Kubernetes deployments can be clunky and inefficient compared to Kubernetes-native tools like ArgoCD, FluxCD, or Devtron. For Kubernetes deployment, Jenkins often requires additional tools or scripts for integration, leading to more complex configurations. Additionally, Jenkins is not cloud-native. It was originally designed for on-premise setups. While it can be adapted for cloud environments, it doesn’t offer the seamless integration, autoscaling, and cost optimization features of cloud-native CD tools designed specifically for Kubernetes environments. In cloud-native environments, Jenkins often needs manual scaling for build agents and resources, unlike modern CD tools that automatically scale based on load.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;limited-gitops-support&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limited GitOps Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins doesn’t natively support GitOps workflows, which are increasingly popular for continuous deployment in Kubernetes environments. This requires the integration of additional layers of configuration and tools to achieve a GitOps model which introduces the management of different tools, thus increasing the complexity. Additionally, it doesn’t have an automated/ SLO-based rollback mechanism which is highly critical for continuous deployment pipelines&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-the-ideal-continuous-deployment-platform-checklist-for-kubernetes&#34;&gt;What is the ideal Continuous Deployment Platform checklist for Kubernetes?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Continuous Deployment is a crucial component of the software development lifecycle, which provides the capability to execute lightning-fast deployments. Every deployment going to the production servers is responsible for the status of applications/services for users; for instance, if one single deployment goes wrong, the impact can be worse as disruption of all services. To strike a balance between stability and innovation, every deployment going to any server should be passed through some checklist. The ideal checklist for continuous deployment can be:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;robust-access-management-rbac&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Robust Access Management (RBAC)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Having a robust RBAC is crucial for the deployment process, as it ensures that only authorized stakeholders can take crucial actions, such as triggering deployments at production servers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;policy-driven-pipelines&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Policy-Driven Pipelines&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enforcing certain policies ensures that the best practices are being followed before executing the deployments. For instance, the policies can be like a mandatory scan of Docker images before deployments, on which if vulnerabilities are detected, the deployment will be aborted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;approval-based-deployments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Approval-Based Deployments&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The approval process reduces the chances of the wrong deployment going to the production environments and disrupting the services across regions. Setting up an approval process where the stakeholders need to approve the deployment reduces the chances of service disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;controlled-deployments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Controlled Deployments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It helps you gain control over deployments, ensuring stability and preventing disruptions during peak hours. Define time slots for planned deployments or block deployments entirely for critical business hours.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NOTE: Devtron supports a robust CI, which is precisely crafted for Kubernetes environments and offers multiple features and flexibility. However, in this blog, we will focus exclusively on Devtron’s CD capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;continuous-deployments-with-devtron&#34;&gt;Continuous Deployments with Devtron&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CD capabilities of Devtron include features such as choosing the deployment type Automatic or Manual, way of deployment Helm or GitOps, multiple deployment strategies, approval-based deployments, and pre-post deployment stages. Let’s get our hands on the Devtron dashboard and deploy the application.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For this blog, we will use Jenkins in collaboration with Devtron to build, deploy, and manage our Kubernetes application. In the previous blog where we built an image and pushed it to the Docker hub, we will be using the same image (built by Jenkins) and deploying it through Devtron using all CD capabilities of the dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-1-installation-of-devtron&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1: Installation of Devtron&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To install Devtron the only prerequisite is to have a running Kubernetes cluster. For complete installation of Devtron&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/install?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;follow their documentation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-2-creating-application-workflows&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2: Creating Application Workflows&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once we have installed Devtron, we can start by&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/applications/create-application?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;creating a new application&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;configuring the CI/CD workflows. Before setting CI/CD pipelines we need to set some configurations i.e.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/applications/creating-application/git-material?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Git Repository&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/applications/creating-application/docker-build-configuration?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Build Configurations&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/applications/creating-application/deployment-template?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Base Configurations&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to know how to set them up you can follow&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Devtron’s documentation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Now that we are done with all the required configurations, let’s make our workflows i.e. CI/CD pipelines. As for this blog, we are going to use Jenkins as our CI pipeline Devtron offers two ways to execute deployments. Let’s check them one by one. The first one is Deploy Image from External Service here, Devtron provides us an External Webhook to execute the deployments. Another one is Deployment Using JobCI, which will be executed using the Devtron JobCI of Devtron and Devtron’s plugin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-3-configuring-external-webhook&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3: Configuring External Webhook&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the configurations are done choose the type of pipeline for deployment, for this instance, we are choosing, Deploy Image from External Service as we already have a docker image built through jenkins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/build-with-webhook.png&#34; alt=&#34;Devtron&#39;s-externalwebhook-deployment&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 1] Devtron’s external webhook deployment&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After selecting the type pipeline i.e. Deploy Image from External Service, we are redirected to configurations of the CD pipeline. At the CD pipeline configuration, we need to provide the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Environment&lt;/strong&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Namespace&lt;/strong&gt;, and choose the execution type&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Automatic&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Manual&lt;/strong&gt;. Moreover with Devtron we also get the capability to execute advanced deployment strategies i.e.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Rolling&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Recreate&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Canary&lt;/strong&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Blue-Green&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/configure-external-cd.png&#34; alt=&#34;Externalwebhook-deployment-config&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 2] External webhook deployment config&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On completing the above configurations cliche&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Create Pipeline,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;now we will be able to visualize the application workflow i.e. the CI/CD pipeline for the application. The CI part will be executed on the Jenkins server and the generated Docker image will be fetched by the webhook. The CD pipeline of Devtron will help us perform robust CD operation&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/webhook-pipeline.png&#34; alt=&#34;Devtron-webhook-pipeline&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 3] Devtron webhook pipeline&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s do some configurations for our External Webhook we need to use a cURL request in our Jenkins pipeline which will let Devtron know that the image is built by an external service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On Workflow Editor click External Source (Webhook) &amp;gt; Select or auto-generate token with required permissions &amp;gt; Auto-generate token &amp;gt; {Enter the name for token} &amp;gt; Generate token.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Click Sample cURL request &amp;gt; copy the Sample cURL request and integrate it into your Jenkins pipeline along with the Auto-generate token and tag for Docker Image.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/webhook-config.png&#34; alt=&#34;Webhookconfiguration&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 4] Webhook configuration&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-4-devtron%E2%80%99s-cd-through-external-webhook&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step: 4 Devtron’s CD through External Webhook&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that we have configured the External webhook for CI, let’s set the CD pipeline through Devtron.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Click Deploy (deployment pipeline), and you will be navigated to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Edit deployment pipeline,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;where you can configure a robust CD pipeline.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To make sure that the deployment going to the critical environments is vulnerability-free, you can navigate to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Pre-Deployment stage.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;At this stage, you can configure Devtron’s plugins for scanning the Docker image, in case any vulnerabilities are detected you can stop the deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/scan-plugins.png&#34; alt=&#34;Devtron&#39;s-plugins&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 5] Devtron’s Plugins&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron also allows you to set an approval process, where before the execution of each deployment approval from relevant stakeholders is required. To set an approval navigate to the Deployment stage &amp;gt; Approval for deployment, here you can select the number of approvals required before executing the deployment to specific environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, you can select the way you want to execute the deployment pipeline, i.e. Automatic or Manual.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/approval-flow.png&#34; alt=&#34;Approval-for-deployments&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 6] Approval for deployments&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To set the notifications on completion of the deployment process, you can navigate to the Post Deployment stage and configure the plugins like Custom Email Notifier. Which will be sending notifications for the completion of the deployment process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/CD-Notification.png&#34; alt=&#34;Notifier-on-completion-of-CD&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 7] Notifier on completion of CD&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once every configuration is done click Update Pipeline, and trigger your application pipeline accordingly. Once the application is deployed you can manage your applications through Devtron’s dashboard where you can leverage multiple other features like Deployment Window for controlled deployments, configuration management across environments, robust user access management, and many more. You can follow Devtron’s documentation to explore this further.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;stage5-deployment-using-jobci&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stage:5 Deployment Using JobCI&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another way we can deploy to applications using Devtron and Jenkins is by using a JobCI pipeline. In Devtron we need to select Create a job.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/Job-ci-pipeline.png&#34; alt=&#34;Job-CI-Pipeline&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 8] Job CI Pipeline&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To configure the Job CI and CD pipeline, navigate to New Workflow &amp;gt; Create a job &amp;gt; You will be redirected to the Basic configuration &amp;gt; Set the basic configurations like Pipeline Name, Source Type, and Branch Name.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/jobci-configure.png&#34; alt=&#34;Job-creation&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 9] Job creation&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the Basic Configurations are done, navigate to the Task to be executed. Here, you need to add Devtron’s plugins which will facilitate the triggering of the Jenkins pipeline are deployment of applications through Devtron.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/plugins/plugin-list/jenkins?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;Jenkins plugin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;of Devtron, helps us to remotely trigger our Jenkins pipelines and fetch the logs to the Devtron dashboard. Once the pipeline is executed successfully the generated container image will be available for us to deploy on the Devtron dashboard (provided that your Jenkins pipeline is pushing the docker image to the container registry which is configured with Devtron).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/jenkins-plugin-2.png&#34; alt=&#34;Jenkins-Plugin&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 10] Jenkins Plugin&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In case the container registry is not configured with Devtron, you can utilize the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/plugins/plugin-list/pull-images-from-container-repository?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;pull images from the container repository plugin&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;of Devtron. This plugin continuously polls the specified container registry and pulls images from the container repository to Devtron for deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/pull-image-plugin.png&#34; alt=&#34;Pull-image-from-container-repository&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig. 11] Pull image from container repository&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Click the Update Pipeline button, and that’s it. We have configured Job CI, which will trigger our Jenkins CI pipeline and fetch the container image for deployment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the CD pipeline with Devtron, you can refer to Step No. 4, where it’s been described how we can configure and execute the robust CD pipeline with Devtron.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Jenkins is a powerful CI/CD tool, it has notable disadvantages as a continuous deployment tool, particularly for modern, cloud-native, and Kubernetes-centric environments. Alternatives like ArgoCD, FluxCD, or Devtron offer better out-of-the-box integrations for advanced deployment strategies, GitOps workflows, and Kubernetes management, making them more suitable for many organizations looking for scalable and automated CD solutions. In this blog, we have covered the potential disadvantages of Jenkins when it comes to continuous deployment (CD) for Kubernetes, capabilities for an ideal CD pipeline, and how Devtron helps us to set up a robust CI/CD pipeline integrating with Jenkins.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron stands out as a complete solution when it comes to managing Kubernetes and has the capabilities to handle robust continuous deployment (CD) operations like robust RBAC, approval-workflows, Devtron’s plugins, vulnerability scanning, configuration drift management, release orchestration, and team collaborations. When it comes to managing the multiple Kubernetes cluster resources and day 2 operations like managing multiple applications spread across multiple Kubernetes clusters, Devtron comes as a savior&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have any queries, don’t hesitate to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rebrand.ly/devtron-demo?ref=blog&#34;&gt;connect with us&lt;/a&gt;. Join the lively discussions and shared knowledge in our actively growing&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rebrand.ly/Devtron-Discord?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;Discord Community&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related articles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-ci-cd-pipelines-with-jenkins-and-argocd/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes CI/CD Pipelines with Jenkins and ArgoCD&lt;/a&gt;2 days ago11 min read&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/what-is-jenkins-a-quick-guide-for-ci-cd-with-jenkins/&#34;&gt;What is Jenkins? A Quick Guide for CI/CD with Jenkins&lt;/a&gt;a month ago12 min read&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/devtron-vs-jenkins-how-do-they-stack-against/&#34;&gt;Devtron vs Jenkins: Jenkins Alternatives for Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初发布于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-ci-cd-pipeline-with-jenkins-and-devtron/&#34;&gt;Devtron 博客&lt;/a&gt;作者：Bhushan Nemade&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt;：使用 Jenkins 和 Devtron 构建强大的 Kubernetes CI/CD 管道。 &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/what-is-jenkins-a-quick-guide-for-ci-cd-with-jenkins/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;上一篇博客中Jenkins&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，我们已经介绍了如何设置 Jenkins 管道，以及 Jenkins 用于 Kubernetes 环境的 CI/CD 管道的优缺点。在本博客中，我们将深入探讨通过 Jenkins 管理持续部署 (CD) 时可能面临的潜在挑战。我们还将研究如何在复杂的 Kubernetes 环境中执行强大的持续部署，保持 Jenkins 进行持续集成 (CI) 并将 Jenkins 与 Devtron 集成以获得完整的 CI/CD 体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;continuous-deployment-pipelines-with-jenkins&#34;&gt;使用 Jenkins 持续部署管道&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们建议避免使用 Jenkins 进行持续部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins 最初是为持续集成 (CI) 而设计的。尽管如此，凭借灵活性，Jenkins 已被用于持续部署。它配备了多个 Jenkins 插件，可以集成到管道中以通过 Jenkins 执行持续部署。通过 Jenkins 的 CD 管道可以通过两种方式进行管理：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;作为阶段集成到 Jenkins CI 管道&lt;/strong&gt;：通过这种方法，您可以向现有构建管道添加一个新阶段，该阶段将执行到 Kubernetes 环境的部署。通常，您必须编写自定义脚本才能在目标环境上应用配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;设置专用 Jenkins 代理&lt;/strong&gt;：在目标 Kubernetes 环境上配置单独的 Jenkins 代理。该代理将负责执行到目标环境的部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;disadvantages-of-jenkins-for-continous-deployments-cd-on-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Jenkins 在 Kubernetes 上进行持续部署 (CD) 的缺点&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管 Jenkins 已广泛用于持续集成 (CI) 和持续部署 (CD)，但仍存在某些您不想使用 Jenkins 的陷阱。以下是 Jenkins 在 Kubernetes 上进行持续部署的一些缺点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;extense-scripting&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;扩展脚本&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins 管道是通过 Groovy 脚本执行的，当将应用程序/服务部署到多个环境时，编写和管理这些脚本变得乏味且容易出错。此外，理解 Groovy 和 w 有一个学习曲线编写这些脚本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;complex-configurations&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;复杂配置&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过 Jenkins 脚本管理关键配置会带来配置错误和敏感信息潜在泄露的风险。这也使得有效审核和跟踪配置更改变得具有挑战性。它严重依赖插件，管理大量插件可能会变得具有挑战性，因为它们需要经常更新以避免兼容性问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;security-issues&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安全问题&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Jenkins 中，每个流程/步骤都通过 Jenkins 管道进行处理，该管道采用脚本的形式，随着规模的增加，管理这些脚本变得更加复杂，并且可能会造成人为错误。此外，Jenkins 具有复杂的权限和访问控制系统，尤其是在与大型团队合作时。跨多个团队和项目管理细粒度的访问控制并不像 ArgoCD 或 Devtron 等其他一些现代持续部署 (CD) 工具那么简单。由于 Jenkins 严重依赖第三方插件，因此可能会引入安全漏洞，特别是在插件不定期更新的情况下，管理复杂的插件网络本身就是一个巨大的挑战。由于插件生态系统庞大，因此以下是 Jenkins 中以前的零日漏洞的一些参考。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jenkins.io/security/advisory/2024-01-24/?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://www.jenkins.io/security /咨询/2024-01-24/&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.trendmicro.com/en_in/research/24/c/cve-2024-23897.html?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://www. trendmicro.com/en_in/research/24/c/cve-2024-23897.html&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/jenkins-discloses-dozens-of-zero-day-bugs-in-multiple-plugins/?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt; &lt;u&gt;https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/jenkins-discloses-dozens-of-zero-day-bugs-in-multiple-plugins/&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://nordicdefender.com/blog/ritic-jenkins-vulnerability-cve-2024-23897?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://nordicdefender.com/blog/关键詹金斯漏洞-cve-2024-23897&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;lack-of-product-capability&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;缺乏生产能力&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins 最初是为持续集成（CI）而设计的，但它已通过一些技巧和插件扩展到持续部署。即使使用自定义脚本和插件，它也缺乏内置的生产功能，这对于稳定的生产管道非常重要，例如策略驱动的管道、审批工作流程、产品配置保护、灾难恢复机制、配置漂移、发布管理等等。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;absence-of-Production-grade-capability&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;缺乏生产n 级能力&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins 最初是为持续集成而设计的，但它在部署能力上有局限性。它缺乏用于生产部署的内置审批工作流程和大门，以及对金丝雀发布或蓝绿部署等高级部署策略的本机支持。 Jenkins 还缺乏为生产部署提供可见性和回滚功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;maintenance-overhead&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;维护开销&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用 Jenkins 执行 CI/CD 管道操作是由多个插件和大量脚本处理的。这些插件和管道需要不时进行验证，以确保支持当前版本。随着时间的推移和规模的扩大，这将成为一个乏味的过程，并且是一项使所有内容保持最新的开销工作。此外，Jenkins 可能会变得资源密集型，尤其是在具有多个管道和并发构建的大型设置中。它通常需要专用服务器和频繁的性能调整，因为并发构建和作业会导致性能随着时间的推移而下降。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;lack-of-advanced-deployment-strategies&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;缺乏高级部署策略&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins 本身不支持高级部署策略，例如金丝雀发布、蓝绿部署或滚动更新。实现这些需要自定义脚本或集成第三方工具。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;no-native-monitoring-or-observability&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;无本机监控或可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins 不具备开箱即用的高级监控、日志记录或可观察性功能。为了深入了解部署运行状况或性能，您需要集成外部监控工具并在 Grafana 中创建自定义仪表板。对于部署在 Kubernetes 上的工作负载，您无法看到工作负载的实时状态（无论是已部署还是处于挂起状态），这又是现代持续部署中可用的任何持续部署的重要方面之一(CD) 工具，例如 ArgoCD 或 Devtron。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;not-native-to-kubernetes&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;不是 Kubernetes 原生&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins 并不是专门为 Kubernetes 设计的，因此与 ArgoCD、FluxCD 或 Devtron 等 Kubernetes 原生工具相比，管理 Kubernetes 部署可能会显得笨拙且低效。对于 Kubernetes 部署，Jenkins 通常需要额外的工具或脚本进行集成，导致配置更加复杂。此外，Jenkins 不是云原生的。它最初是为本地设置而设计的。虽然它可以适应云环境，但它不提供专为 Kubernetes 环境设计的云原生 CD 工具的无缝集成、自动扩展和成本优化功能。在云原生环境中，Jenkins经常需要手动与根据负载自动扩展的现代 CD 工具不同，可扩展构建代理和资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;limited-gitops-support&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;有限的 GitOps 支持&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jenkins 本身并不支持 GitOps 工作流程，而 GitOps 工作流程在 Kubernetes 环境中的持续部署中越来越受欢迎。这需要集成额外的配置和工具层来实现 GitOps 模型，该模型引入了不同工具的管理，从而增加了复杂性。此外，它没有自动/基于 SLO 的回滚机制，这对于持续部署管道非常关键&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-the-ideal-continuous-deployment-platform-checklist-for-kubernetes&#34;&gt;理想的 Kubernetes 持续部署平台清单是什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;持续部署是软件开发生命周期的重要组成部分，它提供了执行闪电般快速部署的能力。进入生产服务器的每个部署都对用户的应用程序/服务的状态负责；例如，如果一个部署出现问题，那么影响可能会更严重，因为所有服务都会中断。为了在稳定性和创新之间取得平衡，任何服务器的每次部署都应该通过一些检查表。持续部署的理想清单可以是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;robust-access-management-rbac&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;强大的访问管理 (RBAC)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;拥有强大的 RBAC 对于部署过程至关重要，因为它确保只有授权的利益相关者才能采取关键操作，例如在生产服务器上触发部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;policy-driven-pipelines&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;策略驱动管道&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;执行某些策略可确保在执行部署之前遵循最佳实践。例如，这些策略可以像在部署之前对 Docker 镜像进行强制扫描，如果检测到漏洞，部署就会中止。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;approval-based-deployments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;基于审批的部署&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;审批流程减少了错误部署到生产环境并中断跨区域服务的可能性。设置利益相关者需要批准部署的审批流程可以减少服务中断的可能性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;control-deployments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;受控部署&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它可以帮助您控制部署，确保稳定性并防止高峰时段出现中断。定义计划部署的时间段或在关键业务时间完全阻止部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow” &gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意：Devtron 支持强大的 CI，该 CI 专为 Kubernetes 环境精心设计，并提供多种功能和灵活性。不过，在本博客中，我们将专门关注 Devtron 的 CD 功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;continuous-deployments-with-devtron&#34;&gt;使用 Devtron 进行持续部署&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron 的 CD 功能包括选择部署类型自动或手动、部署方式 Helm 或 GitOps、多种部署策略、基于批准的部署以及部署前阶段等功能。让我们开始使用 Devtron 仪表板并部署应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本博客中，我们将与 Devtron 合作使用 Jenkins 来构建、部署和管理我们的 Kubernetes 应用程序。在上一篇博客中，我们构建了一个映像并将其推送到 Docker 中心，我们将使用相同的映像（由 Jenkins 构建）并使用仪表板的所有 CD 功能通过 Devtron 进行部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-1-installation-of-devtron&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 1 步：安装 Devtron&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要安装 Devtron，唯一的先决条件是拥有正在运行的 Kubernetes 集群。要完整安装 Devtron &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/install?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;请遵循其文档&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-2-creating-application-workflows&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 2 步：创建应用程序工作流程&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;安装 Devtron 后，我们可以开始&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/applications/create-application?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;创建一个新应用程序&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;并配置 CI/CD 工作流程。在设置 CI/CD 管道之前，我们需要设置一些配置，即 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/applications/creating-application/git-material?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt; Git 存储库&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/applications/creating-application/docker-build-configuration?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;构建配置&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/applications/creating-application/deployment-template?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;基础配置&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;要了解如何设置它们，您可以按照&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Devtron 的文档&lt;/u &gt;&lt;/a&gt;。现在我们已经完成了所有必需的配置，让我们创建我们的工作流程，即 CI/CD 管道。对于本博客，我们将使用 Jenkins 作为我们的 CI 管道 Devtron 提供了两种执行部署的方法。让我们一一检查一下。第一个是从外部服务部署映像，Devtron 为我们提供了一个外部 Webhook 来执行部署。另一种是Deployment using JobCI，它将使用Devtron的Devtron JobCI和Devtron的插件来执行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-3-configuring-external-webhook&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 3 步：配置外部 Webhook&lt;/强&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;配置完成后，选择部署管道的类型，在本例中，我们选择从外部服务部署映像，因为我们已经通过 jenkins 构建了 docker 映像。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/build-with-webhook.png&#34; alt= “Devtron&#39;s-externalwebhook-deployment”referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[图 1] 1]Devtron的外部webhook部署&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;选择类型管道（即从外部服务部署映像）后，我们将重定向到 CD 管道的配置。在 CD 管道配置中，我们需要提供&lt;strong&gt;环境&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;命名空间&lt;/strong&gt;，并选择执行类型&lt;strong&gt;自动&lt;/strong&gt;或&lt;strong&gt;手动&lt;/强&gt;。此外，通过 Devtron，我们还能够执行高级部署策略，即&lt;strong&gt;滚动&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;重新创建&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;金丝雀&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;蓝绿&lt;/strong&gt;强&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/configure-external-cd.png&#34; alt= “Externalwebhook-deployment-config”referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“wp-element-caption”&gt; [图。 2]外部webhook部署配置&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成上述配置（陈词滥调）&lt;strong&gt;创建管道&lt;/strong&gt;后，现在我们将能够可视化应用程序工作流程，即应用程序的 CI/CD 管道。 CI 部分将在 Jenkins 服务器上执行，生成的 Docker 镜像将由 webhook 获取。 Devtron的CD管道将帮助我们执行稳健的CD操作&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/webhook-pipeline.png&#34; alt=&#34;Devtron -webhook-pipeline&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[图。 3] Devtron webhook 管道&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们对外部 Webhook 进行一些配置，我们需要在 Jenkins 管道中使用 cURL 请求，这将使 Devtron 知道该映像是由外部服务构建的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在工作流程编辑器上，单击外部源 (Webhook) &gt; 选择或自动生成具有所需权限的令牌 &gt; 自动生成令牌 &gt; {输入令牌的名称} &gt; 生成令牌。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;单击示例 cURL 请求 &gt; 复制示例 cURL 请求并将其与 Docker 映像的自动生成令牌和标记一起集成到 Jenkins 管道中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/webhook-config.png&#34; alt=&#34;Webhookconfiguration “referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“wp-element-caption”&gt; [图。 4]Webhook配置&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;step-4-devtron%E2%80%99s-cd-through-external-webhook&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;步骤：通过外部 Webhook 获取 4 Devtron 的 CD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在我们已经为 CI 配置了外部 webhook，让我们通过 Devtron 设置 CD 管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;点击“部署”（部署管道），您将导航到&lt;strong&gt;编辑部署管道&lt;/strong&gt;，您可以在其中配置强大的 CD 管道。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了确保关键环境的部署没有漏洞，您可以导航到&lt;strong&gt;预部署阶段。 &lt;/strong&gt;在此阶段，您可以配置 Devtron 的插件来扫描 Docker 映像，如果检测到任何漏洞，您可以停止部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/scan-plugins.png&#34; alt=&#34;Devtron的-plugins&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[图。 5] Devtron 的插件&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron 还允许您设置批准流程，在执行每个部署之前都需要获得相关利益相关者的批准。要设置批准，请导航至部署阶段 &gt; 部署批准，您可以在此处选择执行部署到特定环境之前所需的批准数量。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，您还可以选择执行部署管道的方式，即自动或手动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/approval-flow.png&#34; alt=&#34;批准-for-deployments&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[图 1] 6]批准部署&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要设置部署过程完成时的通知，您可以导航到部署后阶段并配置自定义电子邮件通知程序等插件。这将发送部署过程完成的通知。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/CD-Notification.png&#34; alt=&#34;Notifier -on-completion-of-CD&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[图。 7] CD 完成时的通知&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成每个配置后，单击“更新管道”，并相应地触发您的应用程序管道。应用程序部署完成后，您可以通过 Devtron 的仪表板管理您的应用程序，您可以利用多种其他功能，例如用于受控部署的部署窗口、跨环境的配置管理、强大的用户访问管理等等。您可以按照 Devtron 的文档进一步探索。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;stage5-deployment-using-jobci&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用 JobCI 进行阶段 5 部署&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们使用 Devtron 和 Jenkins 部署到应用程序的另一种方法是使用JobCI 管道。在 Devtron 中，我们需要选择创建作业。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/Job-ci-pipeline.png&#34; alt= “Job-CI-Pipeline”referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“wp-element-caption”&gt; [图。 8]作业 CI 管道&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要配置作业 CI 和 CD 管道，请导航到“新建工作流程”&gt;“创建作业”&gt; 您将被重定向到“基本配置”&gt; 设置基本配置，例如“管道名称”、“源类型”和“分支名称”。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/jobci-configure.png&#34; alt=&#34;作业-creation&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[图。 9]创造就业&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成基本配置后，导航到要执行的任务。这里，您需要添加Devtron的插件，这将有助于触发Jenkins管道通过Devtron部署应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron的&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/plugins/plugin-list/jenkins?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;Jenkins插件&lt;/a&gt;，帮助我们远程触发我们的 Jenkins 管道并将日志获取到 Devtron 仪表板。管道成功执行后，生成的容器映像将可供我们部署在 Devtron 仪表板上（前提是您的 Jenkins 管道将 docker 映像推送到使用 Devtron 配置的容器注册表）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/jenkins-plugin-2.png&#34; alt= “Jenkins-Plugin”referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“wp-element-caption”&gt; [图。 10]Jenkins插件&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果容器注册表未使用 Devtron 配置，您可以使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.devtron.ai/usage/plugins/plugin-list/pull-images-from-container-repository ?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;从 Devtron 的容器存储库插件中提取镜像&lt;/a&gt;。该插件不断轮询指定的容器注册表，并将镜像从容器存储库拉取到 Devtron 进行部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/pull-image-plugin.png&#34; alt= “Pull-image-from-container-repository”referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“wp-element-caption”&gt; [图。 11]从容器存储库中提取图像&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;单击“更新管道”按钮即可。我们已经配置了 Job CI，这将触发我们的 Jenkins CI 管道并获取容器映像进行部署。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于 Devtron 的 CD 管道，您可以参考第 4 步，其中描述了我们如何使用 Devtron 配置和执行强大的 CD 管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;结论&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 Jenkins 很强大l CI/CD工具，作为持续部署工具，它有明显的缺点，特别是对于现代、云原生和以Kubernetes为中心的环境。 ArgoCD、FluxCD 或 Devtron 等替代方案为高级部署策略、GitOps 工作流程和 Kubernetes 管理提供了更好的开箱即用集成，使它们更适合许多寻求可扩展和自动化 CD 解决方案的组织。在这篇博客中，我们介绍了 Jenkins 在 Kubernetes 持续部署 (CD) 方面的潜在缺点、理想 CD 管道的功能，以及 Devtron 如何帮助我们建立与 Jenkins 集成的强大 CI/CD 管道。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在管理 Kubernetes 方面，Devtron 作为一个完整的解决方案脱颖而出，并且能够处理强大的持续部署 (CD) 操作，例如强大的 RBAC、审批工作流程、Devtron 插件、漏洞扫描、配置漂移管理、发布编排、和团队协作。在管理多个 Kubernetes 集群资源和第 2 天操作（例如管理跨多个 Kubernetes 集群的多个应用程序）时，Devtron 成为了救世主&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您有任何疑问，请随时&lt;a href=&#34;https://rebrand.ly/devtron-demo?ref=blog&#34;&gt;与我们联系&lt;/a&gt;。加入我们积极发展的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://rebrand.ly/Devtron-Discord?ref=devtron.ai&#34;&gt;Discord 社区&lt;/a&gt;，参与热烈讨论并分享知识。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;相关文章&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-ci-cd-pipelines-with-jenkins-and-argocd/&#34;&gt;使用 Jenkins 和 ArgoCD 的 Kubernetes CI/CD 管道&lt;/a&gt;2天前11 分钟阅读&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/what-is-jenkins-a-quick-guide-for-ci-cd-with-jenkins/&#34;&gt;什么是 Jenkins？ Jenkins 的 CI/CD 快速指南&lt;/a&gt;一个月前阅读 12 分钟&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/devtron-vs-jenkins-how-do-they-stack-against/&#34;&gt;Devtron 与 Jenkins：Kubernetes 的 Jenkins 替代方案&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/李&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to ace the Certified Argo Project Associate (CAPA) exam】如何通过 Argo 项目助理认证 (CAPA) 考试</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/18/how-to-ace-the-certified-argo-project-associate-capa-exam/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Community post originally published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://itnext.io/how-to-ace-capa-certified-argo-project-associate-exam-e80689c12c34&#34;&gt;Medium/IT Next&lt;/a&gt; by Giorgi Keratishvili&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1200&#34; height=&#34;628&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Certified Argo Project Associate logo&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-119128&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1.jpg 1200w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-300x157.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-1024x536.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-768x402.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-388x204.jpg 388w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-900x471.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-382x200.jpg 382w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-764x400.jpg 764w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-590x310.jpg 590w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;fb01&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;a0f3&#34;&gt;Over the last five years,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;GitOps&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;has emerged as one of the most interesting implementations of using GIT in the Kubernetes ecosystem and when people hear about Argo they immediately associate it with&amp;nbsp;Argo CD, but not many people know that there is more than just&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;GitOps&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;tools. The Argo project itself is a tool suite developed as a cloud and Kubernetes-native solution to help with accelerating&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;SDLC&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and automatization of full DevOps solutions. Alongside of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;ArgoCD&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;there are great tools such as&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Workflow&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Rollout&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Events&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;which are extensively covered in this exam and gives real-world examples of how to effectively utilize them. If you are planning to take the CAPA exam, then this blog will be interesting for you as we will dive into domains that are asked during this exam and how to prepare for them as part of my exam preparation journey.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;c10b&#34;&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Project&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;is a suite of open source tools for deploying and running applications and workloads on Kubernetes. It extends the Kubernetes APIs and unlocks new and powerful capabilities in application deployment, container orchestration, event automation, progressive delivery, and more also there is very interesting&amp;nbsp;blog&amp;nbsp;from&amp;nbsp;Argo Project creator&amp;nbsp;that explains why they created it. Argo Workflow was the first tool before Argo CD.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d8fc&#34;&gt;Who should take this exam?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote has-gray-300-background-color has-background is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;fff9&#34;&gt;The CAPA is an associate-level certification designed for engineers, data scientists, and others interested in demonstrating their understanding of the Argo Project ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;773b&#34;&gt;Those who earn the CAPA certification will demonstrate to current and prospective employers they can navigate the Argo Project ecosystem, including when and why to use each tool, understanding the fundamentals around each toolset, explaining when to use which tool and why, and integrating each tool with other tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;92c3&#34;&gt;CAPA will demonstrate a candidate’s solid understanding of the Argo Project ecosystem, terminology, and best practices for each tool and how it relates to common DevOps, GitOps, Platform Engineering, and related practices. Learn more about the exam and sign up for updates on the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/certified-argo-project-associate-capa/?__hstc=60185074.b26b63c073c93f83a3bd0b8c1f23903f.1715940514472.1715940514472.1715940514472.1&amp;amp;__hssc=60185074.1.1715940514472&amp;amp;__hsfp=120088197&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Linux Foundation Training and Certification website.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;f5d4&#34;&gt;Compared to other certifications I wouldn’t say it’s the easiest, but it still falls under the pre-professional level of difficulty and is a great way to test your knowledge of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Project&lt;/strong&gt;. For me, the order of difficulty felt like this:&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/CGOA/CAPA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS&lt;/strong&gt;. One thing to keep in mind is that I had already passed the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CGOA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;before taking the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CAPA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and when I was preparing for the exam, there were no tutorials or blogs to refer to, only some suspiciously scam-like dumps, so don’t fall for them. Below I will mention all the new courses and materials that should help in preparation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7353&#34;&gt;Regarding persons who would benefit&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;SysAdmins/Dev/Ops/SRE/Managers/Platform engineers&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;or any one who is doing anything on production should consider it as knowing basic&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;GitOps&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;is always good thing as we are managing multiple clusters it is handy skill.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*j0pAUqcR2PeP28YkKtOKWw.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;image of a japanese octopus lamp&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;de4d&#34;&gt;Format and PSI Proctored Exam Tips&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7649&#34;&gt;So we are ready to patch every security whole in our cluster, kick out hackers from our production system and make hard them to compromise your cluster? Then, we have a long path ahead until we reach this point. First, we need to understand what kind of exam it is compared to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CKAD&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CKA&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CKS&lt;/strong&gt;. This is exam where the CNCF has adopted multiple-choice questions and compared to other&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;multiple-choice&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;exams, this one, I would say is not an easy-peasy. However it is still qualified as pre-professional, on par with the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/PCA/CGOA/KCSA&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;24e6&#34;&gt;This exam is conducted online, proctored similarly to other Kubernetes certifications and is facilitated by PSI. As someone who has taken more than 15 exams with PSI, I can say that every time it’s a new journey.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;HIGHLY ADVISE joining the exam 30 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;before taking the test because there are pre-checks of ID and the room in which you are taking it needs to be checked for exam criteria. Please check these two links for the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/exam-rules-and-policies&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;exam rules&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/taking-the-exam&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSI portal guide&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;5a61&#34;&gt;You’ll have&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;90 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;to answer&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;60 questions&lt;/strong&gt;, which is generally considered sufficient time,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;passing&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;score is&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;75%&lt;/strong&gt;. Be prepared for some questions that can be quite tricky. I marked a couple of them for review and would advise doing the same because sometimes you could find a hint or partial answers in the next question. By this way, you could refer back to those questions. Regarding pricing, the exam costs&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;$250&lt;/strong&gt;, but you can&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;often&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;find it at a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;discount&lt;/strong&gt;, such as during&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Black Friday&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;promotions or near dates for CNCF events like KubeCon, Open Source Summit, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*7aaPqEpbnIHAc6isW8xDHw.png&#34; alt=&#34;argo logo with computer&#34; style=&#34;width:900px;height:auto&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;7411&#34;&gt;The Path of Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7728&#34;&gt;At this point, we understand what we have signed up for and are ready to dedicate time to training, but where should we start? Before taking this exam, I had a good experience with Kubernetes,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Flux CD&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Argo Project&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;ecosystem and had passed&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CGOA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;exam, but yet I still learned a lot from this exam preparation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4095&#34;&gt;At first glance, this list might seem too simple and easy but however, we need to learn the fundamentals of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;GitOps&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CICD&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;SDLC&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;first in order to understand higher-level concepts such as Branching Strategy, Event Driven Architecture and many more&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;4022&#34;&gt;Let break down Domains &amp;amp; Competencies&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-preformatted&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Argo Workflows 36%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Understand Argo Workflow Fundamentals&lt;br&gt;    Generating and Consuming Artifacts&lt;br&gt;    Understand Argo Workflow Templates&lt;br&gt;    Understand the Argo Workflow Spec&lt;br&gt;    Work with DAG (Directed-Acyclic Graphs)&lt;br&gt;    Run Data Processing Jobs with Argo Workflows&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Argo CD 34%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Understand Argo CD Fundamentals&lt;br&gt;    Synchronize Applications Using Argo CD&lt;br&gt;    Use Argo CD Application&lt;br&gt;    Configure Argo CD with Helm and Kustomize&lt;br&gt;    Identify Common Reconciliation Patterns&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Argo Rollouts 18%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Understand Argo Rollouts Fundamentals&lt;br&gt;    Use Common Progressive Rollout Strategies&lt;br&gt;    Describe Analysis Template and AnalysisRun&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Argo Events 12%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Understand Argo Events Fundamentals&lt;br&gt;    Understand Argo Event Components and Architecture&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;6a17&#34;&gt;ARGO PROJECT&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;49e7&#34;&gt;The Argo Project is headlined by Argo CD and Argo Workflows, two mainstay powerhouses that have become the defacto tools in their respective spaces. Joining Argo CD and Workflows are Argo Events and Rollouts with large successful followings of their own. One of the brilliant decisions made early on was that these tools which have their own uses could be useable with or without the rest of the Argo suite of tooling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;09eb&#34;&gt;Argo CD is the world’s most popular and fastest growing GitOps tool. It allows users to define a git source of truth for an application and keep that in sync with a destination Kubernetes cluster. This powerful tool gets even more powerful when combined with tools like Argo Rollouts, which handles progressive delivery, and other open source tools like Crossplane for managing infrastructure, or OPA and Kyverno for security policy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;6700&#34;&gt;Argo Workflows provides a powerful workflow engine built for Kubernetes where each step operates in its own pod. This provides for massive scale and flexible multi-step workflow tasks. Argo Workflows has been especially popular for data pipelines as well as Kubernetes-native CI/CD pipelines. Workflows becomes especially powerful when paired with Argo Events, a Kubernetes-native event engine. It can be used to detect events in Kubernetes and trigger actions, either in Argo Workflows, or other services, as well as provide a general interface for webhooks and api-calls.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*jI2zNmbco-b9dmmjbd33nw.png&#34; alt=&#34;Argo Workflows&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d462&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Argo Worflows?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;558e&#34;&gt;Argo Workflows is an open source container-native workflow engine for orchestrating parallel jobs on Kubernetes. Argo Workflows is implemented as a Kubernetes CRD.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Define workflows where each step in the workflow is a container.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Model multi-step workflows as a sequence of tasks or capture the dependencies between tasks using a graph (DAG).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Easily run compute intensive jobs for machine learning or data processing in a fraction of the time using Argo Workflows on Kubernetes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Run CI/CD pipelines natively on Kubernetes without configuring complex software development products.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;f101&#34;&gt;Why Argo Workflows?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Designed from the ground up for containers without the overhead and limitations of legacy VM and server-based environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cloud agnostic and can run on any Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Easily orchestrate highly parallel jobs on Kubernetes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Argo Workflows puts a cloud-scale supercomputer at your fingertips!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;14bd&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo Workflows: An Introduction and Quick Guide&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9212&#34;&gt;An in-depth guide on Argo Workflows, covering its basics, core concepts, and a quick tutorial. It explains how Argo Workflows orchestrates parallel jobs on Kubernetes, details on defining workflows with containers and DAGs, and offers practical steps for installing and running Argo Workflows. It also highlights the integration of Argo Workflows with Codefresh for CI/CD pipelines, emphasizing ease of use and cloud-native capabilities. For more details, visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-workflows/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Workflows: The Basics and a Quick Tutorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;c37f&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Setting Up an Artifact Repository for Argo Workflows&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;604f&#34;&gt;This Pipekit explains how to configure an artifact repository for Argo Workflows. It provides step-by-step instructions on setting up and managing artifact repositories, enabling efficient handling and storage of artifacts generated during workflow executions. This guide is valuable for ensuring smooth and effective workflow operations in Kubernetes environments. For more information, visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pipekit.io/blog/configure-artifact-repo-argo-workflows&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;How to Configure an Artifact Repo for Argo Workflows (pipekit.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pipekit.io/blog/configure-artifact-repo-argo-workflows&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;2dab&#34;&gt;Work with DAG (Directed-Acyclic Graphs)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;996f&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directed Acyclic Graph (DAG)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;— A Directed Acyclic Graph (DAG) is a finite graph with directed edges where no cycles exist. It’s used in computer science to model various systems, including task scheduling, data flow, and dependency management. DAGs facilitate efficient algorithms like topological sorting and are central to concepts in computational complexity and data structures.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Directed_acyclic_graph&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Directed acyclic graph&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;79f1&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Overview and Use Cases of Directed Acyclic Graphs (DAGs)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;—&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Directed Acyclic Graph (DAG) is a structure consisting of vertices and directed edges, representing activities and their order. Each edge has a direction, and there are no cycles, meaning you cannot return to a vertex once you leave it. DAGs are useful in modeling data processing flows, ensuring tasks are performed in a specific sequence without repetition. Visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hazelcast.com/glossary/directed-acyclic-graph/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Directed Acyclic Graph (DAG) Overview &amp;amp; Use Cases&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;50c6&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Directed Acyclic Graphs (DAGs) in Argo Workflows&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The Argo Workflows DAG guide explains how to create workflows using directed-acyclic graphs (DAGs). It covers defining task dependencies for enhanced parallelism and simplicity in complex workflows. Examples include a sample workflow with sequential and parallel task execution and features like enhanced dependency logic and fail-fast behavior for error handling. Visit&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-workflows.readthedocs.io/en/latest/walk-through/dag/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;DAG — Argo Workflows&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*wgpVrlAbnDD3ajVKQXG-Fg.png&#34; alt=&#34;ArgoCD with a rocket&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d6fa&#34;&gt;What is Argo CD?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b645&#34;&gt;Argo CD follows the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;GitOps&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;pattern of using Git repositories as the source of truth for defining the desired application state. Kubernetes manifests can be specified in several ways:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kustomize.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;kustomize&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://helm.sh/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;helm&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;charts&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jsonnet.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;jsonnet&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;files&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Plain directory of YAML/json manifests&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Any custom config management tool configured as a config management plugin&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;622b&#34;&gt;Argo CD automates the deployment of the desired application states in the specified target environments. Application deployments can track updates to branches, tags, or pinned to a specific version of manifests at a Git commit. See&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/user-guide/tracking_strategies/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;tracking strategies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for additional details about the different tracking strategies available.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;407a&#34;&gt;Argo CD is implemented as a Kubernetes controller which continuously monitors running applications and compares the current, live state against the desired target state (as specified in the Git repo). A deployed application whose live state deviates from the target state is considered&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;OutOfSync&lt;/code&gt;. Argo CD reports &amp;amp; visualizes the differences, while providing facilities to automatically or manually sync the live state back to the desired target state. Any modifications made to the desired target state in the Git repo can be automatically applied and reflected in the specified target environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;03df&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo CD: The Basics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;0cd2&#34;&gt;The article “Argo CD Fundamentals” by Nandhabalan Marimuthu introduces the basics of Argo CD, a declarative continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. It covers key concepts such as GitOps, application management, synchronization, and automation workflows, providing practical insights and examples for effectively utilizing Argo CD in DevOps environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/understand_the_basics/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Understand The Basics — Argo CD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;241f&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Understand The Basics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;fa08&#34;&gt;Argo CD — Argo CD is a declarative, GitOps continuous delivery tool for Kubernetes. It automates application deployments, allowing users to manage Kubernetes resources through Git repositories. By monitoring and syncing application states, Argo CD ensures that the desired state in Git matches the live state in clusters. Understanding Argo CD&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;5371&#34;&gt;Gaining Insight into Argo CD&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9367&#34;&gt;Explore Argo CD with Codefresh: A comprehensive guide to deploying applications using Argo CD, a GitOps continuous delivery tool. Learn about its features, benefits, and how to set up automated application deployment pipelines seamlessly integrating with Kubernetes. Master the power of GitOps for efficient, scalable software delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;225b&#34;&gt;Synchronize Applications Using Argo CD&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4f14&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Synchronize Applications Using Kubectl with Argo CD&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;— The link provides guidance on syncing Kubernetes resources with Argo CD using kubectl. It highlights kubectl’s compatibility with Argo CD for synchronizing and managing Kubernetes resources. Both imperative and declarative methods are supported, ensuring seamless integration and efficient resource management within Kubernetes clusters.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/user-guide/sync-kubectl/#:~:text=You%20can%20use%20%22kubectl%22%20to,of%20resources%20are%20equally%20supported.&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Sync Applications with Kubectl — Argo CD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7c6c&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Synchronization Choices in Argo CD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Declarative GitOps Continuous Delivery for Kubernetes — Argo CD’s synchronization options streamline Kubernetes deployments. With features like automatic sync, manual sync, and hooks, it ensures seamless application updates. Customize sync policies, including pruning and sync wave limitations, for efficient resource management. Monitor sync status and history effortlessly for comprehensive deployment control.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/user-guide/sync-options/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Sync Options — Argo CD — Declarative GitOps CD for Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;bc17&#34;&gt;Use the Argo CD Application&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;5b5a&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Setting Up Declaratively with Argo CD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;— The link provides a comprehensive guide to Argo CD’s synchronization options. It details various strategies for syncing Kubernetes resources, including automated and manual methods. Users can learn about hooks, resource filtering, and customization, ensuring efficient management and deployment of applications within Kubernetes clusters.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/operator-manual/declarative-setup/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Declarative Setup — Argo CD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*Hi6FoU7hWVxc7HxSa8eH_w.png&#34; alt=&#34;Argo Rollouts&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;a853&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Argo Rollouts?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;f135&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts is a Kubernetes controller and set of CRDs which provide advanced deployment capabilities such as blue-green, canary, canary analysis, experimentation, and progressive delivery features to Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;eb6e&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts (optionally) integrates with ingress controllers and service meshes, leveraging their traffic shaping abilities to gradually shift traffic to the new version during an update. Additionally, Rollouts can query and interpret metrics from various providers to verify key KPIs and drive automated promotion or rollback during an update.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;c472&#34;&gt;Why Argo Rollouts?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;92e5&#34;&gt;The native Kubernetes Deployment Object supports the RollingUpdate strategy which provides a basic set of safety guarantees (readiness probes) during an update. However the rolling update strategy faces many limitations:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Few controls over the speed of the rollout&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Inability to control traffic flow to the new version&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Readiness probes are unsuitable for deeper, stress, or one-time checks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;No ability to query external metrics to verify an update&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can halt the progression, but unable to automatically abort and rollback the update&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4a95&#34;&gt;For these reasons, in large scale high-volume production environments, a rolling update is often considered too risky of an update procedure since it provides no control over the blast radius, may rollout too aggressively, and provides no automated rollback upon failures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;b6da&#34;&gt;Controller Features&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Blue-Green update strategy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Canary update strategy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fine-grained, weighted traffic shifting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automated rollbacks and promotions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manual judgement&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Customizable metric queries and analysis of business KPIs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ingress controller integration: NGINX, ALB&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Service Mesh integration: Istio, Linkerd, SMI&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Metric provider integration: Prometheus, Wavefront, Kayenta, Web, Kubernetes Jobs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;17fd&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo Rollouts: Progressive Delivery for Kubernetes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;56f0&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts” is a progressive delivery tool for Kubernetes. It enables advanced deployment strategies like Canary and Blue-Green deployments, ensuring smooth and controlled updates of applications. With features like traffic shifting and analysis, it empowers teams to deliver software with confidence and reliability in Kubernetes environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/rollouts/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/stable/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/stable/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo Rollouts: A Brief Overview of Concepts, Setup, and Operations&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;—&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-rollouts/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts: Quick Guide to Concepts, Setup &amp;amp; Operations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d5e2&#34;&gt;Use Common Progressive Rollout Strategies&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;bff9&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Progressive Delivery Controller for Kubernetes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;— Argo Rollouts simplifies Kubernetes deployments by offering advanced deployment strategies like blue-green, canary, and experimentation. Automated rollback and rollback analysis, ensure reliability. This documentation introduces its concepts, empowering users to leverage its powerful features for seamless, controlled application deployments in Kubernetes environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/stable/concepts/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Progressive Delivery Controller&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d395&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Executing Progressive Deployment Strategies Using Argo Rollouts —&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.opsmx.com/blog/progressive-deployment-strategies-using-argo-rollout/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Progressive Deployment Strategies using Argo Rollout&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d94a&#34;&gt;Describe the Analysis Template and Analysis Run&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;1465&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Analysis Template&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;—&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.opsmx.com/opsmx-intelligent-software-delivery-isd-platform-argo/user-guide/delivery-verification/analysis-template&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://docs.opsmx.com/opsmx-intelligent-software-delivery-isd-platform-argo/user-guide/delivery-verification/analysis-template&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Creating Analysis Runs for Rollouts —&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/release-1.5/generated/kubectl-argo-rollouts/kubectl-argo-rollouts_create_analysisrun/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/release-1.5/generated/kubectl-argo-rollouts/kubectl-argo-rollouts_create_analysisrun/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*cPztpZ06xvkkUYLX-tyK8w.png&#34; alt=&#34;argo events&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;f28b&#34;&gt;What is Argo Events?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4d32&#34;&gt;Argo Events is an event-based dependency manager for Kubernetes which helps you define multiple dependencies from a variety of event sources like webhook, s3, schedules, streams etc. and trigger Kubernetes objects after successful event dependencies resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*-7cDAu5D6yKXimpZ.png&#34; alt=&#34;argo events image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;8405&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manage dependencies from a variety of event sources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ability to customize business-level constraint logic for event dependencies resolution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manage everything from simple, linear, real-time dependencies to complex, multi-source, batch job dependencies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ability to extends framework to add your own event source listener.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Define arbitrary boolean logic to resolve event dependencies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CloudEvents compliant.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ability to manage event sources at runtime.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;7af2&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo Events- An Introduction and Quick Guide&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d316&#34;&gt;Explore Argo Events on Codefresh: Discover event-driven automation for Kubernetes. Learn to build resilient, scalable workflows triggered by events from various sources. Harness the power of Argo CD, Events, and Workflows to streamline your CI/CD pipelines and optimize Kubernetes deployments. Empower your DevOps with seamless automation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-events/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Events: the Basics and a Quick Tutorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;717d&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo Events: A Dependency Manager for Kubernetes Based on Events&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;fe11&#34;&gt;The Argo Events tutorial introduces Argo, an open-source workflow engine, focusing on event-driven architecture. It details installation, configuration, and usage, emphasizing event-driven workflows for Kubernetes. Learn to automate tasks, trigger workflows based on events, and streamline Kubernetes operations for efficient, scalable development and operations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/argo-events/tutorials/01-introduction/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Events — The Event-Based Dependency Manager for Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;665e&#34;&gt;Understand Argo Event Components and Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ad74&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo Events- The Event-Driven Dependency Manager for Kubernetes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;— Argo Events, part of the Argo project, orchestrates Kubernetes-native event-driven workflows. Its architecture leverages triggers, gateways, and sensors to detect events from various sources like Pub/Sub systems or HTTP endpoints, initiating workflows. This decentralized, cloud-native system enables scalable, resilient event processing and automation within Kubernetes clusters. Argo Events — The Event-Based Dependency Manager for Kubernetes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;2120&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Event-Driven Architecture on Kubernetes&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;— Discover the dynamic world of event-driven architecture on Kubernetes with Argo Events. This blog delves into orchestrating microservices, leveraging Kubernetes’ power, and streamlining workflows with Argo Events. Explore seamless event handling and scalable solutions, unlocking the potential for efficient, responsive systems in the modern tech landscape.&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.devops.dev/event-driven-architecture-on-kubernetes-with-argo-events-75b9115bb1fc&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;Event-Driven Architecture on Kubernetes with Argo Events&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*Fub3JLyCk6Io9ApU86ueyw.png&#34; alt=&#34;argo image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;3b74&#34;&gt;Key Learning Materials:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ecc6&#34;&gt;You can explore and learn about CAPA Certification and related topics freely through the following materials which I have used and of course Argo Project&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;documentation&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;is our best friend&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://trainingportal.linuxfoundation.org/courses/introduction-to-gitops-lfs169&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://trainingportal.linuxfoundation.org/courses/introduction-to-gitops-lfs169&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/devops-and-workflow-management-with-argo-lfs256/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/devops-and-workflow-management-with-argo-lfs256/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://killercoda.com/argo&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://killercoda.com/argo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://argoproj.github.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://akuity.io/what-is-argo/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://akuity.io/what-is-argo/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-cd/what-is-the-argo-project-and-why-is-it-transforming-development/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-cd/what-is-the-argo-project-and-why-is-it-transforming-development/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ravikirans.com/capa-certified-argo-project-associate-study-guide/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://ravikirans.com/capa-certified-argo-project-associate-study-guide/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kloudsaga.com/learning-path-certified-argo-project-associate-exam/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://kloudsaga.com/learning-path-certified-argo-project-associate-exam/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-workflows.readthedocs.io/en/latest/quick-start/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://argo-workflows.readthedocs.io/en/latest/quick-start/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ef48&#34;&gt;At this moment there is not many courses as it is a new exam and&amp;nbsp;I &lt;strong&gt;would highly advise not to click on every course which will pop up from Google search as it is a new exam there are plenty of scams.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;5c5a&#34;&gt;I hope in the near future we will see more courses from bigger platforms such as kodekloud or killersh.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;1221&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9aae&#34;&gt;The exam is not easy. Among other certs I would rank it in this order&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/CGOA/CAPA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;After conducting the exam in 24 hours you will receive grading and after passing the exam it feels pretty satisfying overall. I hope it was informative and useful 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;社区帖子最初发布于&lt;a href=&#34;https://itnext.io/how-to-ace-capa-certified-argo-project-associate-exam-e80689c12c34&#34;&gt;Medium/IT Next&lt; /a&gt; 作者：Giorgi Keratishvili&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1200”高度=“628”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;经过认证的 Argo 项目助理徽标&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-119128&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp -content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1.jpg 1200w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-300x157.jpg 300w，https ://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-1024x536.jpg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ image-2-1-768x402.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-194x102.jpg 194w，https://www.cncf。 io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-388x204.jpg 388w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-900x471 .jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-382x200.jpg 382w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads /2024/10/image-2-1-764x400.jpg 764w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/image-2-1-590x310.jpg 590w“尺寸=” （最大宽度：1200px）100vw，1200px“referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;fb01&#34;&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;a0f3&#34;&gt;在过去五年中，&lt;strong&gt;GitOps&lt;/strong&gt;已成为 Kubernetes 生态系统中使用 GIT 的最有趣的实现之一，当人们听说 Argo 时，他们会立即将其与 Argo 联系起来CD，但没有多少人知道不仅仅是 &lt;strong&gt;GitOps&lt;/strong&gt; 工具。 Argo 项目本身是一个作为云和 Kubernetes 原生解决方案开发的工具套件，有助于加速整个 DevOps 解决方案的&lt;strong&gt;SDLC&lt;/strong&gt;和自动化。除了 &lt;strong&gt;ArgoCD&lt;/strong&gt; 之外，还有一些很棒的工具，例如 &lt;strong&gt;Argo Workflow&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;Argo Rollout&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;Argo Events&lt;/strong&gt;，这些工具在该考试并给出了如何有效利用它们的真实示例。如果您计划参加 CAPA 考试，那么这个博客对您来说将会很有趣，因为我们将深入探讨本次考试期间询问的领域以及如何为这些领域做好准备，作为我考试准备之旅的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;c10b&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argo 项目&lt;/strong&gt;是一套开源工具，用于在 Kubernetes 上部署和运行应用程序和工作负载。它扩展了 Kubernetes API，并在应用程序部署、容器编排、事件自动化、渐进式交付等方面解锁了新的强大功能，Argo 项目创建者还发表了一个非常有趣的博客，解释了他们创建它的原因。 Argo Workflow 是 Argo CD 之前的第一个工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d8fc&#34;&gt;谁应该参加此考试？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;块引用类=wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote has-gray-300-background-color has-background is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;fff9&#34;&gt;CAPA 是一项助理级认证，专为工程师、数据科学家和其他有兴趣展示其对 Argo 项目生态系统了解的人员而设计。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;773b&#34;&gt;获得 CAPA 认证的人将向当前和未来的雇主证明他们可以驾驭 Argo 项目生态系统，包括何时以及为何使用每个工具、了解每个工具集的基础知识、解释何时使用哪些工具工具及其原因，并将每个工具与其他工具集成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;92c3&#34;&gt;CAPA 将展示候选人对 Argo 项目生态系统、术语和每个工具的最佳实践及其与常见 DevOps、GitOps、平台工程和相关实践的关系的深入理解。了解有关考试的更多信息并在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/certified-argo-project-associate-capa/?__hstc=60185074.b26b63c073c93f83a3bd0b8c1f23903f.1715940514472.171594051447 上注册更新2.1715940514472.1&amp;__hssc =60185074.1.1715940514472&amp;__hsfp=120088197&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Linux 基础培训和认证网站。&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;f5d4&#34;&gt;与其他认证相比，我不会说它是最简单的，但它仍然属于准专业难度级别，是测试您对 &lt;strong&gt;Argo 项目知识&lt;/strong&gt;的好方法&lt;/强&gt;。对我来说，难度顺序是这样的：&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/CGOA/CAPA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS&lt;/strong&gt;。需要记住的一件事是，在参加&lt;strong&gt;CAPA&lt;/strong&gt;之前，我已经通过了&lt;strong&gt;CGOA&lt;/strong&gt;，并且当我准备考试时，没有任何教程或博客可供参考，只有一些可疑的骗局，所以不要上当。下面我将提到所有有助于准备的新课程和材料。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7353&#34;&gt;对于&lt;strong&gt;系统管理员/开发/运营/SRE/经理/平台工程师&lt;/strong&gt;受益的人员或任何从事生产工作的人员，应将其视为了解基本知识&lt;strong&gt; GitOps &lt;/strong&gt;总是一件好事，因为我们要管理多个集群，这是一项方便的技能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*j0pAUqcR2PeP28YkKtOKWw.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;image日本章鱼灯”referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;de4d&#34;&gt;格式和 PSI 监考考试提示&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7649&#34;&gt;那么我们准备好修补集群中的每个安全整体，将黑客从我们的生产系统中剔除，并让他们难以危害您的集群吗？然后，在到达这一点之前，我们还有很长的路要走。首先，我们需要了解它与&lt;strong&gt;CKAD&lt;/strong&gt;相比是什么样的考试，&amp;nbsp；&lt;strong&gt;CKA&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;CKS&lt;/strong&gt;。这是 CNCF 采用多项选择题的考试，与其他&lt;strong&gt;多项选择&lt;/strong&gt;考试相比，我想说这不是一件容易的事。不过，它仍然具有与&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/PCA/CGOA/KCSA&lt;/strong&gt;同等的预科资格。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;24e6&#34;&gt;该考试在线进行，监考方式与其他 Kubernetes 认证类似，并由 PSI 提供协助。作为参加过超过 15 场 PSI 考试的人，我可以说每次都是新的旅程。&lt;strong&gt;我&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;强烈建议在参加考试前 30 分钟参加考试&lt;/strong&gt;，因为需要预先检查身份证件，并且需要检查您所在的房间是否符合考试标准。请检查这两个链接以获取 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/exam-rules-and-policies&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank &#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;考试规​​则&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/take-the-exam&#34; rel=&#34; noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSI 门户指南&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;5a61&#34;&gt;您将有&lt;strong&gt;90 分钟&lt;/strong&gt;的时间回答&lt;strong&gt;60 个问题&lt;/strong&gt;，这通常被认为是足够的时间，&lt;strong&gt;及格&lt;/strong&gt;分数为&lt;强&gt;&gt;75％&lt;/强&gt;。为一些可能相当棘手的问题做好准备。我标记了其中几个以供审查，并建议您也这样做，因为有时您可以在下一个问题中找到提示或部分答案。这样你就可以回过头来看看这些问题了。关于定价，考试费用&lt;strong&gt; 250 美元&lt;/strong&gt;，但您&lt;strong&gt;通常&lt;/strong&gt;可以享受&lt;strong&gt;折扣&lt;/strong&gt;，例如在&lt;strong&gt;黑色星期五&lt;/strong&gt;期间&gt; KubeCon、开源峰会等 CNCF 活动的促销活动或近期日期。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*7aaPqEpbnIHAc6isW8xDHw.png&#34; alt =&#34;带有计算机的 argo 徽标&#34; style=&#34;width:900px;height:auto&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;7411&#34;&gt;学习之路&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7728&#34;&gt;至此，我们了解了自己注册的目的，并准备好投入时间进行培训，但我们应该从哪里开始呢？在参加这次考试之前，我对 Kubernetes、&lt;strong&gt;Flux CD&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;Argo Project&lt;/strong&gt; 生态系统有很好的体验，并通过了&lt;strong&gt;CGOA&lt;/strong&gt;考试，但我仍然从这次考试准备中学到了很多东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4095&#34;&gt;乍一看，这个列表似乎过于简单和容易，但是，我们需要学习 &lt;strong&gt;GitOps&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;CICD&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt; 的基础知识&gt;首先是为了理解更高层次的SDLC-级别概念，例如分支策略、事件驱动架构等等&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;4022&#34;&gt;让我们分解一下领域和能力&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-preformatted&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Argo 工作流程 36%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 了解 Argo 工作流程基础知识&lt;br&gt; 生成和使用工件&lt;br&gt; 了解 Argo 工作流程模板&lt;br &gt; 了解 Argo 工作流程规范&lt;br&gt; 使用 DAG（有向无环图）&lt;br&gt; 使用 Argo 工作流程运行数据处理作业&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Argo CD 34%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt; br&gt; 了解 Argo CD 基础知识&lt;br&gt; 使用 Argo CD 同步应用程序&lt;br&gt; 使用 Argo CD 应用程序&lt;br&gt; 使用 Helm 和 Kustomize 配置 Argo CD&lt;br&gt; 识别常见的协调模式&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Argo推出 18%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 了解 Argo 推出基础知识&lt;br&gt; 使用常见的渐进式推出策略&lt;br&gt; 描述分析模板和 AnalysisRun&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Argo 事件 12%**&lt; /strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 了解 Argo Events 基础知识&lt;br&gt; 了解 Argo Event 组件和架构&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;6a17&#34;&gt;ARGO 项目&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;49e7&#34;&gt;Argo 项目以 Argo CD 和 Argo Workflows 为主导，这两个支柱力量已成为各自领域事实上的工具。加入 Argo CD 和工作流程的是 Argo 活动和推出，拥有大量成功的追随者。早期做出的明智决定之一是，这些有其用途的工具可以与或不与 Argo 工具套件的其余部分一起使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;09eb&#34;&gt;Argo CD 是世界上最受欢迎且增长最快的 GitOps 工具。它允许用户为应用程序定义 git 真实来源，并使其与目标 Kubernetes 集群保持同步。当与处理渐进式交付的 Argo Rollouts 等工具以及用于管理基础设施的 Crossplane 或用于安全策略的 OPA 和 Kyverno 等其他开源工具结合使用时，这个强大的工具会变得更加强大。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;6700&#34;&gt;Argo Workflows 提供了一个专为 Kubernetes 构建的强大工作流引擎，其中每个步骤都在自己的 pod 中运行。这提供了大规模且灵活的多步骤工作流程任务。 Argo Workflows 在数据管道以及 Kubernetes 原生 CI/CD 管道中特别受欢迎。当与 Kubernetes 原生事件引擎 Argo Events 配合使用时，工作流变得尤其强大。它可用于检测 Kubernetes 中的事件并触发 Argo 工作流或其他服务中的操作，并为 Webhooks 和 api 调用提供通用接口。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*jI2zNmbco-b9dmmjbd33nw.png&#34; alt= “Argo 工作流程”referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d462&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是 Argo Worflows？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;558e&#34;&gt;Argo Workflows 是一个开源容器用于在 Kubernetes 上编排并行作业的原生工作流引擎。 Argo Workflows 作为 Kubernetes CRD 实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;定义工作流程，其中工作流程中的每个步骤都是一个容器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将多步骤工作流程建模为一系列任务，或使用图表 (DAG) 捕获任务之间的依赖关系。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用 Kubernetes 上的 Argo 工作流程，只需很短的时间即可轻松运行用于机器学习或数据处理的计算密集型作业。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在 Kubernetes 上原生运行 CI/CD 管道，无需配置复杂的软件开发产品。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;f101&#34;&gt;为什么选择 Argo 工作流程？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;专为容器而设计，没有传统虚拟机和基于服务器的环境的开销和限制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;与云无关，可以在任何 Kubernetes 集群上运行。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在 Kubernetes 上轻松编排高度并行的作业。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Argo Workflows 让云级超级计算机触手可及！&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;14bd&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo 工作流程：简介和快速指南&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9212&#34;&gt;Argo 工作流程的深入指南，涵盖其基础知识、核心概念和快速教程。它解释了 Argo Workflows 如何在 Kubernetes 上编排并行作业、使用容器和 DAG 定义工作流的详细信息，并提供安装和运行 Argo Workflows 的实用步骤。它还强调了 Argo Workflows 与 Codefresh 的 CI/CD 管道集成，强调易用性和云原生功能。如需了解更多详情，请访问&lt;a href=&#34;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-workflows/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo 工作流程：基础知识和快速教程&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;c37f&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;为 Argo 工作流程设置工件存储库&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;604f&#34;&gt;此 Pipekit 解释了如何为 Argo Workflows 配置工件存储库。它提供了有关设置和管理工件存储库的分步说明，从而能够有效处理和存储工作流执行期间生成的工件。本指南对于确保 Kubernetes 环境中平稳有效的工作流程操作非常有价值。如需了解更多信息，请访问&lt;a href=&#34;https://pipekit.io/blog/configure-artifact-repo-argo-workflows&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;如何为 Argo 配置 Artifact 存储库工作流程 (pipekit.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pipekit.io/blog/configure-artifact-repo-argo-workflows&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;)&lt;/a &gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;2dab&#34;&gt;使用 DAG（有向无环图）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;996f&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;有向无环图 (DAG)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - 有向无环图 (DAG) 是具有有向边且不存在环的有限图。它在计算机科学中用于对各种系统进行建模，包括Luding任务调度、数据流和依赖管理。 DAG 促进了拓扑排序等高效算法，并且是计算复杂性和数据结构概念的核心。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Directed_acycl_graph&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;有向无环图&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;79f1&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;有向无环图 (DAG) 概述和用例&lt;/em&gt;— &lt;/strong&gt;有向无环图 (DAG) 是一种由顶点和有向边组成的结构，代表活动及其顺序。每条边都有一个方向，并且没有循环，这意味着一旦离开顶点就无法返回该顶点。 DAG 可用于对数据处理流进行建模，确保任务按特定顺序执行而不重复。访问&lt;a href=&#34;https://hazelcast.com/glossary/directed-acycl-graph/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;有向无环图 (DAG) 概述和用例&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;50c6&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo 工作流程中的有向无环图 (DAG)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Argo 工作流程 DAG 指南介绍了如何使用有向无环图创建工作流程 ( DAG）。它涵盖了定义任务依赖性以增强复杂工作流程中的并行性和简单性。示例包括具有顺序和并行任务执行的示例工作流程以及增强的依赖关系逻辑和用于错误处理的快速失败行为等功能。访问&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-workflows.readthedocs.io/en/latest/walk-through/dag/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;DAG — Argo 工作流程&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*wgpVrlAbnDD3ajVKQXG-Fg.png&#34; alt= “ArgoCD 与火箭”referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d6fa&#34;&gt;Argo CD 是什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b645&#34;&gt;Argo CD 遵循 &lt;strong&gt;GitOps&lt;/strong&gt; 模式，即使用 Git 存储库作为定义所需应用程序状态的事实来源。 Kubernetes 清单可以通过多种方式指定：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kustomize.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;kustomize&lt;/a&gt; 应用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://helm.sh/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;helm&lt;/a&gt; 图表&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jsonnet.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;jsonnet&lt;/a&gt; 文件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;YAML/json 清单的普通目录&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;任何配置为配置管理插件的自定义配置管理工具&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;622b&#34;&gt;Argo CD 可在指定的目标环境中自动部署所需的应用程序状态。应用程序部署可以跟踪分支、标签的更新，或在 Git 提交时固定到特定版本的清单。请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/user-guide/tracking_strategies/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;跟踪策略gies&lt;/a&gt;了解有关不同可用跟踪策略的更多详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;407a&#34;&gt;Argo CD 作为 Kubernetes 控制器实现，它持续监控正在运行的应用程序，并将当前的实时状态与所需的目标状态（如 Git 存储库中指定的）进行比较。其实时状态偏离目标状态的已部署应用程序被视为&lt;code&gt;OutOfSync&lt;/code&gt;。 Argo CD 报告并可视化差异，同时提供自动或手动将实时状态同步回所需目标状态的工具。对 Git 存储库中所需目标状态所做的任何修改都可以自动应用并反映在指定的目标环境中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;03df&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo CD：基础知识&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;0cd2&#34;&gt;Nandhabalan Marimuthu 撰写的文章“Argo CD 基础知识”介绍了 Argo CD 的基础知识，Argo CD 是 Kubernetes 的声明式持续交付工具。它涵盖了 GitOps、应用程序管理、同步和自动化工作流程等关键概念，提供了在 DevOps 环境中有效利用 Argo CD 的实用见解和示例。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/understand_the_basics/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;了解基础知识 — Argo CD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;241f&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;了解基础知识&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;fa08&#34;&gt;Argo CD — Argo CD 是 Kubernetes 的声明式 GitOps 持续交付工具。它自动执行应用程序部署，允许用户通过 Git 存储库管理 Kubernetes 资源。通过监控和同步应用程序状态，Argo CD 确保 Git 中的所需状态与集群中的实时状态相匹配。了解Argo CD&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;5371&#34;&gt;深入了解 Argo CD&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9367&#34;&gt;使用 Codefresh 探索 Argo CD：使用 GitOps 持续交付工具 Argo CD 部署应用程序的综合指南。了解其功能、优势以及如何设置与 Kubernetes 无缝集成的自动化应用程序部署管道。掌握 GitOps 的强大功能，实现高效、可扩展的软件交付。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;225b&#34;&gt;使用 Argo CD 同步应用程序&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4f14&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;使用 Kubectl 与 Argo CD 同步应用程序&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - 该链接提供了有关使用 kubectl 将 Kubernetes 资源与 Argo CD 同步的指南。它强调了 kubectl 与 Argo CD 的兼容性，用于同步和管理 Kubernetes 资源。支持命令式和声明式方法，确保 Kubernetes 集群内的无缝集成和高效的资源管理。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/user-guide/sync-kubectl/#:~:text=You%20can%20use%20%22kubectl%22%20to,of %20资源%20均受%20%20支持。” rel =“noreferrer noopener”目标=“_blank”&gt;与 Kubectl 同步应用程序 — Argo CD&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7c6c&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo CD 中的同步选项&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：针对 Kubernetes 的声明式 GitOps 持续交付 — Argo CD 的同步选项简化了 Kubernetes 部署。借助自动同步、手动同步和挂钩等功能，它可确保应用程序的无缝更新。自定义同步策略，包括修剪和同步波限制，以实现高效的资源管理。轻松监控同步状态和历史记录，以实现全面的部署控制。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/user-guide/sync-options/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;同步选项 — Argo CD — 声明式 GitOps Kubernetes CD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;bc17&#34;&gt;使用 Argo CD 应用程序&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;5b5a&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;使用 Argo CD 进行声明式设置&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - 该链接提供了有关 Argo CD 同步选项的全面指南。它详细介绍了同步 Kubernetes 资源的各种策略，包括自动和手动方法。用户可以了解钩子、资源过滤和定制，确保 Kubernetes 集群内应用程序的高效管理和部署。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-cd.readthedocs.io/en/stable/operator-manual/declarative-setup/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;声明式设置 — Argo CD&lt;/a &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*Hi6FoU7hWVxc7HxSa8eH_w.png&#34; alt=&#34;Argo推出“referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;a853&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是 Argo 推出？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;f135&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts 是一个 Kubernetes 控制器和一组 CRD，为 Kubernetes 提供高级部署功能，例如蓝绿、金丝雀、金丝雀分析、实验和渐进式交付功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;eb6e&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts（可选）与入口控制器和服务网格集成，利用其流量整形功能在更新期间逐渐将流量转移到新版本。此外，推出可以查询和解释来自各个提供商的指标，以验证关键 KPI 并在更新期间推动自动升级或回滚。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;c472&#34;&gt;为什么推出 Argo？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;92e5&#34;&gt;原生 Kubernetes 部署对象支持 RollingUpdate 策略，该策略在更新期间提供一组基本的安全保证（就绪探测）。然而滚动更新策略面临着许多限制：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;对推出速度的控制很少&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;无法控制新版本的流量&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;就绪探测不适合进行更深入、压力或一次性检查&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;无法查询外部指标来验证更新&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可以停止进度，但无法自动中止和回滚更新&lt;/里&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4a95&#34;&gt;出于这些原因，在大规模大批量生产环境中，滚动更新通常被认为是更新过程风险太大，因为它无法控制影响范围，可能会过于激进地推出，并且会提供失败时不会自动回滚。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;b6da&#34;&gt;控制器功能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;蓝绿更新策略&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;金丝雀更新策略&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;细粒度、加权流量转移&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自动回滚和升级&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;人工判断&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可定制的业务 KPI 指标查询和分析&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;入口控制器集成：NGINX、ALB&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;服务网格集成：Istio、Linkerd、SMI&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;指标提供商集成：Prometheus、Wavefront、Kayenta、Web、Kubernetes 作业&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;17fd&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo 推出：Kubernetes 渐进式交付&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;56f0&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts”是 Kubernetes 的渐进式交付工具。它支持金丝雀和蓝绿部署等高级部署策略，确保应用程序的平滑和受控更新。凭借流量转移和分析等功能，它使团队能够在 Kubernetes 环境中充满信心、可靠地交付软件。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/rollouts/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo 推出&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-rollouts. readthedocs.io/en/stable/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/stable/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; Argo 推出：概念、设置和操​​作简要概述&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; — &lt;a href=&#34;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-rollouts/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target= &#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo 推出：概念、设置和操​​作快速指南&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d5e2&#34;&gt;使用常见的渐进式部署策略&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;bff9&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes 渐进式交付控制器&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Argo 推出通过提供蓝绿、金丝雀和实验等高级部署策略来简化 Kubernetes 部署。自动回滚和回滚分析，确保可靠性。本文档介绍了其概念，使用户能够利用其强大的功能在 Kubernetes 环境中进行无缝、受控的应用程序部署。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/stable/concepts/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 渐进式交付控制器&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d395&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;使用 Argo 部署执行渐进式部署策略 - &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.opsmx.com/blog/progressive-deployment -strategies-using-argo-rollout/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;使用 Argo Rollout 的渐进式部署策略&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d94a&#34;&gt;描述分析模板和分析运行&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;1465&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;分析模板&lt;/em&gt;—&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.opsmx.com/opsmx-intelligent-software-delivery-isd-platform-argo/user-guide /delivery-verification/analysis-template&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://docs.opsmx.com/opsmx-intelligent-software-delivery-isd-platform-argo/user-guide/delivery -verification/analysis-template&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;为部署创建分析运行 -&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/release-1.5/ generated /kubectl-argo-rollouts/kubectl-argo-rollouts_create_analysisrun/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://argo-rollouts.readthedocs.io/en/release-1.5/ generated/kubectl-argo-推出/kubectl-argo-rollouts_create_analysisrun/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*cPztpZ06xvkkUYLX-tyK8w.png&#34; alt= “阿尔戈事件”referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;f28b&#34;&gt;什么是 Argo 活动？&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4d32&#34;&gt;Argo Events 是 Kubernetes 的基于事件的依赖关系管理器，可帮助您定义来自各种事件源（如 Webhook、s3、计划、流等）的多个依赖关系，并在成功解决事件依赖关系后触发 Kubernetes 对象.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*-7cDAu5D6yKXimpZ.png&#34; alt=&#34; argo 事件图像&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;8405&#34;&gt;功能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;管理来自各种事件源的依赖关系。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;能够为事件依赖项解析自定义业务级约束逻辑。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;管理一切内容，从简单、线性、实时依赖关系到复杂、多源、批处理作业依赖关系。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;能够扩展框架以添加您自己的事件源侦听器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;定义任意布尔逻辑来解决事件依赖性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;符合 CloudEvents 标准。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;能够在运行时管理事件源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;7af2&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo 活动 - 简介和快速指南&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d316&#34;&gt;在 Codefresh 上探索 Argo 事件：探索 Kubernetes 的事件驱动自动化。了解如何构建由各种来源的事件触发的弹性、可扩展的工作流程。利用 Argo CD、事件和工作流的强大功能来简化 CI/CD 管道并优化 Kubernetes 部署。通过无缝自动化为您的 DevOps 提供支持。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-events/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo 事件：基础知识和快速教程&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;717d&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo Events：基于事件的 Kubernetes 依赖管理器&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;fe11&#34;&gt;Argo Events 教程介绍了 Argo，一个开源工作流引擎，用于使用事件驱动架构。它详细介绍了安装、配置和使用，强调 Kubernetes 的事件驱动工作流程。了解如何自动执行任务、根据事件触发工作流程以及简化 Kubernetes 操作，以实现高效、可扩展的开发和操作。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/argo-events/tutorials/01-introduction/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Events — Kubernetes 基于事件的依赖管理器&lt; /a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;665e&#34;&gt;了解 Argo 事件组件和架构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ad74&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Argo Events - Kubernetes 事件驱动的依赖管理器&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Argo Events 是 Argo 项目的一部分，负责协调 Kubernetes 原生事件驱动工作流程。其架构利用触发器、网关和传感器来检测来自各种来源（例如 Pub/Sub 系统或 HTTP 端点）的事件，从而启动工作流程。这种去中心化的云原生系统可在 Kubernetes 集群内实现可扩展、弹性的事件处理和自动化。 Argo Events — Kubernetes 基于事件的依赖关系管理器&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;2120&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes 上的事件驱动架构&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;— 通过 Argo Events 探索 Kubernetes 上事件驱动架构的动态世界。本博客深入探讨了编排微服务、利用 Kubernetes 的强大功能以及通过 Argo Events 简化工作流程。探索无缝事件处理和可扩展解决方案，释放现代技术环境中高效、响应式系统的潜力。&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.devops.dev/event-driven-architecture-on-kubernetes-with-argo -events-75b9115bb1fc&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; 带有 Argo Events 的 Kubernetes 上的事件驱动架构&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*Fub3JLyCk6Io9ApU86ueyw.png&#34; alt=&#34;argo图片&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;3b74&#34;&gt;主要学习材料：&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ecc6&#34;&gt;您可以通过我使用过的以下材料自由探索和了解 CAPA 认证及相关主题，当然 Argo 项目&lt;strong&gt;文档&lt;/strong&gt;是我们最好的朋友&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://trainingportal.linuxfoundation.org/courses/introduction-to-gitops-lfs169&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://trainingportal.linuxfoundation.org/课程/gitops-lfs169简介&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/devops-and-workflow-management-with-argo-lfs256/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https:// /training.linuxfoundation.org/training/devops-and-workflow-management-with-argo-lfs256/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://killercoda.com/argo&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://killercoda.com/argo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/&#34; 目标=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://argoproj.github.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://akuity.io/what-is-argo/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://akuity.io/what-is-argo/&lt; /a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-cd/what-is-the-argo-project-and-why-is-it-transforming-development/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://codefresh.io/learn/argo-cd/what-is-the-argo-project-and-why-is-it-transforming-development/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://ravikirans.com/capa-certified-argo-project-associate-study-guide/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://ravikirans.com /capa-certified-argo-project-associate-study-guide/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kloudsaga.com/learning-path-certified-argo-project-associate-exam/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://kloudsaga.com /learning-path-certified-argo-project-associate-exam/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://argo-workflows.readthedocs.io/en/latest/quick-start/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://argo-workflows.readthedocs .io/en/latest/quick-start/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ef48&#34;&gt;目前课程不多，因为这是一项新考试，我&lt;strong&gt;强烈建议不要点击从 Google 搜索中弹出的所有课程，因为这是一项新考试有很多骗局。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;5c5a&#34;&gt;我希望在不久的将来我们会看到更多来自更大平台（例如 kodekloud 或 Killersh）的课程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;1221&#34;&gt;结论&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;9aae&#34;&gt;考试并不容易。在其他证书中，我会将其按以下顺序排列：&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/CGOA/CAPA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS&lt;/strong&gt;。 24小时内进行考试后，您将收到评分，通过考试后总体感觉相当令人满意。我希望它内容丰富且有用🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>