<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://cloudys-rsshub-ab061133bcab.herokuapp.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【The Best of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon: Watch the video!】KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 的精华：观看视频！</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/02/03/the-best-of-kubecon-cloudnativecon-watch-the-video/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to launch a new video celebrating the energy, people, and community that make&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;what it is. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most powerful things about KubeCon + CloudNativeCon is the sheer scale and diversity of voices it brings together. As CNCF project maintainer Kingdon Barrett shares in the video,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;“The best thing about KubeCon + CloudNativeCon is the sheer number of projects that are represented here… it’s amazing to get to meet people from all over the world with all their diverse experience.”&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;From maintainers to first-time contributors, the conference reflects the truly global nature of cloud native.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For many attendees, KubeCon + CloudNativeCon is also a deeply personal milestone. Dan Kohn Scholarship recipient Unnati Atul Mishra describes finally meeting collaborators she’d only known online:&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;“I’m able to connect with like-minded people, few of the brightest minds in the cloud native space… and meet contributors I used to connect with online, now in person.”&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;These moments, where digital collaboration becomes human connection, are what make the experience unforgettable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That openness is something people feel immediately. CNCF Ambassador Michael Uanikehi puts it simply:&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;“You can literally walk up to anyone and have a conversation without feeling intimidated… everyone is open and willing to talk and express themselves.”&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;Whether you’re new to the community or deeply embedded in it, KubeCon + CloudNativeCon creates space to learn, share, and belong. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Filmed at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America in Atlanta in November 2025, we invite you to experience the magic by watching the video. And as we look ahead to the next chapter of the cloud native journey, we can’t wait to see the community come together again. See you in Amsterdam!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;wp-block-embed__wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; title=&#34;Best of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon!&#34; width=&#34;500&#34; height=&#34;281&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RX0sYHHiFvg?feature=oembed&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴推出一个新视频，庆祝 &lt;strong&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon&lt;/strong&gt; 的能量、人员和社区。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 最强大的功能之一是它汇集的声音的规模和多样性。正如 CNCF 项目维护者 Kingdon Barrett 在视频中分享的那样，“KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 的最佳之处在于这里代表的项目数量之多……能够见到来自世界各地、拥有丰富经验的人们真是太棒了。”从维护者到首次贡献者，这次会议反映了云原生真正的全球性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于许多与会者来说，KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 也是一个深刻的个人里程碑。 Dan Kohn 奖学金获得者 Unnati Atul Mishra 描述了她终于在网上认识的合作者的情况：&lt;em&gt;“我能够与志同道合的人建立联系，云原生领域中很少有最聪明的人......并与我以前在网上联系的贡献者见面，现在是面对面的。”&lt;/em&gt; 在这些时刻，数字协作变成了人与人之间的联系，这让体验变得令人难忘。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人们会立即感受到这种开放性。 CNCF 大使 Michael Uanikehi 简单地说：“您可以真正走到任何人面前并进行对话，而不会感到害怕......每个人都很开放，愿意交谈和表达自己。”无论您是社区新手还是深深融入其中，KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 都会创造学习、分享和归属感的空间。 &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;该视频于 2025 年 11 月在亚特兰大 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 北美会议上拍摄，我们邀请您观看视频来体验其中的魔力。当我们展望云原生之旅的下一章时，我们迫不及待地想看到社区再次聚集在一起。阿姆斯特丹见！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;wp-block-embed__wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; title=&#34;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 最佳作品！&#34; width =“500”height =“281”src =“https://www.youtube.com/embed/RX0sYHHiFvg？feature = oembed”frameborder =“0”allow =“加速计;自动播放;剪贴板写入;加密媒体;陀螺仪;画中画;网络共享”referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”allowfullscreen =“”&gt;&lt;/ iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OpenTelemetry Collector vs agent: How to choose the right telemetry approach】OpenTelemetry Collector 与代理：如何选择正确的遥测方法</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/02/02/opentelemetry-collector-vs-agent-how-to-choose-the-right-telemetry-approach/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As cloud-native architectures continue to mature, observability has become a foundational requirement rather than an optional add-on. According to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/07/18/a-mid-year-2025-look-at-cncf-linux-foundation-and-the-top-30-open-source-projects/&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Computing Foundation,&lt;/a&gt; OpenTelemetry continues to grow its contributor base and remains the second highest velocity project in CNCF, becoming the “kubernetes” of the o11y world. Its rapid growth and strong community momentum reflect accelerating adoption among Kubernetes and cloud-native teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As organizations standardize on OpenTelemetry, one architectural question consistently arises: &lt;strong&gt;should telemetry be collected using an OpenTelemetry Collector, an agent, or a combination of both?&lt;/strong&gt; In this guide, we demystify the OpenTelemetry Collector vs. agent debate, explain how each fits into the OpenTelemetry architecture, and help you choose the right approach for building efficient, scalable observability pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What are the main components of the OpenTelemetry architecture?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before exploring the OpenTelemetry Collector vs agent differences, it’s essential to understand how both components function within the OpenTelemetry architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What is the OpenTelemetry Collector?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OpenTelemetry Collector acts as a centralized service for managing telemetry data. When comparing the OpenTelemetry Collector vs agent, the Collector serves as the central processing hub for telemetry pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is one service that collects traces, metrics, and logs from your applications, sorts them, and then sends them to the observability tools or backends you employ. In a sense, it is the center of your monitoring environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead of your apps talking directly to monitoring backends, the Collector sits between them. It normalizes and prepares all data before forwarding it to the destination.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Collector:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; Central hub for telemetry aggregation, transformation, and export.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What makes Collector so useful?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Data Collection: The Collector can receive telemetry from various sources through receivers, including OpenTelemetry SDKs, agents, and other observability tools.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Data Processing: This step allows you to clean up the data before it is stored. You can filter out the junk you don’t need, batch it up for better efficiency, or tweak it in other ways. You can also add helpful context (metadata) and reduce noise before sending it off.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Data Exporting: Once the data is processed, this feature takes over. It uses exporters to send the data to your storage and analysis tools (backends). The big benefit here is that it doesn’t matter what observability tools you’re using this makes the data compatible with your entire stack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What is the OpenTelemetry agent?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/collector/deployment/agent/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry agent&lt;/a&gt; is a lightweight process that runs alongside your applications to collect telemetry data locally with minimal overhead before forwarding it to a Collector or backend. You can think of it as a lightweight sidecar or daemon that runs along with your app and collects telemetry data from it directly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Agent:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; Lightweight sidecar for data capture at the application level.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Its main job is straightforward: capture and forward. The agent collects traces, metrics, and logs emitted by your app and sends them (often to a Collector) with minimal processing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1468&#34; height=&#34;1000&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26.png&#34; alt=&#34;An image of a flow chart showing how the OpenTelemtry agent collects traces, metrics, and logs emitted by your app and sends them (often to a Collector) with minimal processing.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155814&#34; style=&#34;aspect-ratio:1.4680021408364554;width:812px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26.png 1468w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-300x204.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-1024x698.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-768x523.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-900x613.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-294x200.png 294w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-587x400.png 587w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-380x260.png 380w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1468px) 100vw, 1468px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Where does it differ from the Collector?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The agent focuses on local data collection, which captures telemetry as close to the source as possible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It performs minimal data processing, keeping overhead low to minimize impact on app performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It’s ideal for containerized or microservices environments, where deploying an agent alongside each service ensures complete visibility and control.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Within the OpenTelemetry ecosystem, the agent, Collector, and SDKs integrate with observability tools such as Prometheus, Jaeger, and Grafana. Together, they form a complete pipeline for metrics, logs, and traces across Kubernetes and hybrid cloud environments.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Together, the agent and Collector form the foundation of an observability pipeline.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Feature-by-feature comparison&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The key difference between the OpenTelemetry Collector and OpenTelemetry agent lies in their scope: the agent collects data locally, while the Collector aggregates and processes telemetry data centrally before exporting it to backends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector vs. agent&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Feature&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;OpenTelemetry agent&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Deployment model&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Runs as a centralized service (standalone, gateway, or clustered) that gathers telemetry from multiple sources.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Deployed alongside applications (as a sidecar or daemonset) to collect telemetry data locally.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Primary role&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Acts as a data pipeline receives, processes, and exports telemetry data to various observability platforms.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Functions as a lightweight collector focused on capturing and forwarding raw data from application instances.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Data processing capabilities&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Offers advanced processing such as batching, filtering, sampling, and transformation before exporting.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Performs minimal processing, prioritizing speed and low overhead.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Scalability&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Highly scalable, capable of handling data from hundreds of services or instances.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Scales naturally with the number of application instances each handles its own telemetry.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Performance impact&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Offloads heavy processing away from apps, reducing runtime load.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Very lightweight minimal impact on application performance.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Flexibility and customization&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Extensive customization via multiple receivers, processors, and exporters. Easily integrates with diverse observability tools.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Simpler configuration with limited customization, ideal for consistent deployments.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Security &amp;amp; Compliance&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Requires proper access control, TLS encryption, and authentication for centralized communication.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Operates within the application’s trusted boundary, reducing exposure but limited to local scope.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Integration and compatibility&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Compatible with multiple backends (Prometheus, Jaeger, Elastic, etc.) and supports hybrid or multi-cloud setups.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Tightly integrated with OpenTelemetry SDKs and supports major programming languages.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Best fit&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ideal for centralized, large-scale environments that need data aggregation and transformation.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Best for application-level observability and containerized or distributed architectures.&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key takeaway:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Use the &lt;strong&gt;Collector&lt;/strong&gt; when you need centralized control and scalability; use the &lt;strong&gt;agent&lt;/strong&gt; when you want localized, low-overhead telemetry capture near the source.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Final recommendations&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The right choice between the &lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;agent&lt;/strong&gt; depends on your system’s size and observability goals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use the Collector for centralized data aggregation and transformation across multiple services.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use the Agent for lightweight, local telemetry collection near your applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For most setups, combining both delivers the best performance and scalability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This Member Blog was originally published on the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/&#34;&gt;Middleware&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;blog and is republished here with permission.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着云原生架构的不断成熟，可观察性已成为一项基本要求，而不是可选的附加组件。根据&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/07/18/a-mid-year-2025-look-at-cncf-linux-foundation-and-the-top-30-open-source-projects/&#34;&gt;云原生计算基金会&lt;/a&gt;的数据，OpenTelemetry 的贡献者基础持续扩大，仍然是 CNCF 中第二高速度​​的项目，成为 o11y 世界的“kubernetes”。其快速增长和强大的社区势头反映了 Kubernetes 和云原生团队的加速采用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着组织对 OpenTelemetry 进行标准化，一个架构问题不断出现：&lt;strong&gt;应该使用 OpenTelemetry Collector、代理还是两者的组合来收集遥测数据？&lt;/strong&gt;在本指南中，我们将揭开 OpenTelemetry Collector 与代理争论的神秘面纱，解释每种方法如何适应 OpenTelemetry 架构，并帮助您选择正确的方法来构建高效、可扩展的可观测性管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry 架构的主要组件是什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在探索 OpenTelemetry Collector 与代理的差异之前，有必要了解这两个组件在 OpenTelemetry 架构中的工作原理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;什么是 OpenTelemetry 收集器？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector 充当管理遥测数据的集中服务。在比较 OpenTelemetry Collector 与代理时，Collector 充当遥测管道的中央处理中心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它是一项从应用程序收集跟踪、指标和日志，对它们进行排序，然后将它们发送到您使用的可观察性工具或后端的服务。从某种意义上说，它是您的监控环境的中心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您的应用程序不是直接与监控后端对话，而是收集器位于它们之间。在将所有数据转发到目的地之前，它会标准化并准备好所有数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;收集器：&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;用于遥测聚合、转换和导出的中央枢纽。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;是什么让 Collector 如此有用？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;数据收集：收集器可以通过接收器（包括 OpenTelemetry SDK、代理和其他可观测工具）接收来自各种来源的遥测数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;数据处理：此步骤允许您在存储数据之前清理数据。您可以过滤掉不需要的垃圾，将其批量化以提高效率，或以其他方式进行调整。您还可以在发送之前添加有用的上下文（元数据）并减少噪音。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;数据导出：数据处理完毕后，此功能将发挥作用。它使用导出器将数据发送到您的存储和分析工具（后端）。这里的最大好处是，无论您使用什么可观察性工具，都可以使数据兼容能够处理您的整个堆栈。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;什么是 OpenTelemetry 代理？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/collector/deployment/agent/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry 代理&lt;/a&gt;是一个轻量级进程，与您的应用程序一起运行，在将遥测数据转发到收集器或后端之前以最小的开销在本地收集遥测数据。您可以将其视为与您的应用程序一起运行并直接从中收集遥测数据的轻量级边车或守护程序。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;代理：&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;用于应用程序级别数据捕获的轻量级 sidecar。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它的主要工作很简单：捕获和转发。该代理收集您的应用发出的跟踪、指标和日志，并以最少的处理将它们发送（通常发送到收集器）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1468&#34; height=&#34;1000&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26.png&#34; alt=&#34;流程图的图像，显示 OpenTelemtry 代理如何收集应用程序发出的跟踪、指标和日志并发送它们（通常是收藏家）以最少的处理。”类=“wp-image-155814”样式=“宽高比：1.4680021408364554；宽度：812px；高度：自动”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26.png 1468w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-300x204.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-1024x698.png 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-768x523.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-900x613.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-294x200.png 294w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-587x400.png 587w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-26-380x260.png 380w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1468px）100vw，1468px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;它与收集器有什么不同？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;代理专注于本地数据收集，捕获尽可能靠近数据源的遥测数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;它执行最少的数据处理，保持较低的开销，从而最大限度地减少对应用性能的影响。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;它非常适合容器化或微服务环境，在这些环境中，与每项服务一起部署代理可确保完全的可见性和控制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;在 OpenTelemetry 生态系统中，代理、收集器和 SDK 与 Prometheus、Jaeger 和 Grafana 等可观测性工具集成。它们共同构成了跨 Kubernetes 和混合云环境的指标、日志和跟踪的完整管道。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;代理和收集器共同构成了可观察性管道的基础。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;逐个功能比较&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemet 之间的主要区别Collector 和 OpenTelemetry Agent 的作用范围在于：Agent 在本地收集数据，而 Collector 在将遥测数据导出到后端之前集中聚合和处理数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这里有一个细分：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry 收集器与代理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;功能&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;OpenTelemetry代理&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;部署模型&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;作为集中服务（独立、网关或集群）运行，从多个收集遥测数据&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;与应用程序一起部署（作为 sidecar 或守护程序集），以在本地收集遥测数据。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;主要角色&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;充当数据管道，接收、处理遥测数据并将其导出到各种可观测平台。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;充当轻量级收集器，专注于从应用程序捕获和转发原始数据&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;数据处理功能&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;在导出之前提供批处理、过滤、采样和转换等高级处理功能。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;执行最少的处理，优先考虑速度和低开销。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;可扩展性&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;高度可扩展，能够处理来自数百个服务或实例的数据。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;可扩展自然地，每个处理自己的遥测的应用程序实例的数量。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;性能影响&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;从应用程序中卸载繁重的处理，减少运行时负载。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;对应用程序性能的影响非常轻。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;灵活性和自定义&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;通过多个接收器、处理器和导出器进行广泛的自定义。轻松与各种可观测工具集成。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;配置更简单，自定义有限，非常适合一致部署。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;安全性与合规性&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;需要适当的访问控制、TLS 加密和集中通信身份验证。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;在应用程序的可信边界内运行，减少暴露，但仅限于本地范围。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;集成和兼容性&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;兼容多个后端（Prometheus、Jaeger、Elastic 等）并支持混合或多云设置。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;与 OpenTelemetry SDK 紧密集成并支持主要编程语言。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;最适合&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;非常适合需要数据聚合和分析的集中式大型环境转换。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;最适合应用程序级可观察性和容器化或分布式架构。&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;要点：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;当您需要集中控制和可扩展性时，请使用&lt;strong&gt;收集器&lt;/strong&gt;；当您想要在源附近进行本地化、低开销的遥测捕获时，请使用&lt;strong&gt;代理&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;最终建议&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正确的选择&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector&lt;/strong&gt; 和&lt;strong&gt;代理&lt;/strong&gt;取决于您系统的规模和可观测性目标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用收集器跨多个服务进行集中数据聚合和转换。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用代理在您的应用程序附近进行轻量级本地遥测收集。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;对于大多数设置来说，将两者结合起来可提供最佳性能和可扩展性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;此会员博客最初发布在 &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://middleware.io/&#34;&gt;中间件&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;博客上，经许可在此处重新发布。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From global stages to a local landmark: Organizing KCD Sri Lanka 2025】从全球舞台到当地地标：组织 2025 年斯里兰卡 KCD</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/01/29/from-global-stages-to-a-local-landmark-organizing-kcd-sri-lanka-2025/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Learning from the global cloud native community&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before KCD Sri Lanka 2025, our organizing team received an incredible opportunity to attend and speak at KubeCon events for the very first time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Our organizers &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/chamodshehanka/&#34;&gt;Chamod Perera&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kemilad/&#34;&gt;Kemila De Silva&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sureshmichael/&#34;&gt;Suresh&lt;/a&gt; attended KubeCon India 2024, experiencing firsthand the scale, energy, and community spirit of a global CNCF event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18.png&#34; alt=&#34;A photo group image of KCD organizers Chamod Perera, Kemila De Silva, and Suresh, with a group of colleagues, attending KubeCon India 2024&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155802&#34; style=&#34;width:581px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18.png 640w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18-300x225.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18-267x200.png 267w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18-533x400.png 533w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2025,&amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/chamodshehanka/&#34;&gt;Chamod&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kemilad/&#34;&gt;Kemila&lt;/a&gt;, returned to the same event, this time as speakers at KubeCon India 2025, delivering a talk on lessons learned from &lt;strong&gt;lessons from running a Cloud Native community.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaveeshag/&#34;&gt;Kaveesha&lt;/a&gt; also joined KubeCon India 2025, adding further perspectives to our growing pool of experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1200&#34; height=&#34;1600&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19.png&#34; alt=&#34;A group shot of KCD organizers Chamod, Kemila, and Kaveesha at KubeCon India 2025.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155803&#34; style=&#34;width:578px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19.png 1200w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-225x300.png 225w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-768x1024.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-900x1200.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-150x200.png 150w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-300x400.png 300w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These experiences did more than inspire us. They reshaped how we thought about conference design, speaker diversity, networking spaces, and attendee experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Bringing KubeCon level energy to KCD Sri Lanka&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Armed with global exposure and years of community-building experience, we returned to Sri Lanka determined to raise the bar. KCD Sri Lanka 2025 was not just another local conference. It was a carefully crafted experience that blended global best practices with local community culture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We did not just bring insights back from KubeCon + CloudNativeCon. We brought people, speakers, and connections from those global events into KCD Sri Lanka. This resulted in a richer program, broader perspectives, and stronger networking opportunities for everyone who attended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1600&#34; height=&#34;900&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20.png&#34; alt=&#34;A group shot of 12 members of KCD Sri Lanka 2025, standing in front of a billboard advertising the event with the headline &#39;Sri Lanka&#39;s Biggest Cloud Native Event&#39;. &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155804&#34; style=&#34;width:642px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20.png 1600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-300x169.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-1024x576.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-768x432.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-900x506.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-356x200.png 356w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-711x400.png 711w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Introducing the breakout room concept&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our boldest experiments at KCD Sri Lanka 2025 was the introduction of breakout rooms. While the main hall hosted primary talks, a second hall ran deeper and more technical sessions in parallel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Initially, we were unsure how the Sri Lankan audience would respond but several attendees told us that it felt very similar to the KubeCon experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That feedback alone made the risk worthwhile.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-21.png&#34; alt=&#34;A photo image of &#39;The Blame Game&#39; presentation slide on a projector screen, against a bronze wall backdrop, with the presenter in the foreground at KCD Sri Lanka 2025.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155805&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-21.png 640w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-21-300x169.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-21-356x200.png 356w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;A strong CFP and an exceptional lineup&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We received over 100 CFPs, which was a massive achievement of our community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With such an overwhelming response, we faced the incredibly difficult task of shortlisting those submissions down to just 20 exceptional talks. Every selection required careful discussion, and the process itself showed how far the community has come in terms of depth and quality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The final lineup was truly magnificent. We had leaders from local tech giants sharing real-world production experiences, and we were honored to host outstanding international speakers as well. Some of these speakers had recently presented at major global events such as KubeCon + CloudNativeCon, bringing global perspectives directly to the KCD Sri Lanka stage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; height=&#34;481&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22.png&#34; alt=&#34;A photo complication image of six of the presenters onstage at KCD Sri Lanka 2025, featuring a bottom row of six additional images of attendees receiving awards onstage. &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155806&#34; style=&#34;aspect-ratio:1.496930123769613;width:679px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22.png 720w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22-300x200.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22-299x200.png 299w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22-599x400.png 599w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;A lively and crowded booth area&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The booth area was another highlight of the event. With nine booths set up, the space was constantly busy. Participants were networking, exploring technologies, and engaging with sponsors throughout the day. Some speakers even commented that the atmosphere felt like a mini KubeCon + CloudNativeCon, which was a proud moment for the entire organizing team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-23.png&#34; alt=&#34;An image of the crowded booth area at KCD Sri Lanka 2025. The photo was taken by Iraj Walisinghe. Pulse All Rights Reserved. &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155807&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-23.png 640w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-23-300x200.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-23-600x400.png 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Battle of DevOps: A first for the community&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the first time at a Sri Lankan conference, we organized a hackathon called Battle of DevOps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What made it even more special was that our volunteers built the hackathon platform from scratch. We are now planning to donate this platform to CNCF so that other communities can reuse and benefit from it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;340&#34; height=&#34;556&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24.png&#34; alt=&#34;A photo image of &#39;Battle of DevOps&#39; at KCD Sri Lanka 2025. The image shows the auditorium room and stage area lit up with green and blue lighting, and a green neon aisle and seating area. &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155808&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24.png 340w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24-183x300.png 183w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24-122x200.png 122w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24-245x400.png 245w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 340px) 100vw, 340px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;KCD arena and the Sri Lankan jam&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We ended the event with KCD Arena. This created a relaxed environment for networking while enjoying live music and dinner. In a rare and joyful moment, members of the organizing committee joined the band and played instruments themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was less like a formal conference closing and more like a KCD Sri Lanka Jam, a celebration of community, collaboration, and shared passion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;1166&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25.png&#34; alt=&#34;A photo image of a keyboardist and their keyboard at the KCD Sri Lanka Jam. &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155809&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25.png 640w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25-165x300.png 165w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25-562x1024.png 562w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25-110x200.png 110w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25-220x400.png 220w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Challenges and lessons learned&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KCD Sri Lanka 2025 came with its own set of challenges. On the event day, the production setup was not delivered within the agreed timeline, and we also encountered issues with on-site event badge printing. These factors together caused a delay in the official start of the event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While these situations were not ideal, they provided valuable lessons for future editions. For upcoming events, we plan to complete badge printing well in advance and introduce clearer contractual clauses with production vendors to ensure timely delivery of all setups.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Looking back&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KCD Sri Lanka 2025 was the result of years of persistence, global learning, and local dedication. The lessons gained from KubeCon, and the willingness to experiment with new ideas all came together to shape the strongest KCD Sri Lanka we have organized so far.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We extend our sincere gratitude to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kanchanaw/&#34;&gt;Kanchana&lt;/a&gt; for his continued guidance, and to Audra, and the whole CNCF team for their constant support, trust, and encouragement throughout this journey.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What’s next for KCD Sri Lanka&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While KCD Sri Lanka 2025 has concluded, the journey is far from over. The momentum, feedback, and learnings from this chapter have already sparked conversations within the organizing team about what the next edition could look like.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have begun exploring ideas for the next KCD Sri Lanka, including expanding breakout sessions to allow for even more focused and deeply technical discussions, and continuing to experiment with interactive formats inspired by global Cloud Native events. These ideas are still evolving, and we are taking time to reflect carefully before applying for the next chapter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For now, we will continue strengthening the Kubernetes Sri Lanka community through meetups, knowledge sharing, and collaboration, while quietly preparing for the next opportunity to bring everyone together again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;向全球云原生社区学习&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 KCD 斯里兰卡 2025 之前，我们的组织团队第一次获得了绝佳的机会参加 KubeCon 活动并发表演讲。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;我们的组织者 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/chamodshehanka/&#34;&gt;Chamod Perera&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kemilad/&#34;&gt;Kemila De Silva&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sureshmichael/&#34;&gt;Suresh&lt;/a&gt; 参加了 2024 年 KubeCon India，亲身体验了规模、活力、和全球 CNCF 活动的社区精神。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;480&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18.png&#34; alt=&#34;KCD 组织者 Chamod Perera、Kemila De Silva 和 Suresh 以及一群同事参加的合影KubeCon 印度 2024&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155802&#34; style=&#34;width:581px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18.png 640w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18-300x225.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18-267x200.png 267w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-18-533x400.png 533w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：640px）100vw，640px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2025 年，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/chamodshehanka/&#34;&gt;Chamod&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kemilad/&#34;&gt;Kemila&lt;/a&gt; 再次参加同一活动，这次是在 KubeCon India 2025 上作为演讲者，发表演讲，讲述从运营云原生社区中获得的经验教训。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaveeshag/&#34;&gt;Kaveesha&lt;/a&gt; 也加入了 KubeCon India 2025，为我们不断增长的经验库增添了更多视角。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1200&#34; height=&#34;1600&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19.png&#34; alt=&#34;KCD 组织者 Chamod、Kemila 和 Kaveesha 在 KubeCon India 的集体照2025 年。”类=“wp-image-155803”样式=“宽度：578px;高度：自动”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19.png 1200w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-225x300.png 225w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-768x1024.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-900x1200.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-150x200.png 150w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-19-300x400.png 300w”尺寸=“自动，（最大宽度：1200px）100vw， 1200px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些经历不仅仅启发了我们。他们重塑了我们对会议设计、演讲者多样性、网络空间和与会者体验的看法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;为 KCD Sri 带来 KubeCon 级别的能量兰卡&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;凭借全球视野和多年的社区建设经验，我们回到斯里兰卡，决心提高标准。 KCD 斯里兰卡 2025 不仅仅是另一场本地会议。这是一次精心打造的体验，将全球最佳实践与当地社区文化融为一体。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们不仅仅从 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 中带回见解。我们将这些全球活动中的人员、演讲者和人脉带入 KCD 斯里兰卡。这为每个参加者带来了更丰富的项目、更广阔的视角和更强大的交流机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1600&#34; height=&#34;900&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20.png&#34; alt=&#34;KCD 斯里兰卡 2025 的 12 名成员站在以标题为活动广告的广告牌前合影&#39;斯里兰卡最大的云原生活动&#39;&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155804&#34; style=&#34;width:642px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20.png 1600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-300x169.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-1024x576.png 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-768x432.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-900x506.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-356x200.png 356w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-20-711x400.png 711w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1600px）100vw， 1600px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;介绍分组讨论室概念&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们在 KCD 斯里兰卡 2025 大会上最大胆的实验是引入分组讨论室。在主厅举办主要演讲的同时，第二个厅同时举办了更深入、更具技术性的会议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最初，我们不确定斯里兰卡观众会作何反应，但几位与会者告诉我们，这感觉与 KubeCon 体验非常相似。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仅凭反馈就值得冒这个风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-21.png&#34; alt=&#34;投影仪屏幕上的“指责游戏”演示幻灯片的照片图像，以青铜墙为背景，演示者位于 KCD Sri 的前景兰卡 2025。” class =“wp-image-155805”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-21.png 640w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-21-300x169.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-21-356x200.png 356w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：640px）100vw，640px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;强大的 CFP 和出色的阵容&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们收到了 100 多个 CFP，这是我们社区的一项巨大成就。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有了如此热烈的反响，我们将这些提交材料入围的极其艰巨的任务缩减为仅 20 场出色的演讲。每一个选择都需要仔细的讨论，而过程本身就表明了社区在深度和质量方面所取得的进步。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终的阵容确实非常华丽。我们有来自当地科技巨头的领导者分享了实际的生产经验，我们也很荣幸邀请到了杰出的国际演讲者。其中一些演讲者最近在 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 等重大全球活动中发表演讲，将全球视角直接带到 KCD 斯里兰卡舞台。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;720&#34; height=&#34;481&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22.png&#34; alt=&#34;2025 年 KCD 斯里兰卡舞台上六位演讲者的照片复杂图像，其中底行有六张附加图像&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155806&#34; style=&#34;aspect-ratio:1.496930123769613;width:679px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22.png 720w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22-300x200.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22-299x200.png 299w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-22-599x400.png 599w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：720像素）100vw，720像素“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;热闹且拥挤的展位区&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;展位区是本次活动的另一大亮点。共有九个展位，现场热闹非凡。参与者全天都在交流、探索技术并与赞助商互动。一些演讲者甚至评论说，现场气氛就像迷你KubeCon + CloudNativeCon，这对整个组织团队来说是一个值得骄傲的时刻。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;427&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-23.png&#34; alt=&#34;2025 年 KCD 斯里兰卡展位区拥挤的图片。照片由 Iraj Walisinghe 拍摄。Pulse 保留所有权利。 &#34; class =“wp-image-155807”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-23.png 640w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-23-300x200.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-23-600x400.png 600w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：640px）100vw，640px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;DevOps 之战：社区第一次&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们首次在斯里兰卡会议上组织了一场名为 Battle of DevOps 的黑客马拉松。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更特别的是，我们的志愿者从头开始构建了黑客马拉松平台。我们现在计划将该平台捐赠给 CNCF，以便其他社区可以重用并从中受益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; 解码ing=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;340&#34; height=&#34;556&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24.png&#34; alt=&#34;2025 年斯里兰卡 KCD 上的“DevOps 之战”照片图像。该图像显示礼堂和舞台区被绿色和蓝色灯光照亮，以及绿色霓虹灯过道和座位区。 &#34; class =“wp-image-155808”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24.png 340w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24-183x300.png 183w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24-122x200.png 122w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-24-245x400.png 245w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：340px）100vw， 340px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;KCD 竞技场和斯里兰卡果酱&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们以 KCD Arena 结束了活动。这为您在享受现场音乐和晚餐的同时创造了一个轻松的社交环境。在难得的欢乐时刻，组委会成员也加入了乐队并亲自演奏乐器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这不像是一次正式的会议闭幕式，而更像是 KCD 斯里兰卡即兴表演，是对社区、协作和共同热情的庆祝。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;1166&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25.png&#34; alt=&#34;KCD 斯里兰卡果酱乐队中键盘手及其键盘的照片。&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155809&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25.png 640w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25-165x300.png 165w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25-562x1024.png 562w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25-110x200.png 110w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-25-220x400.png 220w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：640px）100vw，640px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;挑战和经验教训&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;斯里兰卡 2025 年 KCD 大会也面临着一系列挑战。活动当天，生产设置未能在约定的时间内交付，而且我们还遇到了现场活动徽章打印的问题。这些因素共同导致了活动正式开始的延迟。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然这些情况并不理想，但它们为未来的版本提供了宝贵的经验教训。对于即将举行的活动，我们计划提前完成徽章打印，并与生产供应商引入更清晰的合同条款，以确保及时交付所有设置。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;回顾过去&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KCD 斯里兰卡 2025 是多年坚持、全球学习和当地奉献的结果。从 KubeCon 中获得的经验教训以及尝试新想法的意愿共同塑造了我们迄今为止组织的最强大的 KCD 斯里兰卡。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们对 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/kanchanaw/&#34;&gt;Kanchana&lt;/a&gt; 的持续支持表示诚挚的谢意idance，感谢 Audra 和整个 CNCF 团队在整个过程中给予的持续支持、信任和鼓励。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;KCD 斯里兰卡的下一步发展&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 KCD 斯里兰卡 2025 已经结束，但旅程还远未结束。本章的动力、反馈和经验已经引发了组织团队内部关于下一届会是什么样子的对话。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经开始探索下一届 KCD 斯里兰卡的想法，包括扩大分组会议，以便进行更有针对性和更深入的技术讨论，并继续尝试受全球云原生活动启发的交互式格式。这些想法仍在不断发展，我们在申请下一章之前会花时间仔细思考。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，我们将继续通过聚会、知识共享和协作来加强 Kubernetes 斯里兰卡社区，同时静静地准备下一次让大家再次聚集在一起的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Kthena: LLM inference for the cloud native era】Kthena 简介：云原生时代的 LLM 推理</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/01/28/introducing-kthena-llm-inference-for-the-cloud-native-era/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://volcano.sh/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Volcano&lt;/a&gt; community is proud to announce the launch of &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/volcano-sh/kthena&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Kthena&lt;/a&gt;, a new sub-project designed for global developers and MLOps engineers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena is a cloud native, high-performance system for Large Language Model (LLM) inference routing, orchestration, and scheduling, tailored specifically for Kubernetes. Engineered to address the complexity of serving LLMs at production scale, Kthena delivers granular control and enhanced flexibility. Through features like topology-aware scheduling, KV Cache-aware routing, and Prefill-Decode (PD) disaggregation, it significantly improves GPU/NPU utilization and throughput while minimizing latency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a sub-project of Volcano, Kthena extends Volcano’s capabilities beyond AI training, creating a unified, end-to-end solution for the entire AI lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The “Last Mile” Challenge of LLM Serving&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While LLMs are reshaping industries, deploying them efficiently on Kubernetes remains a complex systems engineering challenge. Developers face four critical hurdles:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Low Resource Utilization:&lt;/strong&gt; The dynamic memory footprint of LLM inference—especially the KV Cache—creates massive pressure on GPU/NPU resources. Traditional Round-Robin load balancers fail to perceive these characteristics, leading to a mix of idle resources and queued requests that drives up costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Latency vs. Throughput Trade-off:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference consists of two distinct phases: Prefill (compute-intensive) and Decode (memory-bound). Coupled scheduling limits optimization. While PD Disaggregation is the industry standard solution, efficient routing and scheduling for it remain difficult.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Complex Multi-Model Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Enterprises often serve multiple models, versions, and LoRA adapters simultaneously. Implementing fair scheduling, priority management, and dynamic routing is difficult, leading some to resort to rigid 1:1 mappings between AI Gateways and models.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of Native K8s Integration:&lt;/strong&gt; Many existing solutions are either fragmented from the Kubernetes ecosystem or too complex for standard platform operations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Kthena: The Intelligent Brain for Cloud Native Inference&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena was built to conquer these challenges. Rather than replacing existing inference engines (like vLLM or SGLang), Kthena acts as an intelligent orchestration layer on top of them, deeply integrated into Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;653&#34; height=&#34;414&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Kthena Architecture&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155926&#34; style=&#34;aspect-ratio:1.5540267098340752;width:900px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1.png 653w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1-300x190.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1-315x200.png 315w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1-631x400.png 631w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 653px) 100vw, 653px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Kthena Architecture&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena consists of two core components:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kthena Router:&lt;/strong&gt; A high-performance, multi-model router that acts as the entry point for all inference requests. It intelligently distributes traffic to backend ModelServers based on ModelRoute rules.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kthena Controller Manager:&lt;/strong&gt; The control plane responsible for workload orchestration and lifecycle management. It reconciles Custom Resource Definitions (CRDs) like ModelBooster, ModelServing, and AutoScalingPolicy to convert declarative intent into runtime resources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It orchestrates ServingGroups and roles (Prefill/Decode).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It handles topology-aware affinity, Gang scheduling, rolling updates, and failure recovery.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It drives elastic scaling based on defined policies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Core Features and Advantages&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1. Production-Grade Inference Orchestration (ModelServing)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1070&#34; height=&#34;800&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34.png&#34; alt=&#34;ModelServing architecture&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-156590&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34.png 1070w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-300x224.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-1024x766.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-768x574.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-900x673.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-268x200.png 268w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-535x400.png 535w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1070px) 100vw, 1070px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Kthena introduces a Hierarchical Workload Architecture (ModelServing -&amp;gt; ServingGroup -&amp;gt; Role).&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unified API:&lt;/strong&gt; A single API supports diverse patterns, from standalone deployments to complex PD Disaggregation and Expert Parallelism (EP).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified Management:&lt;/strong&gt; For example, a massive PD deployment is managed as a single ModelServing resource containing multiple ServingGroups.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Native PD Disaggregation:&lt;/strong&gt; Kthena optimizes hardware usage by routing compute-intensive Prefill tasks to high-compute nodes and memory-bound Decode tasks to High Bandwidth Memory (HBM) nodes. It supports independent scaling to dynamically adjust the Prefill/Decode ratio.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topology Awareness &amp;amp; Gang Scheduling:&lt;/strong&gt; Gang scheduling guarantees that pods in a ServingGroup are scheduled as an atomic unit, preventing deadlocks. Topology awareness minimizes data transmission latency by placing related pods closer together in the network fabric.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2. Out-of-the-Box Deployment (ModelBooster)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Templates:&lt;/strong&gt; Provides built-in templates for mainstream models (including PD separation), automatically generating necessary routing and lifecycle resources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexibility:&lt;/strong&gt; Covers general scenarios while allowing granular control via ModelServing for complex needs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;3. Intelligent, Model-Aware Routing&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-Model Routing:&lt;/strong&gt; OpenAI API compatible. Routes traffic based on headers or body content.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pluggable Algorithms:&lt;/strong&gt; Includes Least Request, Least Latency, KV Cache Awareness, Prefix Cache Awareness, LoRA Affinity, and Fairness Scheduling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LoRA Hot-Swapping:&lt;/strong&gt; Detects loaded LoRA adapters for non-disruptive hot-swapping and routing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traffic Governance:&lt;/strong&gt; Supports canary releases, token-level rate limiting, and failover.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;All-in-One Architecture:&lt;/strong&gt; Eliminates the need for a separate Envoy Gateway by natively handling routing logic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;4. Cost-Driven Autoscaling&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Homogeneous Scaling:&lt;/strong&gt; Scales precisely based on business metrics (CPU/GPU/Memory/Custom).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heterogeneous Optimization:&lt;/strong&gt; Optimizes resource allocation across different accelerators based on a “Cost-Performance” ratio.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;5. Broad Hardware &amp;amp; Engine Support&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inference Engines:&lt;/strong&gt; Supports vLLM, SGLang, Triton/TGI, and more via a unified API abstraction.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heterogeneous Compute:&lt;/strong&gt; Enables co-location of GPU and NPU resources to balance cost and Service Level Objectives (SLOs).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;6. Built-in Flow Control &amp;amp; Fairness&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fairness Scheduling:&lt;/strong&gt; Prioritizes traffic based on usage history to prevent “starvation” of low-priority users.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flow Control:&lt;/strong&gt; Granular limits based on user, model, and token length.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Performance Benchmarks&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In scenarios with long system prompts (e.g., 4096 tokens), Kthena’s “KV Cache Awareness + Least Request” strategy delivers significant gains compared to a random baseline:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Throughput:&lt;/strong&gt; Increased by &lt;strong&gt;~2.73x&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TTFT (Time To First Token):&lt;/strong&gt; Reduced by &lt;strong&gt;~73.5%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;End-to-End Latency:&lt;/strong&gt; Reduced by &lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;60%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plugin Configuration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Throughput (req/s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TTFT (s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;E2E Latency (s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Least Request + KVCacheAware&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;32.22&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9.22&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;0.57&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Least Request + Prefix Cache&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;23.87&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;12.47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;0.83&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Random&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;11.81&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;25.23&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;2.15&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: While gaps narrow with short prompts, KV Cache awareness offers decisive advantages for multi-turn conversations and template-heavy workloads.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Community &amp;amp; Industry Support&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena has already attracted widespread attention and support from industry leaders since its inception.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Open source is the lifeblood of technical innovation and the primary driver of industry standardization. As the initiator of Volcano, Huawei Cloud is proud to launch Kthena alongside our community partners.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release marks not only a significant milestone in Volcano’s technical evolution but also underscores Huawei Cloud’s enduring commitment to Cloud Native AI. By deeply integrating with infrastructure like Huawei Cloud CCE and CCI, Kthena unlocks the full potential of diverse computing power—including Ascend—delivering superior cost-efficiency to our customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through Kthena, we look forward to collaborating with global developers to build an open, thriving ecosystem that lays a robust foundation for the intelligent transformation of industries worldwide.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;Xiaobo Qi&lt;/strong&gt;, Director of General Computing Services, Huawei Cloud&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Kthena further solidifies Volcano’s leadership in intelligent workload scheduling. By leveraging Volcano’s unified scheduling and resource pooling capabilities, our platform addresses diverse compute requirements—spanning general-purpose computing, AI training, and inference—within a single, unified framework.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This enables dynamic resource allocation across different scenarios, effectively eliminating resource silos. Looking ahead, we are excited to combine Kthena with Volcano’s elastic scaling and Volcano Global’s cross-cluster scheduling to drive resource utilization to new heights.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;Lei Yang&lt;/strong&gt;, PaaS R&amp;amp;D Director, China Telecom AI&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Since its inception, Volcano has evolved in lockstep with the community to address diverse AI scenarios, establishing a comprehensive ecosystem for AI batch processing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The launch of Kthena marks a major milestone, extending Volcano’s capabilities into the critical realm of Large Model inference. It crystallizes years of Volcano’s best practices in scheduling, elasticity, and multi-architecture support into a powerful engine for unified orchestration and intelligent routing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By leveraging the existing Kubernetes and Volcano ecosystems, teams can achieve smarter scheduling decisions and higher compute efficiency at a lower cost. For DaoCloud, Kthena not only solves tangible inference challenges but also embodies the future of Cloud Native AI—an open, intelligent ecosystem worthy of our long-term investment and deep engagement.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;Paco Xu&lt;/strong&gt;, Open Source Team Lead at DaoCloud, Member of Kubernetes Steering Committee&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Deploying and managing self-hosted LLM inference services at production scale is a complex systems engineering challenge. It encompasses the entire lifecycle—deployment, operations, elasticity, and recovery—alongside critical requirements like GPU stability, scheduling efficiency, and AI observability. Kthena is engineered specifically to address these complexities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During Kthena’s planning phase, the Xiaohongshu Cloud Native team engaged deeply with contributors to co-design various intelligent traffic scheduling strategies. Moving forward, we will continue our collaboration on the AI Gateway front. By leveraging Xiaohongshu’s production insights, we aim to provide the community with production-ready capabilities, including granular traffic scheduling, model API management, and MCP protocol support.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;Kong Gu (Huachang Chen)&lt;/strong&gt;, Cloud Native Business Gateway Lead, Xiaohongshu&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“After an in-depth evaluation of Kthena, China Unicom Cloud is impressed by its forward-looking design. We are particularly excited about its joint scheduling capabilities with Volcano.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Features like topology awareness and Gang Scheduling directly address the critical efficiency and reliability challenges inherent in large-scale distributed inference, offering a promising solution to complex scheduling bottlenecks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We believe Kthena’s superior low latency, high throughput, and intelligent routing will provide the open-source community with a truly production-ready solution, empowering developers to build and manage cloud native AI applications with greater efficiency.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;Zhaoxu Lu&lt;/strong&gt;, Team Lead, Intelligent Computing Center, China Unicom Cloud&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Openness and collaboration fuel innovation. Within the CNCF ecosystem, we are dedicated to driving infrastructure towards an ‘AI Native’ future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By launching the Kthena sub-project, the Volcano community applies its proven expertise in batch computing—like topology awareness and Gang scheduling—to online LLM inference. Kthena introduces essential cloud native scheduling primitives, enabling complex LLM workloads to run efficiently as first-class citizens in Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We invite developers worldwide to join us in refining this critical infrastructure and accelerating the AI Native era.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;Kevin Wang&lt;/strong&gt;, Volcano Maintainer, CNCF TOC Vice Chair&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Start Exploring Kthena Today&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is just the beginning. We plan to support more efficient scheduling algorithms and broader best practices for large model deployment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Repository:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/volcano-sh/kthena&#34;&gt;https://github.com/volcano-sh/kthena&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Official Website:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://kthena.volcano.sh/&#34;&gt;https://kthena.volcano.sh/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud-native.slack.com/archives/C011GJDQS0N&#34;&gt;Join our Slack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join us to unlock the full potential of Cloud Native LLMs!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://volcano.sh/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Volcano&lt;/a&gt; 社区自豪地宣布推出 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/volcano-sh/kthena&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Kthena&lt;/a&gt;，这是一个专为全球开发者和 MLOps 工程师设计的新子项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena 是一个云原生高性能系统，用于大型语言模型 (LLM) 推理路由、编排和调度，专为 Kubernetes 量身定制。 Kthena 旨在解决生产规模的法学硕士服务的复杂性，提供精细的控制和增强的灵活性。通过拓扑感知调度、KV 缓存感知路由和预填充解码 (PD) 分解等功能，它显着提高了 GPU/NPU 利用率和吞吐量，同时最大限度地减少了延迟。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为 Volcano 的子项目，Kthena 将 Volcano 的功能扩展到 AI 训练之外，为整个 AI 生命周期创建统一的端到端解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;LLM 服务的“最后一英里”挑战&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然法学硕士正在重塑行业，但在 Kubernetes 上有效部署它们仍然是一个复杂的系统工程挑战。开发人员面临四个关键障碍：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;资源利用率低&lt;/strong&gt;：LLM 推理的动态内存占用（尤其是 KV 缓存）对 GPU/NPU 资源造成巨大压力。传统的循环负载均衡器无法感知这些特征，从而导致闲置资源和排队请求的混合，从而推高了成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;延迟与吞吐量的权衡：&lt;/strong&gt;推理由两个不同的阶段组成：预填充（计算密集型）和解码（内存密集型）。耦合调度限制了优化。虽然 PD 分解是行业标准解决方案，但高效的路由和调度仍然很困难。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;复杂的多模型管理：&lt;/strong&gt;企业经常同时服务多个模型、版本和 LoRA 适配器。实现公平调度、优先级管理和动态路由很困难，导致一些人在 AI 网关和模型之间采用严格的 1:1 映射。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;缺乏原生 K8s 集成&lt;/strong&gt;：许多现有解决方案要么从 Kubernetes 生态系统中分离出来，要么对于标准平台操作来说过于复杂。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Kthena：云原生推理的智能大脑&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena 的诞生就是为了克服这些挑战。 Kthena 不是取代现有的推理引擎（如 vLLM 或 SGLang），而是充当它们之上的智能编排层，深度集成到 Kubernetes 中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;653&#34;height=&#34;414&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1.png&#34;alt=&#34;Kthena Architecture&#34;class=&#34;wp-image-155926&#34;style=&#34;aspect-比例：1.5540267098340752；宽度：900px；高度：自动&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1.png 653w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1-300x190.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1-315x200.png 315w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1-631x400.png 631w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：653px） 100vw，653px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Kthena 架构&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena 由两个核心组件组成：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kthena 路由器&lt;/strong&gt;：高性能、多模型路由器，充当所有推理请求的入口点。它根据 ModelRoute 规则智能地将流量分配到后端 ModelServer。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kthena Controller Manager&lt;/strong&gt;：负责工作负载编排和生命周期管理的控制平面。它协调 ModelBooster、ModelServing 和 AutoScalingPolicy 等自定义资源定义 (CRD)，将声明性意图转换为运行时资源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;它协调服务组和角色（预填充/解码）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;它可以处理拓扑感知关联、组调度、滚动更新和故障恢复。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;它根据定义的策略推动弹性扩展。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;核心特性和优势&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1.生产级推理编排（ModelServing）&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“async”width=“1070”height=“800”src=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34.png”alt=“ModelServing架构”class=“wp-image-156590” srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34.png 1070w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-300x224.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-1024x766.png 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-768x574.png 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-900x673.png 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-268x200.png 268w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-34-535x400.png 535w&#34;sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1070px) 100vw, 1070px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Kthena 引入了分层工作负载架构（模型服务 -&gt; 服务组 -&gt; 角色）。&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;统一 API：&lt;/strong&gt;单个 API 支持多种模式，从独立部署到复杂的 PD 分解和专家并行 (EP)。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简化管理&lt;/strong&gt;：例如，大规模 PD 部署作为包含多个 ServingGroup 的单个 ModelServing 资源进行管理。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;原生 PD 分解&lt;/strong&gt;：Kthena 通过路由计算来优化硬件使用将紧张的预填充任务分配给高计算节点，将内存密集的解码任务分配给高带宽内存 (HBM) 节点。支持独立缩放，动态调整预填充/解码比例。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;拓扑感知和组调度：&lt;/strong&gt;组调度可确保 ServingGroup 中的 Pod 被调度为原子单元，从而防止死锁。拓扑感知通过在网络结构中将相关 Pod 放置得更近来最大限度地减少数据传输延迟。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2.开箱即用的部署（ModelBooster）&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;模板：&lt;/strong&gt;提供主流模型的内置模板（包括PD分离），自动生成必要的路由和生命周期资源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;灵活性：&lt;/strong&gt;涵盖一般场景，同时允许通过 ModelServing 进行精细控制以满足复杂需求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;3.智能、模型感知路由&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;多模型路由：&lt;/strong&gt;兼容 OpenAI API。根据标头或正文内容路由流量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可插拔算法：&lt;/strong&gt;包括最少请求、最少延迟、KV 缓存感知、前缀缓存感知、LoRA 亲和性和公平调度。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LoRA 热插拔：&lt;/strong&gt;检测已加载的 LoRA 适配器，以实现无中断热插拔和路由。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;流量治理&lt;/strong&gt;：支持金丝雀发布、令牌级速率限制和故障转移。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;一体化架构：&lt;/strong&gt;通过本机处理路由逻辑，无需单独的 Envoy 网关。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;4.成本驱动的自动缩放&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;同质扩展&lt;/strong&gt;：根据业务指标（CPU/GPU/内存/自定义）精确扩展。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;异构优化：&lt;/strong&gt;根据“性价比”优化不同加速器之间的资源分配。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;5.广泛的硬件和引擎支持&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;推理引擎&lt;/strong&gt;：通过统一的 API 抽象支持 vLLM、SGLang、Triton/TGI 等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;异构计算&lt;/strong&gt;：支持 GPU 和 NPU 资源共置，以平衡成本和服务级别目标 (SLO)。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;6.内置流量控制和公平性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;公平调度&lt;/strong&gt;：根据使用历史记录确定流量优先级，以防止低优先级用户“饥饿”。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;流量控制&lt;/strong&gt;：基于用户、模型和令牌长度的精细限制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;性能基准&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在系统提示较长的场景（例如4096个token），Kthena的“KV缓存感知+最少请求”与随机基线相比，策略带来了显着的收益：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;吞吐量：&lt;/strong&gt;增加&lt;strong&gt;~2.73x&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TTFT（首次令牌时间）：&lt;/strong&gt;减少&lt;strong&gt;~73.5%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;端到端延迟：&lt;/strong&gt;减少&lt;strong&gt;&gt;60%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;插件配置&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;吞吐量（req/s）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TTFT（s）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;E2E延迟(s)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;最少请求 + KVCacheAware&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;32.22&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9.22&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;0.57&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;最少请求 + 前缀缓存&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;23.87&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;12.47&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;0.83&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;随机&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;11.81&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;25.23&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;2.15&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：虽然短提示可以缩小差距，但 KV 缓存感知为多轮对话和模板繁重的工作负载提供了决定性的优势。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;社区和行业支持&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena自成立以来就得到了行业领导者的广泛关注和支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“开源是技术创新的命脉，也是行业标准化的首要驱动力。作为Volcano的发起者，华为云很荣幸能够与社区合作伙伴一起推出Kthena。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此次发布不仅标志着Volcano技术演进的一个重要里程碑，也凸显了华为云对云原生AI的持久承诺。通过与华为云 CCE 和 CCI 等基础设施深度集成，Kthena 充分释放了包括 Ascend 在内的多种计算能力的潜力，为我们的客户提供卓越的成本效益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过Kthena，我们期待与全球开发者合作，构建开放、繁荣的生态系统，为全球行业的智能转型奠定坚实的基础。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;——&lt;strong&gt;齐晓波&lt;/strong&gt;，华为云通用计算服务总监&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Kthena 进一步巩固了 Volcano 在智能工作负载调度方面的领先地位。通过利用 Volcano 的统一调度和资源池功能，我们的平台在单个统一框架内满足了多样化的计算需求，涵盖通用计算、人工智能训练和推理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这可以实现跨不同场景的动态资源分配，有效消除资源孤岛。展望未来，我们很高兴将 Kthena 与 Volcano 的弹性扩展和 Volcano Global 的跨集群调度相结合，将资源利用率提升到新的高度。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;——&lt;strong&gt;杨雷&lt;/strong&gt;，中国电信人工智能PaaS研发总监&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“自诞生以来，Volcano 一直与通信同步发展统一应对多样化的AI场景，建立完整的AI批处理生态系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kthena 的推出标志着一个重要的里程碑，将 Volcano 的功能扩展到大型模型推理的关键领域。它将 Volcano 多年在调度、弹性和多架构支持方面的最佳实践结晶为统一编排和智能路由的强大引擎。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过利用现有的 Kubernetes 和 Volcano 生态系统，团队可以以更低的成本实现更智能的调度决策和更高的计算效率。对于 DaoCloud 来说，Kthena 不仅解决了切实的推理挑战，还体现了云原生 AI 的未来——一个值得我们长期投资和深度参与的开放智能生态系统。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;Paco Xu&lt;/strong&gt;，DaoCloud 开源团队负责人、Kubernetes 指导委员会成员&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“在生产规模上部署和管理自托管 LLM 推理服务是一项复杂的系统工程挑战。它涵盖整个生命周期（部署、运营、弹性和恢复）以及 GPU 稳定性、调度效率和 AI 可观测性等关键要求。 Kthena 是专门为解决这些复杂性而设计的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Kthena的规划阶段，小红书云原生团队与贡献者深度接触，共同设计了各种智能流量调度策略。展望未来，我们将继续在人工智能网关方面进行合作。通过利用小红书的生产洞察，我们旨在为社区提供生产就绪的能力，包括精细的流量调度、模型 API 管理和 MCP 协议支持。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;孔谷（陈华昌）&lt;/strong&gt;，小红书云原生业务网关负责人&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“经过对Kthena的深入评估，联通云对其前瞻性的设计印象深刻。我们对其与 Volcano 的联合调度功能感到特别兴奋。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;拓扑感知和组调度等功能直接解决大规模分布式推理中固有的关键效率和可靠性挑战，为复杂的调度瓶颈提供了一种有前景的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们相信 Kthena 卓越的低延迟、高吞吐量和智能路由将为开源社区提供真正的生产就绪解决方案，使开发人员能够更高效地构建和管理云原生 AI 应用程序。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;——&lt;strong&gt;陆兆旭&lt;/strong&gt;，中国联通云智能计算中心团队负责人&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“开放和协作推动创新。在 CNCF 生态系统中，我们致力于推动基础设施迈向“AI Native”未来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过启动 Kthena 子项目，Volcano 社区应用了其在批量计算方面经过验证的专业知识，例如拓扑感知和分组调度——在线 LLM 推理。 Kthena 引入了重要的云原生调度原语，使复杂的 LLM 工作负载能够像 Kubernetes 中的一等公民一样高效运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们邀请世界各地的开发者与我们一起完善这一关键基础设施并加速 AI Native 时代的到来。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—— &lt;strong&gt;Kevin Wang&lt;/strong&gt;，Volcano 维护者、CNCF TOC 副主席&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;立即开始探索 Kthena&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这仅仅是开始。我们计划支持更高效的调度算法和更广泛的大型模型部署最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub 存储库：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/volcano-sh/kthena&#34;&gt;https://github.com/volcano-sh/kthena&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;官方网站：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://kthena.volcano.sh/&#34;&gt;https://kthena.volcano.sh/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;社区：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud-native.slack.com/archives/C011GJDQS0N&#34;&gt;加入我们的 Slack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加入我们，释放云原生 LLM 的全部潜力！&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Navigating the ingress-nginx archival: why now is the time to move to Cilium】浏览 ingress-nginx 档案：为什么现在是迁移到 Cilium 的时候了</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/01/27/navigating-the-ingress-nginx-archival-why-now-is-the-time-to-move-to-cilium/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This Member Blog was originally &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://isovalent.com/blog/post/navigating-the-ingress-nginx-archival-why-now-is-the-time-to-move-to-cilium/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;published on the Isovalent blog&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; and is republished here with permission.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re running Kubernetes, there’s a good chance you rely on ingress-nginx to route external traffic to your workloads. For years, ingress-nginx has been the go-to open source ingress controller, valued for its reliability and broad community support. Data collected from a recent &lt;a href=&#34;https://isovalent.com/blog/post/state-of-kubernetes-networking-report-2025/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;State of Kubernetes Networking Report&lt;/a&gt; shows that 50% of respondents use Ingress-nginx today. But that’s about to change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Archival of Ingress-nginx: What Does This Mean for You?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The maintainers of ingress-nginx have announced that &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2025/11/11/ingress-nginx-retirement/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;the project is being archived at the start of 2026&lt;/a&gt;. This means it will no longer receive active maintenance, security patches, or bug fixes. The news, &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2025.sched.com/event/27No6/to-ingate-and-beyond-ingress-nginx-james-strong-isovalent-cisco-marco-ebert-giant-swarm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;unveiled during KubeCon&lt;/a&gt;, marks a significant turning point for thousands of Kubernetes users and organizations that have built their ingress strategy around it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What Are Your Options?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With ingress-nginx entering retirement, platform teams face a choice: keep a critical control-plane component without upstream maintenance, or move to an actively supported alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Kubernetes community has aligned on the Gateway API as the long-term standard for traffic management. That direction shapes your two primary migration paths:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Move to another ingress controller&lt;/strong&gt; (such as Cilium Ingress, Traefik, or HAProxy Ingress).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adopt the Kubernetes Gateway API&lt;/strong&gt;, the next-generation standard for ingress and traffic management, using a controller like Cilium Gateway API.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium offers both. You can start with Cilium Ingress for a drop-in replacement and later transition to the Gateway API without switching vendors, controllers, or datapaths.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Option 1 – Quickest: Moving to Cilium Ingress&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium Ingress is a drop-in ingress controller that supports standard Kubernetes Ingress resources. It runs on Cilium’s eBPF-powered datapath, which provides excellent performance, deep visibility, and seamless integration with Cilium Network Policies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Teams Choose This Path&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Minimal changes to application manifests and CI/CD pipelines.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Continuity in using an actively maintained product and a clean path away from NGINX-specific annotations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Built-in observability and stronger security through Cilium’s tooling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What to Watch Out For&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;NGINX-only annotations and custom directives will not translate directly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you rely on complex rewrites or advanced NGINX behaviours, plan a validation phase to map those features to Cilium equivalents, or consider the Gateway API for richer routing capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How to Migrate from ingress-nginx to Cilium Ingress:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Inventory current Ingress usage&lt;/strong&gt;: Record hosts, paths, TLS settings, annotations, rewrite rules, and rate limits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;Install or verify Cilium&lt;/strong&gt;: Follow the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.cilium.io/en/stable/gettingstarted/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Cilium Getting Started guide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;Enable Cilium Ingress&lt;/strong&gt;: See &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.cilium.io/en/stable/network/servicemesh/ingress/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Cilium Ingress documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;Update manifests to target Cilium’s ingress class&lt;/strong&gt;: Switch ingressClassName to cilium and remove NGINX-specific annotations where appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: Ingress&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: my-app&#xA;  namespace: apps&#xA;spec:&#xA;  ingressClassName: cilium&#xA;  rules:&#xA;  - host: my-app.example.com&#xA;    http:&#xA;      paths:&#xA;      - path: /&#xA;        pathType: Prefix&#xA;        backend:&#xA;          service:&#xA;            name: my-app-svc&#xA;            port:&#xA;              number: 80&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. &lt;strong&gt;Validate and cut over&lt;/strong&gt;: Test TLS, path routing, and network policies in staging before switching production traffic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Option 2 – Recommended: Upgrading to Cilium’s Gateway API Implementation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While switching to Cilium Ingress is the fastest way to move off ingress-nginx, the Kubernetes ecosystem is shifting towards the Gateway API.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A subproject of &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/tree/master/sig-network&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;SIG-Network&lt;/a&gt;, Gateway API is the successor to Ingress, covering not just north-south traffic but also east-west and service-mesh entry points through a consistent, extensible model.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium’s implementation supports all Core Gateway API resources and features, in addition to most Extended (or optional) features, and enhances them with eBPF-powered performance, observability, and policy integration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why Choose Cilium’s Gateway API Implementation?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium’s Gateway API implementation isn’t just a replacement; it’s an upgrade that brings a host of benefits, from enhanced traffic control to streamlined operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced traffic management&lt;/strong&gt;: Native support for header-based routing, traffic splitting, and cross-namespace routes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unified traffic management (GAMMA)&lt;/strong&gt;: Leverage a single, consistent API (Gateway API) to manage both external (north-south) ingress traffic and internal (east-west) service mesh traffic, simplifying operations and policy enforcement.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role separation&lt;/strong&gt;: Decouple infrastructure from application routing for better security and multi-tenancy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich policy integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Combine L7 routing with Cilium Network Policies and Hubble observability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Future alignment&lt;/strong&gt;: Gateway API is the endorsed standard by Kubernetes SIG-Network and major cloud providers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What Are the Key Features Over Ingress?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Ingress has served us well, its design inherently limits advanced traffic management. The Gateway API, especially with Cilium’s implementation, unlocks a new level of control and flexibility. This table highlights some key areas where Gateway API goes beyond what traditional Ingress can offer, providing more robust and granular control over your traffic flows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Feature&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ingress-nginx&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Cilium Ingress&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Cilium Gateway API&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Basic HTTP routing&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Path-based routing&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Header-based routing&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Traffic splitting&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Cross-namespace support&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;East-West Traffic Management (GAMMA)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Role/resource separation&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Enhanced observability&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Advanced security policies&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Migrating to Cilium’s Gateway API Implementation:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ensure Cilium is installed and configured for Gateway API&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.cilium.io/en/stable/network/servicemesh/gateway-api/gateway-api/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Cilium Gateway API Docs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install Gateway API CRDs&lt;/strong&gt;: If your Kubernetes distribution does not ship with Gateway API, install CRDs as per the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway-api.sigs.k8s.io/guides/#installing-gateway-api&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Gateway API Installation Guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Define GatewayClass and Gateway resources&lt;/strong&gt;: This is a simple example, but you can find more &lt;a href=&#34;https://isovalent.com/blog/post/tutorial-getting-started-with-the-cilium-gateway-api/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;detailed examples in this tutorial blog post&lt;/a&gt; for Gateway API:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1beta1&#xA;kind: GatewayClass&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: cilium&#xA;spec:&#xA;  controllerName: io.cilium/gateway-controller&#xA;---&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1beta1&#xA;kind: Gateway&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: my-gateway&#xA;  namespace: default&#xA;spec:&#xA;  gatewayClassName: cilium&#xA;  listeners:&#xA;  - name: http&#xA;    protocol: HTTP&#xA;    port: 80&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;Translate Ingress rules into HTTPRoute objects&lt;/strong&gt;: The new model offered by Gateway API allows Application teams to define routes and backends, optionally with cross-namespace references. Removing this task from the responsibility of the platform owner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1beta1&#xA;kind: HTTPRoute&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: my-app&#xA;  namespace: apps&#xA;spec:&#xA;  parentRefs:&#xA;  - name: shared-gw&#xA;    namespace: infra&#xA;  rules:&#xA;  - matches:&#xA;    - path:&#xA;        type: PathPrefix&#xA;        value: /&#xA;      headers:&#xA;      - name: X-Canary&#xA;        value: &#34;true&#34;&#xA;    backendRefs:&#xA;    - name: my-app-svc&#xA;      port: 80&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. &lt;strong&gt;Test advanced features&lt;/strong&gt;: Try features such as header-based routing, traffic splitting, and cross-namespace scenarios as needed in staging/development, and promote into production as needed. These are capabilities not previously available with Kubernetes Ingress.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Use the Ingress-to-Gateway Migration Tool&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For teams with many Ingress resources, manual translation can be tedious.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In an effort to keep migration simple, here is a guide, &lt;a href=&#34;https://isovalent.com/blog/post/migrate-from-kubernetes-ingress-to-gateway-api/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;How to Migrate from Kubernetes Ingress to Gateway API&lt;/a&gt;, that introduces a migration utility to automate much of the conversion process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For large estates, manually translating every Ingress is slow and error-prone. The Kubernetes SIG Network utility ingress2gateway converts existing Ingress resources into Gateway API resources, either by reading from your current kubeconfig or from input files. This gives you a solid starting point that you can review and apply with Cilium Gateway API enabled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below is an example of running the tool, specifying Cilium as the destination output.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;ingress2gateway print \&#xA;  --providers=cilium&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;Notifications from CILIUM:&#xA;+--------------+----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------+-----------------------------------------------------------+&#xA;| MESSAGE TYPE |                                                  NOTIFICATION                                                  |                      CALLING OBJECT                       |&#xA;+--------------+----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------+-----------------------------------------------------------+&#xA;| INFO         | parsed &#34;ingress.cilium.io/force-https&#34; annotation of ingress and patched httproute.spec.rules[].filters fields | HTTPRoute: default/basic-ingress-https-httpbin-cilium-com |&#xA;+--------------+----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------+-----------------------------------------------------------+&#xA;&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: Gateway&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  annotations:&#xA;    gateway.networking.k8s.io/generator: ingress2gateway-0.4.0&#xA;  creationTimestamp: null&#xA;  name: cilium&#xA;  namespace: default&#xA;spec:&#xA;  gatewayClassName: cilium&#xA;  listeners:&#xA;  - hostname: httpbin.cilium.com&#xA;    name: httpbin-cilium-com-http&#xA;    port: 80&#xA;    protocol: HTTP&#xA;  - hostname: httpbin.cilium.com&#xA;    name: httpbin-cilium-com-https&#xA;    port: 443&#xA;    protocol: HTTPS&#xA;    tls:&#xA;      certificateRefs:&#xA;      - group: null&#xA;        kind: null&#xA;        name: demo-cert&#xA;status: {}&#xA;---&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: HTTPRoute&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  annotations:&#xA;    gateway.networking.k8s.io/generator: ingress2gateway-0.4.0&#xA;  creationTimestamp: null&#xA;  name: basic-ingress-https-httpbin-cilium-com&#xA;  namespace: default&#xA;spec:&#xA;  hostnames:&#xA;  - httpbin.cilium.com&#xA;  parentRefs:&#xA;  - name: cilium&#xA;  rules:&#xA;  - filters:&#xA;    - requestRedirect:&#xA;        scheme: https&#xA;        statusCode: 301&#xA;      type: RequestRedirect&#xA;    matches:&#xA;    - path:&#xA;        type: PathPrefix&#xA;        value: /&#xA;status:&#xA;  parents: []&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The tool can also run against a cluster and print equivalent Gateways and HTTPRoutes, which you can pipe to files for version control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are options to test the tool with a hands-on Cilium Ingress Controller lab, where you will learn how you can use Cilium to deploy Ingress resources and migrate to Gateway API.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Which Path Should You Take First?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most teams start with Cilium Ingress to remove the maintenance risk immediately, then move to the Gateway API as their routing and organizational needs evolve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your platform already separates infrastructure and application teams, Gateway API will feel natural from the start. If your environment is smaller or less complex, Cilium Ingress offers the fastest path to replace ingress-nginx with minimal change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A practical migration plan&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Document current behaviour&lt;/strong&gt;: Capture hosts, paths, TLS, health checks, and any NGINX annotations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Select a target&lt;/strong&gt;: Choose Cilium Ingress for quick replacement, or Gateway API for long-term flexibility.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deploy and test&lt;/strong&gt;: Install Cilium, configure DNS and certificates, and enable Hubble for visibility.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Run side-by-side&lt;/strong&gt;: Mirror traffic and validate behaviour before cutting over.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switch production&lt;/strong&gt;: Redirect DNS or load balancer targets, monitor closely, and keep a rollback plan.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iterate&lt;/strong&gt;: Once stable, identify services that can benefit from Gateway API features and migrate them next.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why Cilium Is a Sensible Default: Preparing for the Future&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The deprecation of ingress-nginx is a pivotal moment for Kubernetes networking. Rather than patching together point solutions, this is your opportunity to adopt a unified, eBPF-powered platform built for performance, visibility, and security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium gives you:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A drop-in Ingress replacement&lt;/strong&gt;: Minimal migration pain, maximum reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A best-in-class Gateway API implementation&lt;/strong&gt;: Unlock powerful new features and future-proof your stack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unified observability and security&lt;/strong&gt;: Deep insights and fine-grained controls out of the box.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Active support and rapid innovation&lt;/strong&gt;: Cilium is trusted by major cloud providers and community leaders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;此会员博客最初&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://isovalent.com/blog/post/navigating-the-ingress-nginx-archival-why-now-is-the-time-to-move-to-cilium/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;在 Isovalent 博客上发布&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;并在此处重新发布许可。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您正在运行 Kubernetes，那么您很有可能依赖 ingress-nginx 将外部流量路由到您的工作负载。多年来，ingress-nginx 一直是首选的开源入口控制器，因其可靠性和广泛的社区支持而受到重视。从最近的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://isovalent.com/blog/post/state-of-kubernetes-networking-report-2025/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 网络状况报告&lt;/a&gt;收集的数据显示，目前有 50% 的受访者使用 Ingress-nginx。但这种情况即将改变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Ingress-nginx 的存档：这对您意味着什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ingress-nginx 的维护者宣布&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2025/11/11/ingress-nginx-retirement/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;该项目将于 2026 年初存档&lt;/a&gt;。这意味着它将不再接受主动维护、安全补丁或错误修复。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2025.sched.com/event/27No6/to-ingate-and-beyond-ingress-nginx-james-strong-isovalent-cisco-marco-ebert-giant-swarm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;在 KubeCon 期间发布的消息&lt;/a&gt;，对于数千名已建立自己的 Kubernetes 用户和组织来说，标志着一个重要的转折点围绕它的入口策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;您有什么选择？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着 ingress-nginx 进入退役状态，平台团队面临一个选择：保留关键的控制平面组件而不进行上游维护，或者转向积极支持的替代方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 社区已将网关 API 作为流量管理的长期标准。该方向决定了您的两条主要迁移路径：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;移至另一个入口控制器&lt;/strong&gt;（例如 Cilium Ingress、Traefik 或 HAProxy Ingress）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;采用 Kubernetes Gateway API&lt;/strong&gt;，这是下一代入口和流量管理标准，使用 Cilium Gateway API 等控制器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium 两者兼而有之。您可以从 Cilium Ingress 开始进行直接替换，然后过渡到网关 API，而无需切换供应商、控制器或数据路径。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;选项 1 – 最快：迁移到 Cilium Ingress&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium Ingress 是一个嵌入式入口控制器，支持标准 Kubernetes Ingress 资源。它在 Cilium 的 eBPF 支持的数据路径上运行，该数据路径提供卓越的性能、深度可见性以及与 Cilium 网络策略的无缝集成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;团队为何选择这条道路&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&lt;li&gt;对应用清单和 CI/CD 管道进行最少的更改。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;持续使用积极维护的产品，并摆脱 NGINX 特定注释的干净路径。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过 Cilium 工具实现内置可观察性和更强的安全性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;需要注意什么&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;仅限 NGINX 的注释和自定义指令不会直接翻译。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果您依赖复杂的重写或高级 NGINX 行为，请计划一个验证阶段以将这些功能映射到 Cilium 等效项，或考虑使用 Gateway API 来获得更丰富的路由功能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如何从 ingress-nginx 迁移到 Cilium Ingress：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;清点当前 Ingress 使用情况&lt;/strong&gt;：记录主机、路径、TLS 设置、注释、重写规则和速率限制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;安装或验证 Cilium&lt;/strong&gt;：遵循&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.cilium.io/en/stable/gettingstarted/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Cilium 入门指南&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;启用 Cilium Ingress&lt;/strong&gt;：请参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.cilium.io/en/stable/network/servicemesh/ingress/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Cilium Ingress 文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;更新清单以定位 Cilium 的入口类&lt;/strong&gt;：将 ingressClassName 切换为 cilium 并在适当的情况下删除 NGINX 特定的注释。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类: 入口&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：我的应用程序&#xA;  命名空间：应用程序&#xA;规格：&#xA;  ingressClassName：纤毛&#xA;  规则：&#xA;  - 主机：my-app.example.com&#xA;    http：&#xA;      路径：&#xA;      - 路径：/&#xA;        路径类型：前缀&#xA;        后端：&#xA;          服务：&#xA;            名称：我的应用程序 svc&#xA;            港口：&#xA;              数量：80&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. &lt;strong&gt;验证和切换&lt;/strong&gt;：在切换生产流量之前在暂存阶段测试 TLS、路径路由和网络策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;选项 2 – 推荐：升级到 Cilium 的网关 API 实现&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然切换到 Cilium Ingress 是摆脱 ingress-nginx 的最快方法，但 Kubernetes 生态系统正在转向 Gateway API。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gateway API 是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/tree/master/sig-network&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;SIG-Network&lt;/a&gt; 的子项目，是 Ingress 的后继者，通过一致、可扩展的模型不仅覆盖南北流量，还覆盖东西流量和服务网格入口点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了大多数扩展（或可选）功能之外，Cilium 的实现还支持所有核心网关 API 资源和功能，并通过 eBPF 支持的性能、可观察性和策略集成来增强它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;为什么选择 Cilium 的网关 API 实现？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium 的 Gateway API 实现不仅仅是替代品；这是一次升级，带来了很多 b从加强交通控制到简化运营等优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高级流量管理&lt;/strong&gt;：对基于标头的路由、流量分割和跨命名空间路由的本机支持。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;统一流量管理 (GAMMA)&lt;/strong&gt;：利用单一一致的 API（网关 API）来管理外部（南北）入口流量和内部（东西）服务网格流量，从而简化操作和策略实施。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;角色分离&lt;/strong&gt;：将基础架构与应用路由分离，以实现更好的安全性和多租户。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;丰富的策略集成&lt;/strong&gt;：将 L7 路由与 Cilium 网络策略和 Hubble 可观测性相结合。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;未来一致性&lt;/strong&gt;：网关 API 是 Kubernetes SIG-Network 和主要云提供商认可的标准。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Ingress 的主要功能是什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 Ingress 为我们提供了很好的服务，但其设计本质上限制了高级流量管理。 Gateway API，尤其是 Cilium 的实现，将控制和灵活性提升到了一个新的水平。该表重点介绍了 Gateway API 超越传统 Ingress 所能提供的一些关键领域，为您的流量提供更强大、更精细的控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-table&#34;&gt;&lt;table class=&#34;has-fixed-layout&#34;&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;功能&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Ingress-nginx&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Cilium Ingress&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Cilium Gateway API&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;基本 HTTP路由&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;基于路径的路由&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;基于标头的路由路由&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;流量分流&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;跨命名空间支持&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;东西向流量管理（GAMMA）&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;角色/资源分离&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;增强可观察性&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;高级安全性政策&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;❌&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;✔️&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;迁移到 Cilium 的网关 API 实现：&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;确保已安装并配置 Cilium 网关 API&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.cilium.io/en/stable/network/servicemesh/gateway-api/gateway-api/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Cilium Gateway API 文档&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安装 Gateway API CRD&lt;/strong&gt;：如果您的 Kubernetes 发行版未附带 Gateway API，请按照&lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway-api.sigs.k8s.io/guides/#installing-gateway-api&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Gateway API 安装指南&lt;/a&gt;安装 CRD。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;定义 GatewayClass 和 Gateway资源&lt;/strong&gt;：这是一个简单的示例，但您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;https://isovalent.com/blog/post/tutorial-getting-started-with-the-cilium-gateway-api/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;本教程博客文章&lt;/a&gt;中找到有关 Gateway API 的更多详细示例：&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1beta1&#xA;种类：网关类&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称： 纤毛&#xA;规格：&#xA;  控制器名称：io.cilium/gateway-controller&#xA;---&#xA;api版本：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1beta1&#xA;种类: 网关&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：我的网关&#xA;  命名空间：默认&#xA;规格：&#xA;  gatewayClassName：cilium&#xA;  听众：&#xA;  - 名称：http&#xA;    协议：HTTP&#xA;    端口：80&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;将入口规则转换为 HTTPRoute 对象&lt;/strong&gt;：网关 API 提供的新模型允许应用程序团队定义路由和后端，并可选择跨命名空间引用。将此任务从平台所有者的责任中删除。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1beta1&#xA;种类：HTTP 路由&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：我的应用程序&#xA;  命名空间：应用程序&#xA;规格：&#xA;  家长参考：&#xA;  -名称：共享GW&#xA;    命名空间：基础设施&#xA;  规则：&#xA;  - 匹配：&#xA;    - 路径：&#xA;        类型：路径前缀&#xA;        值：/&#xA;      标题：&#xA;      - 名称：X-金丝雀&#xA;        值：“真”&#xA;    后端参考：&#xA;    - 名称：我的应用程序 svc&#xA;      端口：80&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. &lt;strong&gt;测试高级功能&lt;/strong&gt;：根据暂存/开发中的需要尝试基于标头的路由、流量分割和跨命名空间场景等功能，并根据需要升级到生产环境。这些是 Kubernetes Ingress 以前不具备的功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;使用入口到网关迁移工具&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于拥有大量 Ingress 资源的团队来说，手动翻译可能会很乏味。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了使迁移保持简单，这里有一个指南，&lt;a href=&#34;https://isovalent.com/blog/post/migrate-from-kubernetes-ingress-to-gateway-api/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;如何从 Kubernetes Ingress 迁移到 Gateway API&lt;/a&gt;，其中引入了一个迁移实用程序来自动执行大部分转换过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于大型庄园，手动翻译每个 Ingress 的速度很慢且容易出错。 Kubernetes SIG 网络实用程序 ingress2gateway 通过从当前 kubeconfig 或输入文件中读取，将现有 Ingress 资源转换为网关 API 资源。这为您提供了一个坚实的起点，您可以在启用 Cilium Gateway API 的情况下查看和应用该起点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下面是运行该工具的示例，指定 Cilium 作为目标输出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;ingress2gateway 打印 \&#xA;  --providers=纤毛&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;来自 CILIUM 的通知：&#xA;+----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------+--------------------------------------------------------------------------------+&#xA;|消息类型 |通知 |                      调用对象|&#xA;+----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------+--------------------------------------------------------------------------------+&#xA;|信息|解析入口的“ingress.cilium.io/force-https”注释并修补 httproute.spec.rules[].filters 字段 | HTTPRoute：默认/basic-ingress-https-httpbin-cilium-com |&#xA;+----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------+--------------------------------------------------------------------------------+&#xA;&#xA;api版本：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类: 网关&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  注释：&#xA;    gateway.networking.k8s.io/generator：ingress2gateway-0.4.0&#xA;  创建时间戳：空&#xA;  名称： 纤毛&#xA;  命名空间：默认&#xA;规格：&#xA;  gatewayClassName：cilium&#xA;  听众：&#xA;  - 主机名：httpbin.cilium.com&#xA;    名称：httpbin-cilium-com-http&#xA;    端口：80&#xA;    协议：HTTP&#xA;  - 主机名：httpbin.cilium.com&#xA;    名称：httpbin-cilium-com-https&#xA;    端口：443&#xA;    协议：HTTPS&#xA;    :&#xA;      证书参考：&#xA;      - 组：空&#xA;        种类：空&#xA;        名称：演示证书&#xA;状态：{}&#xA;---&#xA;api版本：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类：HTTP 路由&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  注释：&#xA;    gateway.networking.k8s.io/generator：ingress2gateway-0.4.0&#xA;  创建时间戳：空&#xA;  名称： basic-ingress-https-httpbin-cilium-com&#xA;  命名空间：默认&#xA;规格：&#xA;  主机名：&#xA;  - httpbin.cilium.com&#xA;  家长参考：&#xA;  - 名称：纤毛&#xA;  规则：&#xA;  - 过滤器：&#xA;    - 请求重定向：&#xA;        方案：https&#xA;        状态代码：301&#xA;      类型：请求重定向&#xA;    匹配：&#xA;    - 路径：&#xA;        类型：路径前缀&#xA;        值：/&#xA;状态：&#xA;  父母：[]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该工具还可以针对集群运行并打印等效的网关和 HTTPRoutes，您可以将其通过管道传输到文件以进行版本控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可以选择通过 Cilium Ingress Controller 实验室来测试该工具，您将在实验室中了解如何使用 Cilium 部署 Ingress 资源并迁移到 Gateway API。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;你应该先走哪条路？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大多数团队从 Cilium Ingress 开始，以立即消除维护风险，然后随着路由和组织需求的发展而转向网关 API。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的平台已经将基础架构和应用程序团队分开，那么网关 API 从一开始就会感觉很自然。如果您的环境较小或不太复杂，Cilium Ingress 提供了以最小的更改替换 ingress-nginx 的最快路径。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;实用的迁移计划&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;记录当前行为&lt;/strong&gt;：捕获主机、路径、TLS、运行状况检查和任何 NGINX 注释。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;选择目标&lt;/strong&gt;：选择 Cilium Ingress 进行快速替换，或选择 Gateway API 实现长期灵活性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;部署和测试&lt;/strong&gt;：安装 Cilium、配置 DNS 和证书，并启用 Hubble 以获得可见性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;并行运行&lt;/strong&gt;：在切换之前镜像流量并验证行为。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;切换生产&lt;/strong&gt;：重定向 DNS 或负载均衡器目标、密切监控并制定回滚计划。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;迭代&lt;/strong&gt;：稳定后，确定可以从 Gateway API 功能中受益的服务，然后进行迁移。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;为什么 Cilium 是明智的默认选择：为未来做好准备&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ingress-nginx 的弃用是 Kubernetes 网络的关键时刻。您无需将单点解决方案拼凑在一起，而是可以采用由 eBPF 驱动的统一平台，以提高性能、可见性和安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cilium 为您提供：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;直接替代 Ingress&lt;/strong&gt;：最小的迁移痛苦，最大的可靠性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;一流的网关 API 实现&lt;/strong&gt;：解锁强大的新功能并确保您的堆栈面向未来。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;统一的可观察性和安全性&lt;/strong&gt;：开箱即用的深入洞察和细粒度控制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;积极支持和快速创新&lt;/strong&gt;：Cilium 受到主要云提供商和社区领导者的信任。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【k0s in 2025: A year of community growth, governance, and Kubernetes innovation】2025 年的 k0s：社区发展、治理和 Kubernetes 创新的一年</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/01/26/k0s-in-2025-a-year-of-community-growth-governance-and-kubernetes-innovation/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we begin 2026, it’s worth reflecting on the remarkable progress we made with &lt;a href=&#34;https://k0sproject.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; as a project and as a community during 2025. Last year brought exciting advancements, adoption, and stronger community engagement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0sproject/k0s&#34;&gt;k0s&lt;/a&gt; is an open-source, single-binary Kubernetes distribution designed to be lightweight, simple to deploy, and highly flexible. The project aims to reduce the complexity of setting up and managing Kubernetes clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This 2025 review highlights the key milestones for k0s last year and paints a picture of the momentum carrying us into 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Major features and releases&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last year, the k0s project continued to deliver enhancements focused on &lt;strong&gt;stability, extensibility, and multi‑environment operations&lt;/strong&gt;..&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Key improvements included:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stable releases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The k0s project had a total of 39 stable releases done in total. Kubernetes 1.34 is supported now; whereas Kubernetes 1.31 &amp;amp; 1.30 are already end of life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operational and environmental flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Enhanced features tailored for edge use cases, improving resource efficiency and resilience in constrained environments. Usability improvements in installation, upgrades, and automation to lower the barrier for adoption while enabling more flexible deployment profiles for different workloads.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security and governance focus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The k0s community has invested in security hardening, policy interoperability, and observability integrations to support end-users.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;k0s recent and upcoming highlights&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dynamic control plane load balancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;A built-in control plane load balancer now simplifies HA setups. It supports both IPVS and user-space backends for flexible environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;–kubelet-root-dir&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; flag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;This lets users override default kubelet data paths (/var/lib/kubelet), improving compatibility with non-standard or constrained environments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nftables support (GA in v1.33)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Modern firewall support with nftables is now stable, replacing iptables as default on most modern Linux distros.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Declarative Etcd member management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;It enables GitOps-style configuration of etcd cluster membership — safer scaling and recovery workflows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OCI registry-based extensions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;This supports deploying Helm charts and other extensions from OCI-compliant registries, standardizing distribution and updates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows node support (Alpha in v1.34)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Early support for Windows workers is now available, with basic functionality and room for community contribution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RISC-V architecture support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;k0s can be built for RISC-V platforms. While binaries aren’t officially released yet, the groundwork is there, pending infra testing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These enhancements have helped k0s deliver &lt;strong&gt;production‑ready performance across diverse infrastructures&lt;/strong&gt; while preserving the simplicity that defines the project.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0s joining the CNCF sandbox&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; In early 2025, k0s achieved a major milestone by being accepted into the CNCF Sandbox program.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Being part of this program positions k0s to accelerate its development through broader community engagement and feedback, enabling deeper interoperability and innovation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Joining the CNCF Sandbox underscores the project’s commitment to open governance and community‑driven innovation, and opens doors for closer collaboration with other CNCF initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0s CNCF incubation application&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k0s has formally submitted its &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/issues/1962&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF incubation application&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, marking a key step toward broader community governance and ecosystem alignment within the CNCF. This move reflects the project’s maturity, growing adoption, and commitment to open collaboration, inviting increased contributions and tighter integrations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community growth and adoption&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the heart of any open source project is its community. In 2025, the k0s community saw remarkable growth:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increased adoption and contributor expansion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organizations across industries began using k0s as a foundational layer for Kubernetes operations from startups to large enterprises.Contributions in code, documentation, tooling, and testing accelerated, resulting in a broader set of maintainers and contributors participating in shaping the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1600&#34; height=&#34;889&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14.png&#34; alt=&#34;Screenshot of the K0s organization overview featuring line graphs of the number of active participants, active repositories, pull requests, reviews, issues, and new participants. &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155761&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14.png 1600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-300x167.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-1024x569.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-768x427.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-900x500.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-360x200.png 360w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-720x400.png 720w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1464&#34; height=&#34;961&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15.png&#34; alt=&#34;A red line graph showing the number of GitHub stars for k0s by year. The line shows a steep increase in the number of GitHub stars from 2023 to 2025. &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155762&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15.png 1464w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-300x197.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-1024x672.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-768x504.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-900x591.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-305x200.png 305w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-609x400.png 609w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1464px) 100vw, 1464px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steady community calls&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The k0s project has maintained regular&lt;a href=&#34;https://zoom-lfx.platform.linuxfoundation.org/meetings/k0s?view=month&#34;&gt; community calls&lt;/a&gt;, offering a transparent space for discussion, updates, and roadmap alignment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growing community activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Contributor engagement continues to rise. More developers are joining discussions, submitting PRs, reporting issues, and collaborating on features.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community-driven public roadmap&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The k0s roadmap is &lt;strong&gt;shaped by community input&lt;/strong&gt;. Feature requests, issue prioritization, and planning are increasingly community-led, ensuring that development stays aligned with real user needs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Events and community activities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Community engagement was a highlight this year:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;k0s featured prominently in cloud‑native events, meetups, and community discussions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Local meetups, training sessions, and virtual events helped lower the barrier to entry and brought practitioners together around shared challenges.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After becoming a Sandbox project, k0s joined KubeCon India and KubeCon North America with a project lightning talk, contribfest session and a k0s booth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;960&#34; height=&#34;1280&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16.png&#34; alt=&#34;A k0s event setting, showing a large gathering of technologists involved in k0s. &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155763&#34; style=&#34;width:505px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16.png 960w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-225x300.png 225w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-768x1024.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-900x1200.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-150x200.png 150w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-300x400.png 300w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;960&#34; height=&#34;1280&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17.png&#34; alt=&#34;A photo of the k0s booth in the Project Pavillion at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Atlanta&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155764&#34; style=&#34;width:508px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17.png 960w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-225x300.png 225w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-768x1024.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-900x1200.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-150x200.png 150w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-300x400.png 300w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Looking ahead: What’s on the horizon for 2026&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year is set to bring &lt;strong&gt;major innovations&lt;/strong&gt; in both stability and flexibility as the k0s project continues to evolve as a modern Kubernetes distribution. Here’s what’s on the horizon:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0s v1.35 release (Target: Feb 2026)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The upcoming v1.35 release is focused on improving the control plane experience, operational observability, and base compatibility.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upstream alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k0s remains tightly aligned with upstream Kubernetes releases. As Kubernetes introduces new APIs, container runtimes, and network stack changes, k0s ensures timely support and testing for seamless adoption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Deeper community collaboration&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team plans to work more closely with the community during 2026&amp;nbsp; particularly around features, release planning, testing, and supporting new environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for containerd 2.x&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With containerd 2.x now on the horizon, k0s will ensure compatibility and smooth migration paths. This is vital for long-term runtime stability and ecosystem interoperability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Enhanced operational capabilities&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Several key operational improvements are in development:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Etcd management enhancements&lt;/strong&gt;: More robust lifecycle controls and better recovery workflows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Graceful control plane node termination&lt;/strong&gt;: Reducing disruption during planned node shutdowns or scaling events.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Transparent roadmap&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/orgs/k0sproject/projects/4/views/2&#34;&gt;public roadmap&lt;/a&gt; on GitHub helps users and contributors stay aligned with priorities, milestones, and open discussions. It’s a key part of making k0s more community-driven and predictable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Gratitude and invitation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are excited about what’s ahead and invite you to continue contributing, collaborating, and building with k0s in 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s to an even stronger, more vibrant ecosystem in the year ahead.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;k0s community&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The k0s community discussions will commence on the Kubernetes Slack Workspace. Join the &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.slack.com/archives/C0809EA06QZ&#34;&gt;#k0s-users&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.slack.com/archives/C07VAPJUECS&#34;&gt;#k0s-dev&lt;/a&gt; channels to ask your questions, share your user stories and discuss your contributions with the maintainers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get an invite please fill out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/sKwq26McSusRDyoE9&#34;&gt;invitation form&lt;/a&gt;. You can also review the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1K7kc4nARFsM60RpzWF7xREF9FHySDuWSu9_6dstkLlg/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;meeting notes&lt;/a&gt; for the community office hours.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 2026 年伊始，值得反思的是 2025 年我们在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://k0sproject.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 作为一个项目和一个社区所取得的显着进展。去年带来了令人兴奋的进步、采用和更强大的社区参与。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/k0sproject/k0s&#34;&gt;k0s&lt;/a&gt; 是一个开源、单二进制 Kubernetes 发行版，旨在轻量级、易于部署且高度灵活。该项目旨在降低设置和管理 Kubernetes 集群的复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这份 2025 年回顾强调了去年 k0s 的关键里程碑，并描绘了我们进入 2026 年的势头。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;主要功能和版本&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;去年，k0s 项目继续提供专注于&lt;strong&gt;稳定性、可扩展性和多环境操作&lt;/strong&gt;的增强功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主要改进包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;稳定版本&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k0s 项目总共完成了 39 个稳定版本。现在支持 Kubernetes 1.34；而 Kubernetes 1.31 和 1.30 已经停产。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;操作和环境灵活性&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;针对边缘用例量身定制的增强功能，提高受限环境中的资源效率和恢复能力。安装、升级和自动化方面的可用性改进，可降低采用障碍，同时为不同的工作负载提供更灵活的部署配置文件。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;关注安全和治理&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;k0s 社区在安全强化、策略互操作性和可观察性集成方面进行了投资，以支持最终用户。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;k0 最近和即将推出的亮点&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;动态控制平面负载均衡器&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;内置控制平面负载均衡器现在简化了 HA 设置。它支持 IPVS 和用户空间后端，以实现灵活的环境。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;–kubelet-root-dir&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; 标志&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;这允许用户覆盖默认 kubelet 数据路径 (/var/lib/kubelet)，从而提高与非标准或受限环境的兼容性。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nftables 支持（v1.33 中的 GA）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;nftables 的现代防火墙支持现已稳定，取代 iptables 作为大多数现代 Linux 发行版上的默认设置。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;声明式 Etcd 成员管理&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;它支持 GitOps 风格的 etcd 集群成员身份配置 - 更安全的扩展和恢复工作流程。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;基于 OCI 注册表的扩展&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;这支持从符合 OCI 的注册表部署 Helm 图表和其他扩展，从而标准化分发化和更新。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows 节点支持（v1.34 中的 Alpha）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;现已提供对 Windows 工作人员的早期支持，具有基本功能和社区贡献空间。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RISC-V 架构支持&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;可以为 RISC-V 平台构建 k0s。虽然二进制文件尚未正式发布，但基础工作已经存在，有待基础测试。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些增强功能帮助 k0s 在不同的基础设施中提供&lt;strong&gt;生产就绪的性能&lt;/strong&gt;，同时保留了定义项目的简单性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0s 加入 CNCF 沙箱&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2025 年初，k0s 被纳入 CNCF 沙箱计划，实现了一个重要的里程碑。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为该计划的一部分，k0s 能够通过更广泛的社区参与和反馈来加速其发展，从而实现更深入的互操作性和创新。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;加入 CNCF 沙盒强调了该项目对开放治理和社区驱动创新的承诺，并为与其他 CNCF 计划更密切的合作打开了大门。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0s CNCF孵化应用&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k0s 已正式提交&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/issues/1962&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF 孵化申请&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，标志着 CNCF 内朝着更广泛的社区治理和生态系统协调迈出了关键一步。这一举措反映了该项目的成熟度、日益增长的采用率以及对开放协作、邀请更多贡献和更紧密集成的承诺。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;社区发展和采用&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;任何开源项目的核心都是其社区。 2025 年，k0s 社区取得了显着的增长：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;采用率提高和贡献者扩大&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;各行业的组织开始使用 k0s 作为从初创公司到大型企业的 Kubernetes 运营的基础层。代码、文档、工具和测试方面的贡献加速，导致更多的维护者和贡献者参与到项目的制定中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1600&#34; height=&#34;889&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14.png&#34; alt=&#34;K0s 组织概述的屏幕截图，其中包含活跃参与者、活跃存储库、拉取请求、评论、问题和新参与者数量的折线图。 “class =“wp-image-155761”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14.png 1600w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-300x167.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-1024x569.png 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-768x427.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-900x500.png 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-360x200.png 360w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-14-720x400.png 720w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1600像素）100vw，1600像素“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1464&#34; height=&#34;961&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15.png&#34; alt=&#34;红线图，显示每年 k0 的 GitHub 星数。该线显示从 2023 年到 2025 年 GitHub 星数急剧增加。 &#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155762&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15.png 1464w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-300x197.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-1024x672.png 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-768x504.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-900x591.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-305x200.png 305w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-15-609x400.png 609w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1464px）100vw， 1464px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;稳定的社区电话会议&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;k0s 项目保持定期&lt;a href=&#34;https://zoom-lfx.platform.linuxfoundation.org/meetings/k0s?view=month&#34;&gt;社区电话会议&lt;/a&gt;，为讨论、更新和路线图调整提供透明的空间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;社区活动不断增长&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;贡献者参与度持续上升。更多的开发人员正在加入讨论、提交 PR、报告问题以及就功能进行协作。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;社区驱动的公共路线图&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;k0s 路线图&lt;strong&gt;由社区意见制定&lt;/strong&gt;。功能请求、问题优先级和规划越来越由社区主导，确保开发与实际用户需求保持一致。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;活动和社区活动&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;社区参与是今年的一大亮点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;k0s 在云原生活动、聚会和社区讨论中占据显着地位。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;本地聚会、培训课程和虚拟活动有助于降低准入门槛，让从业者聚集在一起应对共同的挑战。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成为沙盒项目后，k0s 加入了 KubeCon India 和 KubeCon North America，举办了项目闪电演讲、contribufest 会议和 k0s 展位。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;960&#34;height=&#34;1280&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16.png&#34;alt=&#34;A k0s 事件设置，s一大群技术人员如何参与 k0s。 “ class =“wp-image-155763” style =“ width：505px;height：auto” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16.png 960w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-225x300.png 225w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-768x1024.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-900x1200.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-150x200.png 150w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-16-300x400.png 300w”尺寸=“自动，（最大宽度：960px）100vw， 960px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;960&#34; height=&#34;1280&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17.png&#34; alt=&#34;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 亚特兰大项目馆 k0s 展位的照片&#34;类=“wp-image-155764”样式=“宽度：508px;高度：自动”srcset=“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17.png 960w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-225x300.png 225w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-768x1024.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-900x1200.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-150x200.png 150w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17-300x400.png 300w”尺寸=“自动，（最大宽度：960px）100vw， 960px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;展望未来：2026 年将会发生什么&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着 k0s 项目作为现代 Kubernetes 发行版的不断发展，今年将在稳定性和灵活性方面带来&lt;strong&gt;重大创新&lt;/strong&gt;。以下是即将发生的事情：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;k0s v1.35 版本（目标：2026 年 2 月）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即将发布的 v1.35 版本专注于改进控制平面体验、操作可观察性和基础兼容性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;上游对齐&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k0s 与上游 Kubernetes 版本保持紧密一致。随着 Kubernetes 引入新的 API、容器运行时和网络堆栈更改，k0s 可确保及时支持和测试以实现无缝采用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;更深入的社区协作&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该团队计划在 2026 年期间与社区进行更密切的合作，特别是在功能、发布规划、测试和支持新环境方面。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;支持containerd 2.x&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着containerd 2.x的出现，k0s将确保兼容性和平滑的迁移路径。这对于长期运行时稳定性和生态系统互操作性至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;增强的运营能力&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;几项关键的运营改进正在开发中：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Etcd 管理增强功能&lt;/strong&gt;：更强大的生命周期控制和更好的恢复工作流程。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;平稳控制平面节点终止&lt;/strong&gt;：减少计划节点关闭或扩展事件期间的中断。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;透明路线图&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitHub 上的&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/orgs/k0sproject/projects/4/views/2&#34;&gt;公共路线图&lt;/a&gt;可帮助用户和贡献者与优先事项、里程碑和公开讨论保持一致。这是让 k0s 更加社区驱动和可预测的关键部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;感谢和邀请&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们对未来的发展感到兴奋，并邀请您在 2026 年继续为 k0s 做出贡献、合作和建设。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为未来一年更加强大、更加充满活力的生态系统干杯。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;k0s 社区&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k0s 社区讨论将在 Kubernetes Slack Workspace 上开始。加入 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.slack.com/archives/C0809EA06QZ&#34;&gt;#k0s-users&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.slack.com/archives/C07VAPJUECS&#34;&gt;#k0s-dev&lt;/a&gt; 频道，提出您的问题、分享您的用户故事并与维护人员讨论您的贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要获得邀请，请填写&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/sKwq26McSusRDyoE9&#34;&gt;邀请表&lt;/a&gt;。您还可以查看社区办公时间的&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1K7kc4nARFsM60RpzWF7xREF9FHySDuWSu9_6dstkLlg/edit?usp=sharing&#34;&gt;会议记录&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The autonomous enterprise and the four pillars of platform control: 2026 forecast】自主企业和平台控制的四大支柱：2026 年预测</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/01/23/the-autonomous-enterprise-and-the-four-pillars-of-platform-control-2026-forecast/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The promise of DevOps and Platform Engineering is to balance developer velocity with enterprise governance. In 2026, AI Agents move from being simple assistance tools to the core mechanisms that automate this balance. Recent publications, such as the CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/cncf_report_stateofcloud_111025a.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;2025 Technology Radar&lt;/a&gt; report, highlight growing experimentation with agentic AI standards (for example, MCP). As we begin 2026, it’s time to forecast how the enterprise shift to autonomy will be defined by four distinct, AI-driven control mechanisms: golden paths, guardrails, safety nets, and manual review workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Governing the autonomous enterprise&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Based on conversations with platform engineering teams at large enterprises and broader industry signals, some fundamental priorities for 2026 are emerging: speed, security, and cost optimization should be achieved autonomously.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This reflects a powerful consensus across the industry, centered on the following key shifts:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A potential 2026 paradigm shift:&lt;/strong&gt; AI’s role may evolve from a copilot to an agent with delegated authority over mission-critical tasks (provisioning, security, incident response).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The necessity of control:&lt;/strong&gt; This new level of automation demands a sophisticated governance framework. A generic “guardrail” approach is insufficient; success depends on a clear taxonomy of controls.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The four pillars of control:&lt;/strong&gt; These pillars—&lt;strong&gt;golden paths, guardrails, safety nets, and manual review workflows&lt;/strong&gt;— could form the adaptive, secure foundation for high-velocity infrastructure management in large enterprises.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Golden paths: The self-tuning, autonomous road&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Golden paths&lt;/strong&gt; are the curated, pre-approved blueprints that make the secure, compliant choice the &lt;em&gt;easiest&lt;/em&gt; choice for developers (e.g., standardized IaC modules, self-service portals). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 Prediction: Increasing autonomy for generation and optimization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intent-to-infrastructure:&lt;/strong&gt; AI Agents will move beyond simple code generation. Developers input high-level requirements (e.g. “I need a secure, scalable service for my application in AWS US-East”), and the AI Agent fully composes, validates, and provisions the compliant infrastructure according to the pre-defined golden path.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The “janitor” agent:&lt;/strong&gt; Provisioning is only half the battle. In 2026, golden paths will include embedded “time-to-live” policies. An autonomous agent will proactively identify and decommission “zombie infrastructure” (orphaned resources, idle dev environments), solving the massive problem of cloud waste and reducing the security attack surface.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous path improvement:&lt;/strong&gt; Agents will continuously monitor the performance, cost, and adoption of these golden paths. They will recommend and, in many cases, autonomously implement improvements—such as swapping out a resource type or optimizing a default configuration—to meet defined SLOs (Service Level Objectives) and FinOps targets.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The platform engineer’s role:&lt;/strong&gt; Shifting to the curation and quality control of the AI-powered golden path, ensuring the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; practice is always the &lt;em&gt;default&lt;/em&gt; practice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Guardrails: Autonomous governance and zero-drift assurance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Guardrails&lt;/strong&gt; are the hard, non-negotiable stops—the “crash barriers”—that prevent actions or configurations that would compromise the security or stability of the platform (e.g., blocking public storage buckets, enforcing binary authorization).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 Prediction: From reactive scanners to proactive AI enforcers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI-Driven Policy-as-Code:&lt;/strong&gt; Agents will translate high-level compliance requirements (e.g., “PCI-DSS compliance”) into executable, deterministic Guardrails and deploy them across the infrastructure lifecycle (CI/CD, runtime).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autonomous vulnerability response:&lt;/strong&gt; Upon the announcement of a new critical vulnerability (CVE) or security patch, AI-driven systems may increasingly automate the creation and deployment of runtime guardrails, under predefined policies and human-approved constraints (e.g., network policies, temporary access restrictions, or container image blocks) across affected environments. This provides an immediate, defensive shield, dramatically reducing the enterprise’s time-to-protection from days to minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The “auditor” agent:&lt;/strong&gt; Compliance evidence collection will be fully automated. Since the AI Agent enforces the guardrails, it will also generate real-time, immutable audit reports for standards like PCI-DSS or SOC2, substantially reducing the manual effort typically associated with audit preparation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autonomous drift remediation:&lt;/strong&gt; This becomes a standard feature. AI Agents will continuously scan the live environment against the desired state defined by the golden path and its embedded guardrails. Upon detecting unauthorized changes (drift), the agent will autonomously revert or fix the misconfiguration instantly, moving closer to near-zero configuration drift for compliance-sensitive environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on prevention:&lt;/strong&gt; The goal is for AI to ensure that developers rarely, if ever, encounter a guardrail by guiding them through the golden path.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Safety nets: Predictive reliability and auto-recovery&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety nets&lt;/strong&gt; are reactive controls that detect failures or threats and facilitate swift recovery (e.g., monitoring, automated rollbacks, backup procedures).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 Prediction: Full autonomy in detection and remediation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Predictive SRE:&lt;/strong&gt; AI Agents, trained on vast quantities of observability data, will predict outages and performance degradation &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; they impact users. They will use sophisticated pattern recognition to trigger proactive scaling or maintenance to avert an incident entirely.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autonomous incident response:&lt;/strong&gt; For incidents that do occur, the agent will move beyond suggestion (AIOps 1.0) to full auto-remediation (AIOps 2.0).&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The agent identifies the root cause, correlates it with the appropriate runbook action, and executes the fix (e.g., traffic shifting, restarting a service, or executing a rollback) autonomously, with the potential to significantly reduce Mean Time to Resolution (MTTR) in many scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The SRE’s evolved role:&lt;/strong&gt; Defining the rules, tolerances, and error budgets for the Safety Net agents, and focusing on complex, novel failure modes that require human creativity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With cost optimization cited as the top priority for 2025 and chaos engineering still at &amp;lt;10% adoption, the market is primed for the autonomous ‘Safety Nets’ and ‘FinOps Agents’ we predict.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Manual review workflows: The strategic human-in-the-loop&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manual review workflows&lt;/strong&gt; are processes requiring human judgment, oversight, and intervention for high-risk, complex, or financial decisions (e.g., architectural reviews, large budget approvals, security post-mortems).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 Prediction: AI-optimized human judgment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Risk scored reviews:&lt;/strong&gt; AI Agents will automate the &lt;em&gt;prep work&lt;/em&gt; for manual reviews. Before a human architect reviews a deployment, the agent will generate a comprehensive risk report, checking compliance, cost forecast, and architectural fitness against the enterprise framework, presenting the reviewer with a simple risk score and a go/no-go Recommendation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic friction:&lt;/strong&gt; This mechanism acts as the necessary point of strategic friction. While golden paths, guardrails, and safety nets achieve near-full autonomy, the manual review remains a crucial step for accountability and holistic risk assessment that only human judgment can provide.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The future of approval:&lt;/strong&gt; Manual review shifts from a bureaucratic bottleneck to a brief, highly informed, high-impact decision-making process.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Conclusion: Architecting for the agentic future&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many of these capabilities are being explored incrementally across the cloud native ecosystem through open source projects, standards discussions, and platform engineering communities, rather than as a single unified solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The new mandate:&lt;/strong&gt; Enterprise IT leaders should stop viewing AI as a feature and start architecting for an &lt;strong&gt;agentic infrastructure platform&lt;/strong&gt; that effectively manages these four distinct control mechanisms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The outcome:&lt;/strong&gt; By granting full autonomy to the steering (golden paths), prevention (guardrails), and recovery (safety nets), and strategically implementing AI-optimized manual review, organizations could achieve unprecedented speed, resilience, and compliance in 2026.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recent data from the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/cncf_report_stateofcloud_111025a.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;CNCF’s State of Cloud Native Development report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Nov 2025) aligns with broader industry signals pointing toward increased interest in autonomous and AI-assisted platforms&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;: with 15.6 million cloud-native developers and ‘Agentic AI’ platforms like MCP already entering the adoption phase, the industry is moving exactly where we predicted—toward a fully autonomous, platform-managed future.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;DevOps 和平台工程的承诺是平衡开发人员速度与企业治理。到 2026 年，人工智能代理将从简单的辅助工具转变为自动化实现这种平衡的核心机制。最近的出版物，例如 CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/cncf_report_stateofcloud_111025a.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;2025 技术雷达&lt;/a&gt;报告，强调了对代理 AI 标准（例如 MCP）不断进行的实验。 2026 年伊始，是时候预测企业将如何通过四种不同的人工智能驱动的控制机制来定义向自治的转变：黄金路径、护栏、安全网和手动审核工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;治理自主企业&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据与大型企业平台工程团队的对话以及更广泛的行业信号，2026 年的一些基本优先事项正在浮现：速度、安全性和成本优化应自主实现。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这反映了整个行业的强大共识，主要集中在以下关键转变：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 年潜在的范式转变：&lt;/strong&gt;人工智能的角色可能会从副驾驶演变为代理，在关键任务（配置、安全、事件响应）上拥有授权。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;控制的必要性：&lt;/strong&gt;这种新的自动化水平需要复杂的治理框架。通用的“护栏”方法是不够的；成功取决于清晰的控制分类。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;四大控制支柱&lt;/strong&gt;：这些支柱（&lt;strong&gt;黄金路径、护栏、安全网和手动审核工作流程&lt;/strong&gt;）可以为大型企业的高速基础设施管理奠定适应性、安全的基础。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;黄金路径：自我调整、自主之路&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;黄金路径&lt;/strong&gt;是精心策划、预先批准的蓝图，使安全、合规的选择成为开发人员&lt;em&gt;最简单&lt;/em&gt;的选择（例如，标准化 IaC 模块、自助服务门户）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 年预测：增加生成和优化的自主权&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;基础设施意图：&lt;/strong&gt;人工智能代理将超越简单的代码生成。开发人员输入高级要求（例如“我需要为 AWS 美国东部的应用程序提供安全、可扩展的服务”），AI 代理将根据预定义的黄金路径完全构建、验证和配置合规基础设施。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“看门人”代理：&lt;/strong&gt;配置只是成功的一半。到 2026 年，黄金路径将包括嵌入的“生存时间”策略。自主代理将主动识别并停用“僵尸基础设施”（孤立资源、闲置开发环境），解决云浪费和减少安全攻击面。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;持续路径改进&lt;/strong&gt;：代理将持续监控这些黄金路径的性能、成本和采用情况。他们会建议并在许多情况下自主实施改进，例如更换资源类型或优化默认配置，以满足定义的 SLO（服务级别目标）和 FinOps 目标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;平台工程师的角色&lt;/strong&gt;：转向人工智能驱动的黄金路径的策划和质量控制，确保&lt;em&gt;最佳&lt;/em&gt;实践始终是&lt;em&gt;默认&lt;/em&gt;实践。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;护栏：自治治理和零漂移保证&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;护栏&lt;/strong&gt;是硬性的、不可协商的停止——“崩溃屏障”——防止危及平台安全性或稳定性的操作或配置（例如，阻止公共存储桶、强制执行二进制授权）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 年预测：从反应式扫描仪到主动式 AI 执行器&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;人工智能驱动的策略即代码：&lt;/strong&gt;代理会将高级合规性要求（例如“PCI-DSS 合规性”）转化为可执行的确定性 Guardrail，并将其部署到整个基础设施生命周期（CI/CD、运行时）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自主漏洞响应&lt;/strong&gt;：在发布新的关键漏洞 (CVE) 或安全补丁后，人工智能驱动的系统可能会在受影响环境中的预定义策略和人工批准的约束（例如网络策略、临时访问限制或容器映像块）下，越来越多地自动化创建和部署运行时护栏。这提供了即时的防御盾牌，将企业的保护时间从几天缩短到几分钟。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“审核员”代理：&lt;/strong&gt;合规证据收集将完全自动化。由于人工智能代理强制执行护栏，它还将针对 PCI-DSS 或 SOC2 等标准生成实时、不可变的审计报告，从而大大减少通常与审计准备相关的手动工作量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自主漂移修复&lt;/strong&gt;：这已成为一项标准功能。人工智能代理将根据黄金路径及其嵌入式护栏定义的所需状态持续扫描实时环境。在检测到未经授权的更改（漂移）后，代理将立即自动恢复或修复错误配置，从而在合规性敏感的环境中接近零配置漂移。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注重预防&lt;/strong&gt;：人工智能的目标是通过引导开发者走上黄金之路，确保他们很少（如果有的话）遇到护栏。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;安全网：预测可靠性和自动恢复&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安全网&lt;/strong&gt;是检测故障或威胁并促进快速恢复的反应控制（例如监控、自动回滚、备份程序）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 年预测：检测和修复完全自主&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;预测性 SRE：&lt;/strong&gt;经过大量可观测性数据训练的 AI 代理将在影响用户之前预测中断和性能下降。他们将使用复杂的模式识别来触发主动扩展或维护，以完全避免事件发生。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自主事件响应&lt;/strong&gt;：对于确实发生的事件，代理将超越建议 (AIOps 1.0) 转向完全自动修复 (AIOps 2.0)。&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;代理会识别根本原因，将其与适当的运行手册操作相关联，并自主执行修复（例如流量转移、重新启动服务或执行回滚），在许多情况下可能会显着缩短平均解决时间 (MTTR)。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SRE 的角色演变：&lt;/strong&gt;为安全网代理定义规则、容差和错误预算，并专注于需要人类创造力的复杂、新颖的故障模式。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于成本优化被视为 2025 年的首要任务，而混沌工程的采用率仍低于 10%，我们预测市场已为自主“安全网”和“FinOps 代理”做好了准备。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;手动审核工作流程：战略性人机交互&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;手动审核工作流程&lt;/strong&gt;是需要人工判断、监督和干预高风险、复杂或财务决策（例如架构审核、大额预算批准、安全事后分析）的流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2026 年预测：人工智能优化的人类判断&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;风险评分审核：&lt;/strong&gt;AI 代理将自动执行手动审核的&lt;em&gt;准备工作&lt;/em&gt;。在人类架构师审查部署之前，代理将生成全面的风险报告，检查合规性、成本预测和架构是否适合企业框架，向审查者提供简单的风险评分和继续/不继续的建议。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;战略摩擦：&lt;/strong&gt;这一机制是战略摩擦的必要点。虽然黄金通道、护栏和安全网实现了近乎完全的自主，但人工审查仍然是问责制和整体风险评估的关键一步，只有人类的判断才能提供。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;审批的未来&lt;/strong&gt;：人工审核将从官僚主义瓶颈转变为简短、信息丰富、影响力大的决策过程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;结论：面向代理未来的架构&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其中许多功能正在云端逐步探索通过开源项目、标准讨论和平台工程社区来构建原生生态系统，而不是作为单一的统一解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;新任务&lt;/strong&gt;：企业 IT 领导者不应再将 AI 视为一项功能，而是开始构建能够有效管理这四种不同控制机制的&lt;strong&gt;代理基础设施平台&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;成果&lt;/strong&gt;：通过赋予指导（黄金路径）、预防（护栏）和恢复（安全网）完全自主权，并战略性地实施人工智能优化的手动审核，组织可以在 2026 年实现前所未有的速度、弹性和合规性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;来自&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/cncf_report_stateofcloud_111025a.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;CNCF 云原生开发状况报告&lt;/a&gt;的最新数据&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;（2025 年 11 月）与更广泛的行业信号一致，表明对自主和人工智能辅助平台的兴趣日益浓厚&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;：随着 1560 万云原生开发者和 MCP 等“代理人工智能”平台已经进入采用阶段，该行业正朝着我们预测的方向发展——迈向完全自主、平台管理的未来。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【LitmusChaos Q4 2025 update: community, contributions, and project progress】LitmusChaos 2025 年第 4 季度更新：社区、贡献和项目进展</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/01/22/litmuschaos-q4-2025-update-community-contributions-and-project-progress/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As we enter the new year, we’re excited to share the Q4 updates from the LitmusChaos community. Over the past few months, the chaos engineering ecosystem and the LitmusChaos community have continued to grow steadily, driven by strong participation, thoughtful contributions, and meaningful collaboration across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This blog captures the highlights from &lt;strong&gt;October, November, and December&lt;/strong&gt;, bringing together key project updates, community initiatives, contributor activities, and ecosystem developments around LitmusChaos. Our goal is to keep the community informed, celebrate the work happening across the project, and reflect on the collective progress made during the quarter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;About LitmusChaos&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://litmuschaos.io/&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos&lt;/a&gt; is an open source chaos engineering platform that helps teams identify weaknesses and potential outages in their infrastructure by running controlled chaos experiments. Built on cloud-native principles, LitmusChaos enables teams to validate system resilience and proactively strengthen their DevOps pipelines against real-world software and infrastructure failures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Started in late 2017 with a focus on simple chaos jobs for Kubernetes, LitmusChaos became a CNCF Sandbox project in 2020 and was promoted to a CNCF Incubating project in January 2022. Today, the project is maintained by contributors from multiple organizations across cloud-native vendors, solution providers, and end users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LitmusChaos is used in production by organizations worldwide, including companies such as Adidas, FIS, iFood, Cyren, Intuit, Lenskart, Orange, as well as technology leaders like Red Hat and VMware.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Project Updates &amp;amp; Releases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Release 3.24.0 (December 2025)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The latest release introduces significant enhancements to user experience and system stability. For more details, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/releases/tag/3.24.0&#34;&gt;release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Key Highlights:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced experiment management with editable step names in fault settings, giving users better control over their chaos experiments&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved ChaosHub customization capabilities, allowing teams to better tailor their chaos engineering workflows&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed critical UI issues, including blank page rendering in experiment run history and caching problems in the overview page&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Added Kubernetes branding updates and refined the visual interface by removing deprecated elements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced image registry flexibility with support for empty registry names&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Contributors:&lt;/strong&gt; @LipsaDas0710, @Kamalesh-Seervi, @Poswark, @1spyral, @SharanRP&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Release 3.23.0 (November 2025)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A security-focused release that also brought significant documentation improvements and UI enhancements.&amp;nbsp;For more details, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/releases/tag/3.23.0&#34;&gt;release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Key Highlights:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Critical security patches addressing multiple CVEs, including authorization bypass vulnerabilities (CVE-2024-45337, CVE-2025-22868, CVE-2025-22869)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Strengthened JWT secret generation with increased salt length for improved authentication security&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced chaos probe functionality, allowing probes with the same name across different projects&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Major documentation updates, including new AWS SSM and GCP experiment coverage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Visual refresh across the platform with updated cloud provider logos (AWS, Azure, GCP, Spring Boot) and improved UI consistency&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed image registry issues and improved error handling for command probes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Contributors:&lt;/strong&gt; @thisis-gp, @Coder-pro1, @Devankguptaa, @VIDHITTS, @72umesh, @khushi1310, @Ayushi-Maurya2904, @harshneyy, @kunalsinghdadhwal, @Avirup-001, @yashgoyal0110, @adi-ray&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Release 3.22.0 (October 2025)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Focused on security hardening and operational improvements.&amp;nbsp;For more details, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/releases/tag/3.22.0&#34;&gt;release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Key Highlights:&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Critical security fixes addressing namespace compromise via hostPID and potential denial of service vulnerabilities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improved resource management with restrictions on CPU/memory usage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced log visibility with fixes to fault execution container logs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resolved the missing experiment pod logs issue, improving debugging capabilities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Removed hardcoded namespaces from Kubernetes manifests for better flexibility&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixed server address scheme handling for manifest re-downloads&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Contributors:&lt;/strong&gt; @prateekch33, @zyue110026, @PriteshKiri, @Gmerold, @UJESH2K, @harshit12339&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Across these three releases, Litmus Chaos welcomed 28 new contributors, demonstrating strong community momentum. The quarter emphasized security hardening, user experience improvements, and enhanced customization capabilities while maintaining the platform’s commitment to comprehensive chaos engineering tooling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Innovation Spotlight: LitmusChaos MCP Server&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;October marked a watershed moment for LitmusChaos with the release of our &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.litmuschaos.io/docs/mcp-server/overview&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP) Server&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; – a revolutionary integration that brings natural language interfaces to chaos engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What is the LitmusChaos MCP Server?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The LitmusChaos MCP Server leverages Anthropic’s Model Context Protocol to enable AI assistants like Claude to interact directly with LitmusChaos through natural language. This integration transforms how teams approach chaos engineering by removing technical barriers and making resilience testing accessible to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Hacktoberfest 2025 (The Month of Open Source)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hacktoberfest has always been special for LitmusChaos, and this year, we made it even bigger. The community came together to contribute to LitmusChaos and Litmus Docs, improving the project’s security, user experience, and accessibility with Litmus 4.0.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what we achieved together in October:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; Stars: 112+ new stars&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;23 new contributors to the Litmus repository&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;18 new contributors to the Litmus Docs repository&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These numbers reflect the incredible passion our contributors showed throughout Hacktoberfest. A big shoutout to everyone who helped strengthen LitmusChaos through code, docs, and discussions!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;In-Person Meetup Events&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This quarter, we hosted 3 in-person meetups in Bangalore and Hyderabad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos x Hacktoberfest Meetup – Bangalore (October 4)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We kicked off October with an incredible gathering, welcoming more than &lt;strong&gt;130 attendees&lt;/strong&gt; who came to celebrate open source and learn about chaos engineering. Check out a snapshot of the event &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RPXbq4pypns&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1279&#34; height=&#34;720&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Group photo of the LitmusChaos Hacktoberfest Meetup in Bangalore&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-154923&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10.jpg 1279w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-1024x576.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-900x507.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-355x200.jpg 355w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-711x400.jpg 711w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1279px) 100vw, 1279px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Hacktoberfest Hyderabad Meetup (October 11)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We hosted an additional Hacktoberfest meetup in&amp;nbsp;Hyderabad that continued to bring together passionate open-source enthusiasts. You can see a short video of the event &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NO_Vfaqnk7E&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1280&#34; height=&#34;720&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Group photo of the second LitmusChaos Hacktoberfest Meetup in Hyderabad&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-154924&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432.jpeg 1280w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-300x169.jpeg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-1024x576.jpeg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-768x432.jpeg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-900x506.jpeg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-356x200.jpeg 356w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-711x400.jpeg 711w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1280px) 100vw, 1280px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Resilience and Chaos Testing Meetup (December 6)&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The energy in the room was incredible for the first meetup that I’ve hosted around Chaos and Resilience testing, and the feedback from the community was amazing. You can read more about the event &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/my-first-resilience-testing-meetup-new-harness-office-pritesh-kiri-mwcqc/?trackingId=YB6wAcKAQPejftX4aoH7WA%3D%3D&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1600&#34; height=&#34;1115&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Group photo of the Resilience and Chaos Testing Meetup&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-154922&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image.jpeg 1600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-300x209.jpeg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1024x714.jpeg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-768x535.jpeg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-900x627.jpeg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-287x200.jpeg 287w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-574x400.jpeg 574w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Latest from the LitmusChaos Community&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;User Stories:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1999&#34; height=&#34;992&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2.png&#34; alt=&#34;intertech logo&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155550&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2.png 1999w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-300x149.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-1024x508.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-768x381.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-900x447.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-1800x893.png 1800w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-403x200.png 403w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-806x400.png 806w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1999px) 100vw, 1999px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is a sneak peek into the adopter story presented by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.intertech.com.tr/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intertech&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on how they are using LitmusChaos:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Intertech, Turkey’s largest financial technology software company, uses Litmus to proactively ensure the resilience of its critical banking infrastructure. Integrated into their SRE practices on a Kubernetes-based platform, Litmus enables Intertech to run chaos experiments such as pod failures, network latency, and resource stress to validate system behavior under real-world failure scenarios. By leveraging Litmus’ Kubernetes-native and customizable chaos engineering framework, Intertech has strengthened incident response readiness and improved the overall reliability of its banking applications, helping safeguard services for millions of customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Community Content&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the community continues to grow, so does the content. Over the quarter, the community members have created some amazing and exciting content to uplift the presence of LitmusChaos on the Cloud Native map. Check out all the latest content curated by the community for the community:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Monthly Community Meetings&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Held every third Wednesday of the month at 10 PM IST / 6:30 PM CET / 5:30 PM BST / 11:30 AM CT / 9:30 AM PST, community meetings remained vibrant hubs of discussion throughout Q4. You can find the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLmM1fgu30seVxbGPRTG8sRwILwDTHhuUn&#34;&gt;recordings of all meetings&lt;/a&gt; on our YouTube channel, along with the meeting notes &lt;a href=&#34;https://hackmd.io/a4Zu_sH4TZGeih-xCimi3Q?view&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Monthly Contributors Meetings&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Held every second and last Thursday at 7:00 PM IST / 1:30 PM GMT / 3:30 PM CEST / 9:30 AM ET, our contributor meetings maintained strong participation. Topics included technical implementation discussions, code reviews, documentation improvements, new feature proposals, and bug triage and prioritization. Find the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLmM1fgu30seUavpD-pBRsmWiUCZ2EaM_G&#34;&gt;videos on YouTube&lt;/a&gt; and the meeting notes &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1AoXIPofrl1qEsPENVuYCJJxdB0kTjvRC3j5JRXmz8d4/edit?tab=t.0&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Videos and Blogs:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can see other previously held in-person and virtual meetups on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@litmuschaos&#34;&gt;YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;, in addition to getting started content and technical deep dives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For blog content, visit the &lt;a href=&#34;https://litmuschaos.io/blog&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos blog&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://dev.to/&#34;&gt;DEV.to&lt;/a&gt; for the latest community updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Closing Thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Q4 2025 exemplified what makes open-source communities powerful: collaboration, innovation, and shared purpose. From the groundbreaking MCP Server to record-breaking Hacktoberfest participation, from enterprise adoption milestones to vibrant in-person meetups – every achievement reflects the passion and dedication of this community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we enter 2026, we’re energized by the possibilities ahead. Chaos engineering is evolving from a specialized practice to an essential discipline, and LitmusChaos is at the forefront of this transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s to building more resilient systems together. Here’s to chaos engineering for everyone. Here’s to an incredible 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Keep Learning. Keep Testing. Keep Building Resilience&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Connect with LitmusChaos&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The LitmusChaos community continues to grow with amazing contributions (issue identification, suggestions, and PRs), and is looking forward to another year of contributions and growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Visit the &lt;a href=&#34;https://litmuschaos.io/&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos Website&lt;/a&gt; for more detailed information about LitmusChaos and getting involved with the community.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Resources&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Join the #litmus channel on Kubernetes Slack to engage the community and learn, ask, and contribute.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Stay updated with the blog, and contribute your own blog content by using the tag #litmuschaos on DEV.to.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fill out &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/TYGmnCfGjuQDYHMc7&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;this&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; form to get an invite to our contributors and community calls.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/blob/master/CONTRIBUTING.md&#34;&gt;Contributing Guide&lt;/a&gt; to get started with contributions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Subscribe to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCa57PMqmz_j0wnteRa9nCaw&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos YouTube Channel&lt;/a&gt; for the latest videos.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Follow &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/LitmusChaos&#34;&gt;@LitmusChaos&lt;/a&gt; on X/Twitter for the latest social updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在进入新的一年之际，我们很高兴分享 LitmusChaos 社区的第四季度更新。在过去的几个月里，在全球范围内的大力参与、深思熟虑的贡献和有意义的合作的推动下，混沌工程生态系统和 LitmusChaos 社区持续稳定增长。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此博客记录了&lt;strong&gt;10 月、11 月和 12 月&lt;/strong&gt;的亮点，汇集了围绕 LitmusChaos 的关键项目更新、社区计划、贡献者活动和生态系统开发。我们的目标是让社区随时了解情况，庆祝整个项目所开展的工作，并反思本季度取得的集体进展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;关于 LitmusChaos&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://litmuschaos.io/&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos&lt;/a&gt; 是一个开源混沌工程平台，可帮助团队通过运行受控混沌实验来识别其基础设施中的弱点和潜在中断。 LitmusChaos 基于云原生原则构建，使团队能够验证系统弹性并针对现实世界的软件和基础设施故障主动加强其 DevOps 管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LitmusChaos 于 2017 年底启动，专注于 Kubernetes 的简单混沌作业，于 2020 年成为 CNCF 沙箱项目，并于 2022 年 1 月晋升为 CNCF 孵化项目。如今，该项目由来自云原生供应商、解决方案提供商和最终用户的多个组织的贡献者维护。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LitmusChaos 被世界各地的组织用于生产，包括 Adidas、FIS、iFood、Cyren、Intuit、Lenskart、Orange 等公司，以及 Red Hat 和 VMware 等技术领导者。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;项目更新和发布&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;版本 3.24.0（2025 年 12 月）&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最新版本显着增强了用户体验和系统稳定性。有关更多详细信息，请查看&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/releases/tag/3.24.0&#34;&gt;版本&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;主要亮点：&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过故障设置中的可编辑步骤名称增强实验管理，让用户更好地控制混沌实验&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;改进了 ChaosHub 自定义功能，使团队能够更好地定制混沌工程工作流程&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;修复了关键的 UI 问题，包括实验运行历史记录中的空白页面呈现以及概览页面中的缓存问题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;添加了 Kubernetes 品牌更新，并通过删除已弃用的元素来完善可视界面&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过支持空注册表名称增强映像注册表灵活性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;新贡献者：&lt;/strong&gt;@LipsaDas0710、@Kamalesh-Seervi、@Poswark、@1spyral、@SharanRP&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;版本 3.23.0（2025 年 11 月）&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个以安全为重点的版本还带来了重大的文档改进和 UI 增强。 有关更多详细信息，请查看&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/releases/tag/3.23.0&#34;&gt;版本&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;主要亮点：&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;针对多个 CVE 的关键安全补丁，包括授权绕过漏洞（CVE-2024-45337、CVE-2025-22868、CVE-2025-22869）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过增加盐长度来增强 JWT 密钥生成，以提高身份验证安全性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;增强了混沌探针功能，允许在不同项目中使用相同名称的探针&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;主要文档更新，包括新的 AWS SSM 和 GCP 实验范围&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过更新云提供商徽标（AWS、Azure、GCP、Spring Boot）和改进的 UI 一致性，实现整个平台的视觉刷新&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;修复了图像注册表问题并改进了命令探测的错误处理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;新贡献者：&lt;/strong&gt;@thisis-gp、@Coder-pro1、@Devankguptaa、@VIDHITTS、@72umesh、@khushi1310、@Ayushi-Maurya2904、@harshneyy、@kunalsinghdadhwal、@Avirup-001、@yashgoyal0110、@adi-ray&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;版本 3.22.0（2025 年 10 月）&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;专注于安全强化和运营改进。 有关更多详细信息，请查看&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/releases/tag/3.22.0&#34;&gt;版本&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;主要亮点：&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;重要的安全修复，解决了通过 hostPID 造成的命名空间泄露和潜在的拒绝服务漏洞&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;改进了资源管理，限制了 CPU/内存使用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过修复故障执行容器日志来增强日志可见性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;解决了实验 Pod 日志缺失的问题，提高了调试能力&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;从 Kubernetes 清单中删除了硬编码命名空间，以提高灵活性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;修复了清单重新下载的服务器地址方案处理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;新贡献者：&lt;/strong&gt;@prateekch33、@zyue110026、@PriteshKiri、@Gmerold、@UJESH2K、@harshit12339&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这三个版本中，Litmus Chaos 迎来了 28 位新贡献者，展现了强大的社区势头。本季度强调安全强化、用户体验改进和增强的定制功能，同时保持平台对全面混沌工程工具的承诺。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;创新聚焦：LitmusChaos MCP 服务器&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;10 月标志着 LitmusChaos 的一个分水岭，我们发布了&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.litmuschaos.io/docs/mcp-server/overview&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;模型上下文协议 (MCP) 服务器&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，这是一种革命性的集成，为混沌工程带来了自然语言界面。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;什么是 LitmusChaos MCP 服务器？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;石蕊混沌MCP 服务器利用 Anthropic 的模型上下文协议，使 Claude 等 AI 助手能够通过自然语言直接与 LitmusChaos 交互。这种集成消除了技术障碍并使每个人都可以进行弹性测试，从而改变了团队处理混沌工程的方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Hacktoberfest 2025（开源月）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hacktoberfest 一直对 LitmusChaos 来说很特别，今年我们把它做得更大。社区齐心协力为 LitmusChaos 和 Litmus Docs 做出贡献，利用 Litmus 4.0 提高项目的安全性、用户体验和可访问性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是我们在 10 月份共同取得的成就：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; 星星：112+ 新星星&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Litmus 存储库的 23 位新贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Litmus Docs 存储库新增 18 位贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些数字反映了我们的贡献者在 Hacktoberfest 期间表现出的令人难以置信的热情。向所有通过代码、文档和讨论帮助加强 LitmusChaos 的人表示大力的感谢！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;面对面聚会活动&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本季度，我们在班加罗尔和海得拉巴举办了 3 场面对面聚会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos x Hacktoberfest 聚会 - 班加罗尔（10 月 4 日）&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们以一次令人难以置信的聚会拉开了 10 月的序幕，欢迎超过 &lt;strong&gt;130 名与会者&lt;/strong&gt;前来庆祝开源并了解混沌工程。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RPXbq4pypns&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;查看活动快照。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1279&#34; height=&#34;720&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;班加罗尔 LitmusChaos Hacktoberfest 聚会合影&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-154923&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10.jpg 1279w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-300x169.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-1024x576.jpg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-768x432.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-900x507.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-355x200.jpg 355w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-10-711x400.jpg 711w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1279px）100vw，1279px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Hacktoberfest 海得拉巴聚会（10 月 11 日）&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们在海得拉巴举办了另一场 Hacktoberfest 聚会，继续将热情的开源爱好者聚集在一起。您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NO_Vfaqnk7E&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;观看该活动的短视频。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1280”高度=“720”src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;海得拉巴第二届 LitmusChaos Hacktoberfest 聚会合影&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-154924&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432.jpeg 1280w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-300x169.jpeg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-1024x576.jpeg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-768x432.jpeg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-900x506.jpeg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-356x200.jpeg 356w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/1760268625432-711x400.jpeg 711w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1280像素）100vw，1280像素“referrerpolicy=”no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;弹性和混沌测试聚会（12 月 6 日）&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于我举办的第一次围绕混沌和弹性测试的聚会，房间里的能量令人难以置信，来自社区的反馈也令人惊叹。您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/my-first-resilience-testing-meetup-new-harness-office-pritesh-kiri-mwcqc/?trackingId=YB6wAcKAQPejftX4aoH7WA%3D%3D&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;了解有关该活动的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; Decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1600&#34; height=&#34;1115&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;弹性和混沌测试聚会合影&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-154922&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image.jpeg 1600w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-300x209.jpeg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1024x714.jpeg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-768x535.jpeg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-900x627.jpeg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-287x200.jpeg 287w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-574x400.jpeg 574w&#34;sizes=&#34;auto,(最大宽度:1600px)100vw,1600px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos 社区的最新动态&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;用户故事：&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img load =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“1999”height =“992”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2.png”alt =“intertech徽标”class =“wp-image-155550” srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2.png 1999w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-300x149.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-1024x508.png 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-768x381.png 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-900x447.png 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-1800x893.png 1800w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-403x200.png 403w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image2-806x400.png 806w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：1999px）100vw，1999px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.intertech.com.tr/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intertech&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 介绍的采用者故事，了解他们如何使用 LitmusChaos：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;土耳其最大的金融技术软件公司 Intertech 使用 Litmus 主动确保其关键银行基础设施的弹性。 Litmus 集成到基于 Kubernetes 的平台上的 SRE 实践中，使 Intertech 能够运行 Pod 故障、网络延迟和资源压力等混沌实验，以验证真实故障场景下的系统行为。通过利用 Litmus 的 Kubernetes 原生和可定制的混沌工程框架，Intertech 加强了事件响应准备并提高了其银行应用程序的整体可靠性，帮助保护数百万客户的服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;社区内容&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着社区不断发展，内容也在不断发展。在本季度，社区成员创建了一些令人惊叹且令人兴奋的内容，以提升 LitmusChaos 在云原生地图上的存在感。查看社区为社区策划的所有最新内容：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;每月社区会议&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每月第三个星期三晚上 10 点（美国标准时间）/下午 6:30（欧洲中部时间）/下午 5:30（英国夏令时）/上午 11:30（中部时间）/上午 9:30（太平洋标准时间）举行，社区会议在整个第四季度仍然是活跃的讨论中心。您可以在我们的 YouTube 频道上找到&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLmM1fgu30seVxbGPRTG8sRwILwDTHhuUn&#34;&gt;所有会议的录音&lt;/a&gt;，以及&lt;a href=&#34;https://hackmd.io/a4Zu_sH4TZGeih-xCimi3Q?view&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;的会议记录。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;每月贡献者会议&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的贡献者会议每隔一秒举行一次，时间为上周四晚上 7:00（美国标准时间）/下午 1:30（格林尼治标准时间）/下午 3:30（欧洲中部夏令时间）/上午 9:30（美国东部时间），我们的贡献者会议保持了强劲的参与度。主题包括技术实施讨论、代码审查、文档改进、新功能提案以及错误分类和优先级。查找 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLmM1fgu30seUavpD-pBRsmWiUCZ2EaM_G&#34;&gt;YouTube 上的视频&lt;/a&gt;和会议记录&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1AoXIPofrl1qEsPENVuYCJJxdB0kTjvRC3j5JRXmz8d4/edit?tab=t.0&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;视频和博客：&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了入门内容和技术深入探讨之外，您还可以在我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@litmuschaos&#34;&gt;YouTube 频道&lt;/a&gt;上观看之前举办的其他现场和虚拟聚会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关博客内容，请访问 &lt;a href=&#34;https://litmuschaos.io/blog&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos 博客&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;http://dev.to/&#34;&gt;DEV.to&lt;/a&gt; 了解最新的社区更新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;结束语&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2025 年第四季度的示例它使开源社区变得强大：协作、创新和共同目标。从突破性的 MCP 服务器到破纪录的 Hacktoberfest 参与，从企业采用里程碑到充满活力的面对面聚会 - 每一项成就都体现了这个社区的热情和奉献精神。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;进入 2026 年，我们对未来的可能性充满活力。混沌工程正在从一种专业实践发展成为一门重要学科，而 LitmusChaos 处于这一转变的最前沿。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是为了共同构建更具弹性的系统。这是为大家带来的混沌工程。为令人难以置信的 2026 年干杯。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不断学习。继续测试。不断增强韧性&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;与 LitmusChaos 联系&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LitmusChaos 社区凭借惊人的贡献（问题识别、建议和 PR）继续发展，并期待新的一年的贡献和增长。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;访问 &lt;a href=&#34;https://litmuschaos.io/&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos 网站&lt;/a&gt;，了解有关 LitmusChaos 和参与社区的更多详细信息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;资源&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;加入 Kubernetes Slack 上的 #litmus 频道，与社区互动并学习、提问和贡献。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;随时了解博客的最新动态，并使用 DEV.to 上的 #litmuschaos 标签贡献您自己的博客内容。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;填写&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/TYGmnCfGjuQDYHMc7&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;此&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;表单即可获得我们的贡献者和社区电话会议的邀请。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;查看&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/blob/master/CONTRIBUTING.md&#34;&gt;贡献指南&lt;/a&gt;以开始贡献。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;订阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCa57PMqmz_j0wnteRa9nCaw&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos YouTube 频道&lt;/a&gt;以获取最新视频。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 X/Twitter 上关注&lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/LitmusChaos&#34;&gt;@LitmusChaos&lt;/a&gt;，了解最新的社交动态。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Platform engineering maintenance pitfalls and smart strategies to stay ahead】平台工程维护陷阱和保持领先的明智策略</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/01/21/platform-engineering-maintenance-pitfalls-and-smart-strategies-to-stay-ahead/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Platform engineering is a discipline that aims to increase the productivity of software engineering teams by designing, building, and maintaining internal platforms that abstract underlying infrastructure complexity and provide self-service capabilities. Kubernetes-based platforms are often complex multi-Open Source Software (OSS) integrations; thus, platform engineering is not a “declare once and forget it” process. It requires continuous dependency maintenance and strategies for inevitable breaking changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, we’ll go over the integration of fourteen OSS projects to maintain the platform that is built on top of a Kubernetes cluster. We explore the following challenges:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Catching up with software upstream changes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Controlling the supply chain&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Keeping up with Kubernetes upgrades&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Maintaining Helm chart upgrades&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Maintaining Applications with persistent data&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The necessity of runtime validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Catching Up With Software Upstream Changes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For this article, we have analyzed the last three years of releases for the following OSS projects: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/argoproj/argo-cd&#34;&gt;argo-cd&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/knative/serving&#34;&gt;knative-serving&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/istio&#34;&gt;istio&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/goharbor/harbor&#34;&gt;harbor&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://github.com/keycloak/keycloak&#34;&gt;keycloak&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cloudnative-pg/cloudnative-pg&#34;&gt;cloudnative-pg&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/go-gitea/gitea&#34;&gt;gitea&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/ingress-nginx&#34;&gt;ingress-nginx&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana&#34;&gt;grafana&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/bitnami-labs/sealed-secrets&#34;&gt;sealed-secrets&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno&#34;&gt;kyverno&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus/prometheus&#34;&gt;prometheus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/external-dns&#34;&gt;external-dns&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cert-manager/cert-manager&#34;&gt;cert-manager&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Based on our experience and analysis, you can expect between &lt;strong&gt;2-5 major upgrades, 43-52 minor upgrades, and 276-327 software patches every year&lt;/strong&gt;. That’s nearly an update a day!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1200&#34; height=&#34;742&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Platform engineering build from OSS CNCF projects graph showing the aggregated number of changes per release type of major, minor, and patch.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155482&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1.png 1200w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-300x186.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1024x633.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-768x475.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-900x557.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-323x200.png 323w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-647x400.png 647w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A significant challenge arises from the responsibility of maintaining a robust security posture. Every day, a number of security vulnerabilities are discovered. They are addressed in upstream projects that your platform needs to apply as security patches. This significantly contributes to the number of patches from the diagram above. Such changes must be monitored and quickly adopted into your platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In line with this, a project or its chart maintainers may opt to stop maintaining previous versions and only provide an upgrade path towards the latest major release, which effectively marks an older major version as end-of-life. Even if you only intend to adopt a security upgrade, you are practically forced to follow the maintained version.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A significant amount of maintenance effort can be automated, particularly when it comes to identifying new application versions. Helm chart releases are organized in repositories and registries, whereas binary software releases are found on GitHub using their API. This makes essential download and upgrading tasks a good candidate for being delegated to scripts that open a pull request accordingly. Automation addresses the short-term end-of-life problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Controlling the Supply Chain&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recent years taught us that critical parts of the supply chain, such as container registries or Helm chart repositories, can be subject to rate limiting or disruptive changes like deprecation on short notice by either OSS communities or software vendors. Adopting those changes and ensuring platform instances are using the new platform version is often impossible in such a short time frame.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maintaining a platform-dedicated container registry cache and a mono repository with Helm charts makes code-breaking changes transparent to users and buys platform engineers time to adapt. Similarly, this provides platform administrators the time to plan for an upgrade.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Keeping Up With Kubernetes Upgrades&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While each Kubernetes minor version is maintained for 12 months, cloud platform providers often push for faster adoption, and expectations are set that users will keep up with the latest version. A new Kubernetes version may come with deprecated APIs that your Helm chart relies on, making upgrading your Helm chart an inevitability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Kubernetes conformance smoke test enables you to discover potential breaking changes. Render all manifests that the platform would deploy and statically test the entire output against the Kubernetes OpenAPI schema, including all added custom resource definitions (CRDs).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Maintaining Helm Chart Upgrades&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a &lt;em&gt;platform as a product&lt;/em&gt; mindset, you own the full impact of what you deploy. Community Helm charts may reduce the number of manifests you need to define, but they do not remove the responsibility of understanding exactly what is being introduced into your Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In practice, simply reviewing the Go template code is rarely sufficient to assess the effects of a new chart version on your platform, so other strategies need to be applied. Some of the Helm charts upgrades are delivered with modifications to immutable Kubernetes properties, such as Deployment’s label selector, complicating maintenance and upgrades further.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By implementing a custom platform operator capable of managing changes to immutable Kubernetes properties, you can ensure a smooth upgrade. Detect potentially disruptive changes before they affect production environments by analyzing rendered Helm chart manifests: current version vs new version. The diff can also be performed against a running cluster, performing a dry run before applying changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Maintaining Applications With Persistent Data&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many Helm charts are delivered with dependencies that simplify deployment by bundling essential components such as SQL databases and key-value stores. These maintain the state on their dependent apps, and frequently require persistent volumes to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, Helm dependencies declare manifests to deploy a PostgreSQL database service, but do not come with any operator that is aware of database lifecycle management (upgrades, migrations, replication). This “batteries-included” approach simplifies the initial deployment, but is a technical debt for platform operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address these challenges, you must review the included dependency charts to check if they maintain application-critical data. Avoid using SQL databases provided as Helm chart dependencies. Instead, deploy database services via database operators, such as CloudnativePG, that are aware of both Kubernetes storage limitations (e.g., volume attachments) and database lifecycle requirements, such as migration workflows on major upgrades.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Necessity of Runtime Validation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Helm chart upgrade that deploys without errors does not necessarily ensure the application still behaves as expected. This goes regardless of whether it relies on core manifests alone or additional custom resources. Code-breaking changes (whether in the chart or the application itself) often will not surface through simple manifest validation. Resources may appear healthy while silently diverging from their previous configuration, and even logs may fail to expose integration issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This makes robust quality assurance essential, particularly through automated integration tests where possible. Automated tests should operate on a running cluster to ensure that all services can contact their dependencies and that endpoints are exposed as expected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Long-term cluster monitoring is essential as well. Issues like applications OOMKilled, CPU throttling, or running out of disk space often occur only after days or even weeks, depending on workload patterns. Detecting these problems early relies heavily on well-designed Prometheus rules. The Kube-Prometheus-Stack offers a solid foundation, but adding application-specific rules and alerting conditions can provide more insights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Final Thoughts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you commit to delivering a platform, you become responsible for the lifecycle of components. The open source community that develops essential applications usually responds quickly to compatibility and security issues; however, these changes still need to be integrated into your platform. You need to prepare for the operational cost, upgrading parts, and replacing components that are no longer maintained. The upside of coordinating this effort in your platform is that it provides relief to development teams from having to perform all the same work simultaneously. A high degree of automation and development of dedicated platform management components and tools ensures long-term maintainability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, feedback and upstream contributions are an integral part of using open source software that ensures other users in similar scenarios can benefit from the experience and that upstream projects remain healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;平台工程是一门学科，旨在通过设计、构建和维护内部平台来提高软件工程团队的生产力，这些平台抽象了底层基础设施的复杂性并提供自助服务功能。基于 Kubernetes 的平台通常是复杂的多开源软件 (OSS) 集成；因此，平台工程并不是一个“声明一次就可以忘记”的过程。它需要持续的依赖维护和针对不可避免的重大更改的策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇博文中，我们将介绍 14 个 OSS 项目的集成，以维护构建在 Kubernetes 集群之上的平台。我们探讨以下挑战：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;跟上软件上游的变化&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;控制供应链&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;跟上 Kubernetes 升级&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;维护 Helm 图表升级&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用持久数据维护应用程序&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;运行时验证的必要性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;赶上软件上游变化&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们分析了以下 OSS 项目过去三年的版本：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/argoproj/argo-cd&#34;&gt;argo-cd&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/knative/serving&#34;&gt;knative-serving&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/istio&#34;&gt;istio&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/goharbor/harbor&#34;&gt;港口&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;http://github.com/keycloak/keycloak&#34;&gt;keycloak&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cloudnative-pg/cloudnative-pg&#34;&gt;cloudnative-pg&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/go-gitea/gitea&#34;&gt;gitea&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/ingress-nginx&#34;&gt;ingress-nginx&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana&#34;&gt;grafana&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/bitnami-labs/sealed-secrets&#34;&gt;密封秘密&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno&#34;&gt;kyverno&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus/prometheus&#34;&gt;prometheus&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/external-dns&#34;&gt;external-dns&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cert-manager/cert-manager&#34;&gt;cert-manager&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据我们的经验和分析，您每年预计会出现&lt;strong&gt;2-5 个主要升级、43-52 个次要升级和 276-327 个软件补丁&lt;/strong&gt;。这几乎是一天更新一次！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“lazy”decoding =“async”width =“1200”height =“742”src =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1.png”alt =“OSS CNCF项目图表中的平台工程构建，显示主要，次要和补丁的每个版本类型的更改汇总数量。” class =“wp-image-155482”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1.png 1200w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-300x186.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-1024x633.png 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-768x475.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-900x557.png 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-323x200.png 323w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image1-647x400.png 647w&#34;sizes=&#34;auto,(最大宽度:1200px)100vw,1200px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;维护稳健的安全态势的责任带来了重大挑战。每天都会发现许多安全漏洞。它们在您的平台需要作为安全补丁应用的上游项目中得到解决。这极大地增加了上图中的补丁数量。必须监控此类更改并快速将其应用到您的平台中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与此相一致，项目或其图表维护者可能会选择停止维护以前的版本，而只提供通往最新主要版本的升级路径，这实际上将旧主要版本标记为生命周期结束。即使您只想采用安全升级，您实际上也被迫遵循维护版本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大量的维护工作可以实现自动化，特别是在识别新的应用程序版本时。 Helm 图表版本在存储库和注册表中组织，而二进制软件版本则使用其 API 在 GitHub 上找到。这使得基本的下载和升级任务成为委托给相应打开拉取请求的脚本的良好候选者。自动化解决了短期报废问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;控制供应链&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;近年来，我们了解到供应链的关键部分（例如容器注册表或 Helm 图表存储库）可能会受到速率限制或破坏性更改的影响，例如 OSS 社区或软件供应商在短时间内通知弃用。在如此短的时间内采用这些更改并确保平台实例使用新的平台版本通常是不可能的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;维护平台专用的容器注册表缓存和带有 Helm 图表的单一存储库，可以使代码破坏更改对用户透明，并为平台工程师赢得适应时间。同样，这为平台管理员提供了规划升级的时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;跟上 Kubernetes 升级&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然每个 Kubernetes 小版本都会维护 12 个月，但云平台提供商通常会推动更快的采用，并且期望用户能够跟上最新版本。新的 Kubernetes 版本可能附带您的 Helm Chart 所依赖的已弃用的 API，这使得升级您的 Helm Chart 成为必然。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 一致性冒烟测试使您能够发现潜在的重大更改。渲染平台将部署的所有清单，并根据 Kubernetes OpenAPI 架构静态测试整个输出，包括所有添加的自定义资源定义 (CRD)。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 类=“wp-bl”ock-heading&#34;&gt;维护 Helm Chart 升级&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;凭借&lt;em&gt;平台即产品&lt;/em&gt;的心态，您拥有所部署内容的全部影响。社区 Helm 图表可能会减少您需要定义的清单数量，但它们并不能免除准确理解 Kubernetes 集群中引入的内容的责任。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在实践中，仅仅检查 Go 模板代码很少足以评估新图表版本对您平台的影响，因此需要应用其他策略。一些 Helm 图表升级是通过对不可变的 Kubernetes 属性（例如 Deployment 的标签选择器）进行修改而提供的，这使维护和升级进一步复杂化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过实现能够管理不可变 Kubernetes 属性更改的自定义平台操作员，您可以确保顺利升级。通过分析渲染的 Helm 图表清单：当前版本与新版本，在潜在的破坏性更改影响生产环境之前检测到它们。还可以针对正在运行的集群执行差异，在应用更改之前执行试运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;使用持久数据维护应用程序&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多 Helm 图表都附带依赖项，这些依赖项通过捆绑 SQL 数据库和键值存储等基本组件来简化部署。它们维护其依赖应用程序的状态，并且经常需要持久卷来执行此操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，Helm 依赖项声明清单以部署 PostgreSQL 数据库服务，但不附带任何了解数据库生命周期管理（升级、迁移、复制）的操作员。这种“包含电池”的方法简化了初始部署，但对平台运营来说是一种技术债务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了应对这些挑战，您必须查看包含的依赖关系图表，以检查它们是否维护应用程序关键数据。避免使用作为 Helm 图表依赖项提供的 SQL 数据库。相反，通过数据库操作员（例如 CloudnativePG）部署数据库服务，这些操作员了解 Kubernetes 存储限制（例如卷附件）和数据库生命周期要求（例如重大升级时的迁移工作流程）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;运行时验证的必要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;部署无错误的 Helm 图表升级不一定能确保应用程序仍按预期运行。无论它是单独依赖核心清单还是依赖额外的自定义资源，这都是如此。代码破坏性更改（无论是在图表中还是应用程序本身）通常不会通过简单的清单验证而显现出来。资源可能看起来很健康，但悄悄地偏离了以前的配置，甚至日志也可能无法暴露集成问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这使得强大的质量保证变得至关重要，特别是在可能的情况下通过自动化集成测试。自动化测试应该在运行时运行集群以确保所有服务都可以联系其依赖项，并且端点按预期公开。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;长期集群监控也很重要。应用程序 OOMKilled、CPU 限制或磁盘空间不足等问题通常仅在几天甚至几周后发生，具体取决于工作负载模式。及早发现这些问题在很大程度上依赖于精心设计的 Prometheus 规则。 Kube-Prometheus-Stack 提供了坚实的基础，但添加特定于应用程序的规则和警报条件可以提供更多见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;最终想法&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦您承诺交付一个平台，您就需要对组件的生命周期负责。开发重要应用程序的开源社区通常会对兼容性和安全问题做出快速响应；但是，这些更改仍然需要集成到您的平台中。您需要为运营成本、升级零件以及更换不再维护的组件做好准备。在平台中协调这项工作的好处是，它可以让开发团队不必同时执行所有相同的工作。高度自动化以及专用平台管理组件和工具的开发确保了长期的可维护性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，反馈和上游贡献是使用开源软件不可或缺的一部分，可确保类似场景中的其他用户可以从体验中受益，并确保上游项目保持健康。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes Fuels AI Growth; Organizational Culture Remains the Decisive Factor】Kubernetes 推动人工智能增长；组织文化仍然是决定性因素</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2026/01/20/kubernetes-fuels-ai-growth-organizational-culture-remains-the-decisive-factor/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/the-cncf-annual-cloud-native-survey/&#34;&gt;CNCF Annual Cloud Native Survey&lt;/a&gt; confirms a long-developing trend: Kubernetes has moved from container orchestration to becoming the backbone of modern infrastructure—including AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Production usage of Kubernetes now stands at 82% among container users, and 66% of AI adopters are using it to scale inference workloads. Kubernetes is no longer a niche tool; it’s a core infrastructure layer supporting scale, reliability, and increasingly AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This shift reflects both the technical evolution and growing operational maturity of the cloud native ecosystem. 98% of organizations surveyed have now adopted cloud native technologies, making it the near-universal standard for modern enterprise infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image aligncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;434&#34; height=&#34;230&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cloud native adoption reaches 98% across surveyed organizations.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155422&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2.jpg 434w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2-300x159.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2-377x200.jpg 377w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 434px) 100vw, 434px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes: From Infrastructure Choice to Infrastructure Standard&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Survey data shows that Kubernetes has matured into the enterprise default. Organizations have moved beyond experimentation and are now focused on standardizing their infrastructure strategies. With this maturity comes more consistent deployment models and a broader application of cloud native best practices across teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image aligncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;886&#34; height=&#34;230&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;66% of organizations use Kubernetes to host generative AI workloads and 82% of container users deploy Kubernetes in production, up from 66% in 2023.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155423&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3.jpg 886w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3-300x78.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3-768x199.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3-600x156.jpg 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 886px) 100vw, 886px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes is now the default choice for building scalable, observable systems. It’s the platform teams rely on as they move from pilots to production-grade AI workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI Adoption Is Infrastructure-First&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s often a gap between AI ambition and what infrastructure can support. The 2025 data found that only 7% of organizations deploy AI models daily, and over half don’t train models at all. Instead, many prioritize the reliable and cost-effective operation of pre-trained models.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image aligncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;430&#34; height=&#34;228&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;47% of organizations deploy AI models occasionally, with only 7% deploying daily.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155429&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4.jpg 430w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4-300x159.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4-377x200.jpg 377w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes is helping bridge that gap, enabling teams to unify how they scale, deploy and manage AI workloads. As the report notes, &lt;em&gt;“Success requires treating AI/ML as a first-class infrastructure challenge, not just an algorithmic one.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Mature Teams Are Doing: GitOps, Platforms, Observability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The survey reinforces the growing trend toward platform engineering. Teams that have adopted GitOps workflows, internal developer portals, and automated pipelines are better positioned to scale AI and cloud native workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A clear signal of maturity: 0% of “explorers” report using GitOps, compared to 58% of “innovators.” These practices represent well-established methods that support consistency, scalability, and operational efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image aligncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;430&#34; height=&#34;228&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;GitOps adoption jumps from 0% among cloud native explorers to 58% among cloud native innovators&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155430&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5.jpg 430w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5-300x159.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5-377x200.jpg 377w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Observability also continues to be critical as workloads become more dynamic. OpenTelemetry’s position as the second-highest-velocity CNCF project reflects strong momentum for vendor-neutral, standardized instrumentation. Teams now depend on real-time visibility to keep systems reliable and performant in production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Culture Is Now the Primary Barrier&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the first time, culture—not complexity or security—is the top barrier to cloud native adoption. 47% of organizations cite cultural change with development teams as their biggest challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image aligncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;430&#34; height=&#34;228&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Cultural changes with the development team ranks as the #1 challenge for deploying containers (47%), surpassing technical concerns.&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-155417&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12.jpg 430w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-300x159.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-377x200.jpg 377w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 430px) 100vw, 430px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This highlights a recurring insight from the survey: the technical foundation is in place, but many organizations still need to adapt their internal structures and workflows to fully benefit from cloud native capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Looking Ahead: Infrastructure and Sustainability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As Kubernetes cements its position as the infrastructure for AI and modern workloads, the community faces the new challenge of sustainability. AI workloads are increasing pressure on open source infrastructure through machine-driven usage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The report warns that many systems operate on a “dangerously fragile premise.” Ensuring continued innovation will depend on organizations stepping up to contribute, support maintainers, and participate actively in sustaining the ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sustaining the future of cloud native will require intentional investment in infrastructure, governance, and community. CNCF will continue advancing this work through open collaboration, evolving standards, and support for maintainers and contributors across the ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those building at scale, now is the time to align your infrastructure strategy with what the data—and the community—clearly show.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join our upcoming webinar, &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/events/details/cncf-cncf-online-programs-presents-cloud-native-live-the-cncf-annual-cloud-native-survey-infrastructure-of-ais-future/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cloud Native Live: The CNCF Annual Cloud Native Survey — Infrastructure of AI’s Future&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;on February 3, 2026, to hear SVP of research Hilary Carter and a special guest analyst discuss the results of the survey and what that means for the future of the cloud native ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/the-cncf-annual-cloud-native-survey/&#34;&gt;CNCF 年度云原生调查&lt;/a&gt;证实了一个长期发展趋势：Kubernetes 已从容器编排转变为包括人工智能在内的现代基础设施的支柱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前容器用户中 Kubernetes 的生产使用率为 82%，66% 的 AI 采用者正在使用它来扩展推理工作负载。 Kubernetes 不再是一个小众工具；它是支持规模、可靠性和日益增长的人工智能系统的核心基础设施层。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种转变反映了云原生生态系统的技术演变和运营成熟度的提高。 98% 的受访组织现已采用云原生技术，使其成为现代企业基础设施的近乎通用标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-imagealigncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;434&#34;height=&#34;230&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;在接受调查的组织中，云原生采用率达到 98%。&#34; class =“wp-image-155422”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2.jpg 434w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2-300x159.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2-194x102.jpg 194w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-2-377x200.jpg 377w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：434px）100vw， 434px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes：从基础设施选择到基础设施标准&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;调查数据显示，Kubernetes 已成熟为企业默认。组织已经超越了实验，现在专注于标准化其基础设施战略。随着这种成熟度的到来，部署模型更加一致，云原生最佳实践在团队中得到更广泛的应用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-imagealigncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;886&#34;height=&#34;230&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;66%的组织使用Kubernetes来托管生成式AI工作负载，82%的容器用户在生产中部署Kubernetes，这一比例从2023 年将达到 66%。” class =“wp-image-155423”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3.jpg 886w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3-300x78.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3-768x199.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-3-600x156.jpg 600w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：886px）100vw， 886px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 现在是构建可扩展、可观察系统的默认选择。这是团队从试点转向生产级人工智能工作负载时所依赖的平台。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;人工智能采用是基础设施优先&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;经常有一个g人工智能的雄心与基础设施可以支持的内容之间存在一定的差距。 2025 年的数据发现，只有 7% 的组织每天部署人工智能模型，超过一半的组织根本不训练模型。相反，许多人优先考虑预训练模型的可靠且经济高效的运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-imagealigncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;430&#34;height=&#34;228&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;47% 的组织偶尔部署 AI 模型，只有 7% 每天部署。&#34; class =“wp-image-155429”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4.jpg 430w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4-300x159.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4-194x102.jpg 194w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-4-377x200.jpg 377w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：430px）100vw， 430px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 正在帮助弥合这一差距，使团队能够统一扩展、部署和管理 AI 工作负载的方式。正如报告指出的那样，“成功需要将 AI/ML 视为一流的基础设施挑战，而不仅仅是算法挑战。”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;成熟团队正在做什么：GitOps、平台、可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该调查强化了平台工程日益增长的趋势。采用 GitOps 工作流程、内部开发人员门户和自动化管道的团队能够更好地扩展人工智能和云原生工作负载。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成熟度的明确信号：0% 的“探索者”报告使用 GitOps，而“创新者”的比例为 58%。这些实践代表了支持一致性、可扩展性和运营效率的成熟方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-imagealigncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;430&#34;height=&#34;228&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;云原生探索者中的 GitOps 采用率从 0% 跃升至云原生创新者中的 58%&#34; class =“wp-image-155430”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5.jpg 430w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5-300x159.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5-194x102.jpg 194w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-5-377x200.jpg 377w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：430px）100vw， 430px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着工作负载变得更加动态，可观察性也仍然至关重要。 OpenTelemetry 作为第二高速度​​ CNCF 项目的地位反映了供应商中立的标准化仪器的强劲势头。团队现在依靠实时可见性来保持系统在生产中的可靠性和性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;文化现在是主要障碍&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第一次，文化——而不是复杂性或安全性——成为了p 云原生采用的障碍。 47% 的组织将开发团队的文化变革视为最大的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-imagealigncenter size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;430&#34;height=&#34;228&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;开发团队的文化变化被列为部署容器的第一大挑战 (47%)，超过了技术问题。&#34; class =“wp-image-155417”srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12.jpg 430w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-300x159.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-194x102.jpg 194w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-12-377x200.jpg 377w“尺寸=”自动，（最大宽度：430px）100vw， 430px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这凸显了调查中反复出现的一个见解：技术基础已经到位，但许多组织仍然需要调整其内部结构和工作流程，以充分受益于云原生功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;展望未来：基础设施和可持续发展&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着 Kubernetes 巩固其作为人工智能和现代工作负载基础设施的地位，社区面临着可持续性的新挑战。人工智能工作负载通过机器驱动的使用给开源基础设施带来越来越大的压力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该报告警告说，许多系统都在“危险脆弱的前提下”运行。确保持续创新将取决于组织加紧贡献、支持维护者并积极参与维持生态系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;维持云原生的未来需要对基础设施、治理和社区进行有意投资。 CNCF 将通过开放协作、不断发展的标准以及对整个生态系统的维护者和贡献者的支持来继续推进这项工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于那些大规模建设的人来说，现在是根据数据和社区明确显示的内容调整基础设施策略的时候了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;参加我们即将举行的网络研讨会，&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/events/details/cncf-cncf-online-programs-presents-cloud-native-live-the-cncf-annual-cloud-native-survey-infrastruct-of-ais-future/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;云原生直播：CNCF 年度云原生调查 — 人工智能未来的基础设施&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;， &lt;/em&gt;2026 年 2 月 3 日，聆听研究高级副总裁 Hilary Carter 和一位特邀客座分析师讨论调查结果以及这对云原生生态系统的未来意味着什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>