<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://rsshub.rssforever.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 co-located event deep dive: Kubernetes on Edge】KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 同期举办活动深入探讨：边缘上的 Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/28/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2024-co-located-event-deep-dive-kubernetes-on-edge/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;380&#34; height=&#34;152&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/K8ED_North-America_400x275-Logo-Color.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Kubernetes on Edge Day&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-119643&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Co-chairs: Tina Tsou and Mars Toktonaliev&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;November 12, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Salt Lake City, Utah&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co-located-events/kubernetes-on-edge-day/#about&#34;&gt;Kubernetes on Edge Day&lt;/a&gt; demonstrates edge computing is here, and it’s powered by Kubernetes. We’re showcasing real-world use cases, best practices, and cutting-edge technologies that are driving the adoption of Kubernetes at the edge. This is a community-driven event. We’ve curated a program featuring industry leaders, developers, and end-users who are passionate about shaping the future of edge computing. We really hope you’ll have fun, connect and learn with fellow practitioners. This event first occurred during KubeCon EU in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who will get the most out of attending this event?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyone involved in deploying, managing, or developing applications for edge environments will get a lot out of attending our event. This includes DevOps engineers, SREs, developers, architects, and technical decision-makers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is new and different this year?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We hope to provide a progression in the conversation around Kubernetes at the edge, moving from introductory topics to more advanced applications and real-world implementations covering diverse areas such as federated machine learning, operating kiosks or revolutionizing specific industries like cargo shipment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will the day look like?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes on Edge will be a half-day event focusing specifically on the use of Kubernetes for managing and orchestrating applications and workloads at the edge. We’ll start at 1:25pm and will be done before the end of the day. Here’s the &lt;a href=&#34;https://colocatedeventsna2024.sched.com/overview/type/Kubernetes+on+Edge+Day&#34;&gt;full schedule&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should I do any homework first?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No preparation is needed, and please remember that all presentations will be recorded and later published on CNCF’s YouTube channel&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Submitted by Mars Toktonaliev, who is looking forward to seeing old friends, making new friends, and of course all the canyons!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/register/&#34;&gt;Don’t forget to register&lt;/a&gt; for KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“380”高度=“152”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/K8ED_North-America_400x275-Logo-Color.svg&#34; alt=&#34;边缘日上的 Kubernetes&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-119643&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;联合主席：Tina Tsou 和 Mars Toktonaliev&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2024 年 11 月 12 日&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;犹他州盐湖城&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/co- located-events/kubernetes-on-edge-day/#about&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 边缘日&lt;/ a&gt; 演示了边缘计算，它由 Kubernetes 提供支持。我们展示了推动 Kubernetes 在边缘采用的真实用例、最佳实践和尖端技术。这是一个社区驱动的活动。我们策划了一个由热衷于塑造边缘计算未来的行业领导者、开发人员和最终用户参加的计划。我们真诚地希望您能与其他从业者一起享受乐趣、交流和学习。该事件首次发生在 2021 年 KubeCon EU 期间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;谁将从参加本次活动中获益最多？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;参与边缘环境部署、管理或开发应用程序的任何人都将从参加我们的活动中获益匪浅。这包括 DevOps 工程师、SRE、开发人员、架构师和技术决策者。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;今年有什么新的和不同的？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们希望在边缘围绕 Kubernetes 的对话取得进展，从介绍性主题转向更高级的应用程序和实际实施，涵盖不同领域，例如联合机器学习、操作信息亭或彻底改变货运等特定行业。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;这一天会是什么样子？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;边缘上的 Kubernetes 将是一个为期半天的活动，专门关注使用 Kubernetes 来管理和编排边缘的应用程序和工作负载。我们将于下午 1:25 开始，并在当天结束前完成。这是&lt;a href=&#34;https://co locatedeventsna2024.sched.com/overview/type/Kubernetes+on+Edge+Day&#34;&gt;完整时间表&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我应该先做作业吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无需准备，请记住，所有演示文稿都将被录制并随后发布在 CNCF 的 YouTube 频道上&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;由 Mars Toktonaliev 提交，他期待着见到老朋友，结交新朋友，当然还有所有的峡谷！&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/register/&#34;&gt;不要忘记注册&lt;/a&gt;参加 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div样式=“高度：80px”aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-powered observability: picking up where AIOps failed】AI 支持的可观察性：弥补 AIOps 失败的地方</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/28/ai-powered-observability-picking-up-where-aiops-failed/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally posted on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://logz.io/blog/ai-powered-observability-picking-up-where-aiops-failed/?utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_source=cncf&#34;&gt;Logz.io blog&lt;/a&gt; by Asaf Yigal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;is-style-spaced-uppercase has-gray-200-background-color has-background&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;GenAI promises evolutionary changes in how we use observability tools, but meeting expectations means heeding the lessons of our AIOps mistakes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The emergence of generative AI in observability tools was inevitable, but there’s already been an extreme degree of hype in the market. Monitoring, DevOps and ITOps have never been immune to trends, and with GenAI capabilities, the propaganda hype&amp;nbsp;machine is running out of control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organizations looking to ride the wave of GenAI undoubtedly recall&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://insights.compucom.com/insights/aiops-going-beyond-the-buzzword&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;the massive hype around AIOps tools&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;in the not-so-distant past. The core purpose of AIOps was to address the complexity, volume and velocity of operational telemetry, enabling proactive incident response and reducing manual intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many believed that AIOps was the future that could solve problems within systems, but adoption lagged because&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/sres-wish-automation-solved-all-their-problems/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;AIOps didn’t meet the needs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;of critical IT use cases. What were organizations trying to get out of AIOps? What were the right tools? Those questions were never answered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To succeed,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/peer-community/oneminuteinsights/aiops-hype-practical-i-o-solution-yn5&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;AIOps needed organizations to change their processes&lt;/a&gt;, and many organizations were reluctant to do that. Failure to realize benefits from those solutions wasn’t due to the technology — it was because organizations weren’t making the changes required to get those benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How AI-Powered Observability Can Meet Expectations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organizations are looking for productivity gains in their IT environments. Many ask: “How can we complete tasks faster? How can we increase our time-to-value? What can we do to remediate issues faster so we can get the most out of core issues in our business?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GenAI and AI-powered observability tools can help in all of these areas. Surfacing insights about system behavior — and providing direct knowledge on how to remediate issues that arise in telemetry data (logs, metrics and traces) — is what observability should provide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, these insights haven’t been available to anyone except technical experts and analysts who understand complex query language or have an intimate understanding of the telemetry data flowing through a system. But what if AI-powered observability can take things even a step further? What if you could interact using natural language with your system?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s potential for these tools to open up deeper insights to a much broader user base. This could significantly increase awareness of system behavior, democratize observability to nontechnical users and provide greater understanding of points of failure or difficulty in environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In an era of IT staffing knowledge gaps and hiring difficulties, AI-powered observability could fill some of those needs. What would it mean for your team to have the equivalent of a junior developer working directly within your technology platform?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The strongest applications of observability today involve strategic capabilities delivered through GenAI integration. These range from automatic collection of relevant contextual insights and anomaly detection, to the ability to pinpoint critical data to optimize data and costs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI-powered capabilities can transform the day-to-day interactions of engineering and DevOps teams by reinventing core monitoring and troubleshooting practices, spanning from querying to root cause analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These types of AI-powered systems — with full dashboarding, data visualizations and answers to pressing questions in seconds — can help meet the promise AIOps was intended to provide.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The core idea of AIOps is to pull in as much telemetry data as possible to identify anomalies. However, this is different from what observability solutions provide. Observability provides services on selective telemetry data and displays real-time metrics, such as CPU usage or other areas of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While incorporating AI for anomaly detection within these metrics might seem like an AIOps feature, it actually is an enhancement to an observability solution. In contrast, AIOps starts with AI and might not offer a single dashboard.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Revolution Is Waiting, But We Must Evolve First&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The lessons from AIOps must be applied to the next generation of observability tools for them to help organizations meet varied and intricate use cases around cloud-native, ephemeral architectures.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to GenAI, there is potential for evolutionary changes in the way we interact with our observability tools, as well as revolutionary changes in how we organize our operations teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re already seeing benefits of bringing GenAI into observability tools, such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Teams can use these capabilities to filter out irrelevant data and speed troubleshooting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;AI can identify top errors and suggest potential mitigation strategies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manual processes can be automated to save engineers hours of work, so they can focus on bigger-picture strategies and projects.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is one thing to talk about implementing these capabilities and another to take advantage of them. The question remains about what benefit organizations realistically can get from these shifts. Use cases have to be met, and productivity gains must be realized. It can be challenging for organizations to understand and accept the necessary changes; if the barriers are too great, the benefits won’t materialize.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The next-generation approach to system monitoring and management, which leverages GenAI and machine learning to automatically detect, diagnose and resolve issues without human intervention, isn’t far off. This evolution will allow technical teams to focus on strategic tasks while ensuring optimal system performance and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Teams are best served by remembering the successes and failures of past rapid technology shifts. Be prepared to shift mindsets across an organization to meet your goals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;会员帖子最初发布于&lt;a href=&#34;https://logz.io/blog/ai-powered-observability-picking-up-where-aiops-failed/?utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=cncf&#34; &gt;Logz.io 博客&lt;/a&gt;，作者：Asaf Yigal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;is-style-spaced-uppercase has-gray-200-background-color has-background&#34;&gt;​​&lt;em&gt;GenAI 承诺在我们使用可观察性工具的方式上发生革命性的变化，但满足期望意味着要听取 AIOps 的经验教训错误。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;生成式人工智能在可观察性工具中的出现是不可避免的，但市场上已经进行了极端程度的炒作。监控、DevOps 和 ITOps 从来都无法免受趋势的影响，而借助 GenAI 功能，宣传炒作机器正在失控。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;希望顺应 GenAI 浪潮的组织无疑会记得&lt;a href=&#34;https://insights.compucom.com/insights/aiops-going-beyond-the-buzzword&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener ”在不远的过去，围绕 AIOps 工具的大规模炒作&lt;/a&gt;。 AIOps 的核心目的是解决操作遥测的复杂性、数量和速度，实现主动事件响应并减少人工干预。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多人认为 AIOps 是可以解决系统内问题的未来，但采用滞后，因为&lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/sres-wish-automation-solved-all-their-problems/&#34;目标=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;AIOps 无法满足关键 IT 用例的需求&lt;/a&gt;。组织试图从 AIOps 中获得什么？什么是正确的工具？这些问题从未得到解答。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要取得成功，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/peer-community/onemillioninsights/aiops-hype-practical-i-o-solution-yn5&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; &gt;AIOps 需要组织改变其流程&lt;/a&gt;，但许多组织不愿意这样做。未能从这些解决方案中实现收益并不是因为技术，而是因为组织没有做出获得这些收益所需的更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;人工智能驱动的可观察性如何满足期望&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;组织正在寻求提高其 IT 环境的生产力。许多人问：“我们怎样才能更快地完成任务？我们如何才能缩短实现价值的时间？我们可以采取哪些措施来更快地修复问题，以便充分利用业务中的核心问题？”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GenAI 和人工智能驱动的可观察性工具可以在所有这些领域提供帮助。可观察性应该提供有关系统行为的洞察，并提供有关如何修复遥测数据（日志、指标和跟踪）中出现的问题的直接知识。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统上，除了了解复杂查询语言或对流经系统的遥测数据有深入了解的技术专家和分析师之外，任何人都无法获得这些见解。但如果 AI-p 会怎样呢？拥有可观察性可以让事情更进一步吗？如果您可以使用自然语言与您的系统进行交互会怎么样？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些工具有潜力为更广泛的用户群提供更深入的见解。这可以显着提高对系统行为的认识，使非技术用户的可观察性民主化，并更好地理解环境中的故障​​点或困难点。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 IT 人员知识缺口和招聘困难的时代，人工智能驱动的可观察性可以满足其中一些需求。对于您的团队来说，让初级开发人员直接在您的技术平台上工作意味着什么？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当今最强大的可观察性应用涉及通过 GenAI 集成提供的战略能力。这些范围从自动收集相关上下文洞察和异常检测，到精确定位关键数据以优化数据和成本的能力。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能支持的功能可以通过重新发明核心监控和故障排除实践（从查询到根本原因分析）来改变工程和 DevOps 团队的日常互动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些类型的人工智能驱动系统——具有完整的仪表板、数据可视化和在几秒钟内回答紧迫问题的能力——可以帮助实现 AIOps 的承诺。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AIOps 的核心思想是获取尽可能多的遥测数据来识别异常。然而，这与可观测性解决方案提供的不同。可观测性提供选择性遥测数据的服务并显示实时指标，例如 CPU 使用率或其他感兴趣的领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然在这些指标中纳入用于异常检测的 AI 可能看起来像是 AIOps 功能，但它实际上是对可观察性解决方案的增强。相比之下，AIOps 从人工智能开始，可能不提供单个仪表板。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;革命正在等待，但我们必须首先发展&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AIOps 的经验教训必须应用于下一代可观察性工具，以帮助组织满足围绕云原生、短暂架构的各种复杂用例。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;感谢 GenAI，我们与可观察性工具交互的方式有可能发生革命性的变化，以及我们组织运营团队的方式也可能发生革命性的变化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经看到将 GenAI 引入可观测性工具的好处，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;团队可以使用这些功能过滤掉不相关的数据并加快故障排除速度。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;人工智能可以识别最严重的错误并提出潜在的缓解策略。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;手动流程可以实现自动化，以节省工程师的工作时间，让他们能够专注于更宏观的战略和项目。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;谈论实现是一回事掌握这些能力以及利用它们的另一种能力。问题仍然是组织实际上可以从这些转变中获得什么好处。必须满足用例，并且必须实现生产力的提高。对于组织来说，理解并接受必要的变革可能具有挑战性；如果障碍太大，收益就不会实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下一代系统监控和管理方法，利用 GenAI 和机器学习自动检测、诊断和解决问题，无需人工干预，已经为时不远。这种演变将使技术团队能够专注于战略任务，同时确保最佳的系统性能和可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;团队最好记住过去快速技术变革的成功和失败。准备好转变整个组织的思维方式以实现您的目标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to transform Telemetry data from ingest to actionable insights】如何将遥测数据从摄取转化为可操作的见解</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/22/how-to-transform-telemetry-data-from-ingest-to-actionable-insights/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post by Ranjan Parthasarathy, CPO/CTO of&amp;nbsp;Apica&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc9ax-OYYvPGIUPNoKYB4dDj6GhLj4DMH2CXIzlaZIeEyZRmCvmq7GUrnx1ABUT1q9YRjE1KFnL3vjpA5Mq3E7SpWj1Li_q29YeCbeuGD8gq1IwqGDrNVkD-9s3gQ9yoqaIdPHsdxIu0oNNRukCm6uk5d-GszWxkehje-hw1a4sNK0X0Lg3TFc?key=c3whGqIEg1CWX5cws-BO6w&#34; alt=&#34;Telemetry Data: From Ingest to Insights&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Telemetry data is to your system what sensors are to an automobile. Put simply, it is vital. However, handling telemetry data is cumbersome, particularly with the current data explosion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enterprises require telemetry data for proactive management of complex systems and informed strategic planning with:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-time system monitoring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rapid issue detection and diagnosis&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance optimization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data-driven decision making&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thus, telemetry is a goldmine of critical data. The caveat is turning that ingested data into useful insights. While it is challenging, with the right strategies, best practices and solutions like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apica.io/blog/what-is-fleet-management-in-telemetry/&#34;&gt;fleet management&lt;/a&gt;, you can tame the power of telemetry.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s break down the process of turning your telemetry data into actionable insights.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Best Practices to Follow&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Raw data comes in all shapes and forms. Turning that raw data into context-rich insights is imperative to unlock critical business and technical decisions. Thus, several key areas must be addressed to leverage the unprecedented amounts of ingested data effectively.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are a few practices for turning ingested data into meaningful insights:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Quality and Integrity:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Cleansing:&lt;/strong&gt; Remove noise, inconsistencies, and errors from the data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Validation:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensure the data complies with business standards.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Enrichment:&lt;/strong&gt; Put context and value to the data via external sources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Governance:&lt;/strong&gt; Add clear policies and procedures for fair data management.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Analysis and Visualization:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Descriptive Analytics:&lt;/strong&gt; Parse historical data and understand trends and patterns.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Predictive Analytics:&lt;/strong&gt; Predict inevitable outcomes based on statistical data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prescriptive Analytics:&lt;/strong&gt; Suggest actions based on stats data and ML to enhance performance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Visualization:&lt;/strong&gt; Generate neat and vivid dashboards &amp;amp; reports.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business Context and Goals:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Define Key Performance Indicators (KPIs):&lt;/strong&gt; Isolate the metrics that matter most to your enterprise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Align Data Insights with Business Objectives:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensure your analysis efforts touch focused business problems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communicate Insights Effectively:&lt;/strong&gt; Use clear language &amp;amp; visualization to present major insights to stakeholders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology and Infrastructure:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Storage and Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Select modern and apt tools &amp;amp; services for storing, managing, and accessing the data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Pipelines:&lt;/strong&gt; Use Automation to your benefit for data ingestion, transformation, &amp;amp; loading into analytics tools.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analytical Tools:&lt;/strong&gt; Use relevant tools for statistical analysis, machine learning, and visualization purpose.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organizational Culture and Processes:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data-Driven Culture:&lt;/strong&gt; Build a culture focused on data insights and data-informed decision-making.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Literacy:&lt;/strong&gt; Equip your team with data analysis knowledge and interpretation practices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration and Communication: &lt;/strong&gt;Encourage collaboration between data analysts, tech leaders, business users, and stakeholders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security and Privacy:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Security Measures:&lt;/strong&gt; Practice robust security measures to protect all your sensitive data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Privacy Compliance:&lt;/strong&gt; Stick to relevant data privacy regulations. Address the key considerations that businesses can leverage data from, gaining actionable insights and driving better decision-making.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Steps for turning the ingested data into insights&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You need a structured strategy to extract relevant insights from a dynamic data pool. This ensures informed decision-making and strategic planning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following steps outline a comprehensive method for turning ingested data into valuable insights, guiding you through the process of filtering, aggregation, visualization, and analysis:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start with filtering. &lt;/strong&gt;Not all data is relevant, so focus on what matters. Use time ranges, specific metrics, or error types to narrow your scope.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aggregate the data: &lt;/strong&gt;Look for patterns, then group by time intervals or categories. This gives you a bird’s-eye view.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visualize: &lt;/strong&gt;Use charts and graphs to visualize information better. For instance, Line charts show changes over time, and heatmaps highlight problem areas.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use Dashboards. &lt;/strong&gt;Dashboards tie it all together.&lt;strong&gt; T&lt;/strong&gt;hey give real-time overviews, allowing you to spot issues immediately and customize them to your needs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Root-Cause Issues: &lt;/strong&gt;Look for performance bottlenecks. Are certain operations slowing things down? Identify them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch for anomalies. &lt;/strong&gt;Sudden spikes or drops are red alerts. They often signal problems that must be resolved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing: &lt;/strong&gt;Finally, track trends over time. Are things improving or getting worse? This will guide your long-term strategy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Takeaway&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the right tools and strategies, you can maximize the value of your data, reduce downtime, and improve overall operations efficiency. Proactively managing telemetry turns data chaos into clarity and smarter decision-making. That said, you can unleash your systems’ full potential with the power of telemetry. Thus, a well-designed data pipeline is key to transforming raw information into game-changing insights.&amp;nbsp;For more insights, connect directly with Ranjan Parthasarathy, feel free to reach out on &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ranjanparth&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ranjanp/&#34;&gt;LinkedIn,&lt;/a&gt; or explore more about Apica’s observability solutions on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apica.io/&#34;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Apica 首席产品官/首席技术官 Ranjan Parthasarathy 的成员帖子&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc9ax-OYYvPGIUPNoKYB4dDj6GhLj4DMH2CXIzlaZIeEyZRmCvmq7GUrnx1ABUT1q9YRjE1KFnL3vjpA5Mq3E7SpWj 1Li_q29YeCbeuGD8gq1IwqGDrNVkD-9s3gQ9yoqaIdPHsdxIu0oNNRukCm6uk5d-GszWxkehje-hw1a4sNK0X0Lg3TFc?key=c3whGqIEg1CWX5cws- BO6w&#34; alt=&#34;遥测数据：从摄取到洞察&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;遥测数据对于您的系统就像传感器对于汽车一样。简而言之，这至关重要。然而，处理遥测数据很麻烦，尤其是在当前数据爆炸的情况下。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;企业需要遥测数据来主动管理复杂系统并制定明智的战略规划：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;实时系统监控&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;快速问题检测和诊断&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;性能优化&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据驱动的决策&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，遥测是关键数据的金矿。需要注意的是，将获取的数据转化为有用的见解。虽然这具有挑战性，但需要采取正确的策略、最佳实践和解决方案，例如&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apica.io/blog/what-is-fleet-management-in-telemetry/&#34;&gt;车队管理&lt;/ a&gt;，您可以驾驭遥测的力量。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们分解一下将遥测数据转化为可行见解的过程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;要遵循的最佳实践&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;原始数据有各种形式。将原始数据转化为上下文丰富的见解对于解锁关键业务和技术决策至关重要。因此，必须解决几个关键领域的问题，才能有效地利用前所未有的大量数据。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是将获取的数据转化为有意义的见解的一些做法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据质量和完整性：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据清理&lt;/strong&gt;：消除数据中的噪音、不一致和错误。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据验证&lt;/strong&gt;：确保数据符合业务标准。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据丰富&lt;/strong&gt;：通过外部来源为数据添加背景信息和价值。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据治理&lt;/strong&gt;：添加明确的政策和程序以实现公平的数据管理。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据分析和可视化：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;描述性分析&lt;/strong&gt;：解析历史数据并了解趋势和模式。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;预测分析&lt;/strong&gt;：根据统计数据预测不可避免的结果。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;规范性分析&lt;/strong&gt;：根据统计数据和机器学习提出操作建议，以提高性能。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据可视化：&lt;/strong&gt; 生成整洁、生动的仪表板和报告。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;业务背景和目标：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;定义关键绩效指标 (KPI)&lt;/strong&gt;：隔离对您的企业最重要的指标。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使数据洞察与业务目标保持一致：&lt;/strong&gt;确保您的分析工作能够触及重点业务问题。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;有效传达见解&lt;/strong&gt;：使用清晰的语言和可视化方式向利益相关者展示主要见解。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;技术和基础设施：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据存储和管理：&lt;/strong&gt;选择现代且合适的工具和服务来存储、管理和访问数据。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据管道&lt;/strong&gt;：使用自动化来获取、转换数据并加载到分析工具中，为您带来好处。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;分析工具&lt;/strong&gt;：使用相关工具进行统计分析、机器学习和可视化目的。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;组织文化和流程：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据驱动文化&lt;/strong&gt;：建立专注于数据洞察和基于数据的决策的文化。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据素养&lt;/strong&gt;：为您的团队提供数据分析知识和解释实践。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;协作与沟通&lt;/strong&gt;：鼓励数据分析师、技术领导者、业务用户和利益相关者之间的协作。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安全和隐私：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据安全措施&lt;/strong&gt;：采取强有力的安全措施来保护您的所有敏感数据。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据隐私合规性：&lt;/strong&gt;遵守相关数据隐私法规。解决企业可以利用数据、获得可行见解并推动更好决策的关键考虑因素。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;将摄取的数据转化为见解的步骤&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您需要一个结构化策略来从动态数据池中提取相关见解。这确保了明智的决策和战略规划。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下步骤概述了将提取的数据转化为有价值的见解的综合方法，指导您完成过滤、聚合、可视化和分析的过程：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;从过滤开始。 &lt;/strong&gt;并非所有数据都是相关的，因此请关注重要的数据。使用时间范围、特定指标或错误类型来缩小范围。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;聚合数据：&lt;/strong&gt;寻找模式，然后按时间间隔或类别进行分组。这为您提供了鸟瞰图。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可视化：&lt;/strong&gt;使用图表和图表以更好地可视化信息。例如，折线图显示随时间的变化，热图突出显示问题区域。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用仪表板。 &lt;/strong&gt;仪表板将所有内容联系在一起。&lt;strong&gt;它们提供实时概览，使您能够立即发现问题并根据您的需求进行自定义。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;根本原因问题：&lt;/strong&gt;查找性能瓶颈。某些操作是否会减慢速度？识别他们。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意异常情况。突然的峰值或下降是红色警报。它们经常发出必须解决的问题的信号。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;测试：&lt;/strong&gt;最后，跟踪一段时间内的趋势。情况是在改善还是在变得更糟？这将指导您的长期战略。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;外卖&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借助正确的工具和策略，您可以最大限度地发挥数据价值、减少停机时间并提高整体运营效率。主动管理遥测可以将混乱的数据变得清晰和更明智的决策。也就是说，您可以利用遥测的力量释放系统的全部潜力。因此，精心设计的数据管道是将原始信息转化为改变游戏规则的见解的关键。 如需更多见解，请直接与 Ranjan Parthasarathy 联系，请随时通过 &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ranjanparth&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; 或 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ranjanparthasarathy.com&#34; 联系我们。 linkedin.com/in/ranjanp/&#34;&gt;LinkedIn，&lt;/a&gt; 或在&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apica.io/&#34;&gt;网站&lt;/a&gt;上探索有关 Apica 可观测性解决方案的更多信息。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubestronaut in Orbit: Maria Salcedo】在轨宇航员：玛丽亚·萨尔塞多</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/22/kubestronaut-in-orbit-maria-salcedo/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1650&#34; height=&#34;866&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;kubestronaut image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-119379&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2.jpg 1650w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-300x157.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-1024x537.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-388x204.jpg 388w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-776x408.jpg 776w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-1552x816.jpg 1552w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-900x472.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-381x200.jpg 381w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-762x400.jpg 762w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-590x310.jpg 590w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-1180x620.jpg 1180w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 1650px) 100vw, 1650px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get to know Maria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This week’s Kubestronaut in Orbit, Maria Salcedo, is a full stack DevOps backend engineer in Germany with experience in cloud native Kubernetes deployments. Maria is passionate about GitOps, cloud native development of CI/CD pipelines, IaC automation, and open source software.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to be a Kubestronaut like Maria, get more details on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/&#34;&gt;CNCF Kubestronaut&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When did you get started with Kubernetes and/or cloud-native? What was your first project?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I started first using containers in 2017 as a backend engineer, deploying through a Jenkins server. Back then, I wasn’t part of the infrastructure team, so I didn’t have access to the K8s server. However my curiosity led me to create a tiny playground to see what an end-to-end solution would look like. Gradually, as I joined new projects, I went deeper into K8s and infrastructure as code. I approached this cautiously –as K8s evolved side-by-side with the CNCF ecosystem, I saw the potential to eventually safely onboard it in highly productive environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the primary CNCF projects you work on or use today?&amp;nbsp; What projects have you enjoyed the most in your career?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the CNCF Landscape, the primary ones that I’ve enjoyed the most are (in no particular order): &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/flux/&#34;&gt;FluxCD&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/linkerd/&#34;&gt;Linkerd&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/istio/&#34;&gt;Istio&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/prometheus/&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/Jaeger/&#34;&gt;Jaeger,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/OpenTelemetry/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/quarkusio&#34;&gt;Quarkus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gradle&#34;&gt;Gradle&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/postgres/&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/kyverno/&#34;&gt;Kyverno&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ansible&#34;&gt;Ansible&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hashicorp/terraform&#34;&gt;Terraform&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/containers/podman&#34;&gt;Podman&lt;/a&gt;, and of course, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/kubernetes/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How have the certs or CNCF helped you in your career?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Highly automated environments sometimes lead us to miss some feature details that might be important to consider. More so on security, it is extremely important to be aware of what’s currently being offered, what gets deprecated, and what are indeed the best practices to follow. For that, continuous learning must be a top priority in our careers as software developers, and one tool to “push” you to get better are certificates. For that, I find the certs very useful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It might sound obvious, but without CNCF we would have no CI/CD pipelines, GitOps, IaC, Monitoring, Storage Management, or Service Mesh solutions. Kubernetes without them is like farming with a fork instead of a tractor. I cannot imagine deploying new features and keeping track of multiple handmade productive clusters without the help provided by CNCF supported projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are some other books/sites/courses you recommend for people who want to work with k8s?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many YouTube channels have very good videos explaining the very basics. I 100% recommend watching YouTube videos to validate your knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you assess your skill level, you can see how far you wanna go. For instance, get your own little playground started. Most, if not all, cloud providers offer free credits, which can be used for learning purposes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some other knowledge sources can be found at The Linux Foundation online courses. I recommend &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/kubernetes-for-developers/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes for Developers (LFD259)&lt;/a&gt; in particular. You will get your money’s worth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KodeKloud also offers some courses. Those courses are focused on the K8s certificates. I haven’t done them myself, however the community speaks well about their impact, and how clear their explanations are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aside from K8s, there is so much more you can learn, such as deployments, pipeline automation, monitoring, etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitOps, Infra as Code, and automation are as important as the very basics of K8s, for building a proper production-ready setup. For that, I recommend checking the &lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;CNCF Landscape&lt;/a&gt; page to find tools for it. At a project’s repository, tutorials and examples are usually offered to learn how to implement it in a more interactive way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you do in your free time?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I enjoy nature while hiking. It allows my brain to relax and reflect on what happened during the week.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What would you tell someone who is just starting their K8s certification journey? Any tips or tricks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For beginners, it pretty much depends where you are starting, so assessing your knowledge plays a big role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself questions such as: How much experience do you have using Docker and containers overall? Have you ever logged into a Kubernetes cluster before? If so, was it self managed or installed “from scratch”? Are you dealing with GitOps and Infrastructure as Code?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many people underestimate their beginner knowledge, because you probably know many things about Kubernetes just by using some of their components on a day to day basis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Today the Cloud native ecosystem is way more than Kubernetes. Do you plan to get other cloud native certifications from the CNCF ?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course! I am interested in both the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/pca/&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; (PCA) and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cca/&#34;&gt;Cilium &lt;/a&gt;(CCA) certifications, as well as the Linux Foundation’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/linux-foundation-certified-sysadmin-lfcs/&#34;&gt;Sysadmin&lt;/a&gt; (LFCS) and &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/certified-gitops-associate-cgoa/&#34;&gt;GitOps&lt;/a&gt; (CGOA) certs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1650”高度=“866”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;kubetronaut 图像&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-119379&#34; srcset =“https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2.jpg 1650w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/ uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-300x157.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-1024x537.jpg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads /2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-194x102.jpg 194w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads /2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-388x204.jpg 388w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-776x408.jpg 776w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads /2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-1552x816.jpg 1552w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-900x472.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads /2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-381x200.jpg 381w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-762x400.jpg 762w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads /2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-590x310.jpg 590w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Kubestronaut-in-Orbit-1-2-1180x620.jpg 1180w“尺寸=”（最大宽度：1650px）100vw，1650px“引用策略=“无引用者”&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;了解玛丽亚&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本周 Orbit 的 Kubetronaut Maria Salcedo 是德国的一名全栈 DevOps 后端工程师，拥有云原生 Kubernetes 部署经验。 Maria 热衷于 GitOps、CI/CD 管道的云原生开发、IaC 自动化和开源软件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您想成为像 Maria 一样的 Kubestronaut，请在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/&#34;&gt;CNCF Kubestronaut&lt;/a&gt; 页面获取更多详细信息。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您什么时候开始使用 Kubernetes 和/或云原生？您的第一个项目是什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我于 2017 年作为后端工程师首次使用容器，通过 Jenkins 服务器进行部署。当时，我不是基础设施团队的一员，所以我无法访问 K8s 服务器。然而，我的好奇心促使我创建了一个小型游乐场，以了解端到端解决方案是什么样子。渐渐地，随着我加入新项目，我更深入地了解了 K8s 和基础设施即代码。我谨慎地对待这个问题——随着 K8s 与 CNCF 生态系统并肩发展，我看到了最终在高生产力环境中安全使用它的潜力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您目前从事或使用的主要 CNCF 项目是什么？  在您的职业生涯中您最喜欢哪些项目？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来自 CNCF 景观，我最喜欢的主要景观最多的是（排名不分先后）：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/flux/&#34;&gt;FluxCD&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf. io/projects/linkerd/&#34;&gt;Linkerd&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/istio/&#34;&gt;Istio&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https:// www.cncf.io/projects/prometheus/&#34;&gt;普罗米修斯&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https:// www.cncf.io/projects/Jaeger/&#34;&gt;Jaeger，&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/OpenTelemetry/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34; https://github.com/quarkusio&#34;&gt;Quarkus&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gradle&#34;&gt;Gradle&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github. com/postgres/&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/kyverno/&#34;&gt;Kyverno&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/postgres/&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/kyverno/&#34;&gt;Kyverno&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github. com/ansible&#34;&gt;Ansible&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hashicorp/terraform&#34;&gt;Terraform&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/containers/ podman&#34;&gt;Podman&lt;/a&gt;，当然还有 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/kubernetes/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;证书或 CNCF 对您的职业生涯有何帮助？ &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;高度自动化的环境有时会导致我们错过一些可能需要考虑的重要功能细节。更重要的是，在安全性方面，了解当前提供的内容、已弃用的内容以及确实要遵循的最佳实践是什么是极其重要的。为此，持续学习必须成为我们作为软件开发人员职业生涯中的首要任务，而“推动”你变得更好的工具之一就是证书。为此，我发现证书非常有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这听起来似乎很明显，但如果没有 CNCF，我们就不会有 CI/CD 管道、GitOps、IaC、监控、存储管理或服务网格解决方案。没有它们的 Kubernetes 就像用叉子而不是拖拉机耕作。我无法想象如果没有 CNCF 支持项目提供的帮助，部署新功能并跟踪多个手工制作的生产集群。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您为想要使用 k8s 的人推荐了哪些其他书籍/网站/课程？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多 YouTube 频道都有非常好的视频来解释基本知识。我 100% 建议您观看 YouTube 视频来验证您的知识。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦您评估了自己的技能水平，您就可以看到自己想要走多远。例如，开始你自己的小游乐场。大多数（如果不是全部）云提供商都提供免费积分，可用于学习目的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其他一些知识来源可以在 Linux 基金会在线课程中找到。我特别推荐&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/kubernetes-for-developers/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes for Developers (LFD259)&lt;/a&gt;。你会得到你的钱的价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KodeKloud 还提供一些课程。这些课程主要针对 K8s 证书。我自己没有做过这些，但是社区很好地谈论了它们的影响以及它们的解释是多么清晰。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了K8s，还有很多东西你可以学到n，例如部署、管道自动化、监控等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于构建适当的生产就绪设置，GitOps、基础设施即代码和自动化与 K8s 的基础知识一样重要。为此，我建议检查 &lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;CNCF Landscape&lt;/a&gt; 页面来查找相关工具。在项目的存储库中，通常会提供教程和示例来学习如何以更具交互性的方式实现它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;你空闲时间做什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我在徒步旅行时享受大自然。它让我的大脑放松并反思这一周发生的事情。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您会对刚刚开始 K8s 认证之旅的人说些什么？有什么提示或技巧吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于初学者来说，这很大程度上取决于您从哪里开始，因此评估您的知识起着重要作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;问自己这样的问题：您总体上有多少使用 Docker 和容器的经验？您以前登录过 Kubernetes 集群吗？如果是，是自行管理还是“从头开始”安装？您正在处理 GitOps 和基础设施即代码吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多人低估了他们的初学者知识，因为您可能仅通过日常使用 Kubernetes 的一些组件就了解了有关 Kubernetes 的许多知识。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;如今，云原生生态系统远远超出了 Kubernetes。您是否计划获得 CNCF 的其他云原生认证？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当然！我对 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/pca/&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; (PCA) 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf .io/training/certification/cca/&#34;&gt;Cilium &lt;/a&gt;(CCA) 认证，以及 Linux 基金会的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/linux-foundation-certified- sysadmin-lfcs/&#34;&gt;Sysadmin&lt;/a&gt; (LFCS) 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/certified-gitops-associate-cgoa/&#34;&gt;GitOps&lt;/a&gt; (CGOA)证书。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Don’t miss The Project Pavillion at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024】不要错过 2024 年 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 的项目展馆</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/24/dont-miss-the-project-pavillion-at-kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2024/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;By Jorge Castro, Developer Relations at CNCF&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/project-engagement/#project-pavilion&#34;&gt;The Project Pavilion&lt;/a&gt; is our dedicated space on the show floor for CNCF Projects. Since there are over 200 projects this can make the Pavilion a rapidly changing landscape, so projects shift in and out in the mornings and afternoons. You will want to drop by often!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Its purpose is to act as a direct means for attendees to interact with CNCF Projects. Additionally, it acts as our rallying point for CNCF Maintainers and Ambassadors. We want to create a mix of creators, consumers, and advocates, and we all wear our ”upstream hats.” There’s no commercial selling in the Project Pavilion; it’s an open invitation for everyone to actively participate in open source so that they can &lt;em&gt;understand&lt;/em&gt; how open source works. If you’ve been to a farmer’s market before, it’s like that, but for software.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the projects, it’s their chance to show off the things they work on and share, as well as give introductory material to attendees. For end users, it offers a “live R&amp;amp;D lab”, where they can check in on the projects that they depend on and support, but also dip their toes into the CNCF Sandbox and see what all the “cool kids” are into.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Attendees get the best benefits because KubeCon + CloudNativeCon can be so overwhelming, especially for new folks. If you ask someone who has been to many of them they will commonly say that the “hallway track” is where it is at. We wanted to revitalize the Pavilion to be the place where new attendees can start their journey, by directly interacting with the projects and maintainers to get a grasp of the big picture. A CNCF Ambassador is usually close by to help out because it’s always better when you have a guide with you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are technically minded and want direct access to CNCF Contributors, then the Pavilion is the place to find them. If you want to get right into the weeds then this is where you want to be. We’ve got plenty of space and power for you to break off and do focused hacking, or just hang out and get to know each other.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get ready for KubeCon with Project Lightning Talks!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Project Lightning talks are a great way to get ready for KCCNC. Since they are the day before and the show floor is closed they are a good primer. Each project does a 7 minute presentation. You can find the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;full schedule here&lt;/a&gt;, and as always, we record each one.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And we have two fabulous new hosts, Lori Lorusso and Katherine Druckman, who will be doing the introduction and covering it via the “&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/event/1iW8A/welcome-and-introduction-a-hitchhikers-guide-to-the-cncf-landscape-katherine-druckman-and-lori-lorusso-cncf-ambassador?iframe=no&amp;amp;w=100%&amp;amp;sidebar=yes&amp;amp;bg=no&#34;&gt;Hitchhiker’s Guide to the CNCF Landscape&lt;/a&gt;.” We strongly recommend this session to new attendees so that you can have a good idea of what you are heading into before the show floor opens up.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image aligncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXe2NVJOYrONp6SmdSdVLvsud5KO2ihU-kNtb8Ta94Sx3D_uKkoXxr61BqyzjvQWvXHKTpC4q8VR-8XJGYNR8FeqUzeTF-WPMAIZT1L_chR5kMS_3gJfv8ThDAxWWGtQsUp_nzDk8Q3G63PW1QDm-nrurTGA?key=M43r7CqKyuJ4H4Fv4uOzgg&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Lori Lorusso &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image aligncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc4pthx-E9fe6usZxuEbHEAFYnyAxg3l3CsAAqT2mE0EocDUqOIuiwXJxoe5qgNCqJplyUbcZ4blYS4v5RLi2YObT1kXCsGczGI11YJQPa40QpR2AmCwIHURJE4_7RD79DM8QglZt0JJEQQyGEZypqGJv5c?key=M43r7CqKyuJ4H4Fv4uOzgg&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Katherine Druckman&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s new at this Project Pavilion?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After you’ve gotten your initial orientation at the Lighting Talks you can come check out the new things at the Pavilion. This year we added an entire stage with screens and plenty of seating. This stage is available exclusively for CNCF Maintainers to run additional demos and talks throughout the day, right next to the Pavilion. There will likely be a demo every 20 minutes throughout Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We purposely run this one as a bit of an unconference. These talks aren’t on the schedule and provide attendees a chance to experience what happens when open source maintainers speak passionately about their projects “live.” This is our first time trying this, and we strongly recommend stopping by for at least some of the talks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And this year we’re happy to partner with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.unifiedpatents.com/&#34;&gt;Unified Patents&lt;/a&gt;, which will be running office hours and sessions throughout the week educating people about the importance of invalidating bad software patents. They will even show you how to search for prior art and we’ll be announcing a contest with prizes pretty soon!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t forget to take a tour!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year we also added more tours by CNCF Ambassadors. Tours will be running daily and there will be a “safari tour” of the CNCF Landscape. They run Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday and you can find them on &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;this section of the schedule&lt;/a&gt;. This is also the first time we’ve run this and the Ambassadors are already excited to show you what’s out there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This gives attendees an option to have someone with cloud native experience walk them through the myriad of options available, give them guidance, and help them connect with the projects and people that are important to know. This one is also a strong recommendation for new attendees!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First-timers, this one’s for you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If it’s your first KubeCon this is a great place to start. We see cloud native as a vast ecosystem of projects and people, all looking for opportunities to learn something new. Come with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shoshin&#34;&gt;beginner’s mind &lt;/a&gt;and leave plenty of room for stickers in your bag!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come for the Projects, stay for the caffeine, couches, and stickers!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Project Pavilion is ideally positioned in the middle of the show floor. We have the best couches in the conference center and we’re close to caffeine and the bathrooms. The hugely popular sticker dispensers will be returning, as will our job board and everything is centrally located.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our hope is that you see the Pavilion as a lens right into the cloud native ecosystem, not just to observe but to participate and meet the people who are waiting to work with you! A CNCF Ambassador, Maintainer, or Staffer is almost always an arm’s length away to help guide you. We’ll see you there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;作者：CNCF 开发者关系部 Jorge Castro&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/project-engagement/#project-pavilion&#34;&gt;项目馆&lt;/a&gt;是我们的专用空间CNCF 项目展示厅。由于有超过 200 个项目，这会使展馆成为一个快速变化的景观，因此项目会在早上和下午进出。您会想经常过来！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其目的是作为与会者与 CNCF 项目互动的直接方式。此外，它还是 CNCF 维护者和大使的集结点。我们希望打造一个由创作者、消费者和倡导者组成的组合，我们都戴着“上游帽子”。项目馆内不进行任何商业销售；这是对每个人积极参与开源的公开邀请，以便他们能够&lt;em&gt;理解&lt;/em&gt;开源是如何运作的。如果你以前去过农贸市场，那就是这样，只不过是买软件。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于这些项目，他们有机会展示自己所做的工作和分享的内容，以及向与会者提供介绍性材料。对于最终用户来说，它提供了一个“实时研发实验室”，他们可以在这里检查他们依赖和支持的项目，还可以深入 CNCF 沙箱，看看所有“酷孩子”都在做什么。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与会者可以获得最大的好处，因为 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 可能会让人难以抗拒，尤其是对于新人来说。如果你问去过很多地方的人，他们通常会说“走廊轨道”就是它所在的地方。我们希望振兴展馆，使其成为新与会者可以开始他们的旅程的地方，通过直接与项目和维护人员互动来了解全局。 CNCF 大使通常会在附近提供帮助，因为有向导陪伴总是更好。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您有技术头脑并希望直接接触 CNCF 贡献者，那么展馆就是找到他们的地方。如果你想直接进入杂草，那么这就是你想去的地方。我们有足够的空间和力量供您休息并进行集中的黑客攻击，或者只是闲逛并相互了解。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;通过 Project Lightning Talks 为 KubeCon 做好准备！&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;闪电计划演讲是为 KCCNC 做好准备的好方法。由于它们是在前一天进行的，而且展厅已关闭，因此它们是很好的入门读物。每个项目都有 7 分钟的演示。您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;此处找到完整的时间表&lt;/a&gt;，并且一如既往，我们记录了每一个时间表。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们有两位出色的新主持人，洛里·洛鲁索 (Lori Lorusso) 和凯瑟琳·德鲁克曼 (Katherine Druckman)，他们将通过“&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/event/1iW8A/welcome-”进行介绍和报道。和-introduction-a-hitchhikers-guide-to-the-cncf-landscape-katherine-druckman-and-lori-lorusso-cncf-ambassador?iframe=no&amp;w=100%&amp;sidebar=yes&amp;bg=no&#34;&gt;CNCF 景观搭便车指南&lt;/a&gt;”。我们强烈向新与会者推荐此会议，以便您可以在展会开放之前清楚地了解自己将要做什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-imagealigncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXe2NVJOYrONp6SmdSdVLvsud5KO2ihU-kNtb8Ta94Sx3D_uKkoXxr61BqyzjvQWvXHKTpC4q8VR-8XJGYNR8Feq UzeTF-WPMAIZT1L_chR5kMS_3gJfv8ThDAxWWGtQsUp_nzDk8Q3G63PW1QDm-nrurTGA?key=M43r7CqKyuJ4H4Fv4uOzgg &#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;洛里·洛鲁索 &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-imagealigncenter&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc4pthx-E9fe6usZxuEbHEAFYnyAxg3l3CsAAqT2mE0EocDUqOIuiwXJxoe5qgNCqJplyUbcZ4blYS4v5RLi2YObT1kXC sGczGI11YJQPa40QpR2AmCwIHURJE4_7RD79DM8QglZt0JJEQQyGEZypqGJv5c?key=M43r7CqKyuJ4H4Fv4uOzgg&#34; alt=&#34;图像&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;凯瑟琳·德鲁克曼&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;该项目展馆有哪些新内容？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在灯光讲座中初步了解情况后，您可以来展馆看看新事物。今年，我们增加了整个舞台，配有屏幕和充足的座位。该舞台专供 CNCF 维护人员在展馆旁边全天运行额外的演示和讲座。周三、周四和周五可能每 20 分钟就有一次演示。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们特意将这次会议当作一次非正式会议。这些演讲并未列入日程，但为与会者提供了体验当开源维护者“现场”热情谈论他们的项目时会发生什么的机会。这是我们第一次尝试这一点，我们强烈建议至少停下来参加一些会谈。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年我们很高兴与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.unifiedpatents.com/&#34;&gt;Unified Patents&lt;/a&gt; 合作，该组织将在一周内举办办公时间和会议，以教育人们关于使不良软件专利无效的重要性。他们甚至会向您展示如何搜索现有技术，我们很快就会宣布举办有奖竞赛！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;别忘了参观一下！&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年我们还增加了更多 CNCF 大使的游览活动。每天都有游览活动，并将有 CNCF 景观的“游猎之旅”。它们在周三、周四和周五运行，您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;时间表的这一部分&lt;/一个&gt;。这也是我们第一次开展此活动，大使们已经很高兴向您展示其中的内容。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这使与会者可以选择让具有云原生经验的人引导他们了解无数可用的选项，为他们提供指导，并帮助他们与重要的项目和人员建立联系。这也是对新与会者的强烈推荐！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;新手，这个适合你&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果这是您第一次参加 KubeCon，这是一个很好的起点。我们将云原生视为一个由项目和人员组成的庞大生态系统，所有人都在寻找学习新知识的机会。带着&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shoshin&#34;&gt;初学者的心态&lt;/a&gt;来，并在包里留出足够的空间来放置贴纸！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;来参加项目，留下来享受咖啡因、沙发和贴纸！&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;项目馆地理位置优越，位于展厅中央。我们的会议中心拥有最好的沙发，而且靠近咖啡因和浴室。广受欢迎的贴纸分配器将回归，我们的工作板和所有东西都位于中心位置。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们希望您将Pavilion视为进入云原生生态系统的一个镜头，不仅可以观察，还可以参与并会见那些等待与您合作的人！ CNCF 大使、维护人员或工作人员几乎总是在一臂之遥之外为您提供帮助指导。我们在那里见！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s new at this year’s KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024】今年 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 的新增内容</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/24/whats-new-at-this-years-kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2024/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We have many exciting new events happening in this Salt Lake City KubeCon, as well as a number of unique &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/&#34;&gt;Experiences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, and we don’t want you to miss anything. Here’s everything you need to know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, if you haven’t registered yet, &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/?utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=paid-search&amp;amp;utm_campaign=kubecon-na-2024&amp;amp;utm_term=events-kubecon-na-2024-cncf&amp;amp;utm_content=kubecon-na_rsa&amp;amp;campaignid=21541954784&amp;amp;adgroupid=166431838780&amp;amp;creative=708046449585&amp;amp;matchtype=p&amp;amp;network=g&amp;amp;device=c&amp;amp;keyword=kubecon%20salt%20lake%20city&amp;amp;utm_term=kubecon%20salt%20lake%20city&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Events+-+KubeCon+NA+2024+-+CNCF&amp;amp;utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=ppc&amp;amp;hsa_acc=8666746580&amp;amp;hsa_cam=21541954784&amp;amp;hsa_grp=166431838780&amp;amp;hsa_ad=708046449585&amp;amp;hsa_src=g&amp;amp;hsa_tgt=kwd-2334017742870&amp;amp;hsa_kw=kubecon%20salt%20lake%20city&amp;amp;hsa_mt=p&amp;amp;hsa_net=adwords&amp;amp;hsa_ver=3&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAAD2R-lpx0js_GAcAytzQO9oVMbUWq&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwmt24BhDPARIsAJFYKk1jSAymN6KzP2PTXiUWVpmjJmmsUWYcnRr-h8dy3dxW3qWu5WVpDlEaAt8SEALw_wcB&#34;&gt;it’s not too late&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s start with what’s new this year:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Donate an old laptop and help two great causes!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re hosting &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/laptop-drive/#donate-your-old-laptop-for-a-good-cause&#34;&gt;a laptop drive&lt;/a&gt; during this year’s KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 that will benefit two non-profits in the tech space: Black Girls Code and Kids on Computers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wearebgc.org/&#34;&gt;Black Girls Code&lt;/a&gt; wants to show black girls ages 7 to 17 that they belong in tech and offers workshops, day camps, hackathons and other courses. They utilize laptops in their programming.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kidsoncomputers.org/&#34;&gt;Kids on Computers&lt;/a&gt; is an all-volunteer group that provides computer labs to low-income schools to ensure all kids are computer literate. The group uses both donated and new hardware.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order to donate your laptop, make sure it meets the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/laptop-drive/#device-requirements&#34;&gt;device requirements&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/laptop-drive/#data-wiping-instructions&#34;&gt;wipe the data&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSf3VqEznVLmQevrAMIrkkH59xMlzMW74zcnh1GIQTvHK6Gz_g/viewform&#34;&gt;fill out the form&lt;/a&gt;, and then you can drop it off at the Coat and Bag Check area of the Salt Lake City Convention Center during KubeCon + CloudNativeCon during the following hours:&lt;br&gt;Tuesday November 12 – 7:30am – 7:00pm&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wednesday November 13 – 7:30am – 8:00pm&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thursday November 14 – 8:00am – 6:00pm&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Friday November 15 – 8:00am – 11:00am&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t miss the new DEI Community Hub&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The DEI Community Hub is an exciting new space to connect, learn, and celebrate diversity, equity, and inclusion and accessibility! Join community groups, participate in allyship and advocacy workshops, or simply relax in a safe space during open lounge hours.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Talk software supply chains with the Public Sector User Group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Attend a BoF session with the Public Sector User Group and take a deep dive into software supply chains and how to integrate Sigstore and in-toto to meet global government needs. Get &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/event/1nBx4&#34;&gt;all the details&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go Inside Argo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss the world premiere of &lt;em&gt;Inside Argo: Automating the Future&lt;/em&gt;, a documentary set in 2017 that follows the project teams as they develop and launch Argo and the suite of tools around it. If you need a visual embodiment of the spirit of innovation and collaboration in the world of open source, Inside Argo will give you just that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#inside-argo-a-documentary-film-world-premiere&#34;&gt;The film&lt;/a&gt; debuts on Thursday November 14 at 6:15 at the Salt Lake City Convention Center, Salt Palace, Level 2, room 254.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Add these Experiences to your schedule:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the KubeCrawl + CloudNativeFest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday November 13 from 6pm to 8pm, plan to attend the launch party in the Solutions Showcase where you can enjoy local seasonal treats and drinks while exploring sponsor booths, being entertained, and even taking a “ski lift” photo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activation Zones&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understand the differences between malware and vulnerabilities – sponsored by Sonatype – and then pop into the Open Telemetry Observatory powered by Splunk where you can relax, power up, and talk all things OTel. These opportunities will be available in the Solution Showcase Wednesday through Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sign up for a new headshot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Coder is offering attendees the opportunity to get a new professional headshot, but you have to &lt;a href=&#34;https://calendly.com/cncf-photography-headshots/coder?month=2024-11&#34;&gt;sign up in advance here&lt;/a&gt; and space is limited!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep Cloud Native Well&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss the many, many options to keep your body and mind healthy and happy during KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024. From petting a therapy dog to &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/attend/cncf-ombudsperson-mediator/&#34;&gt;meeting with a wellbeing coach&lt;/a&gt;, getting a chair massage, self-led runs and recharges with pure oxygen, make sure to schedule some time to decompress. Find &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#keep-cloud-native-well&#34;&gt;all the available options&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tour the Project Pavilion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to see what cloud native literally looks like? There’s no better place than the Project Pavilion where you can see CNCF’s 200 projects in action and interact with maintainers, CNCF staffers and more. &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;Guided tours run daily&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capture the Flag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re brand new to CTF or well-versed, join us in the Salt Palace on Level 2 in Room 255A for three increasingly difficult and treacherous capture the flag scenarios. Beginners can take one of two introductory workshops (&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/event/1kGDV&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/event/1kGCI&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;) on Wednesday November 13, then jump in fully on Thursday the 14th beginning at 11am. Explore &lt;a href=&#34;https://controlplaneio.github.io/kubecon-na-2024-ctf/&#34;&gt;all the details&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the End User Reception&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday November 13 from 6pm to 8pm, meet and greet other end users at the Hyatt Regency’s Broadcast Lounge on Level 4. Expect food, beverages, networking &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#cncf-end-user-reception&#34;&gt;and more&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience a ClashLoopBackOff (CLBO)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also on November 13, meet at the Project Pavilion in the Solutions Showcase at 6:30pm to watch two people solve a tricky technical problem in just a very limited amount of time and with no advanced knowledge or preparation. Be prepared to be on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#clbo-clashloopbackoff&#34;&gt;edge of your seats&lt;/a&gt;!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes SIG Meet and Greet Lunch and Learn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grab your lunch and come meet other new and experienced K8s contributors and find out how to &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#kubernetes-sig-meet-and-greet-lunch-and-learn&#34;&gt;expand your participation in SIGs and WGs&lt;/a&gt;. The event will take place in the Project Pavilion on November 14 from 12:30pm – 2:30pm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们在盐湖城 KubeCon 上举办了许多激动人心的新活动，以及许多独特的&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/ program/experiences/&#34;&gt;体验&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;，我们不希望您错过任何内容。这是您需要了解的所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，如果您尚未注册，&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/?utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=paid-search&amp;utm_campaign=kubecon-na-2024&amp;utm_term =events-kubecon-na-2024-cncf&amp;utm_content=kubecon-na_rsa&amp;campaignid=21541954784&amp;adgroupid=166431838780&amp;creative=708046449585&amp;matchtype=p&amp;network=g&amp;device=c&amp;keyword=kubecon%20salt%20lake%20city&amp;utm_term=ku becon%20salt%20lake%20city&amp;utm_campaign=活动+-+KubeCon+NA+ 2024+-+CNCF&amp;utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=ppc&amp;hsa_acc=8666746580&amp;hsa_cam=21541954784&amp;hsa_grp=166431838780&amp;hsa_ad=708046449585&amp;hsa_src=g&amp;hsa_tgt=kwd-2334017 742870&amp;hsa_kw=kubecon%20salt%20lake%20city&amp;hsa_mt=p&amp;hsa_net=adwords&amp;hsa_ver=3&amp;gad_source=1&amp;gbraid=0AAAAD2R-lpx0js_GAcAytzQO9oVMbUWq&amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjwmt24BhDPARISAJFYKk1 jSAymN6KzP2PTXiUWVpmjJmmsUWYcnRr-h8dy3dxW3qWu5WVpDlEaAt8SEALw_wcB&#34;&gt;它是还不算太晚&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们从今年的新变化开始：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;捐赠一台旧笔记本电脑并帮助两项伟大事业！&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在托管&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/laptop-drive/#donate-your-old-laptop-for-a-good -cause&#34;&gt;今年的 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 期间推出的笔记本电脑驱动器&lt;/a&gt;将使科技领域的两个非营利组织受益：Black Girls Code 和 Kids on Computers。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wearebgc.org/&#34;&gt;Black Girls Code&lt;/a&gt; 希望向 7 至 17 岁的黑人女孩展示她们属于科技行业，并提供研讨会、日间营、黑客马拉松和其他课程。他们在编程中使用笔记本电脑。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kidsoncomputers.org/&#34;&gt;Kids on Computers&lt;/a&gt; 是一个全志愿者团体，为低收入学校提供计算机实验室，以确保所有孩子都具备计算机知识。该小组使用捐赠的硬件和新硬件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了捐赠您的笔记本电脑，请确保它符合&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/laptop-drive/#device-requirements&#34;&gt;设备要求&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/laptop-drive/#data-wiping-instructions&#34;&gt;擦除数据&lt;/a &gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSf3VqEznVLmQevrAMIrkkH59xMlzMW74zcnh1GIQTvHK6Gz_g/viewform&#34;&gt;填写表单&lt;/a&gt;，然后您可以将其交给外套和行李寄存处KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 期间盐湖城会议中心区域以下时间：&lt;br&gt;11 月 12 日星期二 – 上午 7:30 – 晚上 7:00&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;11 月 13 日星期三 – 上午 7:30 – 晚上 8:00&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;11 月 14 日星期四 – 上午 8:00 – 下午 6:00&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;11 月 15 日星期五 – 上午 8:00 – 上午 11:00&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;不要错过新的 DEI 社区中心&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DEI 社区中心是一个令人兴奋的新空间，可以用来联系、学习和庆祝多样性、公平性、包容性和可访问性！加入社区团体，参加联盟和宣传研讨会，或者只是在开放休息室时间在安全的空间中放松身心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;与公共部门用户组讨论软件供应链&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;参加 BoF 与公共部门用户组的会议，深入探讨软件供应链以及如何集成 Sigstore 和 in-toto 以满足全球政府需求。获取&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/event/1nBx4&#34;&gt;所有详细信息&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;进入Argo内部&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不要错过《Inside Argo：自动化未来》的全球首映，这是一部以 2017 年为背景的纪录片，讲述了项目团队开发和推出 Argo 及其相关工具套件的过程。如果您需要开源世界中创新与协作精神的视觉体现，Inside Argo 将为您提供。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#inside-argo-a-documentary-film-world-premiere&#34;&gt;这部电影&lt;/ a&gt; 将于 11 月 14 日星期四 6:15 在盐湖城会议中心盐宫 2 层 254 室首次亮相。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将这些体验添加到您的日程中：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加入 KubeCrawl + CloudNativeFest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;11 月 13 日星期三下午 6 点至晚上 8 点，计划参加解决方案展示会的发布会，您可以在探索赞助商展位、享受娱乐甚至拍摄“滑雪缆车”照片的同时享受当地时令美食和饮料。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;激活区域&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解恶意软件和漏洞之间的差异（由 Sonatype 赞助），然后进入由 Splunk 提供支持的开放遥测观测站，在这里您可以放松、启动并谈论 OTel 的所有事情。这些机会将在周三至周五的解决方案展示中提供。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注册新头像&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Coder 为与会者提供获得新专业头像的机会，但您必须&lt;a href=&#34;https://calendly.com/cncf-photography-headshots/coder?month=2024-11&#34;&gt;注册提前在此&lt;/a&gt;，空间有限！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;保持云原生良好&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不要错过 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North Ame 期间保持身心健康和快乐的众多选择2024 年黎加。从抚摸治疗犬到&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/attend/cncf-ombudsperson-mediator/&#34;&gt;与健康教练会面&lt;/a &gt;、享受椅子按摩、自主跑步和纯氧充电，确保安排一些时间减压。查找&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#keep-cloud-native-well&#34;&gt;所有可用选项&lt;/a&gt;。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;参观项目馆&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想看看云原生到底是什么样子吗？没有比项目展馆更好的地方了，在这里您可以看到 CNCF 的 200 个项目正在运行，并与维护人员、CNCF 工作人员等进行互动。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/schedule/&#34;&gt;每天都有导游&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;夺旗&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是 CTF 新手还是老手，都可以加入我们的盐宫 2 层 255A 房间，体验三个日益困难和危险的夺旗场景。初学者可以参加两个介绍性研讨会之一（&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/event/1kGDV&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/ event/1kGCI&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;）将于 11 月 13 日星期三举行，然后于 14 日星期四上午 11 点开始全面投入。探索&lt;a href=&#34;https://controlplaneio.github.io/kubecon-na-2024-ctf/&#34;&gt;所有详细信息&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加入最终用户接待会&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;11 月 13 日星期三下午 6 点至晚上 8 点，在凯悦酒店 4 楼的广播休息室与其他最终用户见面并打招呼。期待食物、饮料、社交&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon -cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#cncf-end-user-reception&#34;&gt;还有更多&lt;/a&gt;！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;体验 ClashLoopBackOff (CLBO)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同样在 11 月 13 日下午 6:30 在解决方案展示的项目展馆见面，观看两个人在非常有限的时间内解决棘手的技术问题，并且没有任何高级知识或准备。准备好&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#clbo-clashloopbackoff&#34;&gt;坐在座位边缘&lt;/a&gt;！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes SIG 见面会午餐和学习&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;吃完午餐，来会见其他新的和经验丰富的 K8s 贡献者，并了解如何&lt;a href=&#34;https://events.linuxfoundation.org/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america/program/experiences/#kubernetes- sig-meet-and-greet-lunch-and-learn&#34;&gt;扩大您对 SIG 和 WG 的参与&lt;/a&gt;。该活动将于 11 月 14 日中午 12:30 至下午 2:30 在项目展馆举行。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-样式-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Kubestronaut origin story】Kubetronaut 的起源故事</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/23/the-kubestronaut-origin-story/</link>
      <description>【&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;An interview with Ramesh Kumar&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A special thanks to one of our CNCF Ambassadors, Ramesh Kumar for inspiring us to create the Kubestronaut program. We recently interviewed Ramesh to ask about how the Kubestronaut program came to be. If you’d like to be a Kubestronaut like Ramesh, get more details on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/&#34;&gt;CNCF Kubestronaut &lt;/a&gt;page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How did you come up with the Kubestronaut idea?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2017, CNCF released the Certified Kubernetes Administrator (CKA) exam. I was among the first few people to study day and night to pass it. It was an exhilarating journey filled with passion and excitement. The CKA exam lit a fire in me—it was unlike any other exam, being a hands-on, scenario-based challenge. That unique aspect made it thrilling. The following year, in 2018, came the Certified Kubernetes Application Developer (CKAD) exam, which was just as exciting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A fun fact: the late and excellent Dan Kohn sponsored my CKA and CKAD exams. In 2019, during KubeCon San Diego, I hosted a roundtable QA session on certifications. Dan Kohn observed my enthusiasm and excitement and suggested I start a study group to help others, especially students, kickstart their Kubernetes careers and certification goals. That suggestion led to me becoming an author for several Kubernetes certification exams, starting many workgroups in the Sacramento area and a few online groups. I also launched a meetup for Kubernetes certifications and workshops like CKA/CKAD to help spread the word about CNCF and its incredible resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Around 2021, after taking and getting all upcoming Kubernetes certifications, I wanted to create something special for those who achieved CNCF and Kubernetes certifications—a program that would recognize their accomplishments and inspire and motivate others to set ambitious goals. I shared this idea with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/caniszczyk/&#34;&gt;Chris Aniszczyk&lt;/a&gt;, and he found it intriguing and worth implementing. The idea initially originated in November 2022 during KubeCon Detroit. It kept evolving for a while, and by February 2024, we had the perfect name: “Kubestronaut.” My journey deeply inspired the concept, where I often felt like an astronaut navigating&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes’s vast, uncharted territory. I wanted others to experience that same sense of exploration and discovery but with guidance and a supportive community to help them succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;799&#34; height=&#34;533&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ramesh at KubeCon&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-119416&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c.jpg 799w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c-300x200.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c-600x400.jpg 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 799px) 100vw, 799px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;Here I am at Kubecon NA 2019&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why did you think people would be so excited to be Kubestronauts?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Kubernetes community is one of the most dynamic and enthusiastic groups in tech. People are always eager to learn, contribute, push boundaries, and help others grow, encourage, and support one another. I’ve found many amazing mentors in this community and had the opportunity to be both a mentee and a mentor. This level of collaboration and growth is only possible with CNCF communities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Being a Kubestronaut is very special. It’s a sense of achievement, fulfillment, and inspiration. The Kubestronaut initiative is unique in its focus on Kubernetes/CNCF education, certifications, and fostering a sense of community among learners. Hands-on certifications like CKA, CKAD, and CKS, along with foundational exams like Kubernetes and Cloud Native Associate (KCNA) and Kubernetes and Cloud Security Associate (KCSA), provide learners with opportunities to deepen their knowledge across different levels and domains. These certifications help participants develop hands-on skills and theoretical understanding, supporting their personal and professional growth. By incorporating diverse certifications, the Kubestronaut initiative empowers individuals to build expertise in Kubernetes and cloud-native technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What else would you want people to know about the program?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Kubestronaut is a unique initiative focused on Kubernetes education, certification, and fostering a sense of community among learners. It is designed to be inclusive and community-driven, emphasizing growth through learning, collaboration, and mentorship. One of the program’s highlights is the opportunity to connect with experts in the field, exchange ideas, and be part of a global network of Kubernetes professionals. We aim to make Kubernetes more accessible and rewarding for anyone, whether just starting their cloud-native journey or advancing their existing skills.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF certifications and programs have a profound impact. For example, one of our community members, a chef with 18 years of experience, transitioned into the tech industry within 18 months by earning Kubernetes certifications. His journey is a powerful reminder of how these certifications can change lives. Programs like Kubestronaut and Kubernetes can inspire growth and open new opportunities, regardless of where you start.&amp;nbsp; I can’t wait to see how many more lives will be impacted through the Kubestronaut initiative. This initiative is about empowering everyone to reach their full potential.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the primary CNCF projects you work on or use today? What projects have you enjoyed the most in your career?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At&amp;nbsp; Apple, we always think big, whether it’s about scale or innovation. Currently, I work extensively with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/kubernetes/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;, which is central to my projects, particularly in managing cloud infrastructure at scale. I also engage with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/helm/&#34;&gt;Helm&lt;/a&gt; for package management, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/prometheus/&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; for monitoring, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; for dashboarding, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/flux&#34;&gt;Flux&lt;/a&gt; for continuous delivery (CD), and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/emissary-ingress&#34;&gt;Emissary Ingress&lt;/a&gt; (formerly known as Ambassador) for service proxies. These CNCF projects are fundamental to building and operating cloud-native architectures in my work. Managing applications requires a lot of standards and security enforcement, and I always take these aspects very seriously, ensuring they are handled with deep precision.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In terms of what I’ve enjoyed the most, Kubernetes has always been my passion. It’s a continuously evolving platform, and working with it has been incredibly rewarding. Prometheus and Grafana have been exciting to work with, mainly because of their robust monitoring capabilities and how they empower teams to gain real-time insights into their systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How have the certifications helped you in your career?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m a big believer in learning, training, and certifications because they provide a clear path, goal, and target. Certifications offer a structured roadmap, helping you gain deep knowledge in specific areas. While certifications may not make you a complete master in a subject, they provide a strong foundation and clear direction for continuous learning and growth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CNCF certifications— &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/kcna/&#34;&gt;KCNA&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cka/&#34;&gt;CKA&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/ckad/&#34;&gt;CKAD&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/kcsa/&#34;&gt;KCSA&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cks/&#34;&gt;CKS&lt;/a&gt; –&amp;nbsp; all have been pivotal in my career. These certifications validated my skills and pushed me to develop a deeper understanding of Kubernetes and cloud-native technologies. They helped me transition into roles where I could build, manage, and operate complex Kubernetes environments at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The certifications also opened doors for me to engage with the broader cloud-native community, participate in discussions, and collaborate on meaningful projects. More importantly, they gave me the confidence to share my knowledge with others, leading to my involvement in mentoring and creating educational programs like Kubestronaut. These certifications have played a key role in elevating my career, expanding my network, and connecting me with opportunities that align with my passion for Kubernetes and cloud-native technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;More about Ramesh&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/rk132&#34;&gt;Ramesh Kumar&lt;/a&gt; is a passionate advocate for cloud-native technologies with a deep background in Kubernetes and DevOps. Ramesh works at Apple as a Systems Architect, building and managing the next generation of cloud infrastructure and has had the opportunity to run and operate hundreds of applications from the ground up, ensuring they meet CNCF standards for cloud deployments. Over the years, he’s worked on various Kubernetes-related projects in education and hands-on enterprise-grade implementations. He’s also a teacher and enjoys mentoring others in navigating the rapidly evolving Kubernetes landscape. Ramesh is dedicated to fostering the communities that grow through shared learning and practical experiences. And he has a pretty unique email at Apple: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Kubernetes@apple.com&#34;&gt;Kubernetes@apple.com&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ramesh Kumar 访谈&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;特别感谢我们的一位 CNCF 大使 Ramesh Kumar 激励我们创建 Kubetronaut 计划。我们最近采访了 Ramesh，询问 Kubetronaut 计划是如何诞生的。如果您想成为像 Ramesh 一样的 Kubestronaut，请在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/&#34;&gt;CNCF Kubestronaut&lt;/a&gt; 页面获取更多详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您是如何想到 Kubetronaut 的想法的？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2017年，CNCF发布了Kubernetes管理员认证（CKA）考试。我是最早日夜学习通过考试的少数人之一。这是一次充满激情和兴奋的令人兴奋的旅程。 CKA 考试点燃了我的心——它与任何其他考试不同，它是一项实践性、基于场景的挑战。这种独特的方面让它令人兴奋。第二年，即 2018 年，举行了同样令人兴奋的 Kubernetes 应用程序开发人员认证 (CKAD) 考试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有趣的事实：已故的优秀 Dan Kohn 赞助了我的 CKA 和 CKAD 考试。 2019 年，在圣地亚哥 KubeCon 期间，我主持了一场关于认证的圆桌 QA 会议。 Dan Kohn 观察到了我的热情和兴奋，并建议我成立一个学习小组来帮助其他人，尤其是学生，启动他们的 Kubernetes 职业生涯和认证目标。这个建议让我成为了几项 Kubernetes 认证考试的作者，在萨克拉门托地区成立了许多工作组和一些在线小组。我还发起了 Kubernetes 认证聚会和 CKA/CKAD 等研讨会，以帮助宣传 CNCF 及其令人难以置信的资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 2021 年左右，在获得所有即将到来的 Kubernetes 认证之后，我想为那些获得 CNCF 和 Kubernetes 认证的人创建一些特别的项目——一个认可他们成就并激励和激励其他人设定雄心勃勃目标的计划。我与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/caniszczyk/&#34;&gt;Chris Aniszczyk&lt;/a&gt; 分享了这个想法，他发现它很有趣并且值得实施。这个想法最初起源于 2022 年 11 月底特律 KubeCon 期间。它不断发展了一段时间，到 2024 年 2 月，我们有了一个完美的名字：“Kubestronaut”。我的旅程深深地激发了这个概念，我经常感觉自己像一名宇航员在导航&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 广阔的未知领域。我希望其他人也能体验到同样的探索和发现感，但有指导和支持社区来帮助他们取得成功。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“799”高度=“533”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ramesh at KubeCon&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-119416&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024 /10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c.jpg 799w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c-300x200.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c-768x512.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/49097108021_9576329ec9_c- 600x400.jpg 600w&#34;sizes=&#34;(max-width: 799px) 100vw, 799px&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;我在 Kubecon NA 2019&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您为什么认为人们会对成为 Kubestronaus 感到如此兴奋？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 社区是技术领域最具活力和热情的团体之一。人们总是渴望学习、贡献、突破界限、帮助他人成长、互相鼓励和支持。我在这个社区中找到了许多出色的导师，并且有机会既成为受训者又成为导师。只有 CNCF 社区才能实现这种级别的协作和发展。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成为一名 Kubetronaut 是非常特别的。这是一种成就感、满足感和灵感。 Kubetronaut 计划的独特之处在于它专注于 Kubernetes/CNCF 教育、认证以及培养学习者的社区意识。 CKA、CKAD 和 CKS 等实践认证，以及 Kubernetes 和云原生助理 (KCNA) 以及 Kubernetes 和云安全助理 (KCSA) 等基础考试，为学习者提供了加深不同级别和领域知识的机会。这些认证帮助参与者培养实践技能和理论理解，支持他们的个人和职业成长。通过整合多种认证，Kubestronaut 计划使个人能够积累 Kubernetes 和云原生技术方面的专业知识。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您还希望人们了解该计划的哪些内容？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubestronaut 是一项独特的计划，专注于 Kubernetes 教育、认证和培养学习者的社区意识。它的设计具有包容性和社区驱动性，强调通过学习、协作和指导实现成长。该计划的亮点之一是有机会与该领域的专家联系、交流想法并成为 Kubernetes 专业人士全球网络的一部分。我们的目标是让 Kubernetes 对任何人来说都更容易使用并获得回报，无论是刚刚开始他们的云原生之旅还是提高他们现有的技能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF 认证和计划具有深远的影响。例如，我们的一位社区成员是一位拥有 18 年经验的厨师，他在 18 个月内通过获得 Kubernetes 认证进入科技行业。他的旅程有力地提醒人们这些认证如何改变生活。无论您从哪里开始，Kubestronaut 和 Kubernetes 等计划都可以激发成长并创造新的机会。  我迫不及待地想看看 Kubetronaut 计划将影响到多少人的生活。该倡议旨在让每个人都能做出反应他们的全部潜力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您目前从事或使用的主要 CNCF 项目是什么？在您的职业生涯中您最喜欢哪些项目？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Apple，我们总是胸怀大志，无论是规模还是创新。目前，我广泛使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/kubernetes/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;，这对我的项目至关重要，尤其是在大规模管理云基础设施方面。我还使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/helm/&#34;&gt;Helm&lt;/a&gt; 进行包管理，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects /prometheus/&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; 用于监控，&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; 用于仪表板，&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ Flux&#34;&gt;Flux&lt;/a&gt; 用于持续交付 (CD)，&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/emissary-ingress&#34;&gt;Emissary Ingress&lt;/a&gt;（以前称为大使）用于服务代理。这些 CNCF 项目是我工作中构建和运营云原生架构的基础。管理应用程序需要大量标准和安全执行，我总是非常认真地对待这些方面，确保它们得到高度精确的处理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;就我最喜欢的方面而言，Kubernetes 一直是我的热情所在。这是一个不断发展的平台，使用它是非常有意义的。 Prometheus 和 Grafana 的合作令人兴奋，主要是因为它们强大的监控功能以及它们如何使团队能够实时了解其系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;这些认证对您的职业生涯有何帮助？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我非常相信学习、培训和认证，因为它们提供了明确的路径、目的和目标。认证提供结构化的路线图，帮助您获得特定领域的深入知识。虽然认证可能无法让您完全掌握某一学科，但它们为持续学习和成长提供了坚实的基础和明确的方向。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF 认证 - &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/kcna/&#34;&gt;KCNA&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io /training/certification/cka/&#34;&gt;CKA&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/ckad/&#34;&gt;CKAD&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https ://www.cncf.io/training/certification/kcsa/&#34;&gt;KCSA&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/certification/cks/&#34;&gt;CKS&lt;/a&gt; a&gt; – 所有这些都对我的职业生涯至关重要。这些认证验证了我的技能，并促使我对 Kubernetes 和云原生技术有更深入的了解。他们帮助我过渡到可以大规模构建、管理和操作复杂的 Kubernetes 环境的角色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些认证还为我与更广泛的云原生社区接触、参与讨论以及在有意义的项目上进行协作打开了大门。更重要的是，他们让我有信心与他人分享我的知识，从而使我参与其中指导和创建 Kubetronaut 等教育项目。这些认证在提升我的职业生涯、扩大我的人际网络以及为我提供与我对 Kubernetes 和云原生技术的热情相一致的机会方面发挥了关键作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;有关 Ramesh 的更多信息&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/rk132&#34;&gt;Ramesh Kumar&lt;/a&gt; 是云原生技术的热情倡导者，在 Kubernetes 和 DevOps 方面拥有深厚的背景。 Ramesh 在 Apple 担任系统架构师，负责构建和管理下一代云基础设施，并有机会从头开始运行和操作数百个应用程序，确保它们符合云部署的 CNCF 标准。多年来，他参与了各种与 Kubernetes 相关的教育项目和企业级实施实践。他还是一名教师，喜欢指导他人应对快速发展的 Kubernetes 环境。 Ramesh 致力于培育通过共享学习和实践经验而成长的社区。他在 Apple 有一封非常独特的电子邮件：&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:Kubernetes@apple.com&#34;&gt;Kubernetes@apple.com&lt;/a&gt;！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What is zero trust authorization?】什么是零信任授权？</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/25/what-is-zero-trust-authorization/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/blog/zero-trust-authorization&#34;&gt;Cerbos’s blog&lt;/a&gt; by Twain Taylor&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstylish-appliance-1c1cc1c30d.media.strapiapp.com%2FWhat_is_zero_trust_authorization_695fa6a0dd.png&amp;amp;w=3840&amp;amp;q=75&#34; alt=&#34;What is zero trust authorization?&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional security models, which rely on perimeter-based defenses, have proven to be quite inadequate in the face of sophisticated attacks and the growing adoption of cloud computing and remote work. This shift has given rise to an altogether new approach to security: zero trust authorization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What is zero trust authorization?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/features-benefits-and-use-cases/zero-trust-security&#34;&gt;zero trust authorization (ZTA)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;philosophy represents a seismic shift in cybersecurity, challenging the age-old practice of inherent trust within network boundaries. Instead, it is founded on 3 core principles:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Never trust, always verify: The ZTA model presumes that no entity—be it a user, device, or software—warrants automatic confidence, irrespective of their physical position or historical clearance levels. Each request for entry must undergo scrutiny.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Assume breach: Acknowledge that breaches are inevitable and design security controls to minimize their impact.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Least privileged access: Allocate the absolute minimum necessary permissions to users and applications, allowing them to execute only their designated functions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional models have largely relied on one-time authentication at the perimeter and granted broad network access to authenticated users. In contrast, zero trust authorization regularly verifies the identity and permissions of users and devices, and grants access to resources based on granular, policy-based controls. To that end, it relies on several key components:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Strong authentication and identity management such as multi-factor authentication (MFA) is widely used to verify the identity of users and devices before granting access to resources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Micro-segmentation complements this by dividing the network into smaller, isolated segments, in a bid to limit the lateral movement of attackers and reduce the impact of a breach.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Continuous monitoring and analytics can be leveraged to detect and respond to threats instantaneously.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Finally, access to resources can be granted using atomic, context-aware policies based on models like:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/features-benefits-and-use-cases/abac&#34;&gt;Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC),&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Relationship-Based Access Control (ReBAC), or&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/features-benefits-and-use-cases/rbac&#34;&gt;Role-Based Access Control (RBAC)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These models factor in key vectors such as user identity, device health, and application requirements to make informed access decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why ZTA was developed&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The traditional perimeter-based security model has long been the standard for protecting corporate networks. However, the rise of cloud computing, remote work, and the growing sophistication of cyber threats have exposed the inadequacies of relying solely on these defenses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The previous model’s inherent trust in users and devices within the network made it particularly vulnerable to insider threats and compromised accounts. And without granular control and visibility, organizations may find themselves at a heightened risk of data breaches and intellectual property theft, as malicious actors can operate undetected within the trusted network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This challenge was further compounded by the blurring of network boundaries, which made securing remote access and cloud-based resources increasingly difficult. While traditional VPNs and firewalls remain necessary, they may not be sufficient to defend against sophisticated threats that can circumvent perimeter defenses and exploit weaknesses in remote access systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Implementing ZTA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ZTA implementation is one of those journeys that requires careful planning, execution, and continuous improvement. Broadly speaking, here’s what’s needed to reap the benefits of this perimeter-less security model:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1. Identify and assess&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First of all, identify what needs protecting, and then conduct a comprehensive assessment of all the sensitive data, critical assets, and workflows. You’ll have to map out the entire network architecture, triangulate vulnerabilities, and as you get into the thick of it, prioritize the resources that require the highest level of protection.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2. Design and implement&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the assessment complete, the next step is to architect a Zero Trust Network Access (ZTNA) framework that enforces the granular access control policies we discussed earlier. Here, we will segment the network into smaller, siloed zones, and define access policies that grant users and devices only the permissions necessary to perform their intended functions. Policy-based access control models come in handy here and we can rely on models such as RBAC, ABAC, or ReBAC to ensure that the principle of least privilege is applied consistently across the organization. To streamline the implementation process, developers can make use of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/&#34;&gt;Cerbos&lt;/a&gt;‘s Policy Decision Point (PDP) engine to easily integrate fine-grained access control into their applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;3. Monitor and maintain&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A successful ZTNA implementation will demand multiple iterations of refinement through continuous monitoring. To wit, organizations must regularly review and update their access policies to ensure that they remain aligned with evolving business requirements and security best practices. Everything from monitoring user and device activity, to analyzing security logs, and conducting regular audits to identify potential vulnerabilities or policy violations, etc is included here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that these steps provide only a general blueprint and most organizations will need a more tailored approach to address their specific risks and requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Advantages of ZTA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Zero trust authorization brings to the table several key advantages that help organizations strengthen their security posture and adapt to modern business requirements:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One of the most significant benefits is improved visibility and control over the entire network. ZTA empowers the security teams to detect and respond to potential threats in real time, and a centralized implementation of policy management ensures consistent and auditable access control across the organization, while behavioral analytics powered by machine learning helps to identify anomalous activities that may indicate a security breach.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ZTA also makes compliance with data protection regulations such as GDPR, HIPAA, and PCI-DSS a breeze through increased network visibility which makes dealing with vulnerabilities more effective.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Another advantage of ZTA is its increased agility and scalability. With a cloud-ready architecture that’s platform-agnostic and API-driven, nearly everything on an existing infrastructure can be made to fall under the ‘least privilege’ umbrella.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Yet another key advantage is that going the ZTA route will reduce your reliance on traditional perimeter security measures like firewalls and VPNs. And consequently, you will reduce both costs and complexity associated with maintaining and updating legacy security systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Challenges and considerations while implementing ZTA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even with all its many benefits, implementing ZTA comes with several hurdles:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Integrating ZTA with legacy systems can be costly and complex and often requires significant upgrades or workarounds to ensure compatibility and compliance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We often find resistance to change across organizations at every level since devs are wary of changing functional systems. ZTA may be viewed as a hindrance to productivity and will necessitate clear communication and education (if not convincing) to the team from higher management.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Managing access policies across diverse users, devices, and applications demands extremely careful planning and continuous monitoring to balance security and usability, which can take a significant toll in some cases.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Developers may face increased complexity in balancing the integration of ZTA with performance since we can expect increased latency from all continuous authentication just as we can expect some additional friction in user experience for the same reason.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Parting thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we look to the future, all signs indicate the need for ZTA will only continue to grow, and organizations must adapt to evolving threats and embrace a finer, more context-aware approach to access control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For developers, implementing ZTA can be daunting, especially since there’s this need to balance security with scalability and agility. But&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/&#34;&gt;Cerbos&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;can go a long way to simplify the process. It offers a powerful solution that streamlines the integration of roles, permissions, and access control mechanisms, making it easier than ever to implement a true zero trust architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初由 Twain Taylor 发布于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/blog/zero-trust-authorization&#34;&gt;Cerbos 博客&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/_next/image?url=https%3A%2F%2Fstylish-appliance-1c1cc1c30d。 media.strapiapp.com%2FWhat_is_zero_trust_authorization_695fa6a0dd.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75&#34; alt=&#34;什么是零信任授权？&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;事实证明，面对复杂的攻击以及云计算和远程工作的日益普及，依赖于基于边界的防御的传统安全模型已经远远不够。这种转变催生了一种全新的安全方法：零信任授权。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;什么是零信任授权？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/features-benefits-and-use-cases/zero-trust-security&#34;&gt;零信任授权 (ZTA)&lt;/a&gt; 理念代表着一种震撼人心的理念网络安全的转变，挑战了网络边界内固有信任的古老做法。相反，它建立在 3 个核心原则之上：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;永远不要信任，始终要验证：ZTA 模型假定任何实体（无论是用户、设备还是软件）都可以保证自动置信，无论其物理位置或历史许可级别如何。每个参赛请求都必须经过审查。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;假设违规：承认违规是不可避免的，并设计安全控制措施以尽量减少其影响。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;最小特权访问：为用户和应用程序分配绝对最低限度的必要权限，允许他们仅执行指定的功能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统模型在很大程度上依赖于外围的一次性身份验证，并向经过身份验证的用户授予广泛的网络访问权限。相比之下，零信任授权会定期验证用户和设备的身份和权限，并根据基于策略的细粒度控制授予对资源的访问权限。为此，它依赖于几个关键组件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多重身份验证 (MFA) 等强大的身份验证和身份管理被广泛用于在授予资源访问权限之前验证用户和设备的身份。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;微分段通过将网络划分为更小的隔离分段来对此进行补充，以限制攻击者的横向移动并减少违规的影响。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可以利用持续监控和分析来即时检测威胁并做出响应。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;最后，可以使用基于以下模型的原子上下文感知策略来授予对资源的访问权限：&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/features-benefits-and-use-cases/abac&#34;&gt;基于属性的访问控制 (ABAC)，&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;基于关系的访问控制 (ReBAC)，或&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;一小时f=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/features-benefits-and-use-cases/rbac&#34;&gt;基于角色的访问控制 (RBAC)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些模型考虑了用户身份、设备健康状况和应用程序要求等关键向量，以做出明智的访问决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;为什么开发 ZTA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统的基于边界的安全模型长期以来一直是保护企业网络的标准。然而，云计算、远程工作的兴起以及网络威胁的日益复杂，暴露了仅仅依靠这些防御措施的不足。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以前的模型对网络内用户和设备的固有信任使其特别容易受到内部威胁和受损帐户的影响。如果没有精细的控制和可见性，组织可能会发现自己面临更高的数据泄露和知识产权盗窃风险，因为恶意行为者可以在受信任的网络中进行不被发现的操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;网络边界的模糊进一步加剧了这一挑战，这使得保护远程访问和基于云的资源变得越来越困难。虽然传统的 VPN 和防火墙仍然是必要的，但它们可能不足以防御复杂的威胁，这些威胁可以绕过外围防御并利用远程访问系统的弱点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;实施 ZTA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ZTA 实施是需要仔细规划、执行和持续改进的过程之一。一般来说，要获得这种无边界安全模型的优势，需要满足以下条件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;1.识别和评估&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，确定需要保护的内容，然后对所有敏感数据、关键资产和工作流程进行全面评估。您必须规划整个网络架构，对漏洞进行三角测量，并在深入了解后，优先考虑需要最高级别保护的资源。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2.设计与实现&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;评估完成后，下一步是构建零信任网络访问 (ZTNA) 框架，该框架强制执行我们之前讨论的精细访问控制策略。在这里，我们将网络划分为更小的、孤立的区域，并定义访问策略，仅授予用户和设备执行其预期功能所需的权限。基于策略的访问控制模型在这里派上用场，我们可以依靠 RBAC、ABAC 或 ReBAC 等模型来确保最小权限原则在整个组织中得到一致应用。为了简化实施流程，开发人员可以利用&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/&#34;&gt;Cerbos&lt;/a&gt;的策略决策点（PDP）引擎轻松集成细粒度的访问控制进入他们的应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;3.监控一个并维护&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成功的 ZTNA 实施需要通过持续监控进行多次迭代细化。也就是说，组织必须定期审查和更新其访问策略，以确保它们与不断变化的业务需求和安全最佳实践保持一致。这里包括从监视用户和设备活动到分析安全日志以及进行定期审核以识别潜在漏洞或策略违规等的所有内容。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;值得注意的是，这些步骤仅提供一般蓝图，大多数组织将需要更量身定制的方法来解决其特定风险和要求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;ZTA 的优点&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;零信任授权带来了几个关键优势，可以帮助组织加强安全态势并适应现代业务需求：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;最显着的好处之一是提高了对整个网络的可见性和控制力。 ZTA 使安全团队能够实时检测和响应潜在威胁，策略管理的集中实施可确保整个组织内一致且可审核的访问控制，而由机器学习支持的行为分析有助于识别可能表明安全的异常活动违规。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ZTA 还通过提高网络可见性来轻松遵守 GDPR、HIPAA 和 PCI-DSS 等数据保护法规，从而更有效地处理漏洞。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ZTA 的另一个优势是提高了敏捷性和可扩展性。借助与平台无关且由 API 驱动的云就绪架构，现有基础设施上的几乎所有内容都可以置于“最低权限”保护伞之下。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;另一个关键优势是，采用 ZTA 路线将减少您对防火墙和 VPN 等传统外围安全措施的依赖。因此，您将降低与维护和更新旧安全系统相关的成本和复杂性。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;实施 ZTA 时的挑战和注意事项&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管 ZTA 具有诸多优势，但实施也存在一些障碍：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将 ZTA 与旧系统集成可能成本高昂且复杂，并且通常需要进行重大升级或解决方法以确保兼容性和合规性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我们经常发现组织各个层面的变革都遇到阻力，因为开发人员对改变功能系统持谨慎态度。 ZTA 可能被视为生产力的障碍，因此需要高层管理人员向团队进行清晰的沟通和教育（如果不令人信服）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;管理不同用户、设备和应用程序的访问策略需要极其仔细的规划和持续监控，以确保平衡安全性和可用性，这在某些情况下可能会造成重大损失。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;开发者在平衡 ZTA 与性能的集成时可能会面临更大的复杂性，因为我们预计所有连续身份验证的延迟都会增加，正如我们预计出于同样的原因，用户体验会出现一些额外的摩擦。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;离别感想&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;展望未来，所有迹象都表明对 ZTA 的需求只会继续增长，组织必须适应不断变化的威胁，并采用更精细、更具上下文感知能力的访问控制方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于开发人员来说，实施 ZTA 可能令人畏惧，尤其是因为需要在安全性与可扩展性和敏捷性之间取得平衡。但是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cerbos.dev/&#34;&gt;Cerbos&lt;/a&gt; 可以在很大程度上简化流程。它提供了一个强大的解决方案，可以简化角色、权限和访问控制机制的集成，使实现真正的零信任架构变得比以往更容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to ace (KCNA) Kubernetes and Cloud Native Associate exam】如何在 (KCNA) Kubernetes 和 Cloud Native Associate 考试中取得好成绩</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/23/how-to-ace-kcna-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-associate-exam/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Community post originally published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://faun.pub/how-to-ace-kcna-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-associate-exam-ac7bceace1eb&#34;&gt;Medium &lt;/a&gt;by Giorgi Keratishvili&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1000/1*C3cDB_-9a-dDurR_iRZN3w.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;2105&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;abb9&#34;&gt;Most probably if you have been working in IT over&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;last decate&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;you would heared such words as&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;containers&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;docker&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;cloud native&lt;/strong&gt;, maybe even&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;, but wonder what does all those&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;buzz words&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;mean and where you could start your learning jorny then my dear friend buckle up as we are about to dive in the word of container and kubernetes with the help of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;entry level certification&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;from CNCF as it is very good&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;entry point&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and aims to be beginer friendly as it was first multiple choose fromat exam which was introduced from linux fundation, I had opportunity to be first&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;beta tester&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;when this exam was first showcased and in this blog I will share materials and over all the style of exam in order to pass it and gain foundational knowledge&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;f73e&#34;&gt;Who should take this exam?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;99a3&#34;&gt;The goal of this certification is to provide individuals with&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;basic knowledge&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;of implementing container&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;best practices&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;in a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;vendor-neutral&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;way and giving them foundation to explore other cloud native ecosystems as this exam is belived to be first step to this whole world it is not intended to be super hard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;3765&#34;&gt;Compared to other certifications I would say it’s the easiest, but it still falls under the pre-professional level of difficulty and is a great way to test your knowledge before tackling the CKAD or CKA. For me, the order of difficulty felt like this:&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/CGOA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS&lt;/strong&gt;. One thing to keep in mind is that I had already passed the couple kubernetes exams and when I was preparing for the exam, there were no tutorials or blogs to refer at that time , only some suspiciously scam-like dumps, so don’t fall for them. Below I will mention all the new courses and materials that should help in preparation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;5482&#34;&gt;Regarding persons who would benefit&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;SysAdmins/Dev/Ops/SRE/Managers/Platform engineers&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;or any one who is doing anything on production should consider it as knowing basic security is always good thing or somebody whom wants to becombe&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;kubestronaut&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;😉 more about it in next blog…&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;db3b&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The KCNA is a pre-professional certification designed for candidates interested in advancing to the professional level through a demonstrated understanding of kubernetes foundational knowledge and skills. This certification is ideal for students learning about or candidates interested in working with cloud native technologies.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;cf59&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A certified KCNA will confirm conceptual knowledge of the entire cloud native ecosystem, particularly focusing on Kubernetes. The KCNA exam is intended to prepare candidates to work with cloud native technologies and pursue further CNCF credentials, including KCSA, CKA, CKAD, and CKS.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;17ff&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;KCNA will demonstrate a candidate’s basic knowledge of Kubernetes and cloud-native technologies, including how to deploy an application using basic kubectl commands, the architecture of Kubernetes (containers, pods, nodes, clusters), understanding the cloud-native landscape and projects (storage, networking, GitOps, service mesh), and understanding the principles of cloud-native security.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*u8LhW9zQxv3iGohzx_WuSA.png&#34; alt=&#34;The CNCF&amp;nbsp;Cloud Native Trail Map&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;The CNCF&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/landscape#trail-map&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Trail Map&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;4ad1&#34;&gt;Exam Format and PSI Proctored Exam Tips&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;99bf&#34;&gt;So we are ready to deploy vanilla clusters, make higly avalable enviroments and rock the world of fast software delivery? Then, we have a long path ahead until we reach this point. First, we need to understand what kind of exam it is compared to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CKAD&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CKA&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;CKS,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;or others. This is exam where the CNCF has adopted first time multiple-choice questions and compared to other&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;multiple-choice&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;exams, this one, I would say is on an easy level. and it qualified as pre-professional, on par with the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KCSA/PCA/CGOA&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;25e2&#34;&gt;This exam is conducted online, proctored similarly to other Kubernetes certifications and is facilitated by PSI. As someone who has taken more than 15 exams with PSI, I can say that every time it’s a new journey.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;I&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;HIGHLY ADVISE joining the exam 30 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;before taking the test because there are pre-checks of ID and the room in which you are taking it needs to be checked for exam criteria. Please check these two links for the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/exam-rules-and-policies&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;exam rules&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/taking-the-exam&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSI portal guide&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7b5b&#34;&gt;You’ll have&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;90 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;to answer&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;60 questions&lt;/strong&gt;, which is generally considered sufficient time,&amp;nbsp;the &lt;strong&gt;passing&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;score is&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;gt;75%&lt;/strong&gt;. Be prepared for some questions that can be quite tricky. I marked a couple of them for review and would advise doing the same because sometimes you could find a hint or partial answers in the next question. By this way, you could refer back to those questions. Regarding pricing, the exam costs&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;$250&lt;/strong&gt;, but you can&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;often&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;find it at a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;discount&lt;/strong&gt;, such as during&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Black Friday&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;promotions or near dates for CNCF events like KubeCon, Open Source Summit, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*VYKpNWIk0Hqb8CoOCvJ62g.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;b120&#34;&gt;The Path of Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ca84&#34;&gt;At this point, we understand what we have signed up for and are ready to dedicate time to training, but where should we start? Before taking this exam, I had a good experience with Kubernetes and its ecosystem and experience with the CKA exam, but yet I still learned a lot from this exam preparation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;e8a6&#34;&gt;At first glance, this list might seem too simple and easy but we need to learn the fundamentals of Kubernetes first in order to understand higher-level concepts such as Architecture, Core Components, 4C’s, and many more&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;0baa&#34;&gt;Let break down Domains &amp;amp; Competencies&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-preformatted&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Kubernetes Fundamentals 46%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Kubernetes Resources&lt;br&gt;    Kubernetes Architecture&lt;br&gt;    Kubernetes API&lt;br&gt;    Containers&lt;br&gt;    Scheduling&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Container Orchestration 22%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Container Orchestration Fundamentals&lt;br&gt;    Runtime&lt;br&gt;    Security&lt;br&gt;    Networking&lt;br&gt;    Service Mesh&lt;br&gt;    Storage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Cloud Native Architecture 16%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Autoscaling&lt;br&gt;    Serverless&lt;br&gt;    Community and Governance&lt;br&gt;    Roles and Personas&lt;br&gt;    Open Standards&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Cloud Native Observability 8%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Telemetry &amp;amp; Observability&lt;br&gt;    Prometheus&lt;br&gt;    Cost Management&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Cloud Native Application Delivery 8%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Application Delivery Fundamentals&lt;br&gt;    GitOps&lt;br&gt;    CI/CD&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;6871&#34;&gt;Cloud Native and Kubernetes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4a31&#34;&gt;There are 5 key&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;pillars&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;(The key domains&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/kubernetes-cloud-native-associate/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;). Let’s get into some details about it to help direct your studies:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;959c&#34;&gt;The Key Pillars&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes Fundamentals —&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The exam expects that you’ve dabbled into Kubernetes and have a good understanding of all the moving parts. This means, it’s extremely important to review the Kubernetes architecture and components that work together to enable such a powerful container orchestration system. CoreDNS, Kube-API, Kube-Scheduler, and Kube-controller are critical to the control plane, while Kube-proxy, Kubelet, and a CRI are critical to the worker-node. There is also the expectation that you have played on a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;non-production&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;K8S cluster.&lt;br&gt;At this point, you might be wondering how you can accomplish this. Most home-consumer PCs can run Kubernetes locally using&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/start/&#34;&gt;Minikube&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kind.sigs.k8s.io/&#34;&gt;KinD&lt;/a&gt;. I strongly recommend playing with either and familiarizing yourself with the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;kubectl&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;command line.&lt;br&gt;Within a Kubernetes cluster, there are a number of resources like&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Pods, Deployments, DaemonSets, StatefulSets&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Services&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to allow an application to run and be accessible.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/tutorials/stateful-application/zookeeper/&#34;&gt;For example, ZooKeeper is a Headless Service that uses StatefulSets to operate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;You may want to dig into what constructs a Pod YAML, and also dig into why a Pod is&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;immutable&lt;/em&gt;. Consider looking into the various Deployment strategies that exist, like&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;RollingUpdates.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Services act as a way to enable inbound or east-west communications within a cluster. There are a few main types,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;NodePort&lt;/em&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;ClusterIP, LoadBalancer&lt;/em&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;ExternalName&lt;/em&gt;. It’s definitely worth digging into what each of these do and a few use-cases associated.&lt;br&gt;This is where the hands-on component really comes in handy because you can expect the exam to test you on your knowledge of working with these things. Note, this is a not a production-focused exam.&lt;br&gt;With such a huge weight on the exam, consider going through a quick-start K8S course (I’ll link some below).&lt;br&gt;Remember, Kubernetes can be extended with&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Custom Resource Definitions&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;While security isn’t the main focus of this exam, know the&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;4Cs: Code, Container, Cluster, Cloud&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Container Orchestration —&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This section is a bit more generic compared to the previous section because K8S is not the only container orchestration platform out there. That being said, this section focusses more on the pieces that work together to make container orchestration possible. Application platforms will have a container runtime, networking, security, storage, and extended proxies and observability to enhance the experience of managing, maintaining, and scaling applications. Think about things like a Container Networking Interface (CNI), Container Storage Interface (CSI), or Container Runtime Interface (CRI). Look into Istio and LinkerD, Service Mesh technologies, which provide a side-car proxy to the application container, and services connection requests on it’s behalf.&lt;br&gt;Spend time looking into CRIs like&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://containerd.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Containerd&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and CRI-O.&lt;br&gt;Authentication and Authorization are other areas that is worth reviewing as&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;OpenID-Connect&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Open Policy Agent (OPA)&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;are being used more frequently.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native Architecture —&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This part of the exam focusses on addressing how technologies like&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Autoscaling&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Serverless&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;aim to provide a mechanism to control costs, and provide a much more flexible approach to managing and deploying applications. Furthermore, it’s worth digging into how the the CNCF is built, from the community to work-groups to SIGs. It’s worth a mention that a variety of job roles will use cloud-native technologies and have decisions to make. For example,&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Site Reliability Engineers&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;are often tasked with establishing&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SLIs/SLOs/SLAs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;Finally, there are a number of open standards that exist in the CNCF. The Open-Container Initiative (OCI)is one of them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native Observability —&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;While this section isn’t massive, there are a number of observability and logging tools that are used to help pin-point issues in applications in a K8S cluster. Most environments leveraging K8S might make use of tools like&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Prometheus&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;for metrics, data visualization and heat-map graphs. Other tools like&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Jaegar&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Zipkin&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;might be used for&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Tracing&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and reviewing&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;Spans&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;within that trace.&lt;br&gt;Furthermore, managing costs in Kubernetes and Cloud Native become an important business problem to solve. This can be around efficient utilization of compute resources (Scale up and scale back down to zero), and using&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;CronJobs&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;to establish a schedule for when workloads need to run.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native Application Delivery —&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This small section focusses on principles of application delivery. More specifically, it focusses on topics like GitOps, blue-greens, canary deployments, and some of the tools you may use in a cloud native environment. Spend time reviewing tools like ArgoCD and FluxCD to understand how they help with Continous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CICD) in Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*7OhtPL4I68AGB2AwzmI99w.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; style=&#34;width:314px;height:auto&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;aec3&#34;&gt;Key Learning Materials:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b58c&#34;&gt;You can explore and learn about KCNA Certification and related topics freely through the following GitHub repositories which I have used and of course kubernetes&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;documentation&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;is our best friend also there is great courses from linux foundation&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/introduction-to-kubernetes/&#34;&gt;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/introduction-to-kubernetes/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/walidshaari/Kubernetes-and-Cloud-Native-Associate&#34;&gt;https://github.com/walidshaari/Kubernetes-and-Cloud-Native-Associate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/moabukar/Kubernetes-and-Cloud-Native-Associate-KCNA/tree/main&#34;&gt;https://github.com/moabukar/Kubernetes-and-Cloud-Native-Associate-KCNA/tree/main&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kube.academy/&#34;&gt;https://kube.academy/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/home/&#34;&gt;https://kubernetes.io/docs/home/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.edx.org/learn/linux/the-linux-foundation-introduction-to-linux&#34;&gt;https://www.edx.org/learn/linux/the-linux-foundation-introduction-to-linux&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.edx.org/learn/cloud-computing/the-linux-foundation-introduction-to-cloud-infrastructure-technologies&#34;&gt;https://www.edx.org/learn/cloud-computing/the-linux-foundation-introduction-to-cloud-infrastructure-technologies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;00a7&#34;&gt;For structured and comprehensive KCNA exam preparation, consider investing in these paid course Kodekloud, Exam PRO, Oreilly and play a lot with kubernetes playground killercoda from Kim Wüstkamp I have been using for his content a lot for exam preparation CKS/CKAD/CKA/LFCS, indeed it is very useful and I recomend it also&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;I would higly advise not to click on every course which will pop up from google search as it is new exam there are plenty scams.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kodekloud.com/courses/kubernetes-and-cloud-native-associate-kcna/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes and Cloud-Native Associate (KCNA)&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;From KodeKloud&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://app.exampro.co/student/journey/kcna&#34;&gt;Kubernetes and Cloud Native Associate (KCNA) From Exam pro&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AplluksKvzI&amp;amp;t=23521s&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;youtube platform&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;which is free on both&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;3a96&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;c04d&#34;&gt;The exam is not easy among other certs and I would rank it in this order&amp;nbsp;KCNA/CGOA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS.&amp;nbsp;After conducting the exam, within 24 hours you will receive grading and after passing the exam it feel pretty satisfied overall. I hope it was informative and useful 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1000/1*FtZ2wfHioEqd_OFJPIWetQ.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;社区帖子最初发布于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://faun.pub/how-to-ace-kcna-kubernetes-and-cloud-native-associate-exam-ac7bceace1eb&#34;&gt;Medium &lt;/ a&gt;作者：Giorgi Keratishvili&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1000/1*C3cDB_-9a-dDurR_iRZN3w.png&#34; alt=&#34;图片&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;2105&#34;&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;abb9&#34;&gt;如果您&lt;strong&gt;过去十年&lt;/strong&gt;一直从事 IT 工作，您很可能会听到诸如&lt;strong&gt;容器&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;docker&lt;/strong&gt;之类的词，&lt;strong&gt;云原生&lt;/strong&gt;，甚至&lt;strong&gt;kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;，但想知道所有这些&lt;strong&gt;流行语&lt;/strong&gt;是什么意思，以及我亲爱的朋友，你可以从哪里开始你的学习之旅系好安全带，我们即将在 CNCF 的&lt;strong&gt;入门级认证&lt;/strong&gt;的帮助下深入了解容器和 Kubernetes，因为它是非常好的&lt;strong&gt;入门点&lt;/strong&gt;，并且旨在成为初学者友好，因为它是 Linux 基金会推出的第一个多项选择考试，当该考试首次展示时，我有机会成为第一个&lt;strong&gt;测试人员&lt;/strong&gt;，在这个博客中我将分享材料和所有风格为了通过考试并获得基础知识&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;f73e&#34;&gt;谁应该参加这项考试？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;99a3&#34;&gt;此认证的目标是为个人提供在&lt;strong&gt;供应商中立&lt;/strong&gt;中实施容器&lt;strong&gt;最佳实践&lt;/strong&gt;的&lt;strong&gt;基本知识&lt;/strong&gt; &gt; 为他们探索其他云原生生态系统奠定基础，因为这项考试被认为是通向这个世界的第一步，所以它并不是超级难。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;3765&#34;&gt;与其他认证相比，我认为这是最简单的，但它仍然属于专业前的难度级别，是在解决 CKAD 或 CKA 之前测试您的知识的好方法。对我来说，难度顺序是这样的：&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/CGOA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS&lt;/strong&gt;。需要记住的一件事是，我已经通过了几门 kubernetes 考试，当我准备考试时，当时没有教程或博客可供参考，只有一些可疑的骗局转储，所以不要跌倒对于他们来说。下面我将提到所有有助于准备的新课程和材料。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;5482&#34;&gt;对于&lt;strong&gt;系统管理员/开发/运营/SRE/经理/平台工程师&lt;/strong&gt;或任何在生产中从事任何工作的人来说，应该认为了解基本安全始终是重要的好事或想成为&lt;strong&gt;kubetronaut&lt;/strong&gt;的人😉更多关于它在下一篇博客......&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-b锁定引用是布局流&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;db3b&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;KCNA 是一项职业前认证，专为有兴趣通过对 kubernetes 基础知识和技能的理解提升到专业水平的考生而设计。该认证非常适合学习云原生技术的学生或有兴趣使用云原生技术的候选人。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;cf59&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;经过认证的 KCNA 将确认整个云原生生态系统的概念知识，特别是关注 Kubernetes。 KCNA 考试旨在帮助考生做好使用云原生技术的准备，并进一步获得 CNCF 证书，包括 KCSA、CKA、CKAD 和 CKS。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;17ff&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;KCNA 将展示候选人对 Kubernetes 和云原生技术的基本知识，包括如何使用基本 kubectl 命令部署应用程序、Kubernetes 架构（容器、pod、节点、集群） ，了解云原生环境和项目（存储、网络、GitOps、服务网格），并了解云原生安全原理。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*u8LhW9zQxv3iGohzx_WuSA.png&#34; alt=&#34;The CNCF Cloud Native Trail Map&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/landscape#trail-map&#34; rel =&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;云原生路线图&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;4ad1&#34;&gt;考试格式和 PSI 监考考试提示&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;99bf&#34;&gt;那么我们准备好部署普通集群、打造高度可用的环境并震撼快速软件交付的世界了吗？然后，在到达这一点之前，我们还有很长的路要走。首先，我们需要了解与&lt;strong&gt;CKAD&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;CKA&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;CKS &lt;/strong&gt;或其他考试相比，它属于什么类型的考试。这是 CNCF 首次采用多项选择题的考试，与其他&lt;strong&gt;多项选择&lt;/strong&gt;考试相比，我认为这次考试处于简单水平。它具有与 &lt;strong&gt;KCSA/PCA/CGOA&lt;/strong&gt; 同等的预科资格。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;25e2&#34;&gt;该考试在线进行，监考方式与其他 Kubernetes 认证类似，并由 PSI 提供协助。作为参加过超过 15 场 PSI 考试的人，我可以说每次都是新的旅程。&lt;strong&gt;我&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;强烈建议在参加考试前 30 分钟参加考试&lt;/strong&gt;，因为需要预先检查身份证件，并且需要检查您所在的房间是否符合考试标准。请检查这两个链接，了解&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/exam-rules-and-policies&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;考试规​​则&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/taking-the-exam&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSI 门户指南&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;7b5b&#34;&gt;您将有&lt;strong&gt;90 分钟&lt;/strong&gt;的时间回答&lt;strong&gt;60 个问题&lt;/strong&gt;，这通常被认为是足够的时间，&lt;strong&gt;及格&lt;/strong&gt;分数是&lt;strong&gt;&gt;75%&lt;/strong&gt;。为一些可能相当棘手的问题做好准备。我标记了其中几个以供审查，并建议您也这样做，因为有时您可以在下一个问题中找到提示或部分答案。这样你就可以回过头来看看这些问题了。关于定价，考试费用&lt;strong&gt; 250 美元&lt;/strong&gt;，但您&lt;strong&gt;通常&lt;/strong&gt;可以享受&lt;strong&gt;折扣&lt;/strong&gt;，例如在&lt;strong&gt;黑色星期五&lt;/strong&gt;期间&gt; KubeCon、开源峰会等 CNCF 活动的促销活动或近期日期。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*VYKpNWIk0Hqb8CoOCvJ62g.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Image “referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;b120&#34;&gt;学习之路&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ca84&#34;&gt;至此，我们了解了自己注册的目的，并准备好投入时间进行培训，但我们应该从哪里开始呢？在参加这次考试之前，我对 Kubernetes 及其生态系统以及 CKA 考试都有了很好的体验，但我仍然从这次考试准备中学到了很多东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;e8a6&#34;&gt;乍一看，这个列表似乎过于简单和容易，但我们需要首先学习 Kubernetes 的基础知识，以便理解更高层次的概念，例如架构、核心组件、4C 等等&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;0baa&#34;&gt;让我们分解一下领域和能力&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-preformatted&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Kubernetes 基础知识 46%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; Kubernetes 资源&lt;br&gt; Kubernetes 架构&lt;br&gt; Kubernetes API&lt;br&gt; 容器&lt;br&gt; 调度&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**容器编排 22%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 容器编排基础知识&lt;br&gt; 运行时&lt;br&gt; 安全性&lt;br&gt; 网络&lt;br&gt; 服务网格&lt;br&gt; 存储&lt;br &gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**云原生架构 16%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 自动扩展&lt;br&gt; 无服务器&lt;br&gt; 社区和治理&lt;br&gt; 角色和角色&lt;br&gt; 开放标准&lt;br&gt;&lt;br &gt;&lt;strong&gt;**云原生可观测性 8%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 遥测和可观测性&lt;br&gt; Prometheus&lt;br&gt; 成本管理&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**云原生应用交付 8%* *&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 应用程序交付基础知识&lt;br&gt; GitOps&lt;br&gt; CI/CD&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;6871&#34;&gt;云原生和 Kubernetes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4a31&#34;&gt;有 5 个关键&lt;strong&gt;支柱&lt;/strong&gt;（关键领域&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/kubernetes-cloud-native-associate/&#34; &gt;这里&lt;/a&gt;）。让我们详细了解一下它，以帮助指导您的学习：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;959c&#34;&gt;关键支柱&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul 类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes 基础知识 - &lt;/strong&gt;考试要求您涉足 Kubernetes 并对所有活动部分有充分的了解。这意味着，审查 Kubernetes 架构和组件非常重要，它们协同工作以实现如此强大的容器编排系统。 CoreDNS、Kube-API、Kube-Scheduler 和 Kube-controller 对于控制平面至关重要，而 Kube-proxy、Kubelet 和 CRI 对于工作节点至关重要。还期望您在&lt;strong&gt;非生产&lt;/strong&gt;K8S 集群上进行游戏。&lt;br&gt;此时，您可能想知道如何实现这一目标。大多数家庭消费者 PC 可以使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://minikube.sigs.k8s.io/docs/start/&#34;&gt;Minikube&lt;/a&gt; 或 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kind. sigs.k8s.io/&#34;&gt;KinD&lt;/a&gt;。我强烈建议您使用其中任何一个，并熟悉 &lt;strong&gt;kubectl&lt;/strong&gt; 命令行。&lt;br&gt;在 Kubernetes 集群中，有许多资源，例如 Pod、Deployments、DaemonSet、StatefulSet。 &gt; 和&lt;em&gt;服务&lt;/em&gt;，允许应用程序运行并可访问。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/tutorials/stateful-application/zookeeper/&#34;&gt;例如，ZooKeeper 是一个使用 StatefulSet 进行操作的 Headless Service&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;br&gt;您可能想要深入研究 Pod YAML 的构建内容，并深入研究为什么 Pod 是不可变的。考虑研究现有的各种部署策略，例如滚动更新。&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;服务充当集群内启用入站或东西向通信的一种方式。有几种主要类型：&lt;em&gt;NodePort&lt;/em&gt;、&lt;em&gt;ClusterIP、LoadBalancer&lt;/em&gt; 和 &lt;em&gt;ExternalName&lt;/em&gt;。绝对值得深入研究其中每一个的作用以及一些相关的用例。&lt;br&gt;这就是动手组件真正派上用场的地方，因为您可以期望考试测试您使用这些东西的知识。请注意，这不是一项以生产为重点的考试。&lt;br&gt;考试的权重如此之大，请考虑参加快速入门 K8S 课程（我将在下面链接一些内容）。&lt;br&gt;请记住，Kubernetes 可以是使用&lt;em&gt;自定义资源定义进行扩展&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;虽然安全性不是本次考试的主要重点，但请了解&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;4C：代码、容器、集群、云&lt;/em&gt;。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;容器编排 - &lt;/strong&gt;与上一部分相比，本部分更为通用，因为 K8S 并不是唯一的容器编排平台。话虽这么说，本节更多地关注协同工作以使容器编排成为可能的各个部分。应用程序平台将具有容器运行时、网络、安全性、存储以及扩展代理和可观察性，以增强管理、维护和扩展应用程序的体验。想想瘦例如容器网络接口 (CNI)、容器存储接口 (CSI) 或容器运行时接口 (CRI)。研究 Istio 和 LinkerD、Service Mesh 技术，它们为应用程序容器提供 sidecar 代理，并代表应用程序容器服务连接请求。&lt;br&gt;花时间研究 CRI，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://containerd. io/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Containerd&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 和 CRI-O。&lt;br&gt;身份验证和授权是其他值得审查的领域，&lt;em&gt;OpenID-Connect&lt;/em&gt; 和 &lt;em&gt;Open策略代理 (OPA)&lt;/em&gt; 的使用更加频繁。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云原生架构 - &lt;/strong&gt;这部分考试重点关注自动扩展和无服务器等技术如何旨在提供控制成本的机制，并提供更灵活的方法来管理和部署应用程序。此外，值得深入研究 CNCF 的构建方式，从社区到工作组再到 SIG。值得一提的是，各种工作角色将使用云原生技术并需要做出决策。例如，&lt;em&gt;站点可靠性工程师&lt;/em&gt;经常负责建立&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SLI/SLO/SLA&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;br&gt;最后，有许多开放标准存在于 CNCF 中。开放容器计划 (OCI) 就是其中之一。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云原生可观察性 - 虽然本节内容并不多，但有许多可观察性和日志记录工具可用于帮助查明 K8S 集群中应用程序中的问题。大多数利用 K8S 的环境可能会使用 Prometheus 和 Grafana 等工具来实现指标、数据可视化和热图。 &lt;em&gt;Jaegar&lt;/em&gt; 和 &lt;em&gt;Zipkin&lt;/em&gt; 等其他工具可用于&lt;em&gt;跟踪&lt;/em&gt;并在该跟踪内检查&lt;em&gt;跨度&lt;/em&gt;。&lt;br&gt;此外管理 Kubernetes 和 Cloud Native 中的成本成为需要解决的重要业务问题。这可以围绕计算资源的高效利用（扩大和缩小到零），以及使用&lt;em&gt;CronJobs&lt;/em&gt;来建立工作负载需要运行的时间表。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云原生应用程序交付 - &lt;/strong&gt;这一小节重点介绍应用程序交付的原则。更具体地说，它重点关注 GitOps、蓝绿、金丝雀部署以及您可能在云原生环境中使用的一些工具等主题。花时间查看 ArgoCD 和 FluxCD 等工具，了解它们如何帮助 Kubernetes 中的持续集成和持续交付 (CICD)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*7OhtPL4I68AGB2AwzmI99w.jpeg&#34; alt =&#34;图像&#34; style=&#34;width:314px;height:auto&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;aec3&#34;&gt;主要学习材料：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b58c&#34;&gt;您可以通过我使用过的以下 GitHub 存储库自由探索和了解 KCNA 认证及相关主题，当然 kubernetes &lt;strong&gt;文档&lt;/strong&gt;是我们最好的朋友，还有很棒的课程来自 Linux 基金会&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/introduction-to-kubernetes/&#34;&gt;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/training/introduction-to-kubernetes/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/walidshaari/Kubernetes-and-Cloud-Native-Associate&#34;&gt;https://github.com/walidshaari/Kubernetes-and-Cloud-Native-Associate&lt;/一个&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/moabukar/Kubernetes-and-Cloud-Native-Associate-KCNA/tree/main&#34;&gt;https://github.com/moabukar/Kubernetes-and-Cloud -Native-Associate-KCNA/tree/main&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kube.academy/&#34;&gt;https://kube.academy/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/home/&#34;&gt;https://kubernetes.io/docs/home/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.edx.org/learn/linux/the-linux-foundation-introduction-to-linux&#34;&gt;https://www.edx.org/learn/linux/the -linux-foundation-linux 简介&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.edx.org/learn/cloud-computing/the-linux-foundation-introduction-to-cloud-infrastruct-technologies&#34;&gt;https://www.edx.org /learn/cloud-computing/the-linux-foundation-introduction-to-cloud-infrastruct-technologies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;准备CKS/CKAD/CKA/LFCS，确实非常有用，我也推荐它&lt;strong&gt;我强烈建议不要点击从谷歌弹出的每门课程搜索一下，因为这是新考试，有很多骗局。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kodekloud.com/courses/kubernetes-and-cloud-native-associate-kcna/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 和云原生助理 (KCNA)&lt;/a&gt; 来自 KodeKloud&lt;/li &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://app.exampro.co/student/journey/kcna&#34;&gt;来自考试专业人士的 Kubernetes 和 Cloud Native Associate (KCNA)&lt;/a&gt; 或&lt;a href=&#34;https:// www.youtube.com/watch?v=AplluksKvzI&amp;t=23521s&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;YouTube 平台&lt;/a&gt; 两者均免费&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;3a96&#34;&gt;结论&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;c04d&#34;&gt;与其他证书相比，该考试并不容易，我会按以下顺序排列：KCNA/CGOA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS。 进行考试后，24小时之内你就会收到评分，通过考试后总体感觉还算满意。我希望它内容丰富且有用🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1000/1*FtZ2wfHioEqd_OFJPIWetQ.png&#34; alt=&#34;Image “推荐人波利cy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software supply chain compliance and security policies with SignServer, EJBCA, and Chainloop】SignServer、EJBCA 和 Chainloop 的软件供应链合规性和安全策略</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/10/25/software-supply-chain-compliance-and-security-policies-with-signserver-ejbca-and-chainloop/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ejbca.org/resources/software-supply-chain-compliance-and-security-policies-with-signserver-ejbca-and-chainloop/&#34;&gt;EJBCA by Keyfactor &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href=&#34;https://chainloop.dev/blog/securing-the-software-supply-chain-with-signserver-ejbca-and-chainloop-a-comprehensive-guide&#34;&gt;Chainloop blogs&lt;/a&gt; by Ben Dewberry, Product Manager, Signing and Key Management, Keyfactor and Miguel Martinez Trivino, Co-founder,&amp;nbsp;Chainloop&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A software supply chain is the series of steps performed when writing, testing, packaging, and distributing software. During this process, information about what and how the software is built is generated at each step. This is called metadata.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Software Bill of Materials (SBOM) is a canonical example of supply chain metadata, but more examples are scattered across your Software Delivery lifecycle, from QA tests/reports, CVE scans, VEX, legal/security/architecture reviews, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Companies are &lt;strong&gt;starting to rely on this metadata to make critical decisions&lt;/strong&gt;, such as whether to deploy an app to a bank system or whether it is vulnerable, compliant, etc. These decisions could be motivated by wanting to improve your security posture and &lt;a href=&#34;https://slsa.dev/spec/v0.1/levels?&#34;&gt;reach a specific SLSA level&lt;/a&gt; or purely pushed by existing regulations such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisa.gov/topics/cybersecurity-best-practices/executive-order-improving-nations-cybersecurity&#34;&gt;EO 14028&lt;/a&gt; in the US or upcoming ones like the European &lt;a href=&#34;https://digital-strategy.ec.europa.eu/en/library/cyber-resilience-act&#34;&gt;Cyber Resilience Act&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;However, metadata that cannot be trusted is useless and even harmful.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That is why Chainloop and Keyfactor have partnered by integrating Chainloop’s modular evidence-based metadata storing platform with Keyfactor’s enterprise PKI solutions, EJBCA and SignServer. These integrations will allow organizations to collect, verify, trust, and protect the metadata generated by their software supply chain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we are introducing two integrations: &lt;strong&gt;Remote signing with Keyfactor’s SignServer, and Local signing with Keyfactor’s EJBCA using ephemeral certificates.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After implementing this integration, you will have a solid foundation on which to begin making this metadata &lt;strong&gt;actionable &lt;/strong&gt;for implementing automated policies controlling what is allowed to be run in your environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Setting up a metadata evidence store using Chainloop, SignServer, and EJBCA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chainloop-dev/chainloop&#34;&gt;Chainloop&lt;/a&gt; is an open-source evidence store for Software Supply Chain attestations, Software Bill of Materials (SBOMs), VEX, SARIF, CSAF files, QA reports, and more. Metadata sent to Chainloop will get attested, signed, evaluated, routed, and stored.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1949&#34; height=&#34;1224&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chainloop overview&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118518&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview.jpg 1949w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-300x188.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-1024x643.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-768x482.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-900x565.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-1800x1130.jpg 1800w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-318x200.jpg 318w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-637x400.jpg 637w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 1949px) 100vw, 1949px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chainloop offers an opinionated but pluggable end-to-end solution. In this blog post, we will give you an overview of configuring a Chainloop instance with SignServer and EJBCA. The result would be an end-to-end solution that will create in-toto attestations signed with SignServer and EJBCA, stored in an OCI registry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;2125&#34; height=&#34;1881&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers.png&#34; alt=&#34;chainloop layers&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118519&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers.png 2125w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-300x266.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-1024x906.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-768x680.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-900x797.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-1800x1593.png 1800w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-226x200.png 226w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-452x400.png 452w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 2125px) 100vw, 2125px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before you begin, you need SignServer, EJBCA, and Chainloop running.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To learn how to get started with EJBCA Community as a Docker container, you can follow the &lt;a href=&#34;http://20.91.210.51:8090/display/EJBCADS/Quick+Start+Guide+-+Start+EJBCA+Container+with+Client+Certificate+Authenticated+Access&#34;&gt;Quick Start Guide – Start EJBCA Container with Client Certificate Authenticated Access&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To learn how to get started with SignServer Community as a Docker container, you can follow the &lt;a href=&#34;https://doc.primekey.com/signserver/tutorials-and-guides/quick-start-guide-start-signserver-container-with-client-certificate-authenticated-access&#34;&gt;Quick Start Guide – Start SignServer Container with Client Certificate Authenticated Access&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To deploy Chainloop, you can either run a local instance using this &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chainloop-dev/chainloop/tree/main/devel#labs-environments&#34;&gt;docker compose file&lt;/a&gt; or in a Kubernetes Cluster using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chainloop-dev/chainloop/tree/main/deployment/chainloop&#34;&gt;Chainloop Helm Chart&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You should now have a SignServer, EJBCA, and a Chainloop instance running, but Chainloop is not configured to use them yet!&amp;nbsp; By default, Chainloop will sign attestations using Sigstore’s Cosign key pairs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s change that! Keyfactor and Chainloop have partnered to offer two integrations to sign attestations and artifacts, allowing you to bring your own PKI: &lt;strong&gt;Remote signing with SignServer&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Local Signing with an EJBCA ephemeral certificate&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Remote Signing with SignServer&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SignServer is a versatile and high-performing open-source code-signing software that enables secure cryptographic signing operations. It digitally signs different types of workloads including code, artifacts, attestations, and containers to ensure software integrity and authenticity. For more information, see &lt;a href=&#34;http://signserver.org/&#34;&gt;signserver.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This integration allows users to send the attestation payload to a SignServer worker before sending it to Chainloop for storage. Think of this as a KMS-like approach, where the client environment can access the PKI infrastructure and send the data for remote signing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;2600&#34; height=&#34;1538&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview.png&#34; alt=&#34;signserver overview&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118520&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview.png 2600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-300x177.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-1024x606.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-768x454.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-900x532.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-1800x1065.png 1800w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-338x200.png 338w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-676x400.png 676w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 2600px) 100vw, 2600px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of the benefits of this approach:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The key can be stored on hardware security modules (HSMs) where the signing takes place for additional security&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You can leverage this key for signing with additional SignServer workers to handle other artifacts from the pipeline, such as binaries, documents, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.chainloop.dev/guides/signserver/&#34;&gt;The guide: Use Keyfactor SignServer for attestation signing&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;explains this integration in more detail, but the gist is that you should be able to run the attestation push command and have a remote SignServer worker sign the attestation like this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&amp;gt; chainloop attestation push --key signserver://mysignserver/my-signing-worker&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, the integration will send the payload to sign to SignServer, retrieve the signature, and craft and store the attestation DSSE envelope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1690&#34; height=&#34;1168&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Signserver flow&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118521&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow.jpg 1690w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-300x207.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-1024x708.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-768x531.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-900x622.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-289x200.jpg 289w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-579x400.jpg 579w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 1690px) 100vw, 1690px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To verify the payload, just instruct Chainloop to do it using the public key and CA Chain. The CA chain is provided by EJBCA which also issued the signing certificate to the SignServer worker.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&amp;gt; chainloop workflow run describe --digest sha256:a1b2c3 \&#xA;&amp;nbsp; --verify true \&#xA;&amp;nbsp; --cert my-worker-key.pem \&#xA;&amp;nbsp; --chain ManagementCA.pem&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Local Signing with EJBCA ephemeral certificate&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EJBCA is a flexible, scalable, open-source PKI (Public Key Infrastructure) system that manages certificates for a wide range of use cases, such as Kubernetes workloads and digital signing. For more information, see &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ejbca.org/&#34;&gt;ejbca.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this integration, Chainloop can be configured to generate short-lived signing certs by using EJBCA as the certificate authority, enabling a user experience similar to Sigstore Fulcio’s “keyless” approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;2600&#34; height=&#34;1538&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview.png&#34; alt=&#34;ejbca overview&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118522&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview.png 2600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-300x177.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-1024x606.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-768x454.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-900x532.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-1800x1065.png 1800w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-338x200.png 338w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-676x400.png 676w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 2600px) 100vw, 2600px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are some key differences compared to the SignServer approach&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The client will not need access to the PKI infrastructure, and Chainloop will be in charge of exchanging the CLI identity for a short-lived certificate signed by EJBCA. Simplifying authentication.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The signing process will happen locally, in the client.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The verification materials and the final attestation can optionally be downloaded as a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sigstore/protobuf-specs/blob/29cc69d6ad77fc399cd8357820d2b062d0e8a83c/protos/sigstore_bundle.proto#L111&#34;&gt;Sigstore Bundle&lt;/a&gt; for further offline verification.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1455&#34; height=&#34;1070&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;flow&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118523&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow.jpg 1455w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-300x221.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-1024x753.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-768x565.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-900x662.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-272x200.jpg 272w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-544x400.jpg 544w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 1455px) 100vw, 1455px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To enable this feature, you’ll need to add your EJBCA settings to your Chainloop Helm Chart configuration, as explained &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.chainloop.dev/guides/ejbca/#configure-chainloop-to-use-ejbca-as-ca&#34;&gt;the guide: Configure Chainloop to use EJBCA as CA&lt;/a&gt;. Once you have done so, the attestation process will not require providing any signing material; the resulting attestation will be automatically signed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&amp;gt; chainloop attestation push&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Summary and what’s next&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Building a trusted, robust security framework for your software supply chain requires solutions that enforce security policies across your entire infrastructure, including PKI, signing, and the evidence store, and with the integrations presented today you get:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Generated and signed attestations that protect the integrity of the metadata from manipulation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;With the signed metadata, you can verify that the certificate associated with the private key used for signing was issued by a certificate authority (EJBCA) that your organization trusts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;By using Chainloop to manage and package the metadata, you have successfully organized and stored it, which can be audited and used to make &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.chainloop.dev/reference/policies&#34;&gt;actionable policy decisions.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;So, what’s next?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Combining &lt;strong&gt;Chainloop&lt;/strong&gt; with &lt;strong&gt;EJBCA&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;SignServer&lt;/strong&gt; for PKI gives you the foundation to enable automated compliance and security in your organization. This gives you a head start and future-proofs you for upcoming regulations or security practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the next blog post, we’ll show you how to take security and compliance to the next level by running Rego Policies against metadata signed using EJBCA and SignServer ephemeral certificates in a segmented architecture with all keys HSM-protected and centrally stored. Stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Glossary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Attestation: &lt;/strong&gt;A software attestation is an authenticated statement (metadata) about a software artifact or collection of software artifacts. For more information, see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://slsa.dev/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;slsa.dev&lt;/a&gt;. The primary intended use case is to feed into automated policy engines, such as in-toto and Binary Authorization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;One of the most popular attestation implementations is &lt;a href=&#34;http://in-toto.io/&#34;&gt;in-toto&lt;/a&gt;, an open-source framework for modeling software supply chain metadata, steps, and interrelations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Policy Agent and Rego: &lt;/strong&gt;Rego is a language used to write rules for the Open Policy Agent (OPA), a tool that helps control what actions are allowed or denied in a system. Rego policies define conditions that decide if something is permitted, such as who can access certain data or perform specific actions. For more information, see &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.openpolicyagent.org/&#34;&gt;openpolicyagent.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Exploitability eXchange (VEX): &lt;/strong&gt;A VEX document (Vulnerability Exploitability eXchange) is a document that communicates the status of vulnerabilities in software products. Produced by vendors or maintainers, it clarifies whether specific vulnerabilities affect their products and provides guidance on mitigation or resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;About the authors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;900&#34; height=&#34;900&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ben headshot&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118525&#34; style=&#34;width:231px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-300x300.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-150x150.jpg 150w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-768x768.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-200x200.jpg 200w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-400x400.jpg 400w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ben Dewberry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Product Manager, Signing and Key Management, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keyfactor.com/&#34;&gt;Keyfactor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Miguel headshot&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118524&#34; style=&#34;width:229px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino.jpg 400w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino-300x300.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino-150x150.jpg 150w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino-200x200.jpg 200w&#34; sizes=&#34;(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miguel Martinez Trivino&lt;/strong&gt;, Co-founder,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://chainloop.dev/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Chainloop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初发布于&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ejbca.org/resources/software-supply-chain-compliance-and-security-policies-with-signserver-ejbca-and -chainloop/&#34;&gt;EJBCA by Keyfactor&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://chainloop.dev/blog/securing-the-software-supply-chain-with-signserver-ejbca-and-chainloop-a-综合指南&#34;&gt;Chainloop 博客&lt;/a&gt;，作者：Keyfactor 签名和密钥管理产品经理 Ben Dewberry 和 Chainloop 联合创始人 Miguel Martinez Trivino&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;软件供应链是编写、测试、打包和分发软件时执行的一系列步骤。在此过程中，每一步都会生成有关软件构建内容和方式的信息。这称为元数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;软件物料清单 (SBOM) 是供应链元数据的典型示例，但更多示例分散在您的软件交付生命周期中，包括 QA 测试/报告、CVE 扫描、VEX、法律/安全/架构审查等.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;公司&lt;strong&gt;开始依赖此元数据做出关键决策&lt;/strong&gt;，例如是否将应用程序部署到银行系统，或者它是否容易受到攻击、合规等。这些决策的动机可能是：希望改善您的安全状况并&lt;a href=&#34;https://slsa.dev/spec/v0.1/levels?&#34;&gt;达到特定的 SLSA 级别&lt;/a&gt;或纯粹由现有法规（例如&lt;a href）推动=&#34;https://www.cisa.gov/topics/cybersecurity-best-practices/executive-order-improving-nations-cybersecurity&#34;&gt;美国的 EO 14028&lt;/a&gt; 或欧洲等即将推出的&lt;a href= “https://digital-strategy.ec.europa.eu/en/library/cyber-resilience-act&#34;&gt;网络弹性法案&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;但是，不可信的元数据是无用的，甚至是有害的。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是 Chainloop 和 Keyfactor 合作的原因，将 Chainloop 的模块化基于证据的元数据存储平台与 Keyfactor 的企业 PKI 解决方案、EJBCA 和 SignServer 集成。这些集成将使组织能够收集、验证、信任和保护其软件供应链生成的元数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们将推出两种集成：&lt;strong&gt;使用 Keyfactor 的 SignServer 进行远程签名，以及使用临时证书使用 Keyfactor 的 EJBCA 进行本地签名。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;实施此集成后，您将拥有坚实的基础，可以开始使此元数据&lt;strong&gt;可操作&lt;/strong&gt;用于实施自动化策略，控制允许在您的环境中运行的内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;使用 Chainloop、SignServer 和 EJBCA 设置元数据证据存储&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chainloop-dev/chainloop&#34;&gt;Chainloop&lt;/a&gt; 是一个开源证据存储，用于软件供应链证明、软件物料清单 (SBOM)、VEX 、SARIF、CSAF 文件、QA 报告等。发送到 Chainloop 的元数据将得到证明、签名、评估、路由和存储。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1949”高度=“1224”src=“https://www.cncf.io/wp” -content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;chainloop 概述&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118518&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024 /10/chainloop-overview.jpg 1949w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-300x188.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp -content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-1024x643.jpg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-768x482.jpg 768w，https:// /www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-900x565.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview- 1800x1130.jpg 1800w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-overview-318x200.jpg 318w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/ 2024/10/chainloop-overview-637x400.jpg 637w“尺寸=”（最大宽度：1949px）100vw，1949px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Chainloop 提供了一种固执己见但可插入的端到端解决方案。在这篇博文中，我们将向您概述如何使用 SignServer 和 EJBCA 配置 Chainloop 实例。结果将是一个端到端解决方案，该解决方案将创建使用 SignServer 和 EJBCA 签名的完整证明，并存储在 OCI 注册表中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“2125”高度=“1881”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers.png&#34; alt=&#34;chainloop 层&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118519&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/ 2024/10/chainloop-layers.png 2125w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-300x266.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-1024x906.png 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-768x680.png 768w，https： //www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-900x797.png 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers -1800x1593.png 1800w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/chainloop-layers-226x200.png 226w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads /2024/10/chainloop-layers-452x400.png 452w“尺寸=”（最大宽度：2125px）100vw，2125px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开始之前，您需要运行 SignServer、EJBCA 和 Chainloop。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要了解如何开始使用 EJBCA Community 作为 Docker 容器，您可以按照 &lt;a href=&#34;http://20.91.210.51:8090/display/EJBCADS/Quick+Start+Guide+-+Start+EJBCA +Container+with+Client+Certificate+Authenticated+Access&#34;&gt;快速入门指南 – 使用客户端证书验证访问启动 EJBCA 容器&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要了解如何开始使用 SignServer Community 作为 Docker 容器，您可以按照 &lt;a href=&#34;https://doc.primekey.com/signserver/tutorials-and-guides/quick-start-guide-启动signserver-container-with-client-certificate-authenticated-access&#34;&gt;快速启动指南 – 使用客户端证书验证访问启动 SignServer 容器&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要部署 Chainloop，您可以使用此 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chainloop-dev/chainloop/tree/main/devel#labs-environments&#34;&gt;docker compose 文件&lt; /a&gt; 或在 Kubernetes 集群中使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/chainloop-dev/chainloop/tree/main/deployment/chainloop&#34;&gt;Chainloop Helm Chart&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您现在应该有一个 SignServer、EJBCA 和一个正在运行的 Chainloop 实例，但 Chainloop 尚未配置为使用它们！  默认情况下，Chainloop 将使用 Sigstore 的 Cosign 密钥对签署证明。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们改变这一点！ Keyfactor 和 Chainloop 合作提供了两种集成来签署证明和工件，让您可以携带自己的 PKI：&lt;strong&gt;使用 SignServer 进行远程签名&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;使用 EJBCA 临时证书进行本地签名&lt;/strong&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;使用 SignServer 远程签名&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SignServer 是一款多功能且高性能的开源代码签名软件，可实现安全的加密签名操作。它对不同类型的工作负载（包括代码、工件、证明和容器）进行数字签名，以确保软件的完整性和真实性。有关详细信息，请参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;http://signserver.org/&#34;&gt;signserver.org&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此集成允许用户将证明有效负载发送到 SignServer 工作人员，然后再将其发送到 Chainloop 进行存储。将此视为类似 KMS 的方法，其中客户端环境可以访问 PKI 基础设施并发送数据以进行远程签名。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“2600”高度=“1538”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview.png&#34; alt=&#34;signserver 概述&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118520&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/ 2024/10/signserver-overview.png 2600w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-300x177.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-1024x606.png 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-768x454.png 768w，https： //www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-900x532.png 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview -1800x1065.png 1800w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-overview-338x200.png 338w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads /2024/10/signserver-overview-676x400.png 676w“尺寸=”（最大宽度：2600px）100vw，2600px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种方法的一些好处：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;密钥可以存储在硬件安全模块 (HSM) 上，在其中进行签名以提高安全性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;您可以利用此密钥与其他 SignServer 工作人员进行签名，以处理管道中的其他工件，例如二进制文件、文档等等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.chainloop.dev/guides/signserver/&#34;&gt;指南：使用 Keyfactor SignServer 进行证明签名&lt;/a&gt; 更详细地解释了此集成，但要点是您应该能够运行证明推送命令并让远程 SignServer 工作人员像这样签署证明。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&gt; chainloop 证明推送 --key signserver://mysignserver/my-signing-worker&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，集成会将要签名的有效负载发送到 SignServer，检索签名，并制作和存储证明 DSSE 信封。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1690”高度=“1168”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Signserver flow&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118521&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/ 2024/10/signserver-flow.jpg 1690w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-300x207.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-1024x708.jpg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-768x531.jpg 768w，https： //www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-900x622.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow -289x200.jpg 289w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/signserver-flow-579x400.jpg 579w“尺寸=”（最大宽度：1690px）100vw，1690px“引用政策=“无引用者”&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要验证有效负载，只需指示 Chainloop 使用公钥和 CA Chain 进行验证即可。 CA 链由 EJBCA 提供，EJBCA 还将签名证书颁发给 SignServer Worker。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&gt; chainloop工作流程运行describe --digest sha256:a1b2c3 \&#xA;  --验证真实\&#xA;  --cert my-worker-key.pem \&#xA;  --chain ManagementCA.pem&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;使用 EJBCA 临时证书进行本地签名&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;EJBCA 是一个灵活、可扩展的开源 PKI（公钥基础设施）系统，可管理各种用例的证书，例如 Kubernetes 工作负载和数字签名。有关详细信息，请参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ejbca.org/&#34;&gt;ejbca.org&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过这种集成，Chainloop 可以配置为使用 EJBCA 作为证书颁发机构来生成短期签名证书，从而实现类似于 Sigstore Fulcio 的“无密钥”方法的用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“2600”高度=“1538”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview.png&#34; alt=&#34;ejbca 概述&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118522&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/ 2024/10/ejbca-overview.png 2600w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-300x177.png 300w，https://www.cncf.io/ wp-内容/上传/2024/10/ejbca-overview-1024x606.png 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-768x454.png 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024 /10/ejbca-overview-900x532.png 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-1800x1065.png 1800w，https://www.cncf.io /wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-338x200.png 338w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-overview-676x400.png 676w”尺寸=“（最大宽度：2600px）100vw，2600px”referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与 SignServer 方法相比，存在一些关键差异&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;客户端不需要访问 PKI 基础设施，Chainloop 将负责将 CLI 身份交换为由 EJBCA 签名的短期证书。简化身份验证。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;签名过程将在客户端本地进行。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;验证材料和最终证明可以选择以 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sigstore/protobuf-specs/blob/29cc69d6ad77fc399cd8357820d2b062d0e8a83c/protos/sigstore_bundle.proto#L111&#34;&gt;Sigstore 捆绑包的形式下载&lt;/a&gt;进行进一步的离线验证。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class =“wp-block-image size-full”&gt;&lt;img加载=“lazy”解码=“异步”宽度=“1455”高度=“1070”src=“https://www.cncf.io/ wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;flow&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118523&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024 /10/ejbca-flow.jpg 1455w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-300x221.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp -content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-1024x753.jpg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-768x565.jpg 768w，https:/ /www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-900x662.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow- 272x200.jpg 272w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/ejbca-flow-544x400.jpg 544w“尺寸=”（最大宽度：1455px）100vw，1455px“referrerpolicy= “无推荐人”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要启用此功能，您需要将 EJBCA 设置添加到 Chainloop Helm Chart 配置中，如下所述 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.chainloop.dev/guides/ejbca/#configure-chainloop- to-use-ejbca-as-ca&#34;&gt;指南：配置 Chainloop 以使用 EJBCA 作为 CA&lt;/a&gt;。完成此操作后，认证过程将不需要提供任何签名材料；生成的证明将自动签名。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&gt; chainloop 证明推送&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;摘要和下一步&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为您的软件供应链构建可信、强大的安全框架需要能够在整个基础设施（包括 PKI、签名和证据存储）中实施安全策略的解决方案，并且通过今天介绍的集成，您可以获得：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;生成并签署证明，以保护元数据的完整性免遭操纵。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;无线网络通过签名的元数据，您可以验证与用于签名的私钥关联的证书是否由您的组织信任的证书颁发机构 (EJBCA) 颁发。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过使用 Chainloop 管理和打包元数据，您已成功组织和存储元数据，可以对其进行审核并用于使&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.chainloop.dev/reference/policies&#34;&gt;可操作政策决定。&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;那么，下一步是什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将 &lt;strong&gt;Chainloop&lt;/strong&gt; 与 PKI 的 &lt;strong&gt;EJBCA&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;SignServer&lt;/strong&gt; 相结合，为您在组织中实现自动化合规性和安全性奠定了基础。这可以让您抢占先机，并为您未来应对即将出台的法规或安全实践提供保障。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在下一篇博文中，我们将向您展示如何在分段架构中针对使用 EJBCA 和 SignServer 临时证书签名的元数据运行 Rego 策略，从而将安全性和合规性提升到新的水平，所有密钥均受 HSM 保护并集中存储。请继续关注！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;词汇表&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;软件证明：&lt;/strong&gt;软件证明是有关软件工件或软件工件集合的经过身份验证的声明（元数据）。有关详细信息，请参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;https://slsa.dev/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;slsa.dev&lt;/a&gt;。主要预期用例是馈入自动化策略引擎，例如 in-toto 和二进制授权。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;最流行的证明实现之一是 &lt;a href=&#34;http://in-toto.io/&#34;&gt;in-toto&lt;/a&gt;，它是一个用于建模软件供应链元数据的开源框架、步骤和相互关系。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;开放策略代理和 Rego：&lt;/strong&gt;Rego 是一种用于为开放策略代理 (OPA) 编写规则的语言，OPA 是一种帮助控制系统中允许或拒绝哪些操作的工具。 Rego 策略定义了决定是否允许某些操作的条件，例如谁可以访问某些数据或执行特定操作。有关详细信息，请参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.openpolicyagent.org/&#34;&gt;openpolicyagent.org&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;漏洞利用 eXchange (VEX)：&lt;/strong&gt;VEX 文档（漏洞利用 eXchange）是传达软件产品中漏洞状态的文档。它由供应商或维护人员制作，阐明特定漏洞是否影响其产品，并提供缓解或解决方案的指导。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;关于作者&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;900&#34;height=&#34;900&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf .io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;本头像&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118525&#34; style=&#34;width:231px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https: //www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry.jpg 900w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-300x300.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-150x150.jpg 150w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/ uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-768x768.jpg 768w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-200x200.jpg 200w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-200x200.jpg cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Ben-Dewberry-400x400.jpg 400w”尺寸=“（最大宽度：900px）100vw，900px”referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;本·杜伯里&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;产品经理，签名和密钥管理，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keyfactor.com/&#34;&gt;Keyfactor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;imgloading=&#34;lazy&#34;decoding=&#34;async&#34;width=&#34;400&#34;height=&#34;400&#34;src=&#34;https://www.cncf .io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Miguel headshot&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-118524&#34; style=&#34;width:229px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34; https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino.jpg 400w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel -Martinez-Trivino-300x300.jpg 300w，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino-150x150.jpg 150w，https://www.cncf.io /wp-content/uploads/2024/10/Miguel-Martinez-Trivino-200x200.jpg 200w“尺寸=”（最大宽度：400px）100vw，400px“referrerpolicy=“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miguel Martinez Trivino&lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://chainloop.dev/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Chainloop&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>