<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://rsshub.rssforever.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【CNCF and Synadia align on securing the future of the NATS.io project】CNCF和Synadia一致确保Nats.io项目的未来</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/01/cncf-and-synadia-align-on-securing-the-future-of-the-nats-io-project-2/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;CNCF and Synadia have come to an agreement to ensure that NATS continues to thrive as a healthy open source project within CNCF, with Synadia’s continued support and involvement. Please see our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/announcements/2025/05/01/cncf-and-synadia-align-on-securing-the-future-of-the-nats-io-project/&#34;&gt;joint announcement&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; CNCF和Synadia已达成协议，以确保NAT在CNCF内的健康开源项目中继续蓬勃发展，并继续支持和参与。请参阅我们的&lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/announcements/2025/05/01/cncf-and-synadia-align-align-align-align-an-securing-the-the-future-o-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------/-&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Open Source PaaS Cozystack Becomes a CNCF Sandbox Project】开源Paas sozystack成为CNCF沙箱项目</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/28/open-source-paas-cozystack-becomes-a-cncf-sandbox-project/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;On February 28, members of the CNCF Technical Oversight Committee completed their voting and unanimously accepted Cozystack, a platform for building private clouds and PaaS, into the CNCF Sandbox. The project is currently undergoing the onboarding process. Let’s break down what this means in practice, what Cozystack is, and what the CNCF Sandbox represents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What is Cozystack?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cozystack is an open-source platform that enables the creation of a bare metal cloud for deploying proven cloud-native and open-source tools: managed Kubernetes clusters, databases as a service, applications as a service, and virtual machines based on KubeVirt (see the full list of components). Cozystack also provides a ready-made stack for observability and alerting based on Victoria Metrics, Victoria Logs, Grafana, and Alerta.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Service and hosting providers, banks, SaaS solution vendors, medtech, fintech, AI/ML services, and other companies use Cozystack to offer customers managed services, managed Kubernetes, and databases that run directly on hardware, ensuring maximum performance and service stability. Additionally, Cozystack can be used to build geo-distributed clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The platform is developed and maintained by Ænix. The core developer and creator of Cozystack is Andrey Kvapil, known in the engineering community by the nickname “kvaps.” He is an active contributor to Linstor, KubeVirt, Kamaji, Kubernetes, Cilium, and others.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What Does It Mean for Users?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Transferring the project to the CNCF guarantees all Cozystack users that the platform will always be available under the Apache 2.0 license and will not suffer the fate of projects like Mongo, Redis, Terraform, and Vault, whose licenses were changed to closed-source and no longer comply with the Open Source Initiative criteria. From this point forward, the rights to Cozystack belong to the non-profit industry organization, the CNCF.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, inclusion in the CNCF provides an opportunity to engage a broad engineering community in the development and use of Cozystack, making project management more transparent. Expanding the base of contributors and users will, in turn, significantly accelerate the platform’s development and the exploration of a wide range of use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Andrey Kvapil, CEO of Ænix and creator of Cozystack:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I believe in honest and genuine open source, in the tools we use to build the platform, and I am happy that we can be useful to the community. In just one year, our small team of excellent engineers, with the support of our clients and the open-source community, has created a project worthy of inclusion in the CNCF. This is truly a significant achievement. Thank you to everyone who believed in us and supported us throughout this time. We will continue to improve the platform and plan to apply for CNCF Incubating status this fall. From an engineering perspective, we are already a mature project and ready for this. The main task now is to refine the project management process and community interaction.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Matthew Robin, CEO &amp;amp; Founder of Hidora:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;Cozystack represents a significant advancement in simplifying complex cloud infrastructure deployment. Its integration into the CNCF Sandbox marks an important milestone that will accelerate its adoption and enrich its ecosystem through community collaboration. We are confident that Cozystack will play a key role in democratizing cloud-native technologies for businesses of all sizes.&lt;/em&gt;“&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kingdon Barrett, FluxCD &amp;amp; Cozystack maintainer:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Cozystack combines cutting edge open source cloud native technologies in a way that I could probably set up myself, the hard way, if I wanted to spend 6 months figuring out how they fit together. It’s Talos Linux, configured as a cloud on bare metal, ready in half an hour or so!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ænix will continue to actively develop the platform and support both clients and community users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What’s next?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our dev team is currently wrapping up GPU support for virtual machines, and we’re actively testing the new functionality. This will make it possible to run AI and ML workloads directly on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can check out what else we’re working on in our &lt;a href=&#34;https://cozystack.io/docs/roadmap&#34;&gt;public roadmap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Useful Links&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cozystack.io/&#34;&gt;Cozystack Website&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cozystack&#34;&gt;GitHub&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://t.me/cozystack&#34;&gt;Telegram Community&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.k8s.io/&#34;&gt;Slack Community&lt;/a&gt; (registration in the Kubernetes Slack workspace required)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://calendar.google.com/calendar/embed?src=cozystack.io&#34;&gt;Community Meeting Calendar&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtube.com/cozystack&#34;&gt;Cozystack Community Meetings Recordings&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;Cozystack on CNCF Landscape&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/sandbox-projects/&#34;&gt;Cozystack in CNCF Sandbox&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devstats.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;Cozystack on Devstat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; 2月28日，CNCF技术监督委员会的成员完成了他们的投票，并一致接受了Cozystack，这是一个建造私有云和PAAS的平台，用于CNCF Sandbox。该项目目前正在进行入职过程。让我们分解这在实践中的含义，什么是sozystack以及CNCF沙盒所代表的内容。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;什么是cozystack？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; cozystack是一个开源平台，它可以创建裸露的金属云，用于部署经过验证的云本地和开源工具：托管Kubernetes群集，数据库作为服务，应用程序作为服务以及基于Kubevirt的虚拟机（请参阅组件的完整列表）。 Cozystack还提供了一个现成的堆栈，以根据维多利亚指标，维多利亚日志，Grafana和Alerta进行可观察性和警报。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;服务和托管提供商，银行，SaaS解决方案供应商，MedTech，Fintech，AI/ML服务以及其他公司使用CozyStack为客户提供托管服务，托管Kubernetes以及直接在硬件上运行的数据库，以确保最高的性能和服务稳定性。此外，Cozystack可用于构建地理分布的簇。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该平台由Énix开发和维护。 Cozystack的核心开发人员和创建者是Andrey Kvapil，在工程社区中以“ Kvaps”为名。他是Linstor，Kubevirt，Kamaji，Kubernetes，Cilium等的积极贡献者。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;对用户意味着什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将项目转移到CNCF可以保证所有Cozystack用户，即该平台将始终在Apache 2.0许可下可用，并且不会遭受Mongo，Redis，Terraform和Vault等项目的命运，其许可证已更改为封闭消息，并且不再遵守开源启动标准。从这一点开始，Cozystack的权利属于非营利性行业组织CNCF。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;此外，&lt;p&gt;包含在CNCF中，提供了一个机会，可以使广泛的工程社区参与Cozystack的开发和使用，从而使项目管理更加透明。扩大贡献者和用户的基础将大大加快平台的开发和探索广泛的用例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ænix首席执行官和Cozystack的创建者Andrey Kvapil：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我相信我们用来建立平台的工具，我很高兴我们能对社区有用。在短短一年内，我们的优秀工程师的小型团队在我们的客户和开源社区的支持下，为您提供了一个值得一提的是，这是一个非常重要的计划。这是一个重要的计划。申请今年秋天的CNCF状态Gineering的观点，我们已经是一个成熟的项目，并为此做好了准备。现在的主要任务是完善项目管理过程和社区互动。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Hidora的首席执行官兼创始人Matthew Robin：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“ &lt;em&gt; cozystack在简化复杂的云基础架构部署方面是一个重大进步。其集成到CNCF沙箱中标志着一个重要的里程碑，它将加速其采用并通过社区协作来丰富其生态系统。我们将在Cozystack中发挥着重要的作用。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;金登·巴雷特（Kingdon Barrett），Fluxcd＆Cozystack维护者：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“ cozystack结合了最前沿的开源云本地技术，我可能可以设置自己，如果我想花6个月的时间来弄清楚它们如何结合在一起。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ænix将继续积极开发平台并支持客户和社区用户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;下一步是什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的开发团队目前正在整理对虚拟机的GPU支持，我们正在积极测试新功能。这将使直接在平台上运行AI和ML工作负载。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以查看我们在&lt;a href =“ https://cozystack.io/docs/roadmap”&gt;公共路线图&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;中的其他工作。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;有用的链接&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://cozystack.io/”&gt; cozystack网站&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cozystack”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://t.me/cozystack”&gt; Telegram社区&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://slack.k8s.io/”&gt; Slack Community &lt;/a&gt;（需要在Kubernetes Slack Slack Workspace中进行注册）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://calendar.google.com/calendar/embed?src=cozystack.io”&gt;社区会议日历&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://youtube.com/cozystack”&gt; Cozystack社区会议录音&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://landscape.cncf.io/”&gt; cncf landscape上的cozystack &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/sandbox-projects/”&gt; cncf sandbox中的cozystack &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://devstats.cncf.io/”&gt; devstat上的cozystack &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Vitess 22】宣布健身22</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/29/announcing-vitess-22/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The Vitess maintainers are happy to announce the release of version &lt;em&gt;22.0.0&lt;/em&gt;, along with version &lt;em&gt;2.15.0&lt;/em&gt; of the Vitess Kubernetes Operator. This release is the first to benefit from a 6-month-long development cycle, after our &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vitessio/enhancements/pull/12&#34;&gt;recent change to the release cadence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Version 22.0.0 comes with significant enhancements to query serving and cluster management. These changes have allowed Vitess to be more performant and easier to operate compared to version 21. This blog post highlights some of the major changes that went into the release. For a more detailed description of the release, please refer to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vitessio/vitess/releases/tag/v22.0.0&#34;&gt;the release notes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;——————————————————————————————————————————&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Summary&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Query Serving: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prepared statements and new VTGate metrics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cluster Management and VTOrc: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stalled-disk recovery, improved errant GTID discovery and VTOrc performance improvements&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes Operator: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Automated backups, Kubernetes 1.32 support, better examples&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;Improvements compared to v21.0.0&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Query Serving&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vitess 22.0 brings a host of query‑serving enhancements focused on observability, smarter handling of prepared statements, GA support for sharded views, and feature‑complete atomic distributed transactions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Observability&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vitess now emits metrics for query execution plans, which help you analyze execution patterns and optimize costly plans—see the&lt;a href=&#34;https://vitess.io/docs/22.0/reference/query-serving/metrics/&#34;&gt; Query Serving metrics guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Prepared Statements&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have overhauled VTGate’s prepare pipeline: prepared statements are cached as raw SQL to skip redundant parsing, and deferred execution plans are generated using actual bind values for more optimized, parameter‑aware planning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h5 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Views and Atomic Distributed Transactions&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sharded view support is GA now, and the atomic distributed transaction feature is complete—learn more in the&lt;a href=&#34;https://vitess.io/docs/22.0/reference/features/distributed-transaction/&#34;&gt; Distributed Transactions guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Cluster Management and VTOrc&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There were several performance and usability enhancements to VTOrc in the Vitess 22.0 release. It now operates more efficiently, with fewer topology service calls and better overall resource consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;VTOrc now supports specifying shard ranges in the `–keyspaces-to-watch` flag, making it easier to configure in large deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release also introduces stalled disk recovery to VTOrc, along with improved handling of errant GTID detection. Additionally, vttablets are now prevented from joining the replication topology if they contain errant GTIDs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, we’ve added a new semi-sync monitor to VTOrc. This helps detect and unblock vttablets that are stuck waiting for semi-sync ACKs – a situation that can occur if ACKs are lost due to network issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Operator&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The v22.0.0 release of Vitess comes along with the v2.15.0 release of our Kubernetes operator. This new release follows the same release cycle as Vitess. As part of this release, the officially supported Kubernetes version is v1.32.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The original implementation of automated and scheduled backups done in v2.13.0 used an empty pod running &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;vtctldclient BackupShard&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to execute the backup. This approach had trade-offs, the backup process ran faster but effectively removed a serving tablet from the available tablet pool. In v2.15.0, we have changed the implementation to use a VTBackup pod instead, to be consistent with our own recommendations for production deployments and to reduce impact on availability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All our provided examples have been enhanced to illustrate how the VitessOperator and VitessCluster can be run in two different namespaces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/planetscale/vitess-operator/releases/tag/v2.15.0&#34;&gt;operator release notes&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about v2.15.0.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Performance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this release, we have reduced query latency and cut memory allocations across Vitess through targeted optimizations:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;gRPC Codec upgrade&lt;/strong&gt;: Vitess now uses gRPC with Codec v2 and a pooled buffer, yielding a ~3% QPS improvement and ~13% reduction in per‑request allocations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Normalizer AST walk reduction&lt;/strong&gt;: Merged two normalization AST passes into one, speeding VTGate’s normalizer by ~5% and cutting allocations per operation by ~5.5%.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AST rewriting optimization&lt;/strong&gt;: Combined RewriteAST and Normalizer into a single pass, trimming planner latency by ~2.7% and reducing allocations by ~4.3%.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Merge‑sort avoidance on single‑shard queries&lt;/strong&gt;: VTGate now skips redundant merge sorts when only one shard is involved, eliminating unnecessary CPU work for the common single‑shard case.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;——————————————————————————————————————————&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Migrate and Learn More&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To ease migration from a previous version to &lt;em&gt;v22.0.0&lt;/em&gt;, it is highly recommended to read the release notes of both &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vitessio/vitess/releases/tag/v22.0.0&#34;&gt;Vitess&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/planetscale/vitess-operator/releases/tag/v2.15.0&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Operator&lt;/a&gt;. The entire &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vitessio/vitess/blob/main/changelog/22.0/22.0.0/changelog.md&#34;&gt;changelog&lt;/a&gt; for this version is available too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is also recommended to explore our &lt;a href=&#34;https://vitess.io/docs/22.0/&#34;&gt;documentation for &lt;em&gt;v22.0.0&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;where you can find step-by-step user guides, best practices, and tips to run Vitess.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Community&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an open-source project, we truly appreciate feedback, insights, and contributions from our community. Whether you want to share a story, ask a question, or anything else, you can reach out to us on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vitessio/vitess&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; or in our &lt;a href=&#34;http://vitess.io/slack&#34;&gt;Slack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;——————————————————————————————————————————&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Vitess Maintainer Team&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Vitess维护者很乐意宣布版本&lt;em&gt; 22.0.0 &lt;/em&gt;以及Vitess Kubernetes操作员的版本&lt;em&gt; 2.15.0 &lt;/em&gt;。此版本是我们&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/vitessio/enhancements/pull/12”之后的第一个从6个月长的开发周期中受益的版本。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;版本22.0.0对查询服务和群集管理具有重大增强功能。与版本21相比，这些更改使Vitess更具性能和更易于操作。本博客文章突出了该版本中的一些主要更改。有关版本的更详细说明，请参阅&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/vitessio/vitess/releases/tag/v22.0.0”&gt;发行说明&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ————————————————————————————————————————— &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;查询服务：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;准备的语句和新的VTGATE指标&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;群集管理和VTORC：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;停滞磁盘恢复，改进的错误GTID发现和VTORC性能改进&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kubernetes操作员：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;自动备份，kubernetes 1.32支持，更好的示例&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;性能：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;与V21.0.0.0 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;相比&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;查询服务&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Vitess 22.0带来了许多查询性增强功能，重点是可观察性，更明智地处理准备的陈述，对碎片视图的GA支持以及功能 - 完整的原子分布式交易。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h5 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;可观察性&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Vitess现在发布了查询执行计划的指标，可以帮助您分析执行模式并优化昂贵的计划 - 请参阅&lt;a a href =“ https://vitess.io/docs/22.0/2.0/reference/query/query-serving/query-serving/query-serving/metrics/metrics/metrics/”&gt; QUERY SERVing Metrics指南&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h5 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;准备的语句&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经大修了Vtgate的准备管道：准备好的陈述作为RAW SQL缓存，以跳过冗余解析，并使用实际绑定值来生成延期的执行计划，以进行更优化的参数意识计划。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h5 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;视图和原子分布式交易&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;碎片视图支持现在是GA，并且原子分布式事务功能已完成 - 在&lt;a a href =“ https://vitess.io/docs/22.0/reference/features/distributed-transaction/”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;集群管理和VTORC &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Vitess 22.0版本中，VTORC有几种性能和可用性提高。现在，它的运行效率更高，拓扑服务较少和更好的总体资源消耗。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; VTORC现在支持`–keyspaces-to中指定碎片范围-watch`标志，使得更容易在大型部署中配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本还向VTORC引入了停滞的磁盘恢复，并改善了错误的GTID检测的处理。此外，如果VTTABLETS包含错误的GTID，则可以防止它们加入复制拓扑。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，我们已向VTORC添加了一个新的半同步显示器。这有助于检测并解开粘贴的vttbablets等待半同步ACKS  - 如果由于网络问题而丢失ACK，这种情况可能会发生。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; kubernetes操作员&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; V22.0.0 Vitess的释放与我们的Kubernetes操作员的v2.15.0释放相同。这个新版本遵循与Vitess相同的发行周期。作为此版本的一部分，正式支持的Kubernetes版本为v1.32。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在v2.13.0中完成的自动化和计划备份的原始实现使用了一个空的POD &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; vtctldclient backupshard &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;执行备份。这种方法进行了权衡，备份过程的运行速度更快，但有效地从可用的平板电脑池中删除了一份平板电脑。在v2.15.0中，我们更改了使用VTbackup POD的实现，以与我们自己的生产部署建议一致并减少对可用性的影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们所有提供的示例都得到了增强，以说明如何在两个不同的名称空间中运行Vitessoperator和VitessCluster。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请参阅&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/planetscale/vitess-operator/releases/tag/v2.15.0”&gt;操作员发行笔记&lt;/a&gt;以了解有关v2.15.0的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;性能&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此版本中，我们通过目标优化减少了查询潜伏期和削减了整个Vitess的记忆分配：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; GRPC编解码器升级&lt;/strong&gt;：Vitess现在使用编解码器V2和合并缓冲液的GRPC，可提高约3％的QPS，每次要求分配降低约13％。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;标准化器AST步行减少&lt;/strong&gt;：合并两个归一化的AST逐渐变成一个，使VTGATE的标准化器加快了〜5％，每次操作分配〜5.5％。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; AST重写优化&lt;/strong&gt;：将重写和标准式组合成单个通过，将计划者延迟提高〜2.7％，并将分配减少〜4.3％。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;单影查询避免避免使用合并&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;：VTGATE现在仅涉及一个碎片时跳过冗余合并，消除了不必要的CPU在常见的单影案例中工作。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ————————————————————————————————————————— &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;迁移并了解更多&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了简化从以前的版本迁移到&lt;em&gt; v22.0.0 &lt;/em&gt;，强烈建议阅读这两个&lt;a href =&#39;https：// github.com/vitessio/vitess/releases/tag/tag/v22.0&#34;&gt; vitess &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/planetscale/planetscale/vitess-operator/releator/releases/releases/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag/tag&gt; kubernetes&#39;s&gt; Kubernetes&#39;s&gt; href =“ https://github.com/vitessio/vitess/blob/main/main/changelog/22.0/22.0.0.0.0/changelog.md”&gt; changelog &lt;/a&gt;此版本也可用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;还建议探索我们的&lt;a href =“ https://vitess.io/docs/22.0/”&gt; &lt;em&gt; v22.0.0.0.0 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;的文档，您可以在其中找到逐步逐步的用户，最佳实践，最佳实践，最佳练习，vitess。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;社区&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为一个开源项目，我们非常感谢我们社区的反馈，见解和贡献。无论您是想分享一个故事，问一个问题还是其他任何事情，都可以通过&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/vitessio/vitess”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt;与我们联系，或者在我们的&lt;a href =“ http://vitess.io/slack”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ————————————————————————————————————————— &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; Vitess维护者团队&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Istio publishes results of ztunnel security audit】ISTIO发布了Ztunnel安全审核的结果</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/23/istio-publishes-results-of-ztunnel-security-audit/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Passes with flying colors&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio’s ambient mode splits the service mesh into two distinct layers: Layer 7 processing (the “&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/waypoint/&#34;&gt;waypoint proxy&lt;/a&gt;”), which remains powered by the traditional Envoy proxy; and a secure overlay (the “zero-trust tunnel” or “&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel&#34;&gt;ztunnel&lt;/a&gt;”), which is &lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2023/rust-based-ztunnel/&#34;&gt;a new codebase&lt;/a&gt;, written from the ground up in Rust.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is our intention that the ztunnel project be safe to install by default in every Kubernetes cluster, and to that end, it needs to be secure and performant.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We comprehensively demonstrated ztunnel’s performance, showing that it is &lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2025/ambient-performance/&#34;&gt;the highest-bandwidth way to achieve a secure zero-trust network in Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; — providing higher TCP throughput than even in-kernel data planes like IPsec and WireGuard — and that its performance has increased by 75% over the past 4 releases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we are excited to validate the security of ztunnel, publishing &lt;a href=&#34;https://ostif.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Istio-Ztunnel-Final-Summary-Report-1.pdf&#34;&gt;the results of an audit of the codebase&lt;/a&gt; performed by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.trailofbits.com/&#34;&gt;Trail of Bits&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We would like to thank the &lt;a href=&#34;https://cncf.io/&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Computing Foundation&lt;/a&gt; for funding this work, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ostif.org/istio-ztunnel-audit-complete/&#34;&gt;OSTIF for its coordination&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Scope and overall findings&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio has been assessed in &lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2021/ncc-security-assessment/&#34;&gt;2020&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2023/ada-logics-security-assessment/&#34;&gt;2023&lt;/a&gt;, with the Envoy proxy &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/envoyproxy/envoy#security-audit&#34;&gt;receiving independent assessment&lt;/a&gt;. The scope of this review was the new code in Istio’s ambient mode, the ztunnel component: specifically code relating to L4 authorization, inbound request proxying, transport-layer security (TLS), and certificate management.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The auditors stated that “the ztunnel codebase is well-written and structured”, and had no findings relating to vulnerabilities in the code. Their three findings — one of medium severity and two of informational — refer to recommendations regarding external factors, including software supply chain and testing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Resolution and suggested improvements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Improving dependency management&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the time of the audit, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://crates.io/crates/cargo-audit&#34;&gt;cargo audit&lt;/a&gt; report for ztunnel’s dependencies showed three versions with current security advisories. There was no suggestion that any vulnerable code paths in ztunnel dependencies could be reached, and the maintainers would regularly update the dependencies to the latest appropriate versions. To streamline this, we’ve &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1400&#34;&gt;adopted GitHub’s Dependabot&lt;/a&gt; for automated updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The auditors pointed out the risk of Rust crates in the dependency chain of ztunnel that either unmaintained or maintained by a single owner. This is a common situation in the Rust ecosystem (and indeed all of open source). We replaced the two crates that were explicitly identified.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Enhancing test coverage&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Trail of Bits team found that most ztunnel functionality is well-tested, but identified some error-handling code paths which were not covered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://mutants.rs/&#34;&gt;mutation testing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We evaluated the suggestions and found that the gaps in coverage highlighted by these results apply to test code, and to code that does not affect correctness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While mutation testing is useful to identify potential areas to improve, the goal is not to get to a point where a report returns no results. Mutations can trigger no test failures in a number of expected cases, such as behavior with no ‘correct’ result (e.g., log messages), behavior that impacts only performance but not correctness (measured outside of the scope the tooling is aware of), code paths that have multiple ways to achieve the same result, or code used only for testing. Testing and security is a core priority for the Istio team and we are constantly improving our test coverage — using tools like mutation testing and by &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.howardjohn.info/posts/ztunnel-testing/&#34;&gt;developing novel solutions&lt;/a&gt; to testing proxies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Hardening HTTP header parsing&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A third-party library was used for parsing the value of the HTTP &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/HTTP/Reference/Headers/Forwarded&#34;&gt;Forwarded&lt;/a&gt; header, which may be present on connections made to ztunnel. The auditors pointed out that header parsing is a common area of attack, and expressed concern that the library we used was not fuzz tested. Given that we were only using this library for parsing one header, we &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1418&#34;&gt;wrote a custom parser for the Forwarded header&lt;/a&gt;, complete with a fuzzing harness to test it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Get involved&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With strong performance and now validated security, ambient mode continues to advance the state of the art in service mesh design. We encourage you to try it out today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you would like to get involved with Istio product security, or become a maintainer, we’d love to have you! Join &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.istio.io/&#34;&gt;our Slack workspace&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/community/blob/master/WORKING-GROUPS.md&#34;&gt;our public meetings&lt;/a&gt; to raise issues or learn about what we are doing to keep Istio secure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;与飞行色彩通过&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; istio的环境模式将服务网格分为两个不同的层：第7层处理（“ &lt;a href =” https://istio.io.io.io/latest/docs/bambient/usage/usage/waypoint/“&gt; waypoint Proxy Proxy &lt;/a&gt;”），仍然由传统的传统源发动机驱动； and a secure overlay (the “zero-trust tunnel” or “&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel&#34;&gt;ztunnel&lt;/a&gt;”), which is &lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/blog/2023/rust-based-ztunnel/&#34;&gt;a new codebase&lt;/a&gt;, written from the ground up in生锈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的意图是，默认情况下，Ztunnel项目可以安全地安装在每个Kubernetes群集中，为此，它需要安全且性能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们全面证明了Ztunnel的表现，表明它是&lt;a href =“ https：//istio.io.io.io/latest/blog/2025/ambient-performance/”&gt;最高的方法是实现kubernetes and the tcp and tht Planse的最高范围，以实现安全的零-trust Network &lt;/a&gt;  - 甚至是ITIP的数据 - 在过去的4个发行版中，其性能增长了75％。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们很高兴验证Ztunnel的安全性，发布&lt;a href =“ https://ostif.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/04/istio-ztunnel-final-summary-summary-report-report-1.pdf- href =“ https://www.trailofbits.com/”&gt; BITS的踪迹&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们要感谢&lt;a href =“ https://cncf.io/”&gt;云本机计算基金会&lt;/a&gt;为这项工作提供资金，&lt;a href =“ https://ostif.org/istio-ztunnel-audit-complete/&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;范围和整体发现&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; iStio已在&lt;a href =“ https://istio.io.io.io.io.io/latest/blog/2021/ncc-security-assessment/”&gt; 2020 &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“代理&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/envoyproxy/envoy#security-audit”&gt;接受独立评估&lt;/a&gt;。此评论的范围是ISTIO环境模式下的新代码，即Ztunnel组件：专门与L4授权，入站请求代理，运输层安全性（TLS）和证书管理有关的代码。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;审计师说：“ Ztunnel代码库是写得很好且结构化的”，并且没有与代码中漏洞有关的发现。他们的三个发现 - 中等严重性和两个信息的发现 - 是指有关外部因素的建议，包括软件供应链和测试。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;分辨率和建议的改进&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;改善依赖关系管理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在审核时，&lt;a href =“ https://crates.io/crates/cargo-audit”&gt;货物审核&lt;/a&gt; Ztunnel依赖关系的报告显示了三个具有当前安全咨询的版本。没有建议在ztunnel依赖关系中有任何脆弱的代码路径cou可以联系LD，并且维护人员会定期将依赖项更新为最新的适当版本。要简化此内容，我们&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1400”&gt;通过GitHub的Dispripabot &lt;/a&gt;用于自动化更新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;审计师指出，在Ztunnel的依赖关系链中，由单个所有者毫不生计或维护的依赖性链条中有生锈的风险。这是锈生态系统（甚至是所有开源）中的普遍情况。我们更换了明确识别的两个板条箱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;增强测试覆盖范围&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;小组的踪迹发现大多数Ztunnel功能都经过了经过测试，但确定了一些错误处理代码路径，这些路径未覆盖，这些路径未涵盖，&lt;a href =“ https：//mutants.rs/”&gt;突变测试&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;我们评估了这些建议，并发现了这些范围，以适用于覆盖范围，以适用于覆盖范围，以适用于范围，以适用于结果，并在结果上处理了结果。正确性。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;虽然突变测试对于确定可以改进的潜在领域很有用，但目标不是要达到报告没有返回结果的地步。突变可以触发许多预期案例中没有测试失败，例如没有“正确”结果的行为（例如，日志消息），仅影响性能但不正确的行为（在工具范围之外测量工具所意识到的范围之外），具有多种方法可以实现相同结果或仅用于测试的代码的代码路径。测试和安全性是ISTIO团队的核心优先事项，我们正在不断改进测试覆盖范围 - 使用突变测试和&lt;a href =“ https://blog.howardjohn.info/posts/posts/ztunnel-testing/”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用第三方库来解析http &lt;a href =“ https://developer.mozilla.org/en-us/us/docs/web/web/http/reference/headers/headers/forwarded”&gt;转发&lt;/a&gt; header to to ztunnel的连接。审计师指出，标题解析是一个常见的攻击领域，并表示对我们使用的库未经过模糊测试表示担忧。 Given that we were only using this library for parsing one header, we &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/ztunnel/pull/1418&#34;​​&gt;wrote a custom parser for the Forwarded header&lt;/a&gt;, complete with a fuzzing harness to test it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;参与&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;具有强大的性能并验证了安全性，环境模式继续推进服务网格设计中的最新状态。我们鼓励您今天尝试一下。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;如果您想参与ISTIO产品安全，或者成为维护者，我们很乐意拥有您！加入&lt;a href =“ https://slack.istio.io/”&gt;我们的松懈工作区&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/istio/community/community/community/community/blob/master/master/working-groups.md-.md&gt;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【LitmusChaos at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025: A Recap】Kubecon + Cloudnativecon欧洲2025年的Litmuschaos：回顾</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/25/litmuschaos-at-kubecon-cloudnativecon-europe-2025-a-recap/</link>
      <description>【&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;468&#34; height=&#34;246&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;LitmusChaos at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130426&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso.jpg 468w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso-300x158.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso-388x204.jpg 388w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso-380x200.jpg 380w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 468px) 100vw, 468px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The cloud native community recently converged in London from April 1 – 4, 2025, for an incredible edition of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe. From our perspective at LitmusChaos, it was a week filled with inspiring sessions, engaging booth interactions, and deep discussions about the future of chaos engineering.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sessions That Made an Impact&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LitmusChaos played a central role throughout the event with two key sessions that provided deep insights into our journey and the broader realm of chaos engineering in cloud native systems:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Lightning Talk:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/beAoZ2fI-QQ?si=eHo4hEKQIVLrquOm&#34;&gt;Project Lightning Talk: Chaos Unleashed: LitmusChaos and Its Journey Towards CNCF Graduation – Vedant Shrotria, Maintainer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We explored the essence of LitmusChaos and its roadmap to becoming a CNCF Graduated project&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;Maintainer Track Talk:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/6GjLzWtqjlw?si=8Ob1_4FCq7pzS1Bs&#34;&gt;Driving Chaos Engineering Forward: What’s New and Next With LitmusChaos – Sarthak Jain &amp;amp; Saranya Jena, Harness&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This session delved into our latest features, covering enhancements in resilience testing, observability, and scalability, and discussed challenges faced by developers and SREs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;468&#34; height=&#34;264&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/floor.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130429&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/floor.jpg 468w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/floor-300x169.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/floor-355x200.jpg 355w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 468px) 100vw, 468px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Booth Highlights: Engaging Demos and Discussions&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At our booth, we connected with a diverse audience ranging from seasoned chaos engineering experts and existing 2.x users to beginners exploring reliability for the first time. Key topics discussed at the booth included:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IAM Integration for Cloud Providers Based Chaos Faults:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Demonstrations showcased how LitmusChaos integrates with various cloud IAM systems to simulate and mitigate faults in a secure environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Chaos Injection in CI/CD:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Through tools like LitmusCTL, SDKs, and Terraform, we explored how to incorporate chaos experiments seamlessly into CI/CD pipelines, making resilience a natural part of development cycles.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tool Comparisons:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detailed conversations compared various chaos engineering tools, helping attendees understand LitmusChaos’ unique capabilities and positioning in the ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BYOC (Bring Your Own Chaos) – Litmus vs. Harness:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Participants engaged in comparative discussions that shed light on best practices and unique approaches between LitmusChaos and other platforms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Foundations of Chaos Engineering:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those new to the field, our booth served as an educational hub, where core concepts and benefits of chaos engineering were introduced.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Types of Chaos Faults&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;We discussed various fault categories from Kubernetes/Linux specific issues to those related to cloud providers and how our solutions address them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upgrade from 2.x to 3.x:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We listened to community feedback about our 2.x versions and shared insights on transitioning to 3.x, highlighting improvements and new features.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reflecting on a Successful Engagement&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The event was an opportunity for us to reconnect with our community and engage in meaningful dialogue. From clarifying doubts to brainstorming on innovation, every interaction enriched our collective understanding of building resilient cloud native systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;468&#34; height=&#34;313&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/podium-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130430&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/podium-1.png 468w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/podium-1-300x201.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/podium-1-299x200.png 299w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 468px) 100vw, 468px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay Connected with LitmusChaos&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even though KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025 has wrapped up, the conversation continues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re an open, welcoming space for chaos engineering enthusiasts, platform engineers, reliability folks, contributors, or anyone simply curious to learn more about building resilient systems. And we’d love to have you join us!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how you can get involved:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Visit the &lt;a href=&#34;https://litmuschaos.io/&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos website&lt;/a&gt; to learn about the project, use cases, architecture, and everything chaos engineering.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Join the conversation on the &lt;strong&gt;#litmus &lt;/strong&gt;channel in the Kubernetes Slack, ask questions, share ideas, or just hang out with the community.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the project! Check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/blob/master/CONTRIBUTING.md&#34;&gt;Contributing Guide&lt;/a&gt; and start with an issue, suggestion, or PR — every contribution counts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Subscribe to the LitmusChaos YouTube Channel for community meetings, demos, tutorials, and project updates.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Follow &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/LitmusChaos&#34;&gt;@LitmusChaos on Twitter/X&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/company/litmuschaos&#34;&gt;@litmuschaos on LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; for the latest news, release updates, and community shoutouts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Explore the &lt;a href=&#34;https://litmuschaos.io/blog&#34;&gt;LitmusChaos blog&lt;/a&gt; for stories, tutorials, and deep dives. Want to share your own experience with Litmus? Publish a blog on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dev.to/litmus-chaos&#34;&gt;DEV.to&lt;/a&gt; and tag it with &lt;strong&gt;#litmuschaos&lt;/strong&gt;, we’d love to read it!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we reflect on the success and learnings from KubeCon + CloudNativeCon Europe 2025, we appreciate everyone who participated and shared their valuable insights, and we look forward to our next chapter in creating resilient systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for being part of our journey. Cheers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 468”高度=“ 246” kubecon + Cloudnativecon欧洲2025“ class =” wp-image-130426“ srcset =” https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso.jpg 468w，468w，468w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso-300x158.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso-194x102.jpg 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso-388x204.jpg 388w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/litmus-chaso-380x200.jpg 380W“ sizes =” auto，（最大宽度：468px）100VW，468px“ referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云土著社区最近从2025年4月1日至4日在伦敦汇聚，为库贝康 + Cloudnativecon欧洲提供了令人难以置信的版本。从我们在Litmuschaos的角度来看，这是一个充满鼓舞人心的会议，引人入胜的展位互动以及关于混乱工程未来的深入讨论的一周。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;会议&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; litmuschaos在整个活动中发挥了核心作用，并提供了两个关键会议，可深入了解我们的旅程和云本地系统中混乱工程的更广泛领域：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 1。 &lt;strong&gt;闪电谈话：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://youtu.be/beaoz2fi-qq?si=eho4ho4hekqivlrquom”&gt;项目闪电谈话：chaos unleashed：litmuschaos及其进入CNCF毕业的旅程 -  Vedant Shrotria，Vester Shrotria，维护者&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们探索了Litmuschaos及其成为CNCF分级项目的路线图&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 2。 &lt;strong&gt;维护器跟踪说话：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://youtu.be/6gjlzwtqjlw?si=8ob1_4fcq7pzss1bs”&gt;驾驶Chaos Engineering Forward：与LITMUSCHAOS  -  Sarthak Jain＆Sarthak Jain＆Saranya＆Saranya Jena，Harness &lt;/harness &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本届会议深入了我们的最新功能，涵盖了弹性测试，可观察性和可伸缩性的增强功能，并讨论了开发人员和SRES面临的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dexoding =“ async” width =“ 468”高=“ 264” src =“ https://wwwww.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/2025/2025/2025/04/04/floor.floor.floor.floor.floor.jpgloor.jpgg” class =“ wp-image-130429” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/floor.jpg 468w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/floor-300x169.jpg 300W，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/20255/2025/2025/204/04/floor-floor-floor-355555555555555555.JPG00.JPGIS （最大宽度：468px）100VW，468px“ reverrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;展位亮点：引人入胜的演示和讨论&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们的展位上，我们与各种各样的受众联系，从经验丰富的混乱工程专家和现有的2.x用户到首次探索可靠性的初学者。展位上讨论的关键主题包括：＆nBSP; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; IAM集成，用于基于云提供商的混乱故障：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;演示展示了Litmuschaos如何与各种云IAM系统集成以模拟和减轻安全环境中的故障​​。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; CI/CD中的自动化混沌注入：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;通过LitMusCtl，SDKS和Terraform等工具，我们探索了如何将混沌实验无缝地纳入CI/CD管道中，使弹性成为自然的开发循环。&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;工具比较：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;详细的对话比较了各种混乱工程工具，帮助与会者了解Litmuschaos在生态系统中的独特功能和定位。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; byoc（带上自己的混乱） - 石声与线束：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;参与者进行了比较讨论，这些讨论阐明了Litmuschaos和其他平台之间的最佳实践和独特方法。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;混乱工程的基础：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;对于那些新手的人，我们的展位是一个教育枢纽，在其中引入了混乱工程的核心概念和好处。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;混乱故障的类型&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;br&gt;我们讨论了从Kubernetes/Linux特定问题到与云提供商有关的各种故障类别以及我们的解决方案如何解决这些问题。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;从2.x升级到3.x：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;我们听取了有关我们的2.x版本的社区反馈，以及关于过渡到3.x的共享见解，突出了改进和新功能。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;反思成功参与&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这次活动是我们与社区重新建立联系并进行有意义的对话的机会。从澄清疑问到对创新的头脑风暴，每一次互动都丰富了我们对建筑有弹性云本地系统的集体理解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;468&#34; height=&#34;313&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/podium-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class =“ wp-image-130430” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/podium-1.png 468w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/podium-1-300x201.png 300W，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/uploads/uploads/uploads/2025/2025/2044/podim-14/podium-1-200.-200.-200.pnnews = 2200.pnex200.pnews x200&#39; （最大宽度：468px）100VW，468px“ reverrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;与litmuschaos保持联系&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使Kubecon + Cloudnativecon Europe 2025结束了，对话仍在继续。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们是一个开放的，热情的空间，对于混乱工程爱好者，PlatfoRM工程师，可靠性人员，贡献者或任何人都只是想了解有关构建弹性系统的更多信息。我们很乐意让您加入我们！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是您可以参与的方式：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;访问&lt;a href =“ https://litmuschaos.io/”&gt; litmuschaos网站&lt;/a&gt;以了解项目，用例，体系结构和所有混乱工程。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;加入Kubernetes Slack中的&lt;strong&gt; #Litmus &lt;/strong&gt;频道的对话，提出问题，分享想法或与社区闲逛。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;为该项目做出贡献！查看我们的&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/litmuschaos/litmus/litmus/blob/master/master/contributing.md”&gt;贡献指南&lt;/a&gt;，然后从问题，建议或公关开始&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;订阅Litmuschaos YouTube频道进行社区会议，演示，教程和项目更新。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;li &lt;a href =“ https://x.com/litmuschaos”&gt; @litmuschaos在Twitter/x &lt;/a&gt;上或&lt;A href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/company/company/company/litmuschaos-litmuschaos” &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;探索&lt;a href =“ https://litmuschaos.io/blog”&gt; litmuschaos博客&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; for Stories，Tutorials和Deep Diew。想分享自己的经验吗？在&lt;a href =“ https://dev.to/litmus-chaos”&gt; dev.to &lt;/a&gt;上发布博客，并用&lt;strong&gt; #litmuschaos &lt;/strong&gt;标记它，我们很乐意阅读它！  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们反思库贝肯 + Cloudnativecon欧洲2025年的成功和学习时，我们感谢所有参与并分享其宝贵见解的人，我们期待下一章创建弹性系统。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;感谢您成为我们旅程的一部分。欢呼。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubestronaut in Orbit: Jana Vonšák】轨道上的kubestronaut：JanaVonšák</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/29/kubestronaut-in-orbit-jana-vonsak/</link>
      <description>【&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Get to know Jana&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re thrilled to recognize Jana Vonšák from Slovakia as our first-ever female Golden Kubestronaut. A dedicated DevOps Security Engineer with a background in software development, Jana brings a rare blend of development and security expertise to her role. Her passion lies in embedding robust security practices into cloud-native environments, ensuring applications are both scalable and secure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Outside of her day-to-day work, Jana is a strong advocate for continuous learning and community engagement. Her curiosity and drive to explore new frontiers in the cloud-native ecosystem have earned her all of the CNCF certifications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;When did you get started with Kubernetes and/or cloud-native? What was your first project?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I began working with Kubernetes about three years ago when I joined the Technology Delivery International (TDI) unit at Deutsche Telekom, making the leap from software development into the world of DevSecOps. It was a significant transition — and admittedly a bit overwhelming at first — but I quickly grew to enjoy the new challenges and the dynamic, fast-paced nature of the cloud native ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My first project involved an in-house WAF-as-a-Service solution already running on Kubernetes and spanning multiple clusters. Working within the security division, applying Kubernetes security best practices has been a core part of my journey — and it’s a topic I remain deeply passionate about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What are the primary CNCF projects you work on or use today? What projects have you enjoyed the most in your career?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The primary CNCF projects I currently work with include Kubernetes, Helm, Argo, Prometheus, Grafana, and CloudNativePG. Each tool brings unique strengths to the table, and together they create a powerful, well-balanced ecosystem — it’s tough to pick a favorite.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are also a few projects I’m not actively using yet but would love to explore further, especially Kyverno and OpenTelemetry. Both offer exciting capabilities that I’m eager to integrate into my work in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;How have the certs or CNCF helped you in your career?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The certifications themselves haven’t had a major direct impact on my career — aside from attracting a lot more random recruiter messages on LinkedIn. However, the preparation process was incredibly valuable, especially for the hands-on exams. You simply can’t fake your way through those; you need a solid grasp of the core concepts, the ability to navigate the documentation efficiently, and the confidence to apply your knowledge in real-world scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I began studying for the Kubernetes certifications, I was in a position where I had to quickly and thoroughly understand the entire ecosystem for a project I was assigned to. Following the official domains and competencies outlined in the exam guides turned out to be the most effective and structured way to achieve that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What are some other books/sites/courses you recommend for people who want to work with k8s?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to preparing for certifications or deepening your Kubernetes knowledge, official documentation is always the best source of truth — it’s your most reliable companion. Beyond that, there are several hands-on resources I highly recommend:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Killerkoda&lt;/strong&gt; – Excellent hands-on labs that let you practice real scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;KodeKloud&lt;/strong&gt; – Great course content with interactive labs. They operate on a subscription model, but many of their courses are also available individually on Udemy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kim Wüstkamp’s CKS Course&lt;/strong&gt; – Formerly on Udemy, now freely available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/&#34;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a fantastic resource for CKS preparation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Killershell Mock Exams&lt;/strong&gt; – Challenging, but definitely worth doing to get comfortable with the exam environment and expectations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What do you do in your free time?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of my free time is joyfully spent with my two amazing kids and my husband — and I wouldn’t trade it for anything. When I do carve out a bit of time for myself, you’ll usually find me lifting heavy things for fun (a.k.a. weightlifting) or out on a run.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last year, I completed my first Spartan Beast race — and I think I’m officially hooked. I’m already looking forward to joining again and beating my previous time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What would you tell someone who is just starting their K8s certification journey? Any tips or tricks?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes can feel overwhelming at first, but the key is hands-on practice. Start experimenting early — spin up a local cluster, break things, fix them, and repeat. Tools like Kind and Minikube are great for getting started and building confidence in a safe environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, get comfortable with the official Kubernetes documentation. It’s incredibly detailed and allowed during the hands-on certification exams. You don’t need to memorize everything — but knowing how to quickly find what you need is a huge advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The more time you spend working with Kubernetes, the more everything will start to click. Stick with it, and you’ll begin to see how all the pieces fit together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Today the cloud native ecosystem is way more than Kubernetes. Do you plan to get other cloud native certifications from the CNCF?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, I have all of them… let’s see what the future will bring!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What else would you like to share in this feature?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I absolutely &lt;strong&gt;love&lt;/strong&gt; the Kubestronaut community! Honestly, I didn’t expect this to be such a big part of the experience when becoming a Kubestronaut, but it’s turned out to be one of the best perks. It’s a space filled with curious, supportive people who are always ready to share knowledge and offer advice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCons will never be the same for me — not only will I get to attend incredible talks in person, but I’ll also finally have the chance to meet some of these inspiring individuals face-to-face. I’m already looking forward to it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;了解jana &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴将来自斯洛伐克的JanaVonšák认识为我们有史以来的第一个女性金kubestronaut。 Jana是具有软件开发背景背景背景的专用DevOPS安全工程师，他将开发和安全专业知识的罕见融合为她的角色。她的热情在于将强大的安全实践嵌入到云本地环境中，确保应用程序既可扩展又安全。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在日常工作之外，Jana是持续学习和社区参与的强有力的拥护者。她的好奇心和探索云本地生态系统中新边界的动力为她赢得了所有CNCF认证。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;您什么时候开始使用kubernetes和/或云本地？您的第一个项目是什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我大约三年前就开始与Kubernetes合作，当时我加入了Deutsche Telekom的Technology International（TDI）部门，从软件开发到DevSecops的世界。这是一个重大的过渡 - 一开始有点不知所措 - 但我很快就开始享受新的挑战和云本机生态系统的动态，快节奏的本质。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我的第一个项目涉及已经在kubernetes上运行并跨越多个群集的内部WAF-AS-A-Service解决方案。在安全部门工作，应用Kubernetes安全最佳实践一直是我旅程的核心部分 - 这是我对此深表激情的话题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;您今天从事或使用的主要CNCF项目是什么？您在职业生涯中最喜欢哪些项目？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我目前与之合作的主要CNCF项目包括Kubernetes，Helm，Argo，Prometheus，Grafana和CloudNativePG。每个工具都为桌子带来了独特的优势，它们共同创造了一个功能强大，平衡的生态系统 - 很难选择喜欢的生态系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我还没有积极使用一些项目，但很想进一步探索，尤其是kyverno和opentelemetry。两者都提供令人兴奋的功能，我渴望在不久的将来融入我的工作中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;证书或CNCF在职业生涯中如何帮助您？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;认证本身并没有对我的职业产生重大影响 - 除了吸引LinkedIn上更多随机的招聘人员消息。但是，准备过程非常有价值，特别是对于动手考试。您根本无法通过这些方式伪造自己的方式；您需要对核心概念，有效浏览文档的能力以及在现实世界中运用知识的信心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我开始学习Kubernetes认证时，我处于一个必须迅速而彻底地了解被分配给一个项目的整个生态系统的位置。跟随官员考试指南中概述的领域和能力被证明是实现这一目标的最有效和结构化的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;您建议想要与K8合作的人推荐哪些其他书籍/网站/课程？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在准备认证或加深您的Kubernetes知识方面，官方文档始终是真理的最佳来源 - 这是您最可靠的伴侣。除此之外，我强烈建议有几种动手资源：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; killerkoda &lt;/strong&gt;  - 出色的动手实验室，可让您练习真正的场景。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kodekloud &lt;/strong&gt;  - 交互式实验室的出色课程内容。他们以订阅模型运行，但是他们的许多课程也可以在Udemy上单独使用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;KimWüstkamp的CKS课程&lt;/strong&gt;  - 以前在Udemy上，现在在&lt;a href =“ https://www.youtube.com/”&gt; youtube上免费提供。这是CKS准备的绝佳资源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Killershell模拟考试&lt;/strong&gt;  - 具有挑战性，但绝对值得锻炼考试环境和期望。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;您在空闲时间做什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我的大部分空闲时间都与我的两个了不起的孩子和我的丈夫一起度过了快乐的愉快度 - 我不会用任何东西来换它。当我为自己花点时间时，您通常会发现我抬起繁重的东西以娱乐（又称举重）或跑步。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;去年，我完成了我的第一场斯巴达野兽比赛 - 我想我正式迷上了。我已经期待再次加入并击败我的前一次。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;您会告诉一个刚开始K8认证旅程的人？有任何技巧或窍门吗？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubernetes一开始会感到不知所措，但关键是动手实践。开始早日实验 - 旋转当地群集，打破事物，修复它们并重复。诸如Kind和Minikube之类的工具非常适合入门，并在安全环境中建立信心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，对官方的Kubernetes文档感到满意。在动手认证考试中，它非常详细和允许。您不需要记住一切，而是知道如何快速找到所需的东西是一个巨大的优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与Kubernetes合作的时间越多，所有内容都会开始点击的时间越多。坚持下去，您将开始看到所有碎片如何结合在一起。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;今天，云本机生态系统比kubernetes要多。您是否打算从CNCF获得其他云本机认证？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，我都拥有所有……让我们看看未来会带来什么！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;您还想在此功能中分享什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我绝对&lt;strong&gt;爱&lt;/strong&gt; kubestronaut社区！老实说，我没想到这是成为kubestronaut时经历的很大一部分，但事实证明这是最好的津贴之一。这是一个充满好奇，支持的人，他们随时准备分享知识并提供建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubecon + Cloudnativecons对我来说永远不会一样 - 我不仅可以亲自参加令人难以置信的演讲，而且我最终也有机会面对面与其中一些鼓舞人心的人见面。我已经期待它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fluent Bit v4.0: Celebrating new features and 10th anniversary】流利的位v4.0：庆祝新功能和10周年</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/25/fluent-bit-v4-0-celebrating-new-features-and-10th-anniversary/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The Fluent Bit maintainers have exciting news to share! Fluent Bit version 4 is out and just in time to celebrate the project’s 10-year anniversary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The journey: From embedded logging to multi-Signal observability&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With over 15 billion downloads, integration with every major cloud provider, and adoption by thousands of enterprises, Fluent Bit has become the production-grade telemetry pipeline for cloud native environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit began in 2014 with a clear mission: create a lightweight, high-performance log processor that could run efficiently in resource-constrained environments. What distinguished Fluent Bit from the start was its commitment to performance and minimal resource consumption—principles that continue to guide development today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project’s journey has been marked by consistent growth and evolution:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1040&#34; height=&#34;1284&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.53.08%E2%80%AFPM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130468&#34; style=&#34;width:430px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.53.08 PM.jpg 1040w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.53.08 PM-243x300.jpg 243w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.53.08 PM-829x1024.jpg 829w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.53.08 PM-768x948.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.53.08 PM-900x1111.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.53.08 PM-162x200.jpg 162w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.53.08 PM-324x400.jpg 324w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1040px) 100vw, 1040px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Throughout this journey, &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/fluent-bit-v3-2/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt; has maintained its core values: high performance, lightweight footprint, and vendor neutrality. These principles have made it the preferred choice for organizations seeking a reliable observability foundation without vendor lock-in or performance compromises.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Introducing Fluent Bit v4: The next generation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Building on a decade of engineering excellence, v4 introduces transformative capabilities that expand what’s possible with a telemetry agent while maintaining backward compatibility and the performance users expect. Here are four fantastic features you’ll find in v4:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Conditional logic for processors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Head and tail sampling for traces&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Zig language support for extending Fluent Bit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Authentication and TLS improvements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Adding conditional logic for processors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When&amp;nbsp; v2.12 was released, &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt; introduced the concept of &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/fluent-bit-processors-vs-filters/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Processors&lt;/a&gt;, which can enrich or transform telemetry data. Then with v3, Fluent Bit expanded on this foundation by introducing three key processors: Content Modifier, Metric Selector, and which follows last year’s new support for the OpenTelemetry Envelope Enveloper.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ability to transform data in processors by writing rules and configurations is powerful but also complex – until now. With v4, Fluent Bit offers intuitive conditional logic that makes it dramatically easier to implement sophisticated data transformations while improving pipeline performance and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Conditional logic in processors significantly reduces bottlenecks in high-volume data streams, which is especially powerful for use cases with heavy regex processing or complex data transformations.,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s an example of how you can use conditional processing to delete sensitive information based on user permissions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1654&#34; height=&#34;936&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.54.20%E2%80%AFPM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130469&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.54.20 PM.jpg 1654w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.54.20 PM-300x170.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.54.20 PM-1024x579.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.54.20 PM-768x435.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.54.20 PM-900x509.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.54.20 PM-353x200.jpg 353w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.54.20 PM-707x400.jpg 707w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1654px) 100vw, 1654px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;This configuration will transform:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1724&#34; height=&#34;904&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12%E2%80%AFPM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130470&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM.png 1724w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-300x157.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-1024x537.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-768x403.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-194x102.png 194w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-388x204.png 388w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-776x408.png 776w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-900x472.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-381x200.png 381w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-763x400.png 763w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-590x310.png 590w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.56.12 PM-1180x620.png 1180w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1724px) 100vw, 1724px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Head and Tail sampling for traces&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit v4 now offers a new trace sampling processor designed with a pluggable architecture, which allows easy extension to support multiple sampling strategies and backends.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The two main approaches for sampling traces are head and tail sampling:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Head sampling makes the decision whether or not to keep a trace at the very beginning. This is when a root span is created but before the request is actually fulfilled.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tail sampling evaluates the entire trace when making a sampling decision and can inspect the metadata and status of traces to inform the decision.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here’s an example showing head sampling configured at 40%, which would result in approximately 40 traces sampled out of an original dataset of 100.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;730&#34; height=&#34;644&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.57.09%E2%80%AFPM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130472&#34; style=&#34;width:525px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.57.09 PM.jpg 730w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.57.09 PM-300x265.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.57.09 PM-227x200.jpg 227w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.57.09 PM-453x400.jpg 453w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 730px) 100vw, 730px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Trace data volumes can quickly become overwhelming and expensive to store. Intelligent sampling ensures you capture the most valuable traces for debugging and performance analysis while managing costs. I am excited to see expanded support for traces — it means &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit-academy/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit &lt;/a&gt;continues to be a powerful choice for handling all your cloud native telemetry. This is an area the Fluent Bit maintainers are actively working on and welcome your feedback, friction logs, and feature wishlist when it comes to managing traces with Fluent Bit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Zig language support for extending Fluent Bit and developing plugins&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been wanting to contribute to or customize Fluent Bit but weren’t keen on learning the ins and outs of C, you’ll be excited to learn about our support for the Zig language! Zig is a modern systems programming language that combines C-like performance with memory safety and expressive syntax. This complements existing C and Lua plugin options, enabling developers to create high-performance extensions with fewer bugs and security vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Going forward Zig will complement existing extension options like &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/development/golang-output-plugins&#34;&gt;Golang&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/pipeline/filters/lua&#34;&gt;Lua&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/pipeline/filters/wasm&#34;&gt;WASM&lt;/a&gt; opening the door to more contributions from a broader community of developers.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1766&#34; height=&#34;628&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.58.30%E2%80%AFPM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130473&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.58.30 PM.png 1766w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.58.30 PM-300x107.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.58.30 PM-1024x364.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.58.30 PM-768x273.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.58.30 PM-900x320.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.58.30 PM-562x200.png 562w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-24-at-12.58.30 PM-1125x400.png 1125w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1766px) 100vw, 1766px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;https://ziglang.org/&#34;&gt;Zig&lt;/a&gt; here and check out their list of&lt;a href=&#34;https://ziglang.org/learn/&#34;&gt; learning resources&lt;/a&gt; to get started today!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Authentication and TLS improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As observability data increasingly contains sensitive information and spans multiple security domains, robust authentication and encryption are essential. These v4 improvements enable secure telemetry collection across complex environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First is the ability to load Bearer tokens directly from the filesystem—a big improvement over manual configuration. Second, the Fluent Bit maintainers have responded to community requests for more choice and flexibility for the cipher used to encrypt communication via TLS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Conclusion&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Looking ahead: The next decade of Fluent Bit&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we celebrate this milestone, it’s amazing to watch how the community has helped make Fluent Bit’s success possible. From individual contributors and maintainers to enterprise adopters, your feedback, contributions, and support have shaped this project into what it is today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fluent Bit v4 isn’t just a culmination of our first decade—it’s the foundation for the next ten years of innovation. We envision Fluent Bit continuing to evolve as observability practices mature, becoming increasingly intelligent about the data it processes while remaining true to its core principles of efficiency and vendor neutrality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recommend&amp;nbsp; upgrading to v4 today so you can experience first-hand how these transformative capabilities can enhance your observability practice.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to get started? &lt;/strong&gt;Learn more about Fluent bit v4, join our growing community, and visit our documentation to learn more about upgrading. Here’s to the next decade of observability excellence with Fluent Bit!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://go.chronosphere.io/fluent-bit-10-year-journey-the-road-ahead-with-v4.html?utm_source=CNCF&amp;amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Learn more in our next webinar about Fluent Bit v4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.launchpass.com/fluent-all&#34;&gt;Join our growing community on Slack!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/v4&#34;&gt;Upgrade to Fluent Bit v4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;流利的维护者有令人兴奋的消息要分享！ Fluent Bit 4版本已经发布，正好及时庆祝该项目成立10周年。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;旅程：从嵌入式记录到多信号可观察性&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下载超过150亿，与每个主要的云提供商集成以及成千上万的企业的采用，流利的位已成为云本机环境的生产级遥测管道。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;流利位于2014年开始，其任务清晰：创建一个轻巧，高性能的日志处理器，可以在资源约束环境中有效运行。从一开始，有所区别的是它对绩效和最少资源消耗的承诺 - 原告继续指导今天的发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;项目的旅程以一致的增长和进化为标志：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-instrized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 1040” height =“ 1284” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-AT-12.53.08%E2%E2%80%80%AFMAFMAFMAFMAFMAFMAFPM.JPG. srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-04-24-at-12.53.08pmm.jpg 1040w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.53.08pm-243x300.jpg 243w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.53.08pm-829x1024.jpg 829w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-04-24-at-12.53.083.08pm-768x948.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.53.083.08pm-900x1111.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-04-24-at-12.53.0833.08pm-162x200.jpg 162w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-24-at-12.53.08pm-324x400.jpg 324w 324W 324W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Throughout this journey, &lt;a href=&#34;https://chronosphere.io/learn/fluent-bit-v3-2/?utm_source=CNCF&amp;utm_medium=sponsored+content&#34;&gt;Fluent Bit&lt;/a&gt; has maintained its core values: high performance, lightweight footprint, and vendor neutrality.这些原则使其成为寻求可靠的可观察性基金会的组织的首选选择，而无需供应商锁定或绩效妥协。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;介绍流利的位v4：下一代&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在卓越工程卓越的十年中，V4引入了变革性的功能，可以通过遥测代理来扩展遥控器的可能性，同时保持向后兼容性和性能用户的期望。这是您在V4中找到的四个奇妙功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;处理器的条件逻辑&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;痕迹的头部和尾巴采样&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;曲折语言支持延长流利位&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;身份验证和TLS改进&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;为处理器添加条件逻辑&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;发布v2.12时，&lt;a a href =“ https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit/?utm_source = cncf&amp;utm_medium = sponsored+content”&gt; fluent bit &lt;/a&gt;引入了&lt;a的概念href =“ https://chronosphere.io/learn/fluent-bit-processors-vs-filters/?utm_source=cncf&amp;utm_medium = sponsored+content”&gt;处理器&lt;/a&gt;，可以丰富或转换遥测数据。然后，使用V3，Fluent位通过引入三个关键处理器：内容修改器，度量标准选择器，并遵循去年对OpentElemetry Invelope封底的新支持。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;到目前为止，通过编写规则和配置来转换处理器中的数据的能力也很复杂。使用V4，Fluent BIT提供了直观的条件逻辑，这使得在提高管道性能和效率的同时，实施复杂的数据转换非常容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;处理器中的有条件逻辑可显着减少高量数据流中的瓶颈，这对于具有重度正则处理或复杂数据转换的用例特别强大。，&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一个示例，说明如何使用条件处理根据用户权限删除敏感信息：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 1654” height =“ 936” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-AT-12.54.20%2.54.20%E2%E2%80%Afpgmm.jpgm.jpgm.jpgm.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-04-24-AT-12.54.20pm.jpg 1654W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-AT-12.54.20pm-300x170.jpg 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.54.20pm-1024x579.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-AT-12.54.20pm-768x435.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-AT-12.54.20.20pm-900x509.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-AT-12.54.20pm-353x200.jpg 353W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.54.20ptm-707x400.jpg 707W 707W“ sizes =” size =“ auto =” auto，（max-witth：max-witth：max-witth：1654px）100VWW，1654px） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此配置将转换：&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy”解码=“ async” width =“ 1724” height =“ 904” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-AT-12.56.12%E2%80％; srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-04-24-at-12.56.12pm.png 1724W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-AT-12.56.12.12pm-300x157.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.56.12pm-1024x537.PNG 1024W，https：//www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-AT-12.56.12.56.12pm-768x403.png 768w，768w，768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.56.12pm-194x102.png 194w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.56.12pm-388x204.png 388w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.56.12pm-776x408.png 776w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.56.12pm-900x472.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-AT-12.56.12PM-381x200.png 381W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-AT-12.56.12PM-763X400.png 763w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-04-24-at-12.56.12pm-590x310.png 590w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-24-at-12.56.12pm-1180x620.png 1180w“ size =” auto，（max-witth：1724px）10024px） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;痕迹的头和尾巴采样&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Fluent Bit V4现在提供了一个新的痕量采样处理器，设计了可插入式体系结构，该处理器允许轻松扩展以支持多个采样策略和后端。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;采样轨迹的两种主要方法是头和尾巴采样：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;头部采样做出决定是否在一开始是否保持痕迹。这是创建根跨度但在真正满足请求之前的重点的时候。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;尾部采样在做出抽样决定时会评估整个痕迹，并可以检查轨迹和痕迹状态以告知决定。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;这是一个示例，显示了以40％的形式配置的头部采样，这将导致大约40个轨迹从100的原始数据集中采样。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-AT-12.57.09%E2%80%80%80%Afpm.afpmm.jpg.jpg.jpgm.jpgm.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.57.09pm.jpg 730w，730w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.57.09.09pm-300x265.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.57.09.09pm-227x200.jpg 227w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.57.09.09pm-453x400.jpg 453ww“ size =” auto，（max-witth：max-witth：730px）100330px， referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;跟踪数据量可能很快变得压倒性且存储昂贵。智能抽样可确保您在管理成本的同时捕获调试和性能分析的最有价值的痕迹。我很高兴看到对痕迹的扩展支持 - 这意味着&lt;ahref =“ https://chronosphere.io/fluent-bit-academy/?utm_source = cncf&amp;utm_medium = sponsored+content”&gt;流利位&lt;/a&gt;仍然是处理所有云本机遥测的有力选择。这是流利的位维护者正在积极努力的领域，并欢迎您的反馈，摩擦日志和功能愿望清单在管理流利的痕迹方面。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您一直想为流利的位做出贡献或自定义，但不愿意学习C的来龙去脉，您会很高兴能了解我们对Zig语言的支持！ Zig是一种现代系统编程语言，将类似C的性能与内存安全性和表达语法相结合。这对现有的C和LUA插件选项进行了补充，使开发人员能够创建具有更少错误和安全漏洞的高性能扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;向前发展Zig将补充现有的扩展选项，例如&lt;a href =“ https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/manual/manual/development/golang-undput-plugins”&gt; golang &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ href =” href =“ https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/pipeline/pipeline/filters/wasm”&gt; wasm &lt;/a&gt;为更广泛的开发人员社区提供更多贡献的大门。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dexoding =“ async” width =“ 1766” height =“ 628” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-AT-12.58.30%E2%E2%80%80%Afpm.afpm.pm.pm.pmm.png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-04-24-at-12.58.30pmm.png 1766w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.58.30pm-300x107.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.58.30pm-1024x364.png 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.58.30pm-768x273.png 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.58.30pm-900x320.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-24-24-at-12.58.30pm-562x200.png 562w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-24-24-at-12.58.30pm-1125x400.png 1125W 1125W 1125W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解&lt;a href =“ https://ziglang.org/”&gt; Zig &lt;/a&gt;在此处查看他们的&lt;a href =“ https://ziglang.org/learlen/”&gt;“学习资源”&gt;学习资源&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;身份验证和TLS改进&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于可观察性数据越来越包含敏感信息并跨越了多个安全域，因此坚固的身份验证和加密至关重要。这些V4改进可以在复杂的环境中进行安全的遥测收集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先是直接从t加载载体令牌的能力HE文件系统 - 对手动配置的重大改进。其次，流利的钻头维护者已经回应了社区请求，以寻求通过TLS加密通信的密码的更多选择和灵活性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结论&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;向前看：接下来的十年流利位&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们庆祝这一里程碑时，观看社区如何帮助Fluent Bit的成功成为可能，真是太神奇了。从个人贡献者和维护者到企业采用者，您的反馈，贡献和支持已将该项目塑造成今天的项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Fluent Bit V4不仅是我们前十年的高潮，而且是未来十年创新的基础。我们设想流利的位继续演变为可观察性实践的成熟，对其处理的数据变得越来越聪明，同时又符合其效率和供应商中立的核心原则。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我建议今天升级到V4，以便您可以亲身体验这些变革性能力如何增强您的可观察性实践。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;准备开始？ &lt;/strong&gt;更多地了解Fluent Bit V4，加入我们不断增长的社区，然后访问我们的文档，以了解有关升级的更多信息。以下是接下来的十年，即流利的可观察性卓越！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://go.chronosphere.io/fluent-bit-10--journey-journey-the-the-read-ahead-ahead-ahead-with-with-v4.html?utm_source = cncf&amp;utm_medium = sponsored+sponsored+content”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.launchpass.com/fluent-all”&gt;加入我们在Slack上不断发展的社区！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://docs.fluentbit.io/manual/v4”&gt;升级到流利的位v4 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Protecting NATS and the integrity of open source: CNCF’s commitment to the community】保护NAT和开源的完整性：CNCF对社区的承诺</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/05/01/protecting-nats-and-the-integrity-of-open-source-cncfs-commitment-to-the-community/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated May 1, 2025&lt;/em&gt;: CNCF and Synadia have come to an agreement to ensure that NATS continues to thrive as a healthy open source project within CNCF, with Synadia’s continued support and involvement. Please see our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/announcements/2025/05/01/cncf-and-synadia-align-on-securing-the-future-of-the-nats-io-project/&#34;&gt;joint announcement&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Updated: April 28, 2025 with additional information about contents of Synadia’s written&amp;nbsp;proposal and CNCF’s $10,000 reimbursement to Synadia for trademark legal expenses&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When a company contributes a project to the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), it’s not just sharing code—it’s making a commitment to the open source community. It’s a pledge to uphold open collaboration, shared community ownership, and neutral governance. The CNCF exists to protect these values and principles—ensuring no single entity can dominate, relicense, or claw back what has been given to the community. This principled stewardship fosters trust, diverse contributions, and long-term sustainability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those commitments and principles are under threat. Synadia, the original donor of the&lt;a href=&#34;https://nats.io/&#34;&gt; NATS&lt;/a&gt; project, has notified CNCF of its intention to “withdraw” the NATS project from the foundation and “adopt the Business Source License (BUSL) for the NATS.io server —a &lt;strong&gt;non-open source license&lt;/strong&gt; that restricts user freedoms and undermines years of open development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s be clear: this is not a typical license change or fork. It’s an attempt to “take back” a mature, community-driven open source project and convert it into a proprietary product—after years of growth and collaboration under open governance and CNCF’s stewardship.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Linux Foundation and the CNCF have &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linuxfoundation.org/blog/how-open-source-foundations-protect-the-licensing-integrity-of-open-source-projects&#34;&gt;protected the licensing integrity of open source projects before&lt;/a&gt;. There are proper ways for companies to fork projects and take another direction based on business needs. For example, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.com/blog/2022/03/30/qa-with-our-ceo-about-grafana-mimir/&#34;&gt;vendor Grafana forked the CNCF Cortex project under the new name Mimir&lt;/a&gt; while the original Cortex project continues to be maintained by the community within CNCF. Synadia’s actions here are markedly different. Rather than creating a fork of NATS under a new name, Synadia wants to unilaterally seize control of the project’s community-owned assets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Synadia’s recent actions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Synadia-affiliated maintainers appear to have held a private vote to “exit CNCF” (see &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/NATS.io%20Maintainer%20Minutes%20-%20March%202025.pdf&#34;&gt;meeting minutes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/Proposal%20to%20exit%20NATS%20from%20CNCF.pdf&#34;&gt;exit proposal&lt;/a&gt;) without transparency, without a clear transition plan, and without engaging the broader contributor community that has helped shape NATS.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The exit proposal makes clear that Synadia seeks to “retain &lt;strong&gt;complete and exclusive governance&lt;/strong&gt; over the project and its future direction,” further asserting that Synadia “will remain the &lt;strong&gt;sole owner &lt;/strong&gt;of the NATS.io trademark and intellectual property” and “request[ing] the return of the NATS.io domain registration, as well as sole administrative control over the GitHub organization.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a further escalation, Synadia’s legal counsel &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/Cease%20and%20Demand%20Letter%20from%20Synadia%20Counsel.pdf&#34;&gt;demanded in writing&lt;/a&gt; that CNCF hand over “full control of the &lt;strong&gt;nats.io domain name&lt;/strong&gt; and the &lt;strong&gt;nats-io GitHub repository&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;within two weeks&lt;/strong&gt;”, a particularly aggressive timeline given that the proposal had not yet been submitted to the CNCF Technical Oversight Committee (TOC) or shared with the broader community. These demands came despite the fact that:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Synadia &lt;strong&gt;committed in writing&lt;/strong&gt; to transfer the NATS trademark to CNCF as part of the original donation;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CNCF provided &lt;strong&gt;substantial financial, marketing, legal, and technical support&lt;/strong&gt; to the NATS project for more than seven years;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The NATS brand has become synonymous with CNCF and its promise of vendor-neutral governance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The NATS domain name and GitHub repository are assets that serve as community infrastructure and have been managed by CNCF since the project’s acceptance in 2018.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The demand letter also &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/Cease%20and%20Demand%20Letter%20from%20Synadia%20Counsel.pdf&#34;&gt;disputed the enforceability of CNCF’s project and trademark policies&lt;/a&gt;—policies that all CNCF member companies, including Synadia, agreed to in the membership contract they signed. Synadia claims that CNCF’s governance documents are “too vague” to apply to the NATS project—despite a clear statement in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/charter.md#11-ip-policy&#34;&gt;CNCF Charter&lt;/a&gt; that “Any project that is added to the CNCF must have ownership of its trademark and logo assets transferred to the Linux Foundation.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/Proposal%20to%20exit%20NATS%20from%20CNCF.pdf&#34;&gt;exit proposal&lt;/a&gt; also outlines Synadia’s relicensing plans: “Upon leaving CNCF, Synadia will adopt the [BUSL] for the NATS.io server.” “This change in licensing does not signal a departure from our commitment to the open-source community,” Synadia indicated its “plan to specify the Apache License as the ‘Change License’ in the [BUSL].”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s important to understand that under the BUSL, regardless of which “change license” is specified, the code would be subject to significant commercial restrictions and would not be licensed as open source until after a significant delay, which could be up to 4 years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF has offered multiple paths that would allow Synadia to pursue its goals while respecting open source principles and community governance. Synadia is free to walk away from contributing to the existing NATS project. They’re also free to fork NATS and build a proprietary offering under a new name. What they &lt;strong&gt;can’t&lt;/strong&gt; do is unilaterally claw back a community project and its infrastructure, assets, and branding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Synadia has unfortunately declined to work with us on an appropriate option that respects open source principles and CNCF community governance processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a further escalation, Synadia’s legal counsel sent a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/Cease%20and%20Demand%20Letter%20from%20Synadia%20Counsel.pdf&#34;&gt;letter challenging the enforceability of CNCF’s project and trademark policies&lt;/a&gt;—policies that all CNCF member companies, including Synadia, agreed to in the membership contract they signed. Synadia claims that CNCF’s governance documents are “too vague” to apply to the NATS project—despite a clear statement in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/charter.md#11-ip-policy&#34;&gt;CNCF Charter&lt;/a&gt; that “Any project that is added to the CNCF must have ownership of its trademark and logo assets transferred to the Linux Foundation.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Synadia-affiliated maintainers appear to have held a private vote to “exit CNCF” (see &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/NATS.io%20Maintainer%20Minutes%20-%20March%202025.pdf&#34;&gt;meeting minutes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/Proposal%20to%20exit%20NATS%20from%20CNCF.pdf&#34;&gt;exit proposal&lt;/a&gt;) without transparency, without a clear transition plan, and without engaging the broader contributor community that has helped shape NATS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short: Synadia is attempting to convert a successful open source project into a closed, commercial product—and take the NATS community’s name, trust, and infrastructure with it. Imagine if Google tried to take back Kubernetes after all these years of it being a neutral open source and community-driven project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF IP and Trademarks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Open source foundations exist in part to protect the ecosystem from unilateral license changes and other vendor-driven rug-pulls. That’s why CNCF, per its charter (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/charter.md#11-ip-policy&#34;&gt;Section 11a&lt;/a&gt;), requires all contributed projects to transfer trademark and logo ownership to the Linux Foundation. This ensures that no single vendor can later assert control of the project through trademark rights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Synadia’s CEO, as one of the original members of the CNCF Governing Board, has been aware of this policy from the start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When NATS was contributed in 2018, Synadia had already filed for trademark registrations on both the NATS name and logo. Synadia’s CEO explicitly committed—in writing—to transfer those trademarks upon the project’s acceptance into CNCF. However, a trademark dispute with Major League Baseball (MLB) over the name “NATS” (related to the Washington Nationals) delayed the transfer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To resolve the issue, CNCF paid for legal counsel to work with Synadia’s trademark attorneys throughout 2018–2019. When proposed settlement terms threatened to limit community use, CNCF rejected them. CNCF then presented Synadia with two clear paths:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rename the open source project and retain “NATS” as a commercial brand for Synadia.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resolve the dispute with MLB and transfer the marks to CNCF post-settlement.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Synadia chose the latter. Once the dispute was resolved, Synadia requested and was paid $10,000 as a reimbursement from CNCF for Synadia’s NATS trademark registration legal expenses. While the LF originally sent a check for the trademark expenses, at Synadia’s request, that check was cancelled and an ACH payment was made. The ACH payment was received by Synadia as can be seen in the screen shot below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1220&#34; height=&#34;668&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ACH payment screenshot&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130836&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1.jpg 1220w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1-300x164.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1-1024x561.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1-768x421.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1-900x493.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1-365x200.jpg 365w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1-731x400.jpg 731w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1220px) 100vw, 1220px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yet even after the issue was cleared and the payment was made, Synadia did not complete the promised transfer of the trademark registration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, Synadia still refuses to follow through on its promise—despite years of commitment, financial support, and active stewardship from CNCF. And despite significant contributions from hundreds of other organizations and individuals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not only has Synadia broken its promise; it’s now weaponizing that broken promise against the community and foundation that helped make NATS successful, by asserting that its status as the current holder of record of the NATS trademark registrations entitles it to unilaterally take over project infrastructure and assets that have been community-owned for seven years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF support of NATS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since NATS joined the CNCF in 2018, the foundation has provided extensive support—financial, technical, legal, and organizational—to help the project grow, mature, and thrive as a trusted part of the cloud native ecosystem. This support has included:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Funding two third-party security audits (over $90,000)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Supporting legal and trademark work&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;KubeCon + CloudNativeCon speaking slots, keynotes, booths, and marketing inclusion&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ongoing mentorship and contributor growth programs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to this support—and the dedication of the community—NATS has flourished. Downloads, contributors, and integrations with CNCF and third-party projects (like Helm, Kubernetes, Prometheus, ClickHouse, JetStream, and more) have grown significantly. Although Synadia has indeed been a significant contributor, over 700 other organizations have also contributed to the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped wp-block-gallery-1 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1620&#34; height=&#34;654&#34; data-id=&#34;130389&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-23-at-8.17.44%E2%80%AFPM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Contributions under CNCF for past 7 years&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130389&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-23-at-8.17.44 PM.jpg 1620w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-23-at-8.17.44 PM-300x121.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-23-at-8.17.44 PM-1024x413.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-23-at-8.17.44 PM-768x310.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-23-at-8.17.44 PM-900x363.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-23-at-8.17.44 PM-495x200.jpg 495w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-23-at-8.17.44 PM-991x400.jpg 991w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1620px) 100vw, 1620px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image: Contributions under CNCF for past 7 years&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The success and reputation of NATS today is not just due to one company’s efforts—it’s the result of years of community collaboration, CNCF stewardship, and a commitment to open governance. And that’s what we’re committed to defending.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF’s response and actions to protect NATS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CNCF will continue to host and support NATS under its Apache-2.0 license for as long as there is community interest. We are committed to ensuring that NATS continues to be governed openly, available freely, and protected from unilateral takeover.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this in mind, CNCF and the Linux Foundation are taking the following actions in response to Synadia’s legal demands:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Initiating a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/issues/1632&#34;&gt;CNCF TOC health check issue&lt;/a&gt; to evaluate the health of the project&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Making a call for support and additional maintainers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Asking the USPTO to cancel the conflicting Synadia trademark registrations (see our &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/Petition%20for%20cancellation%20NATS%20stylized%20Reg%20No%206216924%20final.pdf&#34;&gt;cancellation petitions for the NATS logo&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/Petition%20for%20cancellation%20NATS%20IO%20Reg%20No%206216925%20final.pdf&#34;&gt;for NATS.IO&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Continuing to reject Synadia’s demands that the NATS infrastructure and assets be handed over to them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will continue to update the CNCF community and ecosystem on our work to protect the project’s open source license and neutral governance. We are sharing this information to foster continued discussion out in the open–within the Technical Oversight Committee (TOC) and the broader community–following CNCF’s standard governance processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can follow or comment on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/issues/1632&#34;&gt;discussion about NATS’s future&lt;/a&gt; in the CNCF TOC repository. If you’re a NATS user, contributor, or stakeholder, we invite you to help us protect the future of this important project. Please consider becoming a NATS maintainer or increasing your contributions to the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; 2025年5月1日更新：CNCF和Synadia已达成协议，以确保NAT在CNCF内的健康开源项目中继续壮成长，并在Synadia的持续支持和参与下蓬勃发展。请参阅我们的&lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/announcements/2025/05/01/cncf-and-synadia-align-align-align-align-align-align-securing-the-the-the-the-future-o------------------------------------------------------------ &lt;/a&gt;有关更多信息。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;更新：2025年4月28日，还有有关Synadia书面提案内容的其他信息，以及CNCF的10,000美元报销，以支付Synadia的商标法律费用&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/prong&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当公司向云本地计算基金会（CNCF）贡献项目时，它不仅是共享代码，而且还对开源社区做出了承诺。这是维护公开合作，共享社区所有权和中立治理的承诺。 CNCF的存在是为了保护这些价值观和原则，没有一个实体可以统治，重新统治，或缩减给社区的内容。这种原则的管理促进了信任，多样化的贡献和长期的可持续性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些承诺和原则受到威胁。 Synadia, the original donor of the&lt;a href=&#34;https://nats.io/&#34;&gt; NATS&lt;/a&gt; project, has notified CNCF of its intention to “withdraw” the NATS project from the foundation and “adopt the Business Source License (BUSL) for the NATS.io server —a &lt;strong&gt;non-open source license&lt;/strong&gt; that restricts user freedoms and undermines years of open development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们清楚：这不是典型的许可证更改或叉子。这是一种试图“收回”一个成熟的，社区驱动的开源项目并将其转换为专有产品 - 在公开治理和CNCF的管理下的增长和协作之后。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Linux基金会和CNCF具有&lt;a href =“ https://www.linuxfoundation.org/blog/blog/how-open-source-foundations-protect-protect-protect-licensing-incensing-integrity-open-source-projects-- protinally-open-source-projects”&gt;在&lt;/a&gt;之前推动了开放式启动项目的许可完整性。公司有适当的方法可以根据业务需求进行项目并采取另一个方向。 For example, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.com/blog/2022/03/30/qa-with-our-ceo-about-grafana-mimir/&#34;&gt;vendor Grafana forked the CNCF Cortex project under the new name Mimir&lt;/a&gt; while the original Cortex project continues to be maintained by the community within CNCF. Synadia在这里的行动明显不同。 Synadia并没有以新名称创建一小块NAT，而是希望单方面抓住该项目的社区拥有的资产。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Synadia的最新动作&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Synadia-cropliatied Mainters似乎已经举行了私人投票来“退出CNCF”（请参阅​​&lt;a a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/main/main/documents/nats/nats.io%20mint.20minutes;g分钟&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/documents/nats/nats/proposal%20to%20to%20exit%20nats%20nats%20from%20cncncf.pdf”&gt; exit exit提案无需透支而无需透支，而无需跨越透支，而无需跨越跨越计划。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The exit proposal makes clear that Synadia seeks to “retain &lt;strong&gt;complete and exclusive governance&lt;/strong&gt; over the project and its future direction,” further asserting that Synadia “will remain the &lt;strong&gt;sole owner &lt;/strong&gt;of the NATS.io trademark and intellectual property” and “request[ing] the return of the NATS.io domain registration, as well as sole administrative control over the GitHub organization.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在进一步的升级中，Synadia的法律顾问&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/main/documents/nats/nats/cease%20and%20demand%20letter%20letter%20letper%20FROM20FROM20FROM 20SYNADIA； &lt;strong&gt; nats.io域名&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt; nats-io github存储库&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在两周内&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;”，鉴于该提案尚未提交给CNCF技术监督委员会（TOC）或与更广泛的社区共享。尽管事实是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Synadia &lt;strong&gt;以书面形式致力于&lt;/strong&gt;作为原始捐赠的一部分将NATS商标转移到CNCF； &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; cncf提供了&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; NATS品牌已成为CNCF的代名词及其对供应商中性治理的承诺。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; NATS域名和GitHub存储库是作为社区基础架构的资产，自2018年项目接受以来已由CNCF管理。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需求信还&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/documents/nats/nats/cease%20and%20demand%20letter%20letter%20from%20synadia%20synadia%20Counsel.pdf”包括Synadia在内的CNCF会员公司在他们签署的会员合同中同意。 Synadia声称，CNCF的治理文件“太模糊”以至于适用于NATS项目，尽管在&lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/parter.md#11-policy.md-policy.md-ip-policy.md-ip-policy.m.md-ippolicy obly operlip &lt;a a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/foundation y&gt; cncf charter oblosean ast of the Project”徽标资产转移到Linux基金会。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/documents/nats/nats/nats/proposal%20to%20to%20exit%20nats%20nats%20from%20cncf.pdf”&gt; exit提议&gt; exit提议&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;在connadia cornadia will planica will plancair planica will plancair will ply connc. nats.io服务器。” “许可的变化并不表示偏离我们对开源社区的承诺。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;重要的是要了解，在Busl下，无论指定“更改许可证”，该守则都将受到重大商业限制，并且直到大量延迟后才能将其作为开源许可，最多可达4年。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CNCF提供了多种途径，可以使Synadia在尊重开源原则和社区治理的同时追求其目标。 Synadia可以自由地摆脱为现有NATS项目的贡献。他们还可以自由地叉，并以新名称建立专有产品。他们&lt;strong&gt;不能做的是单方面缩减社区项目及其基础设施，资产和品牌。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不幸的是，Synadia拒绝与我们合作采用尊重开源原则和CNCF社区治理流程的适当选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在进一步的升级中，Synadia的法律顾问向A &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/main/documents/nats/nats/cease%20and%20demand%20letter%20letter%20letper%20from%20from%20from%20synadia；政策&lt;/a&gt;  - 包括Synadia在内的所有CNCF成员公司都同意他们签署的会员合同中同意的政策。 Synadia声称，CNCF的治理文件“太模糊”以至于适用于NATS项目，尽管在&lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/parter.md#11-policy.md-policy.md-ip-policy.md-ip-policy.m.md-ippolicy obly operlip &lt;a a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/foundation y&gt; cncf charter oblosean ast of the Project”徽标资产转移到Linux基金会。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同时，与Synadia相关的维护者似乎已经举行了私人投票来“退出CNCF”（请参阅​​&lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/main/documents/nats/nats/nats/nats.io； href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/documents/nats/nats/proposal%20to 20 exit%20nats%20nats%20from%20cncf.pdf“&gt; exit progosal &lt;/a&gt;）没有透明的态度，没有明确的过渡计划，没有更广泛的贡献，&lt;/ext &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;）&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;简而言之：Synadia试图将成功的开源项目转换为封闭的商业产品，并使用NATS社区的名称，信任和基础架构。想象一下，如果Google成为一个中立的开源和社区驱动的项目，Google是否试图取回Kubernetes。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; cncf ip和商标&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开源基础部分是为了保护生态系统免受单方面许可变化和其他供应商驱动的地毯扣。这就是为什么CNCF，根据其章程（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/charter.md#11）-ip-policy“&gt;第11a节&lt;/a&gt;）要求所有贡献项目以将商标和徽标所有权转让给Linux Foundation。这确保没有单个供应商以后可以通过商标权来控制项目。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Synadia的首席执行官是CNCF管理委员会的原始成员之一，从一开始就意识到了这一政策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当NATS于2018年捐款时，Synadia已经对NATS名称和徽标进行了商标注册。 Synadia的首席执行官在书面上明确承诺将这些商标转移到CNCF中。但是，与美国职棒大联盟（MLB）的商标争端有关“ Nats”（与华盛顿国民有关）的名称推迟了转会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了解决这个问题，CNCF付款，要求法律顾问在2018  -  2019年间与Synadia的商标律师合作。当拟议的和解条款威胁要限制社区使用时，CNCF拒绝了它们。然后，CNCF向Synadia提供了两个清晰的路径：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;重命名开源项目并将“ NAT”保留为Synadia的商业品牌。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;解决与MLB的争议，并将标记转移到CNCF后解决后。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Synadia选择了后者。一旦解决争议，请要求Synadia，并获得10,000美元的报销，以偿还CNCF的Synadia NATS商标注册法律费用。尽管LF最初根据Synadia的要求发送了商标费用的支票，但该支票被取消并进行了ACH付款。 Synadia收到了ACH付款，如下面的屏幕截图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy”解码=“ async” width =“ 1220” height =“ 668” src =“ https://wwwww.cncf.io of class =“ wp-image-130836” srcSet =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/artboard-board-1.jpg 1220w，https://www.cncf.io of 300W，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/artboard-1024x561.jpg 1024w，https://www.cncf.io https：//www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/upploads/2025/2025/1488888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888848888888888888888888888888888888888888 8888888888888888意 https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1-900x493.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Artboard-1-365x200.jpg 365w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/artboard-1-731x400.jpg 731W“ sizes =” size =“ auto，（max-width：1220px）100vw，100vw，1220px“ referrerpolerpolicy =” notrerpolicy =&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;即使在清除了问题并付款后，Synadia也无法完成商标注册的承诺转让。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，Synadia仍然拒绝遵守其承诺，尽管有多年的承诺，财政支持和CNCF的积极管理。尽管其他数百个组织和个人做出了重大贡献。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Synadia不仅违反了其诺言；现在是武器Zing对社区和基金会的承诺破裂，这有助于使NATS成功，通过断言其作为NATS商标注册记录持有人的地位使其有权单方面接管已有7年社区拥有的项目基础设施和资产。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; nats的CNCF支持&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自NATS于2018年加入CNCF以来，该基金会提供了广泛的支持（财务，技术，法律和组织），以帮助该项目作为云本地生态系统的值得信赖的部分增长，成熟和成长。此支持包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;资助两个第三方安全审核（超过$ 90,000）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持法律和商标工作&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; kubecon + CloudNativeCon讲话老虎机，主题演讲，展位和营销包容&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;持续的指导和贡献者成长计划&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;感谢这种支持以及社区的奉献精神 - 纳特人蓬勃发展。下载，贡献者以及与CNCF和第三方项目的集成（例如Helm，Kubernetes，Prometheus，clickhouse，Jetstream等）已大大增长。尽管Synadia确实是一个重要的贡献者，但其他700多个组织也为该项目做出了贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figue class =“ WP-block-Gallery具有nest-nested-inted-bailts列 - 默认为wp-block-gallery-1 is-layout-layout-flex-flex-block-gallery-is-layout-layout-flex”&gt;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 1620” height =“ 654” data-id =“ 130389” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-23-04-23-at-8.17.44%E2%80%80%80%80%80%Afpm.jpgm.jpg. srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-23-04-23-at-8.17.44pm.jpg.jpg 1620w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-23-04-23-at-8.17.4444pm-300x121.jpg 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-23-04-23-at-8.17.4444pm-1024x413.jpg 1024w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-23-04-23-at-8.17.4444pm-768x310.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-23-04-23-at-8.17.44.44pm-900x363.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-23-04-23-at-8.17.4444pm-495x200.jpg 495w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-23-AT-8.17.44pm-991x400.jpg 991W 991W“ sizes =” sizes =“ auto，（max-witth：max-witth：max-witth：1620px）100vx） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;图片：CNCF下的贡献过去7年&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当今NAT的成功和声誉不仅是由于一家公司的努力，而且是社区合作，CNCF管理的多年的结果以及对公开治理的承诺。这就是我们致力于捍卫的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; CNCF的响应和保护NATS &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;的行动&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;只要有社区兴趣，CNCF将继续在其Apache-2.0许可下托管和支持NAT。我们致力于确保NAT继续公开，自由使用，并保护NAT，免受单方面的接管。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;考虑到这一点，CNCF和Linux基金会正在采取以下措施，以应对Synadia的法律要求：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;启动a &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/toc/issues/1632”&gt; cncf toc toc健康检查问题&lt;/a&gt;评估项目的健康&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;呼吁支持和其他维护者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;要求USPTO取消矛盾的Synadia商标注册（请参阅我们的&lt;a a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/blob/main/main/main/documents/nats/petition%20for%20for%20cancell%20cancellation; NATS徽标的请愿书&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/foundation/blob/main/main/documents/nats/petition%20for%20cancellation%20cancellation%20nats%20nats%20IO20IO20IO20IO20REG20REG 20NO；&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;继续拒绝Synadia要求将NAT的基础设施和资产移交给它们&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将继续在保护项目的开源许可和中立治理方面的工作中更新CNCF社区和生态系统。我们正在分享此信息，以促进在技术监督委员会（TOC）和更广泛的社区的公开讨论中继续讨论。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以关注或评论&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/toc/issues/1632”&gt;在CNCF TOC存储库中讨论NATS的未来&lt;/a&gt;。如果您是NATS的用户，贡献者或利益相关者，我们邀请您帮助我们保护这个重要项目的未来。请考虑成为NAT的维护者或增加您对项目的贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Prepare your application landscape for zero trust with Keycloak 26.2】用KeyCloak 26.2准备零信托的应用程序景观</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/24/prepare-your-application-landscape-for-zero-trust-with-keycloak-26-2/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Strong identity and access management is a key component of a zero trust architecture for cloud native applications. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/&#34;&gt;Keycloak&lt;/a&gt; is well-known for its single-sign-on capabilities based on open standards. It provides you all the building blocks you need to run this in self-hosted environments on-premise and in the cloud. It lets you securely manage your users’ data, credentials and permissions, offers strong authentication, and acts as an integration hub for internal and external identity providers like Entra ID or Okta.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Keycloak release 26.2, released on April 11 2025, comes with the following highlights:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Least-privileged delegated access&lt;/strong&gt; for day-to-day operations without service desk tickets by delegating administrative tasks to application owners.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced token-exchange&lt;/strong&gt; for accurate and narrowly scoped tokens for zero trust architectures.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pre-defined Grafana dashboard&lt;/strong&gt; to monitor service level indicators and key metrics of your self-hosted installations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified update and configuration &lt;/strong&gt;to increase availability, security-by-default and automation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Read on to learn why these new release highlights are important, and how Keycloak delivers them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Least-privileged delegated access for effective management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/docs/latest/server_admin/index.html#_fine_grained_permissions&#34;&gt;Fine-Grained Admin Permissions&lt;/a&gt; allow administrations to delegate administrative tasks to groups and individuals while complying with zero trust requirements and least privilege. This helps to reduce administrative costs and keep information up-to-date without service desk tickets, and enables organizations to scale and react faster to changes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This supports setups like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delegating administration of members of a group to an owner of the group.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delegating administration of a set of one or more clients in a realm to a person or a team that is managing the clients.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Keycloak 26.2, this is now fully supported and no longer in preview. You can enable it on a per-realm basis. One of the major goals of the release was to improve the user experience as well as build an extensible framework to enable more fine-grained control over realm resources. There is now a dedicated section on the realm to manage permissions, and a form based UI to manage each permission. It also scales better for large setups with a lot of resources that need to be filtered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;512&#34; height=&#34;403&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-2-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;create permission image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130435&#34; style=&#34;width:567px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-2-1.jpg 512w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-2-1-300x236.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-2-1-254x200.jpg 254w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-2-1-508x400.jpg 508w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Read more about the permission model, scopes and resource type, see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/docs/latest/server_admin/#_fine_grained_permissions&#34;&gt;Server Administration Guide&lt;/a&gt; for examples on how to set this up.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Token Exchange for accurately constrained tokens&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The authorization to access resources is critical and delicate in a zero trust architecture. Key to the evaluation are tokens that are accurately scoped to both the application’s and the user’s context. In some scenarios, also the user’s consent that an application may access the data needs to be tracked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The key to accurately scoped tokens is OAuth 2.0 Token Exchange, which has been standardized in the internet standard RFC 8693. Token exchange can be used in all scenarios where one application calls another application and needs to forward a token which is common in modern microservice architectures. To correctly assess the user’s and the calling application’s context, each application needs each token to have an explicit named audience, and neither too many nor too few scopes and permissions connected to it. A too small scope will not allow to satisfy the user’s needs, while a too broad scope would open the door to misuse or exfiltration of data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/securing-apps/token-exchange&#34;&gt;Token exchange for applications within your organisation’s realm is now fully supported.&lt;/a&gt; The process of which applications may exchange tokens is governed by Keycloak, including the revocation of tokens and keeping track of user consents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We also improved the user interface to configure which applications can exchange tokens and for which scopes to better align with how other grant types are configured.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;512&#34; height=&#34;263&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-1-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image 2&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130436&#34; style=&#34;width:552px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-1-1.jpg 512w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-1-1-300x154.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-1-1-389x200.jpg 389w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Effective management for self-hosted instances with Service Level Indicators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Keycloak handling the authentication of users and applications in your application landscape, it is a critical part of your infrastructure. To avoid outages, you want to track its performance using service level indicators (SLIs).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For Keycloak 26.1, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/observability/keycloak-service-level-indicators&#34;&gt;we published a guide on how to track the service level indicators availability, latency and error rate for instances of Keycloak&lt;/a&gt;, complete with example queries for Prometheus. They capture the performance of a system as perceived by end users. You can use these indicators to track your system’s performance on a day-to-day basis to identify system degradations, and track them against an internal target value which is then called service level objective (SLO). You can also use them to negotiate target values with your stakeholders which are then called service level agreements (SLA), or which are captured for DevOps scenarios as error budgets for both planned and unplanned maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the latest release 26.2, we also ship a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/observability/grafana-dashboards&#34;&gt;ready-to-use Grafana dashboard&lt;/a&gt; to track SLIs and other key metrics. Each key metric comes with extensive documentation on how to spot errors and remedies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Logs, traces and metrics as the three pillars of observability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When analyzing incidents, the three observability pillars logs, traces and metrics guide you to the cause and allow you to find a remedy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Logs contain essential information about application behavior and security events.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analyzing the logs helps admins to detect incidents and investigate attacks. While we supported structured logging with JSON and syslog for a long time, the latest version of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/server/logging&#34;&gt;Keycloak supports the ECS JSON format for logging&lt;/a&gt;, which will make it simpler to integrate Keycloak in an existing application landscape that relies on a common logging format.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traces connect a failure seen by a caller to its root cause like a flaky network connection to an external system.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;They are available in the OpenTelemetry tracing format which has become a standard in industry with a wide support for tooling. For Keycloak, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/observability/tracing&#34;&gt;it allows you to trace all incoming requests and connect them to the triggered activities&lt;/a&gt; like database access, calls to external identity providers, or internal LDAP access, which speeds up a root-cause-analysis during an incident a lot.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metrics keep track of service level indicators and allow alerting and auto-scaling.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;They track system and user activity, anything from the number of successful and failed logins to the utilization of caches and database connection pools. In Keycloak, they are available using the well-known Prometheus format and in the OpenMetrics format. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/observability/metrics-for-troubleshooting&#34;&gt;In Keycloak 26.1, we published a full metrics and trouble shooting guide&lt;/a&gt;. New in 26.2 is the support for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/observability/event-metrics&#34;&gt;user event metrics&lt;/a&gt; which were in preview before. We now also support exemplars, which allow you to jump directly from an outlier metric or an error rate to a recorded trace that will guide you to the root cause of an error or an incurred latency.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified update and configuration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Keycloak is now even simpler to upgrade and to configure for environments both inside and outside of Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/operator/rolling-updates&#34;&gt;Keycloak Operator now supports rolling updates&lt;/a&gt; for theme and provider updates to avoid downtimes. Our work continues to allow rolling updates also in other scenarios. The same functionality is also available &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/server/update-compatibility&#34;&gt;for deployments not using the Operator&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Keycloak clusters can now form automatically without the need to configure multicast or UDP, which was hard when deploying to cloud providers. Since Keycloak 26.1, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/server/caching&#34;&gt;Keycloak has been using its database to coordinate instances, and communicate between instances using TCP&lt;/a&gt;. New in 26.2 is that the encryption for the cluster communication is done automatically without additional steps required by an administrator.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Keycloak Operator now configures the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/operator/advanced-configuration#_network_policies&#34;&gt;matching Network policies in Kubernetes automatically&lt;/a&gt; to shield internal ports from unwanted traffic. Again one step less to configure for admins, and a better secure-by-default configuration.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fast-forward to the next releases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Work for the next feature release, which is scheduled for June 2025, is already underway. Join &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/community&#34;&gt;our forum and slack channel&lt;/a&gt; to hear the latest news and contribute!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;强大的身份和访问管理是用于云本机应用程序的零信任体系结构的关键组成部分。 &lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/”&gt; keycloak &lt;/a&gt;以其基于开放标准的单sign-on功能而闻名。它为您提供了在本地和云中自托环境中运行此操作所需的所有构建块。它使您可以安全地管理用户的数据，凭据和权限，提供强大的身份验证，并充当内部和外部身份提供商（如ENTRA ID或OKTA）的集成中心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; KeyCloak版本26​​.2，于2025年4月11日发布，带有以下亮点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;最小私人的委派访问&lt;/strong&gt;日常运营，没有服务办公桌票，通过将管理任务委派给应用程序所有者。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;增强了令牌 - 交换&lt;/strong&gt;，以准确且狭窄的令牌用于零信任体系结构。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;预定的Grafana仪表板&lt;/strong&gt;监视您的自托管安装的服务水平指标和关键指标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简化的更新和配置&lt;/strong&gt;以增加可用性，安全性和自动化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;继续阅读以了解为什么这些新版本的亮点很重要，以及KeyCloak如何提供它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/docs/latest/server_admin/index.html#_fine_grained_permissions”&gt;罚款的管理权限&lt;/a&gt;允许管理行政任务允许行政任务委托行政任务并委托个人和Zero的个人信任，并在Zero中进行Zero和Zero的要求，并最少有要求。这有助于降低管理成本，并在没有服务台票的情况下保持信息的最新信息，并使组织能够扩展和更快地对更改的反应。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这支持：&lt;/p&gt;之类的设置&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将小组成员委派给该小组的所有者。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将一个或多个客户的一组或多个领域的客户委派给管理客户的人或团队。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在KeyCloak 26.2中，现在得到了完全支持，并且不再在预览中。您可以按每次启用。发行版的主要目标之一是改善用户体验，并建立可扩展的框架，以使对领域资源更加细粒度的控制。现在，该领域有一个专门的部分来管理权限，以及一个基于表格的UI来管理每个许可。对于需要过滤的大量资源的大型设置，它也可以更好地缩放。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;512&#34; height=&#34;403&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-2-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;create permission image&#34;class =“ wp-image-130435” style =“宽度：567px;高度：自动” srcset =“ https://wwwww.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/04/2025/04/unnamed-2-1.jpg 512w，512w，512w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-2-1-300x236.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-2-1-254x200.jpg 254w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-c-1-1-508x400.jpg 508w“ sizes =” sizes =“ auto，（max-width：512px）100vw，100vw，512px“ reverrerpolicy =” notrerpolicy =“ not-referrricy&gt;”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;阅读有关权限模型，范围和资源类型的更多信息，请参见&lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/docs/latest/server_admin/server_admin/#_fine_grained_permissions”&gt;服务器管理指南&lt;/a&gt;有关如何设置此设置的示例。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;代币交换以准确约束令牌&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在零信任体系结构中，访问资源的授权至关重要。评估的关键是代币，这些令牌可准确地范围为应用程序和用户的上下文。在某些情况下，用户同意应用程序可以访问需要跟踪数据的同意。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;准确范围代币的关键是OAuth 2.0代币交换，它已在Internet Standard RFC 8693中进行了标准化。在所有情况下，都可以使用一个应用程序来调用另一个应用程序，并且需要转发一个在现代Microservice Architectures中常见的令牌。要正确评估用户和调用应用程序的上下文，每个应用程序都需要每个令牌才能具有明确的命名受众，并且与之相关的范围和范围太多也不太少。太小的范围将不允许满足用户的需求，而过于广泛的范围将打开滥用或去渗透数据的大门。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/securing-apps/token-exchange”&gt;现在完全支持您组织领域内的申请的代币交换。&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;哪些应用程序可能由keycloak进行了交换，包括keycloak，包括keycloak，包括use of user pr &lt;/the use。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还改进了用户界面，以配置应用程序可以交换令牌，以及哪些范围可以更好地与其他授予类型的配置方式保持一致。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full iS-radized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy”解码=“ async” width =“ 512”高=“ 263” src =“ https：///www.cncf.io ol class =“ wp-image-130436” style =“宽度：552px;高度：自动” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/04/2025/04/unnamed-1-1-1.jpg 512w，512w，512w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-1-1-300x154.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/unnamed-1-1-389x200.jpg 389w&#34; sizes =“自动，（最大宽度：512px）100VW，512px” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;有效管理服务级别指标的自托管实例&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;通过KeyCloak处理您的应用程序景观中用户和应用程序的身份验证，它是基础架构的关键部分。为了避免停电，您想使用服务级别指标（SLIS）跟踪其性能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于KeyCloak 26.1，&lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/observiability/keycloak-service-level-indicators”&gt;我们发布了一份指南，有关如何跟踪服务水平指示器的可用性，延迟性和错误率的keycloak &lt;/a&gt;的延迟率和错误率的指南。他们捕获了最终用户所感知的系统的性能。您可以使用这些指标每天跟踪系统的性能以识别系统降解，并根据内部目标值跟踪它们，然后将其称为服务水平目标（SLO）。您还可以使用它们与利益相关者协商目标价值，然后将其称为服务级别协议（SLA），或将DevOps方案捕获为计划和计划外维护的错误预算。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在最新版本26.2中，我们还运送a &lt;a href =“ https://www.ykeycloak.org/observiality/grafana-dashboards”&gt; Ready-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-the grafana dashboard &lt;/a&gt;以跟踪SLIS和其他关键计量。每个关键指标都有有关如何发现错误和补救措施的广泛文档。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;日志，痕迹和指标作为可观察性的三个支柱&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;分析事件时，三个可观察性支柱日志，跟踪和指标指标指导您引起原因，并允许您找到一种补救措施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;日志包含有关应用程序行为和安全事件的基本信息。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;分析日志有助于管理员检测事件并调查攻击。 While we supported structured logging with JSON and syslog for a long time, the latest version of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/server/logging&#34;&gt;Keycloak supports the ECS JSON format for logging&lt;/a&gt;, which will make it simpler to integrate Keycloak in an existing application landscape that relies on a common logging format. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;痕迹将呼叫者看到的失败与其根本原因一样，例如片状网络连接到外部系统。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;它们以OpentElemetry跟踪格式可用，该格式已成为行业中的标准，并为工具提供了广泛的支持。 For Keycloak, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/observability/tracing&#34;&gt;it allows you to trace all incoming requests and connect them to the triggered activities&lt;/a&gt; like database access, calls to external identity providers, or internal LD​​AP access, which speeds up a root-cause-analysis during an incident a lot. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;指标可以跟踪服务水平指标并允许警报和自动缩放。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;他们跟踪系统和用户活动，从成功的登录和失败的登录数量到使用库和数据库连接池的利用。在KeyCloak中，使用众所周知的Prometheus格式和Openmetrics格式使用它们。 &lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/observability/metrics-for-troubleshooting”&gt;在KeyCloak 26.1中，我们发布了完整的指标和故障射击指南&lt;/a&gt;。 26.2中的新功能是对&lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/observability/event-metrics”&gt;用户事件指标&lt;/a&gt;的支持。现在，我们还支持示例，这使您可以直接从异常指标或错误率跳到记录的跟踪，这将指导您导致错误或延迟产生的根本原因。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简化更新和配置&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; KeyCloak现在更简单地升级并为Kubernetes内外的环境配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/operator/rolling-updates”&gt; KeyCloak Operator现在支持滚动更新&lt;/a&gt;主题和提供者更新以避免下降。在其他情况下，我们的工作继续允许滚动更新。也可以使用相同的功能&lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/server/server/update-compatibility”&gt;用于使用不使用操作员的部署&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; KeyCloak簇现在可以自动形成，而无需配置多播或UDP，这在部署到云提供商时很难。由于KeyCloak 26.1，&lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/server/caching”&gt; keyCloak一直使用其数据库来协调实例，并使用TCP之间的实例进行通信&lt;/a&gt;。 26.2中的新事物是，群集通信的加密是自动完成的，而没有管理员要求的其他步骤。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; KEYCLOAK操作员现在配置&lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/operator/advanced-configuration#_network_policies”&gt;匹配Kubernetes中的网络策略自动&lt;/a&gt;使内部端口自动使内部端口免受不受欢迎的交通。同样，要为管理员配置配置的一步和更好的安全性默认配置。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;快速前向下一个版本&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;已计划于2025年6月的下一个功能版本工作。加入&lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/community”&gt;我们的论坛和Slack Channel &lt;/a&gt;听到最新消息并做出贡献！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building trust with OpenID Federation trust chain on Keycloak】使用OpenID联邦信任链建立信任在KeyCloak上</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/04/25/building-trust-with-openid-federation-trust-chain-on-keycloak/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openid.net/specs/openid-federation-1_0.html&#34;&gt;OpenID Federation 1.0&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;provides a framework to build trust between a Relying Party and an&amp;nbsp;OpenID Provider that have no direct relationship so that the Relying Party can&amp;nbsp; send OIDC/OAuth requests to the OpenID Provider without being previously authorized from that directly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://openid.net/specs/openid-federation-wallet-1_0.html&#34;&gt;One primary use case&lt;/a&gt; is the trust between an Issuer and a Holder on W3C’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.w3.org/TR/vc-overview/&#34;&gt;Verifiable Credential(VC) Data Model&lt;/a&gt;, which is getting a lot of attention as an approach to realize the Digital Identity Wallet ecosystem. (In that context, the word “Wallet” is used instead of “Holder”.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1186&#34; height=&#34;304&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.24.07%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130511&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.24.07 AM.jpg 1186w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.24.07 AM-300x77.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.24.07 AM-1024x262.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.24.07 AM-768x197.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.24.07 AM-900x231.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.24.07 AM-600x154.jpg 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1186px) 100vw, 1186px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenID Foundation provides a couple of specifications based on widely used OIDC/OAuth, such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://openid.net/specs/openid-4-verifiable-credential-issuance-1_0.html&#34;&gt;OpenID for Verifiable Credentials Issuance (OID4VCI)&lt;/a&gt;, where an OpenID Provider as Issuer provides Verifiable Credentials, VCs (protected resources in OAuth term) to a Relying Party as Holder (Wallet).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But in the Digital Identity Wallet ecosystem, the Holder (Wallet) is usually provided as Mobile Native Application and that is classified as a “public” client in OIDC/OAuth terms. It is because they are distributed from application download services of each mobile platform and can not easily issue their client secrets in a safe manner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here using &lt;a href=&#34;https://openid.net/specs/openid-connect-registration-1_0.html&#34;&gt;Dynamic Client Registration&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to provision per-instance secrets is recommended to mitigate that risk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And OpenID Federation can provide a more secure way to realize the provisioning, which makes it easier to implement issuing VCs to the Wallet especially in use cases of accessing sensitive data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.keycloak.org/&#34;&gt;Keycloak&lt;/a&gt;, Identity and Access Management OSS, is working towards implementing OpenID Federation, and it is attracting attention as a component that plays a central role in the Digital Identity Wallet ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article provides how to use OpenID Federation Trust Chain for building trust with 3-rd parties using Keycloak step-by-step.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of OpenID Federation trust framework&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In OIDC/OAuth, a Relying Party and an OpenID Provider have a direct relationship, which means that a Relying Party has registered with an OpenID Provider in advance. When the OpenID Provider gets the registration request from the Relying Party, it has to know that the Relying Party is reliable enough. For that purpose, OpenID Providers usually provide a GUI tool like an admin console for an administrator to register applications or get credentials to use for calling a client registration endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenID Federation is a framework to build trust between a Relying Party and an OpenID Provider before registration or without pre-registration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It can be described with the figure below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenID Provider A has a direct relationship with Relying Party A-1/ A-2. On the other hand, Relying Party B does not have a direct relationship with OpenID Provider A. Based on OpenID Federation Trust Chain, OpenID Provider A trusts Relying Party B so that OpenID Provider A accepts OIDC/OAuth requests from Relying Party B without prior registration or sharing credentials for registration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1186&#34; height=&#34;738&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.26.09%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130512&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.26.09 AM.jpg 1186w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.26.09 AM-300x187.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.26.09 AM-1024x637.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.26.09 AM-768x478.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.26.09 AM-900x560.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.26.09 AM-321x200.jpg 321w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.26.09 AM-643x400.jpg 643w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1186px) 100vw, 1186px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Relying Party B is authorized by the Trust Chain, which is built by third-party&amp;nbsp;authorities. One is a Trust Anchor, which is the origin of a trust chain. The other is an Intermediate Authority, which is authorized by the Trust Anchor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we use Keycloak as the OpenID Provider and show you how to register a client dynamically with OpenID Federation Trust Chain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For registering a client, there are two approaches defined in OpenID Federation and we adapt &lt;a href=&#34;https://openid.net/specs/openid-federation-1_0.html#name-explicit-registration&#34;&gt;Explicit Client Registration&lt;/a&gt;, which is suitable for implementation on top of the&lt;a href=&#34;https://openid.net/specs/openid-connect-registration-1_0.html&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;OpenID Connect Dynamic Client Registration 1.0&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;endpoint of an OpenID Provider deployment. It enables an OpenID Provider to provision a Client ID, potentially a Client Secret, and other metadata parameters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The flow detail of Explicit Client Registration is something like the following figure:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1220&#34; height=&#34;568&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.28.56%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130513&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.28.56 AM.jpg 1220w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.28.56 AM-300x140.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.28.56 AM-1024x477.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.28.56 AM-768x358.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.28.56 AM-900x419.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.28.56 AM-430x200.jpg 430w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.28.56 AM-859x400.jpg 859w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1220px) 100vw, 1220px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here the OpenID provider receives Dynamic Client Registration request with the Entity Configuration of the Relying Party. This includes information about the Relying Party itself such as endpoints of authorities, which authorize the Relying Party.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OpenID provider then sends the request to the one of the authorities, usually called Intermediate Authority, for getting the Entity Configuration of that and the Subordinate Statement which is the statement about a subordinate entity, the Relying Party in this case, with the digital signature of the Intermediate Authority.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the Entity Configuration includes endpoints of authorities again, which authorize the Intermediate Authority, the OpenID provider then sends the request to the one of the authorities for getting the Entity Configuration and the Subordinate Statement pretty much same way as before until the OpenID provider gets the Entity Configuration of the Trust Anchor, of which the Entity Configuration does not include any endpoints of authorities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the below tutorial, we show how to prepare a PoC environment for building trust with OpenID Federation Trust Chain. We use Keycloak as OpenID Provider, which provides a customized dynamic client registration endpoint with OpenID Federation plugin. And it accepts a request with OpenID Federation Trust Chain, validates that with Intermediate Authority/Trust Anchor, and creates a client.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About a PoC environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The table below shows the system configuration for each component of a PoC environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1174&#34; height=&#34;310&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.30.17%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130514&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.30.17 AM.jpg 1174w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.30.17 AM-300x79.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.30.17 AM-1024x270.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.30.17 AM-768x203.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.30.17 AM-900x238.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.30.17 AM-600x158.jpg 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1174px) 100vw, 1174px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the list below is the steps for preparing those components and performing Explicit Client Registration;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set up a mock server for Trust Anchor&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set up a mock server for Intermediate Authority&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set up Keycloak as OpenID Provider&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Perform Explicit Client Registration with OpenID Federation Trust Chain&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the next section, the details of each steps is explained one by one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set up a mock server for Trust Anchor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, prepare a trust anchor as a mock server with two endpoints.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.Federation Entity Configuration endpoint&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A HTTP GET request with the path /.well-known/openid-configuration looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1256&#34; height=&#34;206&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130515&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38 AM.jpg 1256w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38 AM-300x49.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38 AM-1024x168.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38 AM-768x126.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38 AM-900x148.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38 AM-600x98.jpg 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38 AM-1200x197.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1256px) 100vw, 1256px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the GET returns JWT, which payload is like below:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1212&#34; height=&#34;556&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.32.34%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130516&#34; style=&#34;width:883px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.32.34 AM.jpg 1212w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.32.34 AM-300x138.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.32.34 AM-1024x470.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.32.34 AM-768x352.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.32.34 AM-900x413.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.32.34 AM-436x200.jpg 436w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.32.34 AM-872x400.jpg 872w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1212px) 100vw, 1212px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1232&#34; height=&#34;1314&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.33.12%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130517&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.33.12 AM.png 1232w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.33.12 AM-281x300.png 281w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.33.12 AM-960x1024.png 960w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.33.12 AM-768x819.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.33.12 AM-900x960.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.33.12 AM-188x200.png 188w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.33.12 AM-375x400.png 375w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1232px) 100vw, 1232px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This statement is information about the Trust Anchor, so both “iss” and “sub” are the Trust Anchor itself. The “metadata” is the one about this Trust Anchor and among those the most important claim here is “federation_api_endpoint”, which issues Subordinate Statement like the next section.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Subordinate Statement Endpoint&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The HTTP GET request with the path /oidc/fedapi(*) looks like below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(*)”federation_api_endpoint “ in Entity Configuration tells you which path you should use here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1222&#34; height=&#34;236&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.36.26%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130518&#34; style=&#34;width:888px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.36.26 AM.jpg 1222w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.36.26 AM-300x58.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.36.26 AM-1024x198.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.36.26 AM-768x148.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.36.26 AM-900x174.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.36.26 AM-600x116.jpg 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.36.26 AM-1200x232.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1222px) 100vw, 1222px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Query parameter “iss” is the one to specify who issues the requested Subordinate Statement. That is the Trust Anchor here, who also signs that statement. And Query parameter “sub” is the one to specify who is the subject of that statement. That is the Intermediate Authority here, who is authorized by the Issuer with that sign.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the GET returns JWT, which payload is like below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1204&#34; height=&#34;916&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.37.38%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130519&#34; style=&#34;width:881px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.37.38 AM.png 1204w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.37.38 AM-300x228.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.37.38 AM-1024x779.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.37.38 AM-768x584.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.37.38 AM-900x685.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.37.38 AM-263x200.png 263w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.37.38 AM-526x400.png 526w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1204px) 100vw, 1204px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;938&#34; height=&#34;1230&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.39.31%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130520&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.39.31 AM.jpg 938w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.39.31 AM-229x300.jpg 229w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.39.31 AM-781x1024.jpg 781w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.39.31 AM-768x1007.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.39.31 AM-900x1180.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.39.31 AM-153x200.jpg 153w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.39.31 AM-305x400.jpg 305w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 938px) 100vw, 938px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1212&#34; height=&#34;344&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.40.33%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130521&#34; style=&#34;width:884px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.40.33 AM.png 1212w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.40.33 AM-300x85.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.40.33 AM-1024x291.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.40.33 AM-768x218.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.40.33 AM-900x255.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.40.33 AM-600x170.png 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.40.33 AM-1200x341.png 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1212px) 100vw, 1212px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This statement is information about the Intermediate Authority in “sub” and signed by the Trust Anchor in “iss”. A public key in this statement is the Intermediate Authority’s and signed by a private key of the Trust Anchor, like X.509 certificate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Intermediate Authority mentioned here is set up in the following step.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set up a mock server for Intermediate Authority&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then prepare an Intermediate Authority as a mock server with two endpoints.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.Federation Entity Configuration endpoint&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A HTTP GET request with the path /.well-known/openid-configuration looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1218&#34; height=&#34;184&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.41.28%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130522&#34; style=&#34;width:888px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.41.28 AM.png 1218w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.41.28 AM-300x45.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.41.28 AM-1024x155.png 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.41.28 AM-768x116.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.41.28 AM-900x136.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.41.28 AM-600x91.png 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.41.28 AM-1200x181.png 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1218px) 100vw, 1218px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the GET returns JWT, which payload is like below:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;1222&#34; height=&#34;366&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.42.19%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130523&#34; style=&#34;width:886px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.42.19 AM.jpg 1222w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.42.19 AM-300x90.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.42.19 AM-1024x307.jpg 1024w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.42.19 AM-768x230.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.42.19 AM-900x270.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.42.19 AM-600x180.jpg 600w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.42.19 AM-1200x359.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1222px) 100vw, 1222px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;930&#34; height=&#34;1226&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.43.05%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130524&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.43.05 AM.png 930w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.43.05 AM-228x300.png 228w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.43.05 AM-777x1024.png 777w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.43.05 AM-768x1012.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.43.05 AM-900x1186.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.43.05 AM-152x200.png 152w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.43.05 AM-303x400.png 303w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 930px) 100vw, 930px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;912&#34; height=&#34;76&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.13%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130525&#34; style=&#34;width:890px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.13 AM.png 912w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.13 AM-300x25.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.13 AM-768x64.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.13 AM-900x75.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.13 AM-600x50.png 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 912px) 100vw, 912px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here “authority_hints” is a list of authorities who can authorize this Intermediate Authority and which should include the Trust Anchor described in the previous step. This statement is information about the Intermediate Authority itself as same as the one for the Trust Anchor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Subordinate Statement Endpoint&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A HTTP GET request with the path /oidc/fedapi(*) looks like below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(*)”federation_api_endpoint “ in Entity Configuration tells you which path you should use here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;920&#34; height=&#34;182&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.56%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130526&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.56 AM.jpg 920w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.56 AM-300x59.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.56 AM-768x152.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.56 AM-900x178.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.44.56 AM-600x119.jpg 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 920px) 100vw, 920px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Query parameter “iss” is the one to specify who issues the requested Subordinate Statement. That is the Intermediate Authority here, who also signs that statement. And Query parameter “sub” is the one to specify who is the subject of that statement. That is the Relying Party here, who is authorized by the Issuer with that sign.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the GET returns JWT, which payload is like below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;940&#34; height=&#34;416&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.12%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130527&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.12 AM.jpg 940w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.12 AM-300x133.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.12 AM-768x340.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.12 AM-900x398.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.12 AM-452x200.jpg 452w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.12 AM-904x400.jpg 904w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 940px) 100vw, 940px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;904&#34; height=&#34;1224&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.57%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130528&#34; style=&#34;width:869px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.57 AM.jpg 904w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.57 AM-222x300.jpg 222w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.57 AM-756x1024.jpg 756w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.57 AM-768x1040.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.57 AM-900x1219.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.57 AM-148x200.jpg 148w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.46.57 AM-295x400.jpg 295w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 904px) 100vw, 904px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;920&#34; height=&#34;724&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.48.26%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130529&#34; style=&#34;width:881px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.48.26 AM.jpg 920w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.48.26 AM-300x236.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.48.26 AM-768x604.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.48.26 AM-900x708.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.48.26 AM-254x200.jpg 254w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.48.26 AM-508x400.jpg 508w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 920px) 100vw, 920px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This statement is information about the Relying Party in “sub” and signed by the Intermediate Authority in “iss”. A public key in this statement is the Relying Party’s and signed by a private key of the Intermediate Authority, like X.509 certificate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set up Keycloak as OpenID provider&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally prepare Keycloak as OpenID Provider:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, install Keycloak. Download and unzip the Keycloak.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;922&#34; height=&#34;198&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.49.48%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130530&#34; style=&#34;width:880px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.49.48 AM.png 922w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.49.48 AM-300x64.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.49.48 AM-768x165.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.49.48 AM-900x193.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.49.48 AM-600x129.png 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 922px) 100vw, 922px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, install the Keycloak OpenID Federation plugin. Copy the jar file created in the target directory using the commands below to the Keycloak providers directory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;912&#34; height=&#34;210&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.50.45%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130531&#34; style=&#34;width:881px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.50.45 AM.png 912w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.50.45 AM-300x69.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.50.45 AM-768x177.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.50.45 AM-900x207.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.50.45 AM-600x138.png 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 912px) 100vw, 912px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, start Keycloak.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;912&#34; height=&#34;94&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.51.37%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130532&#34; style=&#34;width:885px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.51.37 AM.jpg 912w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.51.37 AM-300x31.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.51.37 AM-768x79.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.51.37 AM-900x93.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.51.37 AM-600x62.jpg 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 912px) 100vw, 912px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Access the 8080 port of the Keycloak host and log in to the admin console with the administrator username/password.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;906&#34; height=&#34;578&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.52.27%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130533&#34; style=&#34;width:874px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.52.27 AM.jpg 906w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.52.27 AM-300x191.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.52.27 AM-768x490.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.52.27 AM-900x574.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.52.27 AM-313x200.jpg 313w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.52.27 AM-627x400.jpg 627w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 906px) 100vw, 906px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Create a realm “fed01”.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;910&#34; height=&#34;548&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.53.16%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130534&#34; style=&#34;width:881px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.53.16 AM.jpg 910w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.53.16 AM-300x181.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.53.16 AM-768x462.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.53.16 AM-900x542.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.53.16 AM-332x200.jpg 332w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.53.16 AM-664x400.jpg 664w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 910px) 100vw, 910px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Register a trust anchor for the new realm:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;914&#34; height=&#34;306&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.54.09%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130535&#34; style=&#34;width:882px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.54.09 AM.png 914w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.54.09 AM-300x100.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.54.09 AM-768x257.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.54.09 AM-900x301.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.54.09 AM-597x200.png 597w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 914px) 100vw, 914px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perform explicit client registration with OpenID Federation trust chain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now your Keycloak is all ready for Explicit Client Registration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, for the Explicit Client Registration request, prepare JWT, which payload is like below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;910&#34; height=&#34;1136&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.55.12%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130536&#34; style=&#34;width:877px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.55.12 AM.png 910w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.55.12 AM-240x300.png 240w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.55.12 AM-820x1024.png 820w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.55.12 AM-768x959.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.55.12 AM-900x1124.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.55.12 AM-160x200.png 160w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.55.12 AM-320x400.png 320w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 910px) 100vw, 910px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;912&#34; height=&#34;668&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.56.07%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130537&#34; style=&#34;width:879px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.56.07 AM.jpg 912w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.56.07 AM-300x220.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.56.07 AM-768x563.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.56.07 AM-900x659.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.56.07 AM-273x200.jpg 273w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.56.07 AM-546x400.jpg 546w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 912px) 100vw, 912px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This statement is information about the Relying Party, so both “iss” and “sub” are the Relying Party itself. On the other hand, “aud” is the OpenID provider which receives this registration request. The “metadata” is the one about this Relying Party, which includes OIDC/OAuth related ones, such as “jwks_uri”, “redirect_uris”. And most importantly “authority_hints” is a list of authorities who can authorize this Relying Party, usually the list of Intermediate Authorities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And send a HTTP POST request with the JWT above:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;904&#34; height=&#34;138&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.17%E2%80%AFAM.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130538&#34; style=&#34;width:876px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.17 AM.png 904w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.17 AM-300x46.png 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.17 AM-768x117.png 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.17 AM-900x137.png 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.17 AM-600x92.png 600w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 904px) 100vw, 904px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally,&amp;nbsp; check if a new client is created on admin console like below:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;918&#34; height=&#34;554&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.53%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130539&#34; style=&#34;width:882px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.53 AM.jpg 918w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.53 AM-300x181.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.53 AM-768x463.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.53 AM-900x543.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.53 AM-331x200.jpg 331w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.57.53 AM-663x400.jpg 663w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 918px) 100vw, 918px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image size-full is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; decoding=&#34;async&#34; width=&#34;908&#34; height=&#34;552&#34; src=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.58.29%E2%80%AFAM.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; class=&#34;wp-image-130540&#34; style=&#34;width:879px;height:auto&#34; srcset=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.58.29 AM.jpg 908w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.58.29 AM-300x182.jpg 300w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.58.29 AM-768x467.jpg 768w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.58.29 AM-900x547.jpg 900w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.58.29 AM-329x200.jpg 329w, https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.58.29 AM-658x400.jpg 658w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 908px) 100vw, 908px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a result, you can see here the client you have just created by Explicit Client Registration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, I explained how to build trust between a 3-rd party Relying Party and Keycloak as an OpenID Provider with OpenID Federation Trust Chain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently in the Keycloak community, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/keycloak/kc-sig-fapi&#34;&gt;OAuth-SIG&lt;/a&gt; (a group whose activity is mainly supporting OIDC/OAuth and its related security features to Keycloak) discusses how to enhance&amp;nbsp; Keycloak to build the Digital Identity Wallet ecosystem, for which we believe OpenID Federation plays a crucial role and we are taking an initiative to include the OpenID Federation functionality into Keycloak.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://openid.net/specs/openid-federation-1_0.html”&gt;开放式联邦1.0 &lt;/a&gt;提供了一个框架来建立一个依赖方和没有直接关系的依赖人物之间的信任，以使依赖的派对可以向以前的operc/oauth provider发送给Oauth provider，以前&lt;oauth provider &lt;oauth provider &lt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://openid.net/specs/openid-federation-wallet-1_0.html”&gt;一个主要用例&lt;/a&gt;是发行人与W3C的持有人之间的信任模型&lt;/a&gt;，它引起了很多关注，作为实现数字身份钱包生态系统的一种方法。 （在这种情况下，使用“钱包”一词代替“持有人”。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.24.07%E2%80%80％; srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.24.07am.jpg 1186W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.24.07AM-300X77.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.24.07AM-1024X262.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.24.07AM-768X197.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.24.07am-900x231.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.24.07AM-600X154.JPG 600W 600W 600W“ sizes =” size =“ auto，（max-witth） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OpenID粉底提供了基于广泛使用的OIDC/OAUTH的几个规格，例如&lt;a href =“ https://openid.net/specs/pecs/openid-4-verifial-verifable-verifial-verectial-credential-issuance-issuance-issuance-1_0.html”凭证，VCS（OAuth术语中受保护的资源）作为依赖方作为持有人（钱包）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是在数字身份钱包生态系统中，持有人（钱包）通常以移动本机应用程序提供，并且在OIDC/OAUTH术语中被归类为“公共”客户端。这是因为它们是从每个移动平台的应用程序下载服务中分发的，并且无法以安全的方式发布其客户秘密。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此处使用&lt;a href =“ https://openid.net/specs/openid-connect-registration-conredration-1_0.html”&gt;动态客户端注册&lt;/a&gt;建议减轻均一分子的求职来减轻这种风险。&lt;/p&gt; p&gt; p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和OpenID联合会可以提供一种更安全的方法来实现供应，这使得更容易地将VC实施到钱包中，尤其是在访问敏感数据的用例中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.keycloak.org/”&gt; keycloak &lt;/a&gt;，身份和访问管理OSS，正在努力努力将OpenID联合会孕育，它引起了人们的关注，作为在数字身份钱包生态系统中起着核心作用的组成部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文提供了如何使用KeyCloak逐步使用OpenID Federation Trust Chain与3-RD派对建立信任。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; OpenID联邦信任框架&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;概述&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在OIDC/OAUTH中，依赖方和开放式提供商有直接关系，这意味着一个依赖方已提前与OpenID提供商注册。当OpenID提供商从依赖方获得注册请求时，它必须知道依赖方足够可靠。为此，OpenID提供商通常提供一个GUI工具，例如管理员供管理员注册应用程序或获取用于调用客户端注册端点的凭据。&lt;/p&gt;的凭据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OpenID联合会是一个框架，可以在注册前或没有预注册之前建立依赖方和开放式提供商之间的信任。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可以用下图描述：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OpenID提供商A与依赖方A-1/ A-2有直接关系。另一方面，依赖方B与OpenID提供商A没有直接关系A。根据OpenID联邦信托链，OpenID提供商A信托基于依靠方B的信托基金，因此OpenID提供商A接受OIDC/OAUTH请求，而无需依靠Partion B而不先前注册或共享注册凭证。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 1186” height =“ 738” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.26.09%E2%80%80%80%Afp. srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.26.09AM.JPG 1186W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.26.09AM-300X187.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.26.09AM-1024X637.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.26.09AM-768X478.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.26.09AM-900X560.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.26.09AM-321X200.JPG 321W，321W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.26.09AM-643X400.JPG 643W 643W 643W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;依靠党的B由第三方当局建造的信托链授权。一个是信托基础，这是信托链的起源。另一个是一个中级权威，由信托主持人授权。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将KeyCloak用作OpenID提供商，并向您展示如何在OpenID Federation Trust链中动态注册客户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用于注册客户RE是OpenID联邦定义的两种方法，我们适应&lt;a href =“ https://openid.net/specs/openid-federation-1_0.html#name-explitic-registration-rigistration”&gt; expllicit客户注册&lt;/a&gt;适用于&lt;a href =“ https://openid.net/specs/openid-connect-registration-connect-registration-1_0.html”&gt; OpenID Connect Dynamic Client Dynamic Client注册1.0 &lt;/a&gt; OpenID提供商部署的端点。它使OpenID提供商能够提供客户ID，可能是客户端秘密和其他元数据参数。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;显式客户注册的流程细节是下图：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 1220” height =“ 568” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.28.56%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.28.28.56am.jpg 1220w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.28.56AM-300X140.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.28.56AM-1024X477.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.28.56am-768x358.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.28.56AM-900X419.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.28.56am-430x200.jpg 430w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.28.56am-859x400.jpg 859W 859W“尺寸” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这里，OpenID提供商通过依赖方的实体配置接收动态客户端注册请求。这包括有关依赖方本身的信息，例如当局的终点，这些信息授权依靠一方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;然后，OpenID提供商将请求发送给一个当局，通常称为中级当局，以获取该实体配置，以及下属语句，该声明是关于下属实体的陈述，在这种情况下，依赖方，具有中间当局的数字签名。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果实体配置再次包含当局的终点（授权中级权威的终点），则OpenID提供者将请求发送给当局之一，以获取实体配置和下属语句与以前几乎相同的方式，直到OpenID提供商获得信任的实体配置，其主持人不包括任何entity Ensiveritionss oferitionss oferitionsssssss。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在下面的教程中，我们展示了如何使用OpenID联合信任链准备POC环境来建立信任。我们使用KeyCloak作为OpenID提供商，该提供商为OpenID Federation插件提供了自定义的动态客户端注册端点。一个nd它接受了使用OpenID联合信任链的请求，验证了中级权威/信托主持人的请求，并创建客户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;关于POC环境&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下表显示了POC环境每个组件的系统配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 1174” height =“ 310” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.30.17%E2%80%80%80%2%Afm.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.30.30.17am.jpg 1174w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.30.17AM-300X79.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.30.17AM-1024X270.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.30.17am-768x203.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.30.17AM-900X238.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.30.17AM-600X158.JPG 600W 600W 600W“ sizes =” size =“ auto referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和下面的列表是准备这些组件并执行明确的客户注册的步骤； &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;为信任锚定设置模拟服务器&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;为中级权威设置模拟服务器&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将KeyCloak设置为OpenID提供商&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用OpenID联合信任链执行明确的客户注册&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从下一节中，每个步骤的详细信息都一个一个一个。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，作为具有两个端点的模拟服务器准备信任锚。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1.Federation Entity配置端点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; http带有路径/.well-newand/openid-configuration的http请求如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.31.31.38%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.31.31.38AM.JPG 1256W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.31.31.38am-300x49.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.31.31.38AM-1024X168.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.31.38AM-768X126.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.31.38AM-900X148.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.31.31.38AM-600X98.JPG 600W，600W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-at-8.31.38 AM-1200x197.jpg 1200w&#34; sizes=&#34;auto, (max-width: 1256px) 100vw, 1256px&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和get返回JWT，哪个有效载荷如下：&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.32.34%E2%80%80%80%Afm.jpg- srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.32.34AM.jpg 1212W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.32.34am-300x138.jpg 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.32.34AM-1024X470.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.32.34am-768x352.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.32.34am-900x413.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.32.34AM-436X200.JPG 436W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.32.34.32.34am-872x400.jpg 872W 872W 872W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.33.12%E2%80%80%80%2%Afam.png.png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.33.12am.png 1232w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.33.12am-281x300.png 281w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.33.12AM-960X1024.PNG 960W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.33.12AM-768X819.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.33.12am-900x960.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.33.12am-188x200.png 188w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.33.12am-375x400.png 375W 375W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此语句是有关信托基金的信息，因此“ ISS”和“ SUB”都是信托锚本身。 “元数据”是关于此信托基金的一个，其中最重要的主张是“ federation_api_endpoint”，它发布了下属语句，例如下一节。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 2。下属语句端点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; http使用路径/oidc/fedapi（*）的http请求如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;（*）” federation_api_endpoint“在实体配置中告诉您应在此处使用的路径。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-instrized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” decoding =“ async” width =“ 1222” height =“ 236” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-04-25-AT-AT-AT-AT-AT-AT-AT-8.36.26.26; 36.26; ALT ALT ALT ALT ALT ALT =” class =“ wp-image-130518”样式=“宽度：888px;高度：自动” srcset =“ https：//www.cncf.io/wp-content/wp-content/2025/04/04/screenshot-2025-2025-2025-2025-04-25--AT-8.8.8.36.36.36.36 am https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.36.26.26AM-300X58.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.36.26AM-1024X198.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.36.26.26am-768x148.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.36.26.26am-900x174.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.36.26.26AM-600X116.JPG 600W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.36.26.26AM-1200X232.JPG 1200W 1200W 1200W” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查询参数“ ISS”是指定谁发出所请求的下属语句的参数。那是这里的信任主持人，他也签署了该声明。查询参数“ sub”是指定谁是该语句的主题的参数。那是这里的中级机构，由发行人授权该标志。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和get返回JWT，有效载荷如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.37.37.38%E2%80%80%80%Afm.png，png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.37.37.37.38AM.png 1204w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.37.38AM-300X228.PNG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.37.37.38AM-1024X7779.PNG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.37.38AM-768X584.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.37.37.38AM-900X685.PNG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.37.37.38am-263x200.png 263w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.37.37.38AM-526X400.png 526W 526W 526W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 938” height =“ 1230” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.39.319.31.31; srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.39.39.31.31am.jpg 938w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.39.39.31.31AM-229x300.jpg 229w，wp-content/uploads/2025/04/屏幕截图-2025-04-25-AT-8.39.31AM-781X1024.JPG 781W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.39.39.31.31AM-768X1007.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.39.39.311AM-900X1180.JPG 900W，900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.39.39.39.31.31AM-153X200.jpg 153w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.39.39.39.31AM-305x400.jpg 305W 305W 305W“ size =” auto =“ auto，（max-witth） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-resized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dexoding =“ async” width =“ 1212” height =“ 344” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.40.33%E2%80%80%80%Afm.png，png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.40.33AM.png 1212W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.40.33AM-300X85.PNG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.40.33AM-1024X291.PNG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.40.33AM-768X218.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.40.33am-900x255.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.40.33AM-600X170.PNG 600W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.40.33AM-1200X341.PNG 1200W 1200W 1200W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此声明是有关“ Sub”中中级权威的信息，并由信托基金主持人在“ ISS”中签署。此声明中的一个公钥是中级当局，并由信托主持人的私钥签名，例如X.509证书。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此处提到的中级权威将在以下步骤中设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后准备一个具有两个端点的模拟服务器中级权威。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1.Federation Entity配置端点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; http带有路径/.well-newand/openid-configuration的http请求如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.41.28%E2%80%80%80%Afm.png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.41.28AM.png 1218W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.41.28AM-300X45.PNG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.41.28AM-1024X155.PNG 1024W，https:///wwwww.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.41.28am-768x116.png 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.41.28AM-900X136.PNG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.41.28am-600x91.png 600w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.41.28AM-1200X181.PNG 1200W 1200W 1200W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和get返回JWT，哪个有效载荷如下：&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.42.19%E2%80%80%80%Afm.jpg- srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.42.19am.jpg 12222w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.42.19am-300x90.jpg 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.42.19AM-1024X307.JPG 1024W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.42.19AM-768X230.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.42.19am-900x270.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.42.19am-600x180.jpg 600w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.42.19AM-1200X359.JPG 1200W 1200W 1200W“ sizes =” size =“ auto，（max-witth of at auto，（max-witth） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” decoding =“ async” width =“ 930” height =“ 1226” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.43.05%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.png，png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.43.05am.png 930w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.43.05am-228x300.png 228w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.43.05AM-7777X1024.PNG 777W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.43.05AM-768X1012.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.43.05AM-900X1186.PNG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.43.05am-152x200.png 152w https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.43.05AM-303X400.png 303W 303W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-instrized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dexoding =“ async” width =“ 912” height =“ 76” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.44.13%E2%80%80%80%Afm.png，png” srcset =“ https：//www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.44.13am.png 912w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.44.13am-300x25.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.44.13AM-768X644.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.44.13am-900x75.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.44.13AM-600X50.PNG 600W 600W 600W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这里的“权限_hints”是可以授权此中级权威的当局的清单，其中应包括上一步中描述的信托锚。该声明是有关中级权威本身与信托主持人一样的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 2。下属语句端点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; http带有路径/oidc/fedapi（*）的http请求如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;（*）” federation_api_endpoint“在实体配置中告诉您应在此处使用的路径。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 920” height =“ 182” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.44.56%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.jpg.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.44.56am.jpg 920w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.44.56am-300x59.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.44.56AM-768X152.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.44.56am-900x178.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.44.56AM-600X119.JPG 600W 600W 600W 600W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查询参数“ ISS”是指定谁发出所请求的下属语句的参数。那是这里的中级权威，他也签署了该声明。查询参数“ sub”是指定谁是该语句的主题的参数。那是这里的依赖方，由发行人授权该标志。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和get返回JWT，有效载荷如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.12%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.12AM.jpg 940W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.12AM-300X133.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.12AM-768X340.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04--25-AT-8.46.12AM-900X398.JPG 900W，https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-04-25-04-25-AT-AT-AT-8.46.46.12AM-46.12AM-4522X2X2X2X232W 452WWER https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.12AM-904X400.JPG 904W 904W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-instrized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dexoding =“ async” width =“ 904” height =“ 1224” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.46.57%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.jpg- srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.57AM.JPG 904W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.57AM-222X300.JPG 222W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.57AM-756X1024W4.JPG 756W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.57AM-768X1040.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.46.57am-900x1219.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.46.57AM-148X200.JPG 148W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.46.57am-295x400.jpg 295w referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-instrized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dexoding =“ async” width =“ 920” height =“ 724” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.48.26%E2%80%80%80%Afm.jpg- srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.48.48.26am.jpg 920w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.48.26AM-300X236.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.48.26AM-768X604.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.48.26AM-900X708.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.48.48.26am-254x200.jpg 254w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.48.26AM-508X400.JPG 508W 508W“ sizes =” size =“ auto =” auto，（max-witth：max-witth：max-witth referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此声明是“ Sub”中有关依赖方的信息，并由中级当局在“ ISS”中签署。该声明中的一个公钥是依赖方，并由中级管理局的私钥签署，例如X.509证书。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;终于准备KeyCloak作为OpenID提供商：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，安装KeyCloak。下载并解开KeyCloak。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在高度=“ 198” style =“ width：880px;高度：自动” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-04-25-AT-8.49.49.49.49.48AM.PNG 9222W，922W，922W，922W，922W，922W，922W，922W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.49.48.48am-300x64.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.49.49.48m-768x165.png 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.49.49.48am-900x193.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.49.499.48AM-600X129.PNG 600W 600W 600W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，安装KeyCloak OpenID联合插件。使用以下命令在目标目录中创建的JAR文件为KeyCloak提供商目录。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.50.45%E2%80%80%80%2%Afam.png.png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.50.40.45AM.png 912w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.50.45AM-300X69.PNG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.50.45AM-768X177.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.50.50.45am-900x207.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.50.45AM-600X138.PNG 600W 600W“ sizes =” size =“ auto =” auto，（max-witth：max-witth：max-witth referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，启动keycloak。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.51.37%E2%80%80%80%2%Afam.jpg” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.51.37AM.JPG 912W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.51.37AM-300X31.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.51.37AM-768X79.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.51.37AM-900X93.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.51.37AM-600X62.JPG 600W 600W 600W“ size =” size =“ auto，（max-witth） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;访问KeyCloak主机的8080端口，并使用管理员用户名/密码登录管理员。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-instrized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dexoding =“ async” width =“ 906” height =“578“ src =” https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.52.27%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.jpg style =“ width：874px;高度：自动” srcset =“ https：//www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-04-25-AT-8.52.27AM.JPG 90AM.JPG 906W，906W，906W，906W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.52.27AM-300X191.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.52.27AM-768X490.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.52.27am-900x574.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.52.27am-313x200.jpg 313w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.52.27AM-627X400.JPG 627W 627W 627W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建一个领域“ fed01”。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.53.16%E2%80%80%80%Afm.jpg- srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.53.16am.jpg 910w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.53.16am-300x181.jpg 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.53.16am-768x462.jpg 768w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.53.16am-900x542.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.53.16am-332x200.jpg 332w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.53.16AM-664X400.JPG 664W 664W 664W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注册新领域的信任锚：&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-resized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 914” height =“ 306” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.54.09%E2%80%80%80%Afm.afam.png.png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.54.09am.png 914w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.54.09am-300x100.png 300w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.54.09AM-768X257.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.54.09am-900x301.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.54.09AM-597X200.png 597W 597W 597W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;使用OpenID联邦信任链执行明确的客户注册&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在您的KeyCloak都准备好进行明确的客户注册。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，对于明确的客户注册请求，准备JWT，哪个有效载荷如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.55.12%E2%E2%80%80%80%Afam.png.png” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.55.12am.png 910w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.55.12am-240x300.png 240w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.55.12am-820x10244.png 820w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.55.12AM-768X959.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.55.12am-900x1124.png 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.55.12AM-160X200.png 160w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.55.12AM-320X400.png 320W 320W“ sizes =” size =“ auto，（max-witth of（max-witth） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-instrized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” decoding =“ async” width =“ 912” height =“ 668” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.56.07%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.jpg- srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.56.07AM.JPG 912W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.56.07AM-300X220.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.56.07AM-768X563.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.56.07AM-900X659.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.56.07AM-273X200.JPG 273W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.56.07AM-546X400.JPG 546W 546W 546W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此陈述是有关依赖方的信息，因此“ ISS”和“ Sub”都是依赖方本身。另一方面，“ AUD”是接收此注册请求的OpenID提供商。 “元数据”是关于这个依赖方的人，其中包括OIDC/OAUTH相关的一方，例如“ jwks_uri”，“ redirect_uris”。最重要的是，“权威_HINTS”是可以授权该依赖方的当局名单，通常是中级当局的列表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;并在上面的JWT上发送HTTP POST请求：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full iS-ress”&gt; &lt;img loading =“懒惰”解码=“ async” width =“ 904”高=“ 138” src =“ https：///www.cncf.io of-25-at-8.57.1​​7％e2％80％afam.png“ alt =“ image” class =“ wp-image-130538” style =“ width：876px;高度：自动：自动” srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.1​​7AM.PNG 904W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.1​​7AM-300X46.PNG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.1​​7AM-768X117.PNG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.1​​7AM-900X137.PNG 900W，900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.1​​7AM-600X92.PNG 600W 600W 600W“ size =” size =“ auto，（max-witth of auto，（max-witth） referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，检查是否在管理控制台上创建新客户端，如下：&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image size-full ins-resized”&gt; &lt;img loading =“ lazy” dododing =“ async” width =“ 918” height =“ 554” src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.53%E2%80%80%80%80%Afm.jpg- srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.57.57.53am.jpg 918w，918W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.53AM-300X181.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.53AM-768X463.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-at-8.57.53am-900x543.jpg 900w， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.53AM-331X200.JPG 331W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.57.53AM-663X400.JPG 663W 663W 663W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在src =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.58.29%E2%80%80%80%Afm.jpg- srcset =“ https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.58.29AM.JPG 908W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.58.29AM-300X182.JPG 300W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.58.29AM-768X467.JPG 768W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.58.29AM-900X547.JPG 900W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.58.29AM-329X200.JPG 329W，329W， https://www.cncf.io/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/screenshot-2025-04-25-04-25-AT-8.58.29AM-658X400.JPG 658W 658W 658W“尺寸referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结果，您可以在此处查看刚刚通过显式客户注册创建的客户端。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;结论&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我解释了如何在第三方依靠政党和KeyCloak作为OpenID联邦信托链的开放式提供商。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently in the Keycloak community, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/keycloak/kc-sig-fapi&#34;&gt;OAuth-SIG&lt;/a&gt; (a group whose activity is mainly supporting OIDC/OAuth and its related security features to Keycloak) discusses how to enhance  Keycloak to build the Digital Identity Wallet ecosystem, for which we believe OpenID Federation plays a至关重要的角色，我们正在主动将开放式联合会功能包括在KeyCloak中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>