<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://cloudys-rsshub-ab061133bcab.herokuapp.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【How OCI Artifacts Will Drive Future AI Use Cases】OCI工件将如何推动未来的AI用例</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/27/how-oci-artifacts-will-drive-future-ai-use-cases/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In recent years, the software industry has seen a strong shift toward enabling and supporting Artificial Intelligence (AI) workloads. While a variety of high level tools like Large Language Models (LLMs) already exist to support generic use cases, many domain specific solutions are either not yet available or come with significant development costs and risks, particularly when targeting more niche problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This raises an important challenge: how can we avoid building a fragmented AI tooling landscape with limited real world applicability?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To truly support the next wave of AI innovation, especially in cloud native environments, we need to rethink and reinforce our software component foundation. This includes standardizing formats, improving cross platform interoperability, and evolving Kubernetes with AI native features in mind. One of the most promising developments in this space revolves around &lt;a href=&#34;https://opencontainers.org/&#34;&gt;Open Container Initiative (OCI)&lt;/a&gt; artifacts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The role of OCI artifacts in the AI ecosystem&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OCI artifacts enable users to store and distribute arbitrary files and metadata using OCI compliant container registries. While originally used for generic purposes (like &lt;a href=&#34;https://oras.land/&#34;&gt;ORAS&lt;/a&gt; supports them), they’re now finding critical roles in AI/ML workflows, especially with the rise of specifications like the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/modelpack/model-spec&#34;&gt;CNCF ModelPack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CNCF ModelPack Specification builds on top of OCI artifacts and aims to standardize the packaging, distribution, and execution of AI models in cloud native environments. By moving away from proprietary formats, ModelPack facilitates reproducibility, portability, and vendor neutrality in machine learning workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This opens the door to several important use cases:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Standardized AI/ML model packaging&lt;/strong&gt;: With OCI artifacts, models can be versioned, distributed, and tracked like container images. This promotes consistency and traceability across environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure model delivery&lt;/strong&gt;: Well established solutions like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sigstore.dev/&#34;&gt;sigstore&lt;/a&gt; signatures offer mechanisms to sign and verify OCI artifacts, improving model integrity and trustworthiness. It also allows to scan artifacts like container images for vulnerabilities or other security issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI/ML model development&lt;/strong&gt;: For example, it is possible to package ML pipelines as OCI artifacts reuse and sharing across teams. Configuration files can be packaed into artifacts for specific environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;How Kubernetes and OCI Artifacts fit together&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Having standards around OCI artifacts are essential for building robust AI features into Kubernetes. For example, the Kubernetes &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/tasks/configure-pod-container/image-volumes&#34;&gt;Image Volume&lt;/a&gt; feature allows pods to mount container image layers as read-only volumes. Image volumes could also support OCI artifacts as a special use case.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXceJ1srpr1hqfO4ANwF2MQcDQVvfvZmEOA_U7lZ1d1HGnd42-MuLY2qJfPh48YnB4Q-m6qVNig2Lv5OtEe_7yJN_pexy1B_WXisXQZsSbR7pXpY8CCfjFMf02YyRC9pd7O60cf_jGp3-MAyqKnafmERvWfC6w4?key=DKqhJJH3beQjK9fBd8h-9w&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of Kubernetes Image Volume feature&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When combining Image Volumes with OCI artifacts, then this capability enables:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Efficient sharing of large model files across containers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Network efficient deployment by leveraging unique and deduplicated layers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fast development iterations with model variants that can reuse common base layers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tools such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/modelpack/modctl&#34;&gt;modctl&lt;/a&gt;, part of the ModelPack ecosystem, provide a CLI interface to manage these models and layers effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, Kubernetes can not do all of this alone, the ecosystem, especially container runtimes like &lt;a href=&#34;https://cri-o.io/&#34;&gt;CRI-O&lt;/a&gt;, have to serve as the bridge between the low level OCI standards and high level Kubernetes features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;CRI-O and OCI Artifact support&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recent versions of CRI-O have added native support for OCI artifacts, storing them in a dedicated directory to keep them separate from traditional container image layouts. This enables a range of AI centric features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mounting OCI artifacts as image volumes in Kubernetes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Attaching models, config files, or even assembling full container file systems from a collection of OCI artifacts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One particularly compelling benefit is architecture independence. OCI artifacts can be platform agnostic, ideal for configuration files or other cross platform assets. And when architecture specific binaries are required, CRI-O also supports multi-architecture manifests (since v1.33). For example, the release bundle at &lt;a href=&#34;https://explore.ggcr.dev/?image=ghcr.io/cri-o/bundle:v1.33.3&#34;&gt;ghcr.io/cri-o/bundle:v1.33.3&lt;/a&gt; allows the runtime to automatically select the appropriate architecture variant from the multi architecture manifest list.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CRI-O is also exploring support for &lt;strong&gt;WebAssembly (Wasm)&lt;/strong&gt; binaries stored as OCI artifacts, which is currently supported through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/containers/crun&#34;&gt;crun&lt;/a&gt; runtime. This could further expand the range of artifact based use cases across lightweight and portable compute platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite the progress, OCI artifacts are still catching up in terms of feature parity with traditional container images. For instance:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Signature validation via &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sigstore.dev/&#34;&gt;sigstore&lt;/a&gt; is not yet fully supported, though it is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cri-o/cri-o/issues/9135&#34;&gt;on the roadmap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Compressed artifact layers, a feature that would benefit workloads dealing with large, compressible files (like datasets or logs), are also &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cri-o/cri-o/issues/9132&#34;&gt;planned for the future&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support for &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/kubernetes/issues/131557&#34;&gt;read-write image volume mounts&lt;/a&gt; to be less restrictive without compromising runtime security would help to simplify distribution setups.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As these capabilities mature, OCI artifacts will become an even more essential part of building scalable, secure, and portable AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Help to shape an AI native Kubernetes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Kubernetes community is actively working to formalize AI support through new working groups (WGs) focused on various aspects of this transformation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/pull/8515&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WG AI Conformance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Defining what AI support should look like across conformant Kubernetes implementations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/pull/8519&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WG AI Integration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Focusing on integrating AI/ML components into the broader Kubernetes ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/community/pull/8521&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WG AI Gateway&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: Exploring service oriented interfaces for model serving and inference workloads.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These initiatives highlight the growing importance of AI workloads in cloud native environments. If you’re passionate about Kubernetes and AI, now is a great time to get involved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading! If this topic resonates with you, consider contributing to the discussions, proposing new features or improvements. If you would like to chat about that, feel free to directly reach out to me directly via the &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.slack.com/team/U53SUDBD4&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Slack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;近年来，软件行业已经朝着启用和支持人工智能（AI）工作量方面发生了巨大的转变。尽管已经存在各种高级语言模型（LLM）等各种高级工具来支持通用用例，但许多特定领域的解决方案尚未可用，或者尚无大量开发成本和风险，尤其是在针对更多的利基问题时。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这引起了一个重要的挑战：我们如何避免建立具有有限现实世界适用性的零散的AI工具景观？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了真正支持下一波AI创新，尤其是在云本地环境中，我们需要重新考虑和加强我们的软件组件基础。这包括标准化格式，改善跨平台互操作性以及具有AI本机功能的Kubernetes。该空间中最有希望的发展之一是围绕&lt;a href =“ https://opencontainers.org/”&gt;打开容器intiative（oci）&lt;/a&gt; tratifacts。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; oci伪像在AI生态系统中的作用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OCI伪像使用户能够使用符合OCI的容器注册表来存储和分发任意文件和元数据。虽然最初用于通用目的（例如&lt;a href =“ https://oras.land/”&gt; oras &lt;/a&gt;支持它们），但他们现在正在在AI/ML工作流中找到关键作用，尤其是随着规格的兴起，&lt;a a href =“ https：//github.com.com.com.com.com/modelpack/modelpack/modelpack/modelpack &lt;mmodelpack &lt;mmodelpack &lt;mmodelpack”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CNCF ModelPack规范构建在OCI工件之上，并旨在标准化云本机环境中AI模型的包装，分发和执行。通过远离专有格式，ModelPack促进了机器学习工作流程中的可重复性，可移植性和供应商中立。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这为几个重要用例打开了门：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;标准化的AI/ML模型包装&lt;/strong&gt;：使用OCI伪像，模型可以像容器图像一样版本，分发和跟踪。这促进了环境之间的一致性和可追溯性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;安全的模型交付&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;a href =“ https://www.sigstore.dev/”&gt; sigstore &lt;/a&gt;签名提供机制来签名和验证OCI文物，改善模型完整性和信任度。它还允许扫描诸如容器图像之类的工件是否存在漏洞或其他安全问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; AI/ML模型开发&lt;/strong&gt;：例如，可以包装ML管道，因为OCI工件在跨团队之间进行了重复使用和共享。配置文件可以包装到特定环境的工件中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; kubernetes和oci伪像&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在OCI文物周围拥有标准，对于在Kubernetes中构建强大的AI功能至关重要。为了例如，kubernetes &lt;a href =“ https://kubernetes.io/docs/tasks/configure-pod-container/image-volumes”&gt;图像卷&lt;/a&gt;功能允许Pods允许Pods安装容器层，以读取读数。图像量还可以支持OCI文物作为特殊用例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcej1srpr1hqfo4anwf2mqccdqvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvvzmeoa_u7lz1d1hgnd1hgnd42-muly242-muly2-muly2qjfph48ynb4 q -M6QVNIG2LV5OTEE_7YJN_PEXY1B_WXISXQZSSSSSBR7PXPY8CCFJFMF02YYRC9PD7O60CF_JGGP3-MAYQP3-MAYQKNAFMERVCKNAFMERVWFC6W4？ alt =“ kubernetes图像卷特征”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将图像量与OCI伪影组合在一起时，此功能可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;有效地共享容器中的大型模型文件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过利用独特和重复的层来有效部署网络有效部署。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用模型变体的快速开发迭代，可以重复使用共同的基础层。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/modelpack/modctl”&gt; modctl &lt;/a&gt;，ModelPack生态系统的一部分，提供CLI接口来有效地管理这些模型和分层。&lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，kubernetes不能单独完成所有这些，尤其是&lt;a href =“ https://cri-o.io//”&gt; Cri-o &lt;/a&gt;的生态系统，尤其是容器运行时，必须充当低级OCI标准和高级Kubernetes特征之间的桥梁。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; cri-o和oci伪像支持&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CRI-O的最新版本增加了对OCI文物的本机支持，将其存储在专用目录中，以使其与传统的容器图像布局分开。这使得各种以AI为中心的功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将OCI文物安装为Kubernetes中的图像量。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;附加模型，配置文件，甚至从OCI伪像的集合中组装完整的容器文件系统。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个特别引人注目的好处是建筑独立性。 OCI工件可以是平台不可知论，是配置文件或其他跨平台资产的理想选择。当需要特定架构的二进制文件时，CRI-O还支持多构造的表现（由于v1.33）。例如，&lt;a href =“ https://explore.ggcr.dev/?image=ghcr.io/cri-o/bundle:v1.33.3”&gt; ghcr.io/cri-o/bundle：v1.33.3 &lt;/a&gt;允许运行时可以自动从适当的架构rentection prectore contrecture &lt;/contrection。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CRI-O还正在探索对&lt;strong&gt; WebAssembly（WASM）&lt;/strong&gt;二进制文件的支持，该二进制文件存储为OCI文物，目前通过&lt;a a href =“ https://github.com/containers/containers/crun”&gt; crun“&gt; crun”&gt; crun &lt;/a&gt;运行时间。这可以进一步扩大轻巧和便携式计算平台的基于人工的用例的范围。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管取得了进展，但OCI文物仍在与传统容器IMA的特征奇偶校验中赶上Ges。例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Signature validation via &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sigstore.dev/&#34;&gt;sigstore&lt;/a&gt; is not yet fully supported, though it is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cri-o/cri-o/issues/9135&#34;&gt;on the roadmap&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;压缩的伪影层，该功能将受益于处理大型，可压缩文件（例如数据集或日志）的功能，也是&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cri-o/cri-o/cri-o/issues/91132”&gt;未来计划的&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kubernetes/kubernetes/kubernetes/issues/131557”&gt; read-write映像卷安装&lt;/a&gt;在不损害运行时安全性的情况下，限制性较低&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着这些功能成熟，OCI工件将成为构建可扩展，安全和便携式AI系统的更重要的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;有助于塑造AI本机kubernetes &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kubernetes社区正在积极努力通过专注于这种转变的各个方面的新工作组（WGS）正式化AI支持：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kubernetes/community/pull/8515”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; wg ai符合&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：定义AI支持应该在跨构象的Kubernetes实施中看起来像什么样&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kubernetes/community/pull/8519”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; wg ai Integnation &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：专注于将AI/ML组件集成到更广泛的Kubernetes EcoSystem。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kubernetes/community/pull/8521”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; wg ai Gateway &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;：探索用于模型服务和推理服务的面向服务的接口。&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些举措强调了在云本机环境中AI工作负载的重要性。如果您对Kubernetes和AI充满热情，那么现在是参与的好时机。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;感谢您的阅读！如果此主题引起您的共鸣，请考虑为讨论，提出新功能或改进做出贡献。如果您想谈论这个问题，请随时直接通过&lt;a href =“ https://kubernetes.slack.com/team/u53sudbd4”&gt; kubernetes slack &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Metal3.io becomes a CNCF incubating project】Metal3.io成为CNCF孵化项目</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/27/metal3-io-becomes-a-cncf-incubating-project/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The CNCF &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/people/technical-oversight-committee/&#34;&gt;Technical Oversight Committee&lt;/a&gt; (TOC) has voted to accept &lt;a href=&#34;https://metal3.io/&#34;&gt;Metal3&lt;/a&gt;.io as a CNCF incubating project. Metal3.io joins a growing ecosystem of technologies tackling real-world challenges at the edge of cloud native infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What is Metal3.io?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Metal3.io project (pronounced: “Metal Kubed”) provides components for bare metal host management with Kubernetes. You can enroll your bare metal machines, provision operating system images, and then, if you like, deploy Kubernetes clusters to them. From there, operating and upgrading your Kubernetes clusters can be handled by Metal3.io. Moreover, Metal3.io is itself a Kubernetes application, so it runs on Kubernetes and uses Kubernetes resources and APIs as its interface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Metal3.io is also one of the providers for the Kubernetes subproject &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/cluster-api&#34;&gt;Cluster API&lt;/a&gt;. Cluster API provides infrastructure-agnostic Kubernetes lifecycle management, and Metal3.io brings the bare metal implementation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Key Milestones and Ecosystem Growth&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project was started in 2019 by Red Hat and was quickly joined by Ericsson. Metal3.io then joined the CNCF sandbox in&lt;strong&gt; September 2020.&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Metal3.io has steadily matured and grown during the sandbox phase, with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;57 active contributing organizations&lt;/strong&gt;, led by Ericsson and Red Hat.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;An &lt;strong&gt;active community&lt;/strong&gt; organizing weekly online meetings with working group updates, issue triaging, design discussions, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Organizations such as Fujitsu, Ikea, SUSE, Ericsson, and Red Hat among the &lt;strong&gt;growing list of adopters&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New features and API iterations&lt;/strong&gt;, including IP address management, node reuse, firmware settings, and updates management both in provisioning time and on day 2, as well as remediation for the bare metal hosts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new operator&lt;/strong&gt;, called the Ironic Standalone Operator, has been introduced to replace the shell-based deployment method for Ironic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Added robust security processes&lt;/strong&gt;, regular scans of dependencies, a vulnerability disclosure process, and automated dependency updates.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Integrations Across the Cloud Native Landscape&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Metal3.io connects seamlessly with many CNCF projects, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;: Metal3.io builds on the success of Kubernetes and makes use of CustomResourceDefinitions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cluster API: &lt;/strong&gt;Turn the bare metal servers into Kubernetes clusters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cert-manager:&lt;/strong&gt; Certificates for webhooks, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ironic:&lt;/strong&gt; Handles the hardware for Metal3.io by interacting with baseboard management controllers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prometheus:&lt;/strong&gt; Metal3.io exposes metrics in a format that Prometheus can scrape&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Technical Components&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Baremetal Operator (BMO)&lt;/strong&gt;: Exposes parts of the Ironic API as a Kubernetes native API&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cluster API Provider Metal³ (CAPM3):&lt;/strong&gt; Provides integration with Cluster API&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IP Address Manager (IPAM)&lt;/strong&gt;: Handles IP addresses and pools&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ironic Standalone Operator (IrSO)&lt;/strong&gt;: Makes it easy to deploy Ironic on Kubernetes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ironic-Image&lt;/strong&gt;: Container image for Ironic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Community Highlights&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1523&lt;/strong&gt; GitHub Stars&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8368&lt;/strong&gt; merged pull requests&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1434&lt;/strong&gt; issues&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;186&lt;/strong&gt; contributors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;187&lt;/strong&gt; Releases&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Maintainer Perspective&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“As a maintainer of the Metal3.io project, I’m proud of its growth towards becoming one of the leading solutions for running Kubernetes on bare metal. I take pride in how it has evolved beyond provisioning bare metal only to support broader lifecycle needs, ensuring users can sustain and operate their bare metal deployments effectively. Equally rewarding has been seeing the community come together to establish strong processes and governance, positioning Metal3.io for CNCF incubation.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—&lt;strong&gt;Kashif Khan,&lt;/strong&gt; Maintainer, Metal3.io&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Metal3.io is a testament to the power of collaboration across open source communities. It marries the battle-tested hardware support of the Ironic project with the Kubernetes API paradigm, using a lightweight Kubernetes-native deployment model. I am delighted to see it begin incubation with CNCF. I have no doubt that the forum the Metal3.io project provides will continue to drive progress in integration between Kubernetes and bare metal.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;—&lt;strong&gt;Zane Bitter,&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; Maintainer, Metal3.io&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;From the TOC&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Metal3.io addresses a critical need for cloud native infrastructure by making bare metal as manageable and Kubernetes-native as any other platform. The project’s steady growth, technical maturity, and strong integration with the Kubernetes ecosystem made it a clear choice for incubation. We’re excited to support Metal3.io as it continues to empower organizations deploying Kubernetes at the edge and beyond.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;— &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ricardo Rocha,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; TOC Sponsor&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Looking Ahead&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Metal3.io’s roadmap for 2025 includes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;New API revisions for CAPM3, BMO, and IPAM&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Maturing IPAM as a Cluster API IPAM provider&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-tenancy support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support for architectures other than x86_64, i.e., ARM&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Improve DHCP-less provisioning&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simplifying Ironic deployment with IrSO&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a CNCF-hosted project, Metal3.io is part of a neutral foundation aligned with its technical interests, as well as the larger Linux Foundation, which provides governance, marketing support, and community outreach. Metal3.io joins incubating technologies ArtifactHUB, Backstage, Buildpacks, Chaos Mesh, Cloud Custodian, Container Network Interface (CNI), Contour, Cortex, Crossplane, Dragonfly, Emissary-Ingress, Flatcar, gRPC, Karmada, Keptn, Keycloak, Knative, Kubeflow, Kubescape, KubeVela, KubeVirt, Kyverno, Litmus, Longhorn, NATS, Notary, OpenCost, OpenFeature, OpenKruise, OpenTelemetry, OpenYurt, Operator Framework, Strimzi, Thanos, Volcano, and wasmCloud. For more information on maturity requirements for each level, please visit the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/blob/main/process/graduation_criteria.md&#34;&gt;CNCF Graduation Criteria&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing how Metal3.io continues to evolve with the backing of the CNCF community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn more: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/metal%C2%B3/&#34;&gt;https://www.cncf.io/projects/metal%C2%B3/&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; cncf &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/people/people/technical-oversight-committee/”&gt;技术监督委员会&lt;/a&gt;（toc）已投票接受&lt;a href =“ href =” https://metal3.io/ inctibation。 Metal3.io加入了一个不断增长的技术生态系统，以应对云本地基础设施边缘的现实世界挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;什么是Metal3.io？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Metal3.io项目（发音：“金属kubed”）提供了用Kubernetes的裸金属宿主管理的组件。您可以注册裸金属机器，配置操作系统图像，然后，如果您愿意，请将Kubernetes簇部署到它们。从那里开始，可以通过Metal3.io处理和升级Kubernetes簇。此外，Metal3.io本身就是Kubernetes应用程序，因此它在Kubernetes上运行，并将Kubernetes资源和API用作其接口。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Metal3.io也是Kubernetes子标记的提供者之一&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kubernetes-sigs/cluster-api”&gt; clast api api &lt;/a&gt;。群集API提供基础架构 - 静态的Kubernetes生命周期管理，Metal3.io带来了裸机的实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ wp-block-neading”&gt;关键里程碑和生态系统增长&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该项目是由红帽于2019年启动的，并迅速由爱立信加入。然后，Metal3.io加入了&lt;strong&gt; 2020年9月的CNCF沙盒。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Metal3.io在沙盒阶段稳步成熟和生长，&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 57活跃的贡献组织&lt;/strong&gt;，由爱立信和红帽领导。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;一个&lt;strong&gt;活跃的社区&lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt;通过工作组更新，发行分盘，设计讨论等组织每周在线会议等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在&lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;中，富士通，宜家，苏斯，爱立信和红帽等组织都在不断增长的采用者&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;新功能和API迭代&lt;/strong&gt;，包括IP地址管理，节点重复使用，固件设置以及在配置时间和第2天的更新管理以及对裸金属宿主的补救。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;已引入了一个新的操作员&lt;/strong&gt;，称为讽刺独立运算符，以替换具有讽刺意味的基于壳的部署方法。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;添加了强大的安全过程&lt;/strong&gt;，定期扫描依赖项，漏洞披露过程以及自动化依赖项更新。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;跨云本地景观的集成&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Metal3.IO无缝连接许多CNCF项目，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kubernetes &lt;/strong&gt;：Metal3.io建立在Kubernetes的成功基础上，并利用CustomResourcercedefinition &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;集群API：&lt;/strong&gt;将裸金属服务器变成kubernetes簇&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; cert-manager：&lt;/strong&gt; Webhooks的证书等&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;具有讽刺意味的：&lt;/strong&gt;通过与底板管理控制器互动来处理Metal3.io的硬件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Prometheus：&lt;/strong&gt; Metal3.io以普罗米修斯可以刮擦的格式公开指标&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;技术组件&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Baremetal Operator（BMO）&lt;/strong&gt;：将讽刺性API的一部分视为Kubernetes本机API &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;群集API提供商金属（CAPM3）：&lt;/strong&gt;提供与群集API &lt;/li&gt;的集成&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; IP地址管理器（IPAM）&lt;/strong&gt;：处理IP地址和池&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;具有讽刺意味的独立操作员（irso）&lt;/strong&gt;：使讽刺在kubernetes &lt;/li&gt;上很容易&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;讽刺图像&lt;/strong&gt;：具有讽刺意味的容器图像&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;社区亮点&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1523 &lt;/strong&gt; github星星&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 8368 &lt;/strong&gt;合并的拉请请求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1434 &lt;/strong&gt;问题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 186 &lt;/strong&gt;贡献者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 187 &lt;/strong&gt;发行&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;维护器透视&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“作为Metal3.io项目的维护者，我为它的发展而自豪地成为在裸机上运行Kubernetes的领先解决方案之一。我为它的发展而自豪。除了提供裸机以提供裸机以支持更广泛的生命周期需求以支持更广泛的生命周期需求，以确保用户能够维持和在裸露的金属中保持良好的态度，以使其与均等的金属融为一体。孵化。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;strong&gt; kashif khan，&lt;/strong&gt;维护器，金属3.io &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“ Metal3.io是跨开源社区协作的力量的证明。它与讽刺项目的战斗测试硬件支持与Kubernetes API范式相结合，使用轻量级的Kubernetes-native部署模型与Kubernetes API范式结合，我很高兴看到它与CNCF一起启动。和裸金属。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;strong&gt; zane苦，&lt;/strong&gt;维护器，金属3.io &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;来自toc &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Metal3.io addresses a critical need for cloud native infrastructure by making bare metal as manageable and Kubernetes-native as any other platform. The project’s steady growth, technical maturity, and strong integration with the Kubernetes ecosystem made it a clear choice for incubation. We’re excited to support Metal3.io as it continues to empower organizations deploying Kubernetes at the edge and beyond.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; ricardo rocha，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; toc发起人&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;向前看&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Metal3.io的路线图2025包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; capm3，b的新API修订MO和IPAM &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将IPAM作为群集API IPAM提供商&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多租户支持&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持X86_64以外的架构，即ARM &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;改善无DHCP供应&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;用IRSO简化讽刺部署&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为一个CNCF主持的项目，Metal3.io是与其技术利益以及更大的Linux基金会相一致的中立基础的一部分，该基金会提供了治理，营销支持和社区外展。 Metal3.io joins incubating technologies ArtifactHUB, Backstage, Buildpacks, Chaos Mesh, Cloud Custodian, Container Network Interface (CNI), Contour, Cortex, Crossplane, Dragonfly, Emissary-Ingress, Flatcar, gRPC, Karmada, Keptn, Keycloak, Knative, Kubeflow, Kubescape, KubeVela, KubeVirt, Kyverno,石英，长角牛，纳特，公证人，opencost，openfeature，openkruise，opentelemetry，opentyurt，operator框架，strimzi，thanos，thanos，Volcano和Wasmcloud。有关每个级别的成熟度要求的更多信息，请访问&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/cncf/cncf/toc/blob/main/main/process/graduation_criteria.md”&gt; cncf毕业标准&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们期待看到Metal3.io如何继续随着CNCF社区的支持而发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解更多信息：&lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/projects/metal%c2%B3/”&gt; https://www.cncf.io/projects/metal%C2%B3/ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Use Envoy Gateway as the Unified Ingress Gateway and Waypoint Proxy for Ambient Mesh】使用Envoy Gateway作为环境网格的统一入口网关和Waypoint代理</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/26/use-envoy-gateway-as-the-unified-ingress-gateway-and-waypoint-proxy-for-ambient-mesh/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/richincapie/&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;In this article, we’ll look at how you can use &lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway.envoyproxy.io/&#34;&gt;Envoy Gateway&lt;/a&gt;, an Envoy project open source solution, together with Istio when running in Ambient mode. This allows you to easily leverage the power of Envoy’s L7 capabilities for Ingress and east-west traffic in your mesh with easy-to-use CRDs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To understand how this integration works, let’s first take a quick look at &lt;strong&gt;Ambient Mesh&lt;/strong&gt; itself. Also known as &lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/overview/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Istio Ambient mode&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, it’s a sidecar-less service mesh architecture that aims to simplify deployments and can boost efficiency for specific use cases. Unlike sidecar-based meshes, Ambient splits the data plane into two key components: the &lt;strong&gt;ztunnel&lt;/strong&gt;, which secures service-to-service communication, and the &lt;strong&gt;Waypoint Proxy&lt;/strong&gt;, which handles Layer 7 traffic routing and policy enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other side, &lt;strong&gt;Envoy Gateway&lt;/strong&gt; is a Kubernetes-native API gateway built on top of Envoy Proxy. It’s designed to work seamlessly with the Kubernetes Gateway API and takes a batteries-included approach—offering built-in support for authentication, authorization, rate limiting, CORS handling, header manipulation, and more. These capabilities are exposed through familiar Kubernetes-style APIs, letting you fully tap into Envoy’s power without needing complex configurations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because both Ambient Mesh and Envoy Gateway are built on top of Envoy, they share a common foundation. This makes integration straightforward and allows &lt;strong&gt;Envoy Gateway to act as both the Ingress Gateway and Waypoint Proxy&lt;/strong&gt;—giving you a consistent and powerful way to manage traffic and apply Layer 7 policies across your mesh.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why use Envoy Gateway with Ambient Mesh?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;While Ambient Mesh simplifies service mesh operations by removing sidecars, its feature set doesn’t yet match the maturity of the sidecar-based model&lt;/strong&gt;. Some advanced Layer 7 capabilities are either missing, considered experimental, or require extra complexity to configure in native Ambient mode.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limited VirtualService Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/l7-features/&#34;&gt;VirtualService—a key resource for traffic management in classic Istio—is only available at Alpha level in Ambient&lt;/a&gt;. On top of that, it can’t be used in combination with Gateway API resources. That leaves you with the Gateway API as the only supported option. While it handles basic routing just fine, it’s intentionally generic to support many gateway implementations. As a result, you lose access to some of the richer, Envoy-specific functionality — such as global rate limiting, circuit breaking, and OIDC authentication.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Lack of&amp;nbsp; EnvoyFilter Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Ambient mode, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/istio/issues/43720&#34;&gt;EnvoyFilters are not supported&lt;/a&gt;. These filters are critical in sidecar deployments when you need to tweak or extend proxy behavior at the xDS level—whether for custom logic, telemetry, or integration with external systems. Without them, your ability to fine-tune proxy behavior is limited, which can be a blocker for advanced or production-grade use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s where &lt;strong&gt;Envoy Gateway&lt;/strong&gt; comes into play. It extends the Gateway API with &lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway.envoyproxy.io/latest/tasks/&#34;&gt;a powerful set of custom policies, including&lt;/a&gt; ClientTrafficPolicy, BackendTrafficPolicy, SecurityPolicy, EnvoyExtensionPolicy, and EnvoyPatchPolicy, to &lt;strong&gt;harness Envoy’s full potential within Ambient&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Mesh&lt;/strong&gt;. These policies can be applied directly to core Gateway API resources, such as Gateway and HTTPRoute, allowing for detailed traffic management, improved security, pluggable extensions, and even low-level xDS patching—all while maintaining the simplicity of a sidecar-free architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcUte5Razx70-v9oPxNwT5e2X-wq8T0A9psMu2rOa5aC9LTXE5tOOYtfPyL3d_8rlrz35_d18zKuDHt1DtefcTbAII7n-nt27GHz_5YpJt9SemHa2djGcTOez5EY3ix4iP1bCNQqQ?key=YPRa9nNd6jZ-mS5fp2vj3g&#34; alt=&#34;Envoy Gateway image&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unlocking Envoy’s Full Potential with Envoy Gateway Policies in Ambient Mesh&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;How Envoy Gateway Works in Ambient Mesh?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a default Ambient Mesh deployment, the waypoint proxy handles both terminating the incoming HBONE tunnel and establishing a new one to the destination service. It also applies Layer 7 traffic policies during this process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXddjesYPjsW315Y2FDGF56D4qeRCEvNwfF0dmGPhDjLNPUZw4Kt_pKENVMjf2n5pKmJW2YaYVR8B2wEybLwuucv-D5A3QLncqNiHBhnQThTRKpZxaha-D1Usp13UYxhC54DuCBRdw?key=YPRa9nNd6jZ-mS5fp2vj3g&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of How Envoy Gateway Works in Ambient Mesh?&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traffic Flow in a Default Waypoint Proxy Deployment&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, Ambient also supports a more modular “sandwich” model, where the ztunnel is logically placed before and after the waypoint proxy, much like a sandwich. In this setup, the ztunnel is responsible for managing the HBONE tunnels on both sides, while the waypoint proxy focuses solely on L7 traffic management and policy enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdIlPZW-B1QAMBLFDLhQgsWv3Xu3N0TnPdDHGpliFw4MjiAt-hsGyvmbkUFc-j1u8tPOD4jGnPZ4ulJpmEFcxjFG299xUSMmbeKstdBfNPF8BA5xk4K0hFhj4oKGLxOmFsr0AJWSw?key=YPRa9nNd6jZ-mS5fp2vj3g&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of how Ambient supports a more modular “sandwich” model&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traffic Flow in a Sandwiched Waypoint Proxy Deployment&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: This diagram illustrates how traffic flows through various components in Ambient Mesh. While it appears that there are two zTunnels placed before and after Envoy Gateway, they’re actually the same instance—let’s gloss over that detail for simplicity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This separation of responsibilities enables the replacement of the default waypoint proxy and Ingress Gateway with Envoy Gateway. By doing so, you can leverage Envoy Gateway’s advanced Gateway API capabilities without giving up the simplicity of Ambient Mesh.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;This also enables the use of Envoy Gateway as the Ingress Gateway for Ambient Mesh. The only difference is that the ztunnel needs to be placed only after Envoy Gateway (not in front), since incoming traffic originates outside the mesh and doesn’t arrive over an HBONE tunnel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Setting Up Envoy Gateway as the Ingress Gateway&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s walk through an example, creating an Envoy Gateway as Ingress, routing to a backend service and defining a global rate limiting for a specific service. Then, you will deploy an Envoy Gateway as a waypoint proxy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To begin with, you need to have a Kubernetes cluster with Istio Ambient mode installed, like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;istioctl install --set profile=ambient&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, install the Envoy Gateway with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;helm install eg oci://docker.io/envoyproxy/gateway-helm \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--version v0.0.0-latest \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--set config.envoyGateway.provider.kubernetes.deploy.type=GatewayNamespace \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-n envoy-gateway-system \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--create-namespace&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notice the flag for the deploy type. With this you make sure the Gateway is deployed where the Gateway resource is created and not in the envoy-gateway-system namespace, which is the default behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Label the default namespace for ambient onboarding:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl label namespace default istio.io/dataplane-mode=ambient&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, deploy a backend service you wish to call. In this case, we use Istio’s classic &lt;a href=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/istio/istio/refs/heads/master/samples/bookinfo/platform/kube/bookinfo.yaml&#34;&gt;Bookinfo&lt;/a&gt; in the default namespace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl apply -f https://raw.githubusercontent.com/istio/istio/refs/heads/master/samples/bookinfo/platform/kube/bookinfo.yaml&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the canvas in place, it’s time to take the brushes. You need a GatewayClass as the Ingress template, a Gateway instantiating this class and the HTTPRoute establishing the data path bridge. Apply them:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;EOF | kubectl apply -f -&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: GatewayClass&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: eg-ingress&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;controllerName: gateway.envoyproxy.io/gatewayclass-controller&#xA;&#xA;EOF&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Gateway, notice the gatewayClassName referencing eg-ingress above as well as the onboarding to the Ambient mesh:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;EOF | kubectl apply -f -&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: Gateway&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;labels:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;istio.io/dataplane-mode: ambient&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: bookinfo-ingress&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;gatewayClassName: eg-ingress&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;listeners:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- allowedRoutes:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespaces:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;from: Same&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: ingress&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 80&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;protocol: HTTP&#xA;EOF&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;EOF | kubectl apply -f -&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: HTTPRoute&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: ingress-bookinfo&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA; parentRefs:&#xA;  - group: gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;    kind: Gateway&#xA;    name: bookinfo-ingress&#xA;  rules:&#xA;  - backendRefs:&#xA;    - group: &#34;&#34;&#xA;      kind: Service&#xA;      name: productpage&#xA;      port: 9080&#xA;EOF&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Now, onto some validations. Attention, as this step will help you get Envoy Gateway and Ambient basic debugging skills. First, check the Gateway is created and that its traffic is intercepted by ztunnel:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ kubectl get pod -l app.kubernetes.io/name=envoy&#xA;&#xA;NAME &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; READY &amp;nbsp; STATUS&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; RESTARTS &amp;nbsp; AGE&#xA;&#xA;bookinfo-ingress-bcc6457b8-qfhcv &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 2/2 &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Running &amp;nbsp; 0&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; 3h11m&#xA;&#xA;$ istioctl ztunnel-config connections --node &amp;lt;NODE_NAME&amp;gt; -o yaml | yq &#39;.[].info | select(.name | test(&#34;^envoy*&#34;))&#39;&#xA;&#xA;name: bookinfo-ingress-bcc6457b8-qfhcv&#xA;&#xA;namespace: default&#xA;&#xA;serviceAccount: bookinfo-ingress-bcc6457b8-qfhcv&#xA;&#xA;trustDomain: &#34;&#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, inspect the HTTPRoute was effectively attached to the Gateway and it could find the backend service:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ kubectl get httproute ingress-bookinfo -oyaml | yq &#39;.status.parents&#39;&#xA;&#xA;- conditions:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- lastTransitionTime: &#34;2025-07-18T03:20:14Z&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;message: Route is accepted&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;observedGeneration: 1&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;reason: Accepted&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;status: &#34;True&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;type: Accepted&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- lastTransitionTime: &#34;2025-07-18T03:20:14Z&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;message: Resolved all the Object references for the Route&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;observedGeneration: 1&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;reason: ResolvedRefs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;status: &#34;True&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;type: ResolvedRefs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;controllerName: gateway.envoyproxy.io/gatewayclass-controller&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;parentRef:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;group: gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;kind: Gateway&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: bookinfo-ingress&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seems like everything’s in order. Time to make the requests:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ export ENVOY_SERVICE=$(kubectl get svc --selector=gateway.envoyproxy.io/owning-gateway-name=bookinfo-ingress -o jsonpath=&#39;{.items[0].metadata.name}&#39;)&#xA;&#xA;$ kubectl port-forward service/${ENVOY_SERVICE} 8080:80 &amp;amp;&#xA;&#xA;$ curl localhost:8080/productpage -w &#39;%{http_code}\n&#39; -o /dev/null -s&#xA;&#xA;200&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ztunnel logs the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;2025-07-18T03:33:20.718599Z info access connection complete src.addr=10.244.1.70:45168 src.workload=&#34;envoy-default-bookinfo-ingress-15c0d731-57b6bb576c-8ltvl&#34; src.namespace=&#34;default&#34; src.identity=&#34;spiffe://cluster.local/ns/default/sa/envoy-default-bookinfo-ingress-15c0d731&#34; dst.addr=10.244.1.68:15008 dst.hbone_addr=10.244.1.68:9080 dst.workload=&#34;productpage-v1-54bb874995-kzpnw&#34; dst.namespace=&#34;default&#34; dst.identity=&#34;spiffe://cluster.local/ns/default/sa/bookinfo-productpage&#34; direction=&#34;outbound&#34; bytes_sent=232 bytes_recv=15245 duration=&#34;2022ms&#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s Envoy Gateway sandwiched by ztunnel working as an Ingress for Istio Ambient Mesh!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hold on. This Ingress needs rate limiting. This is achieved by using a new Redis backend, referencing it in the EG configuration, and applying a BackendTrafficPolicy. We’re deploying a demo Redis instance here for demo purposes. In a production setup, you’ll want to provide your own Redis service—properly secured and scaled to meet your traffic demands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;EOF | kubectl apply -f -&#xA;kind: Namespace&#xA;&#xA;apiVersion: v1&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: redis-system&amp;nbsp;&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiVersion: apps/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: Deployment&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: redis&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: redis-system&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;labels:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;app: redis&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;replicas: 1&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;selector:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;matchLabels:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;app: redis&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;template:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;labels:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;app: redis&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;containers:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- image: redis:6.0.6&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;imagePullPolicy: IfNotPresent&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: redis&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;resources:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;limits:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: 1500m&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: 512Mi&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;requests:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;cpu: 200m&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;memory: 256Mi&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiVersion: v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: Service&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: redis&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: redis-system&amp;nbsp;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;labels:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;app: redis&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;annotations:&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ports:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- name: redis&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 6379&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;protocol: TCP&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;targetPort: 6379&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;selector:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;app: redis&#xA;EOF&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the Redis DB is ready, go ahead and upgrade the eg helm release’s values, adding a rate limit backend:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;helm upgrade eg oci://docker.io/envoyproxy/gateway-helm \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--set config.envoyGateway.rateLimit.backend.type=Redis \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--set config.envoyGateway.rateLimit.backend.redis.url=&#34;redis.redis-system.svc.cluster.local:6379&#34; \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;--reuse-values \&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-n envoy-gateway-system&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, create a BackendTrafficPolicy that enforces a limit of 3 requests per hour for non-admin users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;EOF | kubectl apply -f -&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.envoyproxy.io/v1alpha1&#xA;&#xA;kind: BackendTrafficPolicy&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: productpage-rate-limiting&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;targetRefs:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- group: gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;kind: HTTPRoute&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: ingress-bookinfo&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;rateLimit:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;type: Global&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;global:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;rules:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- clientSelectors:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- headers:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- type: Distinct&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: x-user-id&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- name: x-user-id&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;value: admin&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;invert: true&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;limit:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;requests: 3&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;unit: Hour&#xA;EOF&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And test it:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ while true; do curl localhost:8080/productpage -H &#34;x-user-id: john&#34; -w &#39;%{http_code}\n&#39; -o /dev/null -s; sleep 1; done&#xA;&#xA;Handling connection for 8080&#xA;&#xA;200&#xA;&#xA;Handling connection for 8080&#xA;&#xA;200&#xA;&#xA;Handling connection for 8080&#xA;&#xA;200&#xA;&#xA;Handling connection for 8080&#xA;&#xA;429&#xA;&#xA;Handling connection for 8080&#xA;&#xA;429&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Enabling Envoy Gateway as the Waypoint Proxy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the waypoint proxy, many steps remain the same; you still create a GatewayClass, a Gateway, and HTTPRoutes. However, you define a separate GatewayClass for the waypoint, as its configuration differs from that of the ingress gateway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt;EOF | kubectl apply -f -&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: GatewayClass&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: eg-waypoint&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;controllerName: gateway.envoyproxy.io/gatewayclass-controller&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;parametersRef:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;group: gateway.envoyproxy.io&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;kind: EnvoyProxy&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: waypoint&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespace: default&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.envoyproxy.io/v1alpha1&#xA;&#xA;kind: EnvoyProxy&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: waypoint&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;provider:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;kubernetes:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;envoyService:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;type: ClusterIP&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;patch:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;type: StrategicMerge&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;value:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;ports:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;# HACK:ztunnel currently expects the HBONE port to always be on the Waypoint&#39;s Service&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;# This will be fixed in future PRs to both istio and ztunnel.&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- name: fake-hbone-port&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 15008&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;protocol: TCP&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;targetPort: 15008&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;type: Kubernetes&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: Gateway&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;labels:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;istio.io/dataplane-mode: ambient&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: waypoint&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;gatewayClassName: eg-waypoint&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;listeners:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- allowedRoutes:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespaces:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;from: Same&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: ratings&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 9080&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;protocol: HTTP&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- allowedRoutes:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;namespaces:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;from: Same&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: fake-hbone&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 15008&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;protocol: TCP&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiVersion: gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;kind: HTTPRoute&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: ratings&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;hostnames:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- ratings&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- ratings.default&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- ratings.default.svc.cluster.local&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;parentRefs:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- group: gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;kind: Gateway&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: waypoint&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;rules:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- backendRefs:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- group: &#34;&#34;&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;kind: Service&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: ratings&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;port: 9080&#xA;EOF&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Label the ratings service so it uses the already deployed waypoint. You could also label the namespace for all services to use it:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ kubectl label svc ratings istio.io/use-waypoint=waypoint&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After making the same request as before, check the waypoint’s logs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;{&#34;:authority&#34;:&#34;ratings:9080&#34;,&#34;bytes_received&#34;:0,&#34;bytes_sent&#34;:358,&#34;connection_termination_details&#34;:null,&#34;downstream_local_address&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.73:9080&#34;,&#34;downstream_remote_address&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.68:38315&#34;,&#34;duration&#34;:3,&#34;method&#34;:&#34;GET&#34;,&#34;protocol&#34;:&#34;HTTP/1.1&#34;,&#34;requested_server_name&#34;:null,&#34;response_code&#34;:200,&#34;response_code_details&#34;:&#34;via_upstream&#34;,&#34;response_flags&#34;:&#34;-&#34;,&#34;route_name&#34;:&#34;httproute/default/ratings/rule/0/match/0/ratings&#34;,&#34;start_time&#34;:&#34;2025-07-18T05:16:36.829Z&#34;,&#34;upstream_cluster&#34;:&#34;httproute/default/ratings/rule/0&#34;,&#34;upstream_host&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.65:9080&#34;,&#34;upstream_local_address&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.73:33244&#34;,&#34;upstream_transport_failure_reason&#34;:null,&#34;user-agent&#34;:&#34;curl/8.7.1&#34;,&#34;x-envoy-origin-path&#34;:&#34;/ratings/0&#34;,&#34;x-envoy-upstream-service-time&#34;:null,&#34;x-forwarded-for&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.68&#34;,&#34;x-request-id&#34;:&#34;839bb7b2-af76-496c-9760-b90f118f191c&#34;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now let’s look at a more advanced scenario—using features in Envoy Gateway that aren’t yet available in Ambient L7. Circuit breaking is a great example, enabling your service to fail fast and avoid cascading failures when upstreams become unhealthy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For this, we need a failing service. Luckily, ratings has a delayed mode to simulate it. Add to it this env variable:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl set env deployment/ratings-v1 SERVICE_VERSION=v-delayed&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For testing, you can use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rakyll/hey&#34;&gt;hey load testing tool&lt;/a&gt; to send traffic directly to the ratings service from within the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl run hey --rm -i &amp;nbsp; --image=williamyeh/hey &amp;nbsp; http://ratings:9080/ratings/0&#xA;&#xA;If you don&#39;t see a command prompt, try pressing enter.&#xA;&#xA;Summary:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Total: 28.5228 secs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Slowest: 7.5211 secs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Fastest: 0.0005 secs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Average: 3.6650 secs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Requests/sec: 7.0119&#xA;&#xA;Response time histogram:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.000 [1] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.753 [98] |■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;1.505 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;2.257 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3.009 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;3.761 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;4.513 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;5.265 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;6.017 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;6.769 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;7.521 [101] |■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ratings service adds a 7-second delay to half of the responses, which you can observe in the output from the hey command.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, create a new BackendTrafficPolicy with a deliberately aggressive circuit breaker configuration—just enough to make it easy to trip during testing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: gateway.envoyproxy.io/v1alpha1&#xA;&#xA;kind: BackendTrafficPolicy&#xA;&#xA;metadata:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: circuit-breaker-btp&#xA;&#xA;spec:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;targetRefs:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;- group: gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;kind: HTTPRoute&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;name: ratings&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;circuitBreaker:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;maxPendingRequests: 0&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;maxParallelRequests: 10&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Make sure it has been accepted:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ kubectl get backendtrafficpolicy circuit-breaker-btp -ojsonpath=&#39;{.status.ancestors[0].conditions}&#39;&#xA;&#xA;[{&#34;lastTransitionTime&#34;:&#34;2025-07-22T08:53:59Z&#34;,&#34;message&#34;:&#34;Policy has been accepted.&#34;,&#34;observedGeneration&#34;:2,&#34;reason&#34;:&#34;Accepted&#34;,&#34;status&#34;:&#34;True&#34;,&#34;type&#34;:&#34;Accepted&#34;}]%&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, run the hey test again to check if the circuit breaker is kicking in as expected:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ kubectl run hey --rm -i --image=williamyeh/hey http://ratings:9080/ratings/0&#xA;&#xA;If you don&#39;t see a command prompt, try pressing enter.&#xA;&#xA;Summary:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Total: 0.7135 secs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Slowest: 0.6990 secs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Fastest: 0.0007 secs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Average: 0.1720 secs&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Requests/sec: 280.3131&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Total data: 16200 bytes&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Size/request: 81 bytes&#xA;&#xA;Response time histogram:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.001 [1] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.071 [149] |■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.140 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.210 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.280 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.350 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.420 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.490 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.559 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.629 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;0.699 [50] |■■■■■■■■■■■■■&#xA;&#xA;(trimmed)&#xA;&#xA;Status code distribution:&#xA;&#xA;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;[503] 200 responses&#xA;&#xA;pod &#34;hey&#34; deleted&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notice how most of the requests failed in under 100ms—this indicates that the circuit breaker kicked in and started rejecting traffic quickly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you check the waypoint logs, you’ll see clear signs of this in action: the UO response flag and response_code_details set to overflow show that the circuit breaker was triggered. Envoy Gateway dropped the excess requests without forwarding them to the ratings service, just as expected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;$ kubectl logs waypoint-7cc857d87b-8kv2z&#xA;&#xA;Defaulted container &#34;envoy&#34; out of: envoy, shutdown-manager&#xA;&#xA;{&#34;:authority&#34;:&#34;ratings:9080&#34;,&#34;bytes_received&#34;:0,&#34;bytes_sent&#34;:81,&#34;connection_termination_details&#34;:null,&#34;downstream_local_address&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.36:9080&#34;,&#34;downstream_remote_address&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.41:40909&#34;,&#34;duration&#34;:0,&#34;method&#34;:&#34;GET&#34;,&#34;protocol&#34;:&#34;HTTP/1.1&#34;,&#34;requested_server_name&#34;:null,&#34;response_code&#34;:503,&#34;response_code_details&#34;:&#34;upstream_reset_before_response_started{overflow}&#34;,&#34;response_flags&#34;:&#34;UO&#34;,&#34;route_name&#34;:&#34;httproute/default/ratings/rule/0/match/0/ratings&#34;,&#34;start_time&#34;:&#34;2025-07-22T09:14:19.407Z&#34;,&#34;upstream_cluster&#34;:&#34;httproute/default/ratings/rule/0&#34;,&#34;upstream_host&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.37:9080&#34;,&#34;upstream_local_address&#34;:null,&#34;upstream_transport_failure_reason&#34;:null,&#34;user-agent&#34;:&#34;hey/0.0.1&#34;,&#34;x-envoy-origin-path&#34;:&#34;/ratings/0&#34;,&#34;x-envoy-upstream-service-time&#34;:null,&#34;x-forwarded-for&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.41&#34;,&#34;x-request-id&#34;:&#34;f611fd0a-8b7f-4c7d-ad18-6f0f8812ac6b&#34;}&#xA;...&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, it’s time for you to try it out!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Should You Use Envoy Gateway with Ambient Mesh?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Envoy Gateway offers comprehensive Layer 7 capabilities, including rate limiting, OIDC and JWT authentication, API key checks, CORS support, and detailed observability. All of these features are integrated into Ambient’s simple, sidecar-free design. Combining a lightweight ambient mesh with powerful Layer 7 ingress features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, there are tradeoffs. You’ll need to run a separate control plane to configure Envoy Gateway and manage configuration in addition to your Istio setup.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the built-in ingress and waypoint proxies already meet your needs, there’s no pressure to switch. However, suppose you’re seeking greater control, enhanced security, and increased flexibility at Layer 7. In that case, Envoy Gateway is a powerful way to elevate your Ambient Mesh setup while sticking to fully open-source solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;✅ When to Use Envoy Gateway with Ambient&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consider using Envoy Gateway if you:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Need advanced Layer 7 features like:&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rate limiting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;JWT/OIDC authentication&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;API key validation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CORS handling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wasm or ext_proc extensions&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Want Gateway API compatibility with more powerful, opinionated policies (e.g., SecurityPolicy, ClientTrafficPolicy)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Prefer a unified control plane to manage both ingress and internal Layer 7 traffic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Appreciate a batteries-included gateway that works out of the box—without needing to write custom Envoy filters (unless you really want to)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;❌ When You Might Hold Off (For Now)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You might want to skip Envoy Gateway—at least for now—if you:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are still experimenting with Ambient Mesh and don’t need advanced Layer 7 features&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are fine with the current limitations of Ambient’s built-in Gateway support (e.g., no VirtualService, limited routing options)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Want to keep your control plane as lightweight and simple as possible, avoiding extra CRDs or configuration overhead&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What’s Next?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Envoy Gateway and Ambient are a duo that will optimize some of your workloads, so we encourage you to try it out. It unblocks the migration as your organization doesn’t have to wait for the Istio API to include for Ambient the powerful Envoy features you’ve already experienced in this demo.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Curious to see what else Envoy Gateway can do in an Ambient Mesh? Check out the&lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway.envoyproxy.io/latest/tasks/&#34;&gt; official tasks&lt;/a&gt; to explore its full feature set.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Still, keep in mind that Ambient is not a one-size-fits-all solution, and its usage should be addressed workload by workload. On this matter, Tetrate has the data-driven &lt;a href=&#34;https://mesh-advisor.tetr8.io/&#34;&gt;Istio Ambient Assessment Advisor&lt;/a&gt; to help you understand better the implications based on your own data. Don’t miss it as it’s free!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mesh-advisor.tetr8.io/&#34;&gt;Istio Ambient Assessment Advisor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/l7-features/&#34;&gt;Istio Ambient mode layer 7 features&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/istio/issues/43720&#34;&gt;Add EnvoyFilter support for waypoint proxies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway.envoyproxy.io/latest/tasks/&#34;&gt;Envoy Gateway traffic policies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/richincapie/&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;In this article, we’ll look at how you can use &lt;a href=&#34;https://gateway.envoyproxy.io/&#34;&gt;Envoy Gateway&lt;/a&gt;, an Envoy project open source solution, together with Istio when running in Ambient mode.这使您可以轻松利用Envoy的L7功能的功能，并借助易于使用的CRD在网格中进出。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解这种集成的工作原理，让我们首先快速查看&lt;strong&gt;环境网格&lt;/strong&gt;本身。也称为&lt;a href =“ https://istio.io.io/latest/docs/ambient/overview/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; iStio环境模式&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，这是Sidecar-less服务网格网格结构，旨在简化部署并可以提高特定用例的效率。与基于SIDECAR的网眼不同，环境将数据平面分为两个关键组成部分：&lt;strong&gt; Ztunnel &lt;/strong&gt;，它可以确保服务到服务通信，以及&lt;strong&gt; Waypoint代理&lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt;，该&lt;/strong&gt;处理7层流量路由和策略执行。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在另一侧，&lt;strong&gt;特使门户&lt;/strong&gt;是一个kubernetes-native api网关，建在特使代理的顶部。它的设计旨在与Kubernetes Gateway API无缝合作，并采用包括电池的方法 - 为身份验证，授权，费率限制，CORS处理，标头操纵等提供内置支持。这些功能通过熟悉的Kubernetes风格的API暴露，使您无需复杂的配置即可完全利用Envoy的功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于环境网格和特使门户都建在特使之上，因此它们共同基础。这使集成变得直接，并允许&lt;strong&gt;特使网关充当入口网关和Waypoint代理&lt;/strong&gt;  - 为您提供一种一致而有力的方式来管理流量，并在网眼上应用第7层政策。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么要使用Envoy Gateway与环境网格？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;虽然环境网格通过删除壁炉架简化了服务网格操作，但其功能集尚不匹配基于边缘的模型的成熟&lt;/strong&gt;。一些高级第7层功能要么缺少，被认为是实验性的，要么需要额外的复杂性才能在本机环境模式下配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;有限的虚拟服务支持&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/l7-features/”&gt; VirtualService，这是经典ISTIO中流量管理的关键资源 - 仅在Alpient的Alpha级别可用&lt;/a&gt;。最重要的是，它不能与网关API资源结合使用。这使您拥有网关API，这是唯一的支持选项。尽管它可以很好地处理基本路由，但有意支持许多网关实现。结果，您将无法访问某些富裕，特定特定的功能，例如全球速率限制，电路BReaking和OIDC身份验证。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;缺乏EnvoyFilter支持&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在环境模式下，&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/istio/issues/43720”&gt;不支持EnvoyFilters &lt;/a&gt;。当您需要在XDS级别进行调整或扩展代理行为时，这些过滤器对于边防部署至关重要 - 无论是自定义逻辑，遥测还是与外部系统集成。没有它们，您的微调代理行为的能力是有限的，这可能是高级或生产级用例的阻滞剂。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那是&lt;strong&gt; Engoy Gateway &lt;/strong&gt;发挥作用的地方。它通过&lt;a href =“ https://gateway.envoyproxy.io/latest/tasks/”&gt;一组强大的自定义策略，包括&lt;/a&gt; Client trafficpolicy，backendtrafficpolicy，SecurityPolicy，SecurityPolicy，EnvoyextiensionPolicy，Envoypolticy eveloypatchpathpathpolicy，&lt; &lt;strong&gt;网格&lt;/strong&gt;。这些策略可以直接应用于核心网关API资源，例如Gateway和Httproute，允许详细的流量管理，改进的安全性，可插入的扩展，甚至低级XDS修补程序，同时保持无侧架构的简单性。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcute5razx70-v9opxnwt5e2x-wq8t0a9psmu2roa5ac9ltxe5txe5tooytf pyl3d_8rlrz35_d18zkudht1dtefctbaii7n-nt27ghz_5ypjt9semha2djgctoez5ey3ey3ix4ip1bcnqqq？ alt =“ Envoy Gateway Image” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;解锁特使在环境网格中的特使网关政策的全部潜力&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; Envoy Gateway如何在环境网中工作？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在默认的环境网格部署中，WayPoint代理处理终止传入的HBONE隧道并将新的隧道建立到目标服务。在此过程中，它还适用7层流量策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdjesypjspjspjspjspjspjspjspjspjspjspjspjsypjspf56d4qercevnwff0dmgphdmgphdjlnpuzw4kt_pken VMJF2N5PKMJW2YAYVR8B2WEYBLWUUCV-DA3QLNCQNIHBHNBHNQTRKPZXAHA-D1USP13UYXHC54DUCBRDW？ Alt =“ Envoy Gateway在环境网格中的工作方式？” referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在默认Waypoint代理部署中的流量流&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;然而，环境还支持一个更模块化的“三明治”模型，在该模型上，Ztunnel在Waypoint代理前后的逻辑上放置在逻辑上，就像三明治一样。在此设置中，Ztunnel负责管理双方的HBONE隧道，而Waypoint代理仅着眼于L7交通管理和政策执行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdIlPZW-B1QAMBLFDLhQgsWv3Xu3N0TnPdDHGpliFw4MjiAt-hsGyvmbkUFc-j1u8tPOD4jGnPZ4ulJpmEFcxjFG299xUSMMBEKSTDBFNPF8BA5XK4K0HFHJ4OKGLXOMFSR0AJWSW？key = ypra9nnd6jz-ms5fp2vj3g“ alt =” Alt =“ Alt =” Altic图形图形，说明了更模块化的“ Sandwich”模型“ sandwich” noteRerpolicy =“ not-refigul”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在夹杂的Waypoint代理部署中的交通流量&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意：此图说明了流量如何流过环境网格中的各个组件。尽管似乎有两个Ztunnels在Envoy Gateway之前和之后放置了两个Ztunnels，但它们实际上是同一实例 -  LET在该细节上的掩盖效果。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;这种责任的分离使得可以更换默认的Waypoint代理，并用Envoy Gateway替换Invress Gateway。通过这样做，您可以利用Envoy Gateway的高级Gateway API功能，而无需放弃周围网格的简单性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;这也使Envoy Gateway用作环境网格的入口网关。唯一的区别是，仅在Envoy Gateway（不在前面）之后，需要放置Ztunnel，因为传入的交通源于网格外，并且不会到达HBONE隧道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;设置Envoy Gateway作为入口网关&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们浏览一个示例，创建一个特使网关作为入口，路由到后端服务并定义特定服务的全球速率限制。然后，您将部署一个特使网关作为Waypoint代理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，您需要安装具有ISTIO环境模式的Kubernetes群集，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; &lt;code&gt; istioctl install-set profile = abirt &lt;/code &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，使用：&lt;/p&gt;安装特使网关&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; helm install eg oci：//docker.io/envoyproxy/gatewayway-helm \&#xA;&#xA;   -  version v0.0.0-latest \&#xA;&#xA;  -set config.envoygateway.provider.kubernetes.deploy.type = gatewaynamespace \ type \ type \ type \ type \&#xA;&#xA;  -n特使门道系统\&#xA;&#xA;   -  create-namespace &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意部署类型的标志。通过此，您可以确保在创建网关资源而不是在Envoy-Gateway-System名称空间（默认行为）中部署网关。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;标记用于环境入门的默认名称空间：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl标签命名空间默认iStio.io/dataplane-mode = ambient&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后但并非最不重要的一点是，要部署您要致电的后端服务。在这种情况下，我们使用istio的经典&lt;a href =“ https://raw.githubusercontent.com/istio/istio/istio/refs/refs/refs/master/master/samples/bookinfo/bookinfo/platform/platform/kube/bookinfo.yaml”&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl应用-f https：//raw.githubusercontent.com/istio/istio/istio/istio/refs/refs/refs/heads/master/master/samples/bookinfo/bookinfo/platform/platform/kube/kbook/bookinfo.yaml.yaml &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有了画布，是时候拿起刷子了。您需要一个GatewayClass作为Ingress模板，网关实例化此类和Httproute e稳定数据路径桥。应用它们：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; cat &lt;&lt; eof | kubectl应用-f-&#xA;apiversion：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;善良：GatewayClass&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：EG-Ingress&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  ControllerName：gateway.envoyproxy.io/gatewayclass-controller&#xA;&#xA;eof &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在网关中，请注意上面的GatewayClassName引用EG-Inginress以及对环境网格的登机：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; cat &lt;&lt; eof | kubectl应用-f-&#xA;apiversion：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;善良：网关&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  标签：&#xA;&#xA;    istio.io/dataplane-mode：环境&#xA;&#xA;  姓名：bookinfo-ingress&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  GatewayClassName：EG-Ingress&#xA;&#xA;  听众：&#xA;&#xA;   - 允许流程：&#xA;&#xA;      名称空间：&#xA;&#xA;        来自：同样&#xA;&#xA;    名称：入口&#xA;&#xA;    港口：80&#xA;&#xA;    协议：http&#xA;eof &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; cat &lt;&lt; eof | kubectl应用-f-&#xA;apiversion：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;类型：httproute&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：Ingress-BookInfo&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA; parentrefs：&#xA;   - 组：gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;    善良：网关&#xA;    姓名：bookinfo-ingress&#xA;  规则：&#xA;   -  Backendrefs：&#xA;    - 团体： ””&#xA;      善良：服务&#xA;      名称：产品页面&#xA;      端口：9080&#xA;eof &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，对一些验证。注意，因为这一步将帮助您获得Envoy Gateway和Ambient基本调试技能。首先，检查网关的创建，其流量被Ztunnel截获：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ kubectl获取pod -l app.kubernetes.io/name = envoy&#xA;&#xA;名称准备状态重新开始年龄&#xA;&#xA;BookInfo-Ingress-BCC6457B8-QFHCV 2/2运行0 3H11M&#xA;&#xA;$ istioctl ztunnel -config连接-Node &lt;Node_name&gt; -o yaml | yq&#39;。[]。信息|选择（.Name | test（“^Envoy*”））&#39;&#xA;&#xA;名称：bookinfo-ingress-bcc6457b8-qfhcv&#xA;&#xA;名称空间：默认值&#xA;&#xA;ServiceAccount：BookInfo-Ingress-BCC6457B8-QFHCV&#xA;&#xA;TrustDomain：“” &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，检查httproute已有效地附加到网关上，它可以找到后端服务：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ kubectl获取httproute indress-bookinfo -oyaml | yq&#39;.status.parents&#39;&#xA;&#xA;- 状况：&#xA;&#xA;     -  LastTransitionTime：“ 2025-07-18T03：20：14Z”&#xA;&#xA;      消息：路线被接受&#xA;&#xA;      观察代表：1&#xA;&#xA;      原因：cecceed&#xA;&#xA;      状态：“ True”&#xA;&#xA;      类型：接受&#xA;&#xA;     -  LastTransitionTime：“ 2025-07-18T03：20：14Z”&#xA;&#xA;      消息：解决路由的所有对象引用&#xA;&#xA;      观察代表：1&#xA;&#xA;      原因：ResolvedRefs&#xA;&#xA;      状态：“ True”&#xA;&#xA;      类型：ResolvedRefs&#xA;&#xA;  ControllerName：gateway.envoyproxy.io/gatewayclass-controller&#xA;&#xA;  parentref：&#xA;&#xA;    组：Gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;&#xA;    善良：网关&#xA;&#xA;    名称：bookinfo-ingress &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;似乎一切都在井井有条。是时候提出请求了：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ export envoy_service = $（kubectl get svc -selector = gateway.envoyproxy.io/owning-gateway-name = bookinfo-ingress-&#xA;&#xA;$ kubectl port-forward服务/$ {Envoy_Service} 8080：80＆&#xA;&#xA;$ curl localhost：8080/productpage -w&#39;％{http_code} \ n&#39;-o/dev/null -s&#xA;&#xA;200 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ztunnel记录以下内容：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; 2025-07-18T03：33：20.718599Z信息访问连接完整src.addr = 10.244.1.70：45168 src.workload = src.namespace =“默认” dst.workload =“ productPage-v1-54bb874995-kzpnw” dst.namespace =“ default” dst.Identity =“ spiffe：//cluster.local/ns/ns/ns/defeault/sa/sa/bookinfo-productoductpage”持续时间=“ 2022ms” &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那是由Ztunnel夹在iStio环境网格中的Ztunnel夹在夹具上的门户！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;坚持。此入口需要限制速率。这是通过使用新的Redis后端，在EG配置中引用它并应用后端Trafficpolicy来实现的。我们正在此处部署一个演示实例，以进行演示。在制作设置中，您需要提供自己的Redis服务 - 易于确保和扩展以满足您的交通需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; cat &lt;&lt; eof | kubectl应用-f-&#xA;善：名称空间&#xA;&#xA;apiversion：v1&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：重新系统 &#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiversion：应用程序/V1&#xA;&#xA;类型：部署&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：redis&#xA;&#xA;  名称空间：重新系统&#xA;&#xA;  标签：&#xA;&#xA;    应用：redis&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  复制品：1&#xA;&#xA;  选择器：&#xA;&#xA;    MatchLabels：&#xA;&#xA;      应用：redis&#xA;&#xA;  模板：&#xA;&#xA;    元数据：&#xA;&#xA;      标签：&#xA;&#xA;        应用：redis&#xA;&#xA;    规格：&#xA;&#xA;    ＆nbsp; 容器：&#xA;&#xA;       - 图像：redis：6.0.6&#xA;&#xA;        ImagePullPolicy：ifontresent&#xA;&#xA;        名称：redis&#xA;&#xA;        资源：&#xA;&#xA;          限制：&#xA;&#xA;            CPU：1500m&#xA;&#xA;            内存：512mi&#xA;&#xA;          请求：&#xA;&#xA;            CPU：200m&#xA;&#xA;            内存：256mi&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiversion：v1&#xA;&#xA;善良：服务&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：redis&#xA;&#xA;  名称空间：重新系统 &#xA;&#xA;  标签：&#xA;&#xA;    应用：redis&#xA;&#xA;  注释：&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  端口：&#xA;&#xA;   - 名称：redis&#xA;&#xA;    港口：6379&#xA;&#xA;    协议：TCP&#xA;&#xA;    TargetPort：6379&#xA;&#xA;  选择器：&#xA;&#xA;    应用：redis&#xA;eof &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦Redis DB准备就绪，请继续升级EG Helm版本的值，并添加了一个限制后端：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt;掌舵升级，例如oci：//docker.io/envoyproxy/gateway-helm \&#xA;&#xA;  -set config.envoygateway.ratelimit.backend.type = redis \&#xA;&#xA;  -set config.envoygateway.ratelimit.backend.redis.url =“ redis.redis-system.svc.cluster.local：6379” \ \&#xA;&#xA;   -  reuse-values \&#xA;&#xA;  -n Envoy-Gateway-System &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，创建一个后端交通型物质，该后端限制为非Admin用户每小时3个请求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; cat &lt;&lt; eof | kubectl应用-f-&#xA;apiversion：gateway.envoyproxy.io/v1alpha1&#xA;&#xA;KIND：后端交通质体&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：限制产品页面&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  TargetRefs：&#xA;&#xA;   - 组：gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;&#xA;    类型：httproute&#xA;&#xA;    名称：Ingress-BookInfo&#xA;&#xA;  ratelimit：&#xA;&#xA;    类型：全局&#xA;&#xA;    全球的：&#xA;&#xA;      规则：&#xA;&#xA;       - 客户电机：&#xA;&#xA;         - 标题：&#xA;&#xA;           - 类型：独特&#xA;&#xA;            名称：X-user-id&#xA;&#xA;           - 名称：X-user-id&#xA;&#xA;            价值：管理员&#xA;&#xA;            倒置：是的&#xA;&#xA;        限制：&#xA;&#xA;          请求：3&#xA;&#xA;  ＆nbsp;       单位：小时&#xA;eof &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;并测试它：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ while true; DO curl localhost：8080/productPage -h“ x -user -id：john” -w&#39;％{http_code} \ n&#39;-o/dev/null -s;睡眠1;完毕&#xA;&#xA;8080的处理连接&#xA;&#xA;200&#xA;&#xA;8080的处理连接&#xA;&#xA;200&#xA;&#xA;8080的处理连接&#xA;&#xA;200&#xA;&#xA;8080的处理连接&#xA;&#xA;429&#xA;&#xA;8080的处理连接&#xA;&#xA;429 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于Waypoint代理，许多步骤保持不变；您仍然可以创建一个网关频道，一个网关和HTTPROUTES。但是，随着其配置与Ingress Gateway的配置不同，您为航点定义了一个单独的网关频道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; cat &lt;&lt; eof | kubectl应用-f-&#xA;apiversion：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;善良：GatewayClass&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：EG-Waypoint&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  ControllerName：gateway.envoyproxy.io/gatewayclass-controller&#xA;&#xA;  parametersref：&#xA;&#xA;    组：Gateway.envoyproxy.io&#xA;&#xA;    善良：Envoyproxy&#xA;&#xA;    名称：航向&#xA;&#xA;    名称空间：默认值&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiversion：gateway.envoyproxy.io/v1alpha1&#xA;&#xA;善良：Envoyproxy&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：航向&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  提供者：&#xA;&#xA;    Kubernetes：&#xA;&#xA;      EnvoyService：&#xA;&#xA;        类型：clusterip&#xA;&#xA;        修补：&#xA;&#xA;          类型：策略精神&#xA;&#xA;          价值：&#xA;&#xA;            规格：&#xA;&#xA;              端口：&#xA;&#xA;                ＃hack：Ztunnel当前期望HBONE端口始终在Waypoint的服务上&#xA;&#xA;                ＃这将在ISTIO和Ztunnel的未来PR中固定。&#xA;&#xA;                 - 名称：假hbone-port&#xA;&#xA;                  港口：15008&#xA;&#xA;                  协议：TCP&#xA;&#xA;                  TargetPort：15008&#xA;&#xA;    类型：Kubernetes&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiversion：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;善良：网关&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  标签：&#xA;&#xA;    istio.io/dataplane-mode：环境&#xA;&#xA;  名称：航向&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  网格AYCLASSNAME：EG-Waypoint&#xA;&#xA;  听众：&#xA;&#xA;   - 允许流程：&#xA;&#xA;      名称空间：&#xA;&#xA;        来自：同样&#xA;&#xA;    名称：评分&#xA;&#xA;    端口：9080&#xA;&#xA;    协议：http&#xA;&#xA;   - 允许流程：&#xA;&#xA;      名称空间：&#xA;&#xA;        来自：同样&#xA;&#xA;    名称：假hbone&#xA;&#xA;    港口：15008&#xA;&#xA;    协议：TCP&#xA;&#xA;---&#xA;&#xA;apiversion：gateway.networking.k8s.io/v1&#xA;&#xA;类型：httproute&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：评分&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  主机名：&#xA;&#xA;   - 评分&#xA;&#xA;  -Ratings.default&#xA;&#xA;  -ratings.default.svc.cluster.local&#xA;&#xA;  parentrefs：&#xA;&#xA;   - 组：gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;&#xA;    善良：网关&#xA;&#xA;    名称：航向&#xA;&#xA;  规则：&#xA;&#xA;   -  Backendrefs：&#xA;&#xA;    - 团体： ””&#xA;&#xA;      善良：服务&#xA;&#xA;      名称：评分&#xA;&#xA;      端口：9080&#xA;eof &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;标记评级服务，因此它使用已部署的Waypoint。您还可以标记所有服务的命名空间：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ kubectl标签svc评级istio.io.io.io/use-waypoint = waypoint = wayerpoint&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;提出与以前相同的请求后，请检查Waypoint的日志：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;代码class =“”&gt; {“：权威”：“评分：9080”，“ bytes_received”：0，“ bytes_sent”：358：connection_termination_details “：null，“ downstream_local_address”：“ 10.244.1.73:9080“，”downdownstream_remote_address&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.68:38315“，”ddownderem_arddress“remote_remote_address”：&#34;10.244.1.68:38315&#34;，“ddur ation“：3，“方法”：“ get”，“协议”：“ http/1.1”，“请求_server_name”：null，“ wendespy_code”：200，“ response_code_details”：“ via_upstream”，“评分“，” start_time”：“ 2025-07-18T05：16：36.829Z”，“ upstream_cluster”：“ httprute/default/default/ratings/rule/0”，“ u PSTREAM_HOST”：“ 10.244.1.65:9080“，&#34;upstream_local_address&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.73:33244”，&#34;upstream_transport_failure _REASON“：null，“用户代理”：“ curl/8.7.1”，“ X-Envoy-Origin-Path”：“/ratings/0”，“ X-Envoy-UpStream-Service-Service-Service Time “：null，” x-forwarded-for“：” 10.244.1.68“，” X-REQUEST-ID“：” 839bb7b2-AF76-AF76-AF76C-9760-B90F118F191C“} &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在让我们看一个更高级的方案 - 在Envoy Gateway中使用Enkient L7中尚不可用的功能。断路是一个很好的例子，使您的服务能够快速失败，并在上游不健康时避免级联失败。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为此，我们需要一个失败的服务。幸运的是，评分具有模拟它的延迟模式。添加此ENV变量：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl设置env exployment/ratings-v1 service_version = v-delayed &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用于测试，您可以使用&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/rakyll/hey“&gt;嘿加载测试工具&lt;/a&gt;从集群中直接将流量发送到评级服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; kubectl run hey -rm -i -image = williamyeh/hey http：//评分：9080/ratings/0&#xA;&#xA;如果您看不到命令​​提示符，请尝试按Enter。&#xA;&#xA;概括：&#xA;&#xA;  总计：28.5228秒&#xA;&#xA;  最慢：7.5211秒&#xA;&#xA;  最快：0.0005秒&#xA;&#xA;  平均：3.6650秒&#xA;&#xA;  请求/秒：7.0119&#xA;&#xA;响应时间直方图：&#xA;&#xA;  0.000 [1] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.753 [98] |■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■.。&#xA;&#xA;  1.505 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  2.257 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  3.009 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  3.761 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  4.513 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  5.265 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  6.017 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  6.769 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  7.521 [101] |■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■。/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;评级服务将响应的一半延迟增加了7秒，您可以在HEY命令的输出中观察到。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，创建一个带有故意攻击性断路器配置的新的后端浮力 - 足以使其在测试过程中易于绊倒。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; apiversion：gateway.envoyproxy.io/v1alpha1&#xA;&#xA;KIND：后端交通质体&#xA;&#xA;元数据：&#xA;&#xA;  名称：断路器-BTP&#xA;&#xA;规格：&#xA;&#xA;  TargetRefs：&#xA;&#xA;   - 组：gateway.networking.k8s.io&#xA;&#xA;    类型：httproute&#xA;&#xA;    名称：评分&#xA;&#xA;  断路器：&#xA;&#xA;      MaxPendingRequests：0&#xA;&#xA;      maxparallelleRequests：10 &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确保已被接受：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ kubectl获取backendentrafficpolicy ciruct-breaker-btp-ojsonpath =&#39;{。status.ancestors.ancestors [0] .conditions}&#39;&#xA;&#xA;[{“ last TransitionTime”：“ 2025-07-22T08：53：59Z”，“消息”：“策略已被接受。”，“观察代理”：2，“原因”：“接纳”，“状态”：“ true”：“ true”：“ true”，“ type”，“类型”：&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，再次运行HEY测试以检查断路器是否按预期启动：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class =“ wp-block-code”&gt; &lt;code class =“”&gt; $ kubectl运行hey -rm -i -image = williamyeh/hey http：//评分：9080/ratings/0&#xA;&#xA;如果您看不到命令​​提示符，请尝试按Enter。&#xA;&#xA;概括：&#xA;&#xA;  总计：0.7135秒&#xA;&#xA;  最慢：0.6990秒&#xA;&#xA;  最快：0.0007秒&#xA;&#xA;  平均：0.1720秒&#xA;&#xA;  请求/秒：280.3131&#xA;&#xA;  总数据：16200字节&#xA;&#xA;  尺寸/请求：81个字节&#xA;&#xA;响应时间直方图：&#xA;&#xA;  0.001 [1] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.071 [149] |■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■■.。&#xA;&#xA;  0.140 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.210 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.280 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;＆nbsp; 0.350 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.420 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.490 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.559 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.629 [0] |&#xA;&#xA;  0.699 [50] |■■■■■■■■■■■■■&#xA;&#xA;（修剪）&#xA;&#xA;状态代码分布：&#xA;&#xA;  [503] 200回应&#xA;&#xA;pod“ hey”删除&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请注意，大多数请求在100毫秒以下是如何失败的 - 这表明断路器启动并开始迅速拒绝流量。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您检查了路点日志，则会看到此操作中的明确符号：设置为溢出的UO响应标志和响应_CODE_DETAILS显示了断路器是触发的。 Envoy Gateway丢弃了多余的请求，而无需将其转发到评级服务，就像预期的那样。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;默认容器“ Envoy”删除：Envoy，Shutdown-Manager&#xA;&#xA;{“：权威”：“评分：9080”，“ bytes_received”：0，“ bytes_sent”：81，“ connection_termination_details”：null，“ d ownstream_local_address”：“ 10.244.1.36:9080&#34;，“downdownstream_remote_address&#34;:&#34;10.244.1.41：40909”，“dration&#34;：0， “方法”：“获取”，“协议”：“ http/1.1”，“请求_server_name”：null，``response_code&#39;&#39;：503，“ response_code_details”：“ upstream_reset_before_before_before_response_started_started {vellflof} ault/ratings/rule/0/gation/0/ratings“，” start_time“：” 2025-07-22T09：14：19.407Z“，” upstream_cluster“：” httprout e/default/ratings/rule/0“，“ upstream_host”：“ 10.244.1.37:9080“，”upstream_local_address&#34;:null.null.count：null.dupstream_tran sport_failure_reason”：null，“用户代理”：“ hey/0.0.1”，“ X-Envoy-Origin-Path”：“/ratings/0”，“ X-Envoy-opstream-服务时间“：null，” X-Forwarded-For“：” 10.244.1.41“，” X-Request-id“：” F611FD0A-8B7F-4C7D-AD18-AD18-6F0F88812AC6B“}&#xA;... &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在是时候尝试了！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt;您是否应该使用环境网格的特使网关？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Engoy Gateway提供了全面的第7层功能，包括限制费率，OIDC和JWT身份验证，API键检查，CORS支持和详细的可观察性。所有这些功能都集成到环境简单，无边的设计中。将轻巧的环境网格与强大的第7层入口功能相结合。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当然，有权衡。您需要运行一个单独的控制平面，以配置Envoy Gateway并管理ISTIO设置之外的配置。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果内置的入口和Waypoint代理已经满足您的需求，则没有切换的压力。但是，假设您正在寻求更大的控制权，增强的安全性和提高的灵活性。在这种情况下，Envoy Gateway是提升周围网格设置的强大方法，同时坚持使用完全开源的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;✅何时将特使网关与环境使用&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您：&lt;/p&gt;，请考虑使用Envoy Gateway&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;需要高级第7层功能，例如：&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;利率limiTing &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; JWT/OIDC身份验证&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; API密钥验证&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; CORS处理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; WASM或EXT_PROC扩展&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;想要网关API兼容性与更强大，有用的政策（例如SecurityPolicy，Client Trafficpolicy）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更喜欢统一的控制平面来管理入口和内部第7层流量&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;欣赏包装盒中包括电池的门户 - 不需要编写自定义特使滤波器（除非您真的想）&lt;br&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;❌何时（暂时）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可能想跳过特使网关 - 至少现在 - 如果您：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;仍在尝试环境网格，不需要高级第7层功能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;对环境内置网关支持的当前局限性很好（例如，没有虚拟服务，有限的路由选项）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;想要保持控制平面尽可能轻巧和简单，避免额外的CRD或配置开销&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;下一步是什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;特使网关和环境是一个二人组，可以优化您的某些工作量，因此我们鼓励您尝试一下。它揭开了迁移的阻止，因为您的组织不必等待ISTIO API为环境包括您在此演示中已经遇到的强大的特使功能。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;好奇地看到Envoy Gateway在环境网格中可以做什么？查看&lt;a href =“ https://gateway.envoyproxy.io/latest/tasks/”&gt;官方任务&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;探索其完整功能集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仍然要记住，环境不是一个尺寸的解决方案，应通过工作量来解决其用法。在此问题上，Tetrate具有数据驱动的&lt;a href =“ https://mesh-advisor.tetr8.io/”&gt; ISTIO环境评估顾问&lt;/a&gt;可以帮助您根据自己的数据更好地理解含义。不要错过它，因为它是免费的！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;参考&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://mesh-advisor.tetr8.io/”&gt; istio环境评估顾问&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/l7-features/”&gt; istio环境模式7层7功能&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/istio/istio/issues/43720”&gt;添加EnvoyFilter对Waypoint Proxies &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://gateway.envoyproxy.io/latest/tasks/”&gt; Envoy Gateway交通策略&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Should Prometheus Handle OpenTelemetry Resource Attributes? – A UX Research Report】Prometheus应该如何处理OpenTelemetry资源属性？ -  UX研究报告</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/25/how-should-prometheus-handle-opentelemetry-resource-attributes-a-ux-research-report/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;On May 29th, 2025, I wrapped up my mentorship with Prometheus through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://mentorship.lfx.linuxfoundation.org/project/36e3f336-ce78-4074-b833-012015eb59be&#34;&gt;Linux Foundation Mentorship Program&lt;/a&gt;. My project focused on understanding how Prometheus handles OpenTelemetry resource attributes and how that experience could be improved for users. My job was to conduct user research to get the user perspective on this challenge. In three months, I conducted user and stakeholder interviews, ran a survey, and analyzed the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, I’ll share how I conducted the research, what I uncovered and where the communities involved could go from here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project background&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel) has something called a &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/concepts/resources/&#34;&gt;resource&lt;/a&gt; attribute, which is extra information about the source of a metric, like the service, host, or environment that generated it. Prometheus, a time-series database, uses labels to identify and query metrics. If resource attributes are converted to labels, they can cause what’s known as “a cardinality explosion”, essentially creating too many unique combinations that overwhelm the system. This usually happens if the attributes change often or include a lot of unique values, like user IDs or pod names.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, there are three main approaches to handling this challenge:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Map all resource attributes to labels: This creates cardinality explosion problems, especially for applications with large numbers of attributes or frequently changing attribute values.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Selective promotion: Users manually choose which resource attributes are important enough to be converted to labels in Prometheus.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Target info pattern: Put all resource attributes in a separate metric called target_info. When users need to query metrics involving specific resource attributes, they have to perform a “join” between the target info and their actual metrics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These aren’t bad solutions technically, but they don’t provide the best user experience. So, I conducted this research to understand what the Prometheus maintainers might be missing about the user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The research objectives were:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand how engineers currently use OpenTelemetry resource attributes with Prometheus&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Identify pain points in the current integration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Discover user expectations for how resource attributes should be represented&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research approach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My research approach was a mix of qualitative and quantitative research. I started with stakeholder interviews to understand the historical context and assess how open stakeholders were to changes that might result from my research. The stakeholders I spoke to represented a range of roles, from project founders and co-founders, to long-time maintainers with historical context, and others more directly involved in the ongoing challenges around resource attribute handling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, I conducted user interviews to hear directly from people actually using these tools. Finally, I followed up with a survey to reach a broader audience and validate what I heard in interviews.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stakeholder interviews insights&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I spoke to 6 stakeholders—3 from each project:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prometheus stakeholders:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/juliusv&#34;&gt;Julius Volz&lt;/a&gt; – Prometheus Co-founder&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/beorn7&#34;&gt;Beorn Rabenstein&lt;/a&gt; – Prometheus long-time maintainer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/RichiH&#34;&gt;Richard Hartmann&lt;/a&gt; – OpenMetrics co-founder and Prometheus maintainer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry stakeholders:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jpkrohling&#34;&gt;Juraci Paixão Kröhling&lt;/a&gt; – OpenTelemetry Governance Committee member&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jsuereth&#34;&gt;Josh Suereth&lt;/a&gt; – OpenTelemetry Technical Committee member&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/austinlparker&#34;&gt;Austin Parker&lt;/a&gt; – OpenTelemetry co-founder and Governance Committee member&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My conversations with stakeholders brought several interesting discoveries to light:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Prometheus and OpenTelemetry communities hadn’t always communicated well and that prevented them from collaborating early on.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Much of the interoperability issues that exist now stem from the different philosophical and technical foundations on which each of the projects is built.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“If we think about exploratory situations or use cases, then we can justify a lot of the design decisions behind OpenTelemetry. And if we think about metrics and scaling, monitoring, for huge infra, then the design decisions for Prometheus are justified as well. So both have very good arguments.” — Juraci Paixão Kröhling&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I think one of the biggest [interoperability issues] is the difference between push and pull.” — Julius Volz&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Julius later elaborated that his concern goes beyond the delivery mechanism itself. In his words:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“One of the biggest downsides of using OTLP to push metrics to Prometheus is that you end up throwing away one of the core features of Prometheus as a monitoring system: its pull-based metrics collection model that is based on dynamic service discovery information (so Prometheus always knows which targets should currently exist), and the resulting automatic target health monitoring via the synthetic ‘up’ metric that is generated for each target scrape.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;There’s a shared recognition of the importance of putting user needs first, even while maintaining some non-negotiables (for example, Prometheus keeping its pull model and not alienating existing users).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One key takeaway from the interviews for me was realizing that the current interoperability problems are not failures, but natural consequences of different communities solving different problems at different times. And it’s good to see both projects are working together now to make user experience better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User interviews insights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The user interviews were equally revealing as the stakeholder conversations. I aimed to speak with about 10 users (admittedly ambitious) but managed to interview 7, and they all shared incredibly helpful perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most prominent pain point users shared was the complexity of performing joins with the current integration. Another issue mentioned was the mismatch in metric names caused by character set limitations, but I understand that has since been addressed, as recent Prometheus releases now support UTF-8 characters (though this introduces the need for the more cumbersome quoted selector syntax in PromQL).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Regarding mental models, many users (both interviewees and survey respondents) don’t distinguish between resource attributes and Prometheus labels. They tend to think of them as the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I would expect resource attributes as a rule to be treated exactly the same way as the attributes attached to the tracer, the metric… I wouldn’t draw a boundary between them.” — Interview Participant 1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also learned about the various workarounds people use to handle resource attribute issues in their specific use cases. Some promote selected resource attributes to labels, others handle the conversion at the OpenTelemetry-Collector level to avoid dealing with it in Prometheus, and a few convert all attributes, though usually only when the number of attributes is small.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Survey insights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The survey helped me quantify what I was hearing in interviews and reach a broader audience. At the time of writing, we’ve had 134 responses, with 61 from our target group—people who use OTel and Prometheus together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are the key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users don’t conceptualize resource attributes as different from regular labels, yet current implementation treats them as separate metadata.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Complex join syntax is a big barrier to adoption, with average developers unable to write basic queries accessing resource attributes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manual attribute promotion creates operational overhead that scales poorly with team size and complexity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;78% of respondents find documentation gaps a challenge in their use of resource attributes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The survey patterns were consistent with what emerged from my qualitative research. For detailed results, see the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus-community/ux-research/blob/main/prom-otel-research/survey-results.csv&#34;&gt;anonymized survey responses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I didn’t expect to learn (but did)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I began this research to understand user pain points with resource attribute handling, but I uncovered some unexpected and important findings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most surprising was the realization that &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/specs/otel/resource/#telescoping&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry’s Resource Detection feature&lt;/a&gt; allows users to selectively retain or drop resource attributes based on relevance using a conceptual pattern sometimes referred to as “telescoping.” Despite its potential, many users and even some members of the Prometheus community seem unaware of it. This lack of awareness may have contributed to the adoption of the “join” pattern, which has since proven to be problematic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This highlights a broader issue: documentation and education gaps are a major barrier. In our survey, 78% of respondents cited documentation gaps as a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another key realization is that earlier integration decisions, like the reliance on joins, were made without a full understanding of each tool’s capabilities, an unavoidable consequence of the lack of early collaboration and communication between the Prometheus and OpenTelemetry communities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended solutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Based on conversations with stakeholders and end users, here are some of the proposed solutions, grouped by what’s feasible in the short term vs. what’s part of a longer-term vision:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short-term solutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved documentation for attribute handling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since users find it easier to promote attributes than to join on target info, it may be worth de-emphasizing (or even phasing out) documentation around joins, while making &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/guides/opentelemetry/#promoting-resource-attributes&#34;&gt;attribute promotion docs&lt;/a&gt; more prominent for those not yet aware of the option. The telescoping pattern of resource detection in OpenTelemetry also deserves more visibility and proper documentation. Additionally, users have suggested creating consolidated Prometheus–OpenTelemetry documentation that clearly explains how both systems handle resource attributes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Long-term vision&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entity framework&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry’s developing concept of entities could help Prometheus distinguish between identifying vs. descriptive attributes. This would guide which attributes become labels, and which are stored or filtered out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metadata storage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stakeholders also discussed the idea of adding first-class metadata support to Prometheus itself. This would allow certain resource attributes to be stored as metadata (not labels), avoiding cardinality costs while keeping the information available for queries or joins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expanding for exploratory telemetry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This might be a stretch, but Prometheus could consider expanding its scope to better support exploratory telemetry use cases. Stakeholders showed openness to change, as long as Prometheus’s core architecture remains intact and existing users aren’t alienated. That suggests there may be room for evolution, especially if new capabilities can complement, rather than replace, current behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I see OTel and Prometheus as coming from very different assumptions of how telemetry should work in general. So, while Prometheus is very opinionated on time series storage…OTel, on the other hand, comes from a tracing background, meaning it’s more explorative than Prometheus. So [with] Prometheus, I kinda know upfront what I need. [With] OpenTelemetry, I don’t know what I might need, so I store everything. — Juraci Paixão Kröhling&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-signal correlation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users mention using platforms that can ingest all telemetry types and correlate metrics, traces, and logs within a single system. While Prometheus will likely remain focused on just metrics, it could enable tooling that correlates metrics with telemetry stored in other databases. Prometheus currently supports &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/specs/om/open_metrics_spec/#exemplars&#34;&gt;exemplars&lt;/a&gt;, which allow linking metrics to traces, but that’s about the extent of their scope. They rely on tracing being present, which makes them less useful in environments where traces aren’t available or instrumented.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“One of the key innovative things in OpenCensus was… you could divide CPU usage by which requests were using CPU and get a metric that would say, ‘here’s CPU usage by request.’ That’s a thing you could accomplish in OpenCensus because it was all contextual-based metrics.” — Josh Suereth&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s still work to be done. The communities will need time to develop and test solutions. But I’m proud that this research has provided a user-centered foundation for that work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in the ongoing discussions, proposals, and feedback around these ideas, you can check out the GitHub repository where everything is being documented: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus-community/ux-research/tree/main/prom-otel-research&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Resource Attributes in Prometheus UX Research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acknowledgments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post would be incomplete without acknowledging my incredible mentors: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/amy-super&#34;&gt;Amy Super&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/AndrejKiri&#34;&gt;Andrej Kiripolsky&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ArthurSens&#34;&gt;Arthur Silva Sens&lt;/a&gt; – thank you for trusting me with this challenging project and caring so deeply about my professional journey. You are the real superstars.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To all the stakeholders and users who gave their time: thank you for engaging with this work and trusting me with your honest feedback. Your insights made this research meaningful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s next for me&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m excited to keep working at the intersection of UX and cloud native systems. If you know of opportunities similar to this mentorship, I’d love to hear from you! I’m a hard worker—just ask my mentors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在2025年5月29日，我通过&lt;a a href =“ https://mentorshim.lfx.linuxfoundation.org/project/36e3f336-ce78-ce78-4074-b833-b833-b833-b833-byb833-33-33-33-byb5eb59be”我的项目专注于了解Prometheus如何处理OpenTelemetry资源属性以及如何改善用户的体验。我的工作是进行用户研究，以了解用户对此挑战的看法。在三个月内，我进行了用户和利益相关者访谈，进行了调查，并分析了调查结果。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将分享我如何进行研究，发现的内容以及所涉及的社区可以从这里去的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;项目背景&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OpentElemetry（Otel）具有称为a &lt;a href =“ https://opentelemetry.io/docs/conepts/conepts/resources/”&gt; resource &lt;/a&gt;属性，这是有关指标，服务，主机或生成它的环境的额外信息。 Prometheus是一个时间序列数据库，使用标签来识别和查询指标。如果将资源属性转换为标签，它们可能会引起所谓的“基数爆炸”，从本质上产生了太多的独特组合，使系统不堪重负。如果属性经常更改或包含许多唯一值，例如用户ID或POD名称，通常会发生这种情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，处理这一挑战的主要方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将所有资源属性映射到标签：这会创建基数爆炸问题，尤其是对于具有大量属性或经常更改属性值的应用程序。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;选择性促销：用户手动选择哪些资源属性很重要，可以转换为Prometheus中的标签。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;目标信息模式：将所有资源属性放在称为target_info的单独度量标准中。当用户需要查询涉及特定资源属性的指标时，他们必须在目标信息和实际指标之间执行“加入”。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从技术上讲，这些解决方案不是不良的解决方案，但是它们没有提供最佳的用户体验。因此，我进行了这项研究，以了解Prometheus维护者在用户体验上可能缺少什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;研究目标是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;了解工程师当前如何使用Prometheus &lt;/li&gt;使用OpenTelemetry资源属性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;确定当前整合中的疼痛点&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;发现用户对应如何表示资源属性的期望&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H2 class =“ WP-block-tearing”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;研究方法&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我的研究方法是定性和定量研究的结合。我从利益相关者的访谈开始，以了解历史环境，并评估利益相关者对我研究可能导致的变化的开放式。我说的利益相关者o代表了一系列角色，从项目创始人和联合创始人到具有历史背景的长期维护者，以及其他更直接参与围绕资源属性处理的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，我进行了用户访谈，直接听取实际使用这些工具的人的意见。最后，我跟进了一项调查，以吸引更广泛的受众并验证我在采访中听到的信息。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;利益相关者采访见解&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我与6个利益相关者进行了交谈-3每个项目：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;普罗米修斯利益相关者：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/juliusv”&gt; Julius Volz &lt;/a&gt;  -  Prometheus Co-Founder &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/beorn7”&gt; Beorn Rabenstein &lt;/a&gt;  -  Prometheus长期维护者&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/richih”&gt;理查德·哈特曼（Richard Hartmann）&lt;/a&gt;  -  OpenMetrics联合Founder和Prometheus Verenter &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; opentelemetry利益相关者：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/jpkrohling”&gt;JuraciPaixãoKröhling&lt;/a&gt;  -  Opentelemetry治理委员会成员&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/jsuereth”&gt; Josh Suereth &lt;/a&gt;  -  Opentelemetry技术委员会成员&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/austinlparker”&gt;奥斯汀·帕克（Austin Parker）&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我与利益相关者的对话带来了一些有趣的发现：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Prometheus和Opentelemetry社区并不总是很好地交流，这阻止了他们早期合作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;现在存在的许多互操作性问题源于构建每个项目的不同哲学和技术基础。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“如果我们考虑探索性情况或用例，那么我们可以证明Opentelemetry背后的许多设计决策是合理的。而且，如果我们考虑度量和扩展，监控，对大型下属进行监控，那么Prometheus的设计决策也是合理的。 - JuraciPaixãoKröhling&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我认为最大的（互操作性问题）之一是推动和拉力之间的差异。” - 朱利叶斯·沃尔兹（Julius Volz）&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;朱利叶斯后来阐述了他的关注超出了交付机制本身。用他的话：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“使用OTLP将指标推向Prometheus的最大弊端之一是，您最终将Prometheus作为监控系统的核心特征之一丢弃：其基于拉动的指标收集模型基于动态服务发现信息，因此，Prometheus始终知道当前的目标是自动监控的目标，并且可以通过“自动监控”目标来启动，并通过“启用”目标，并且可以通过“合成”来指示。刮擦。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;即使在维护的同时，也可以共同认识到将用户放在首位的重要性进行一些非商品（例如，Prometheus保持其拉模型而不疏远现有用户）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对我的采访中的一个关键要点是，意识到当前的互操作性问题不是失败，而是在不同时间解决不同社区的自然后果。很高兴看到这两个项目现在正在共同努力以使用户体验更好。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;用户访谈洞察&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户访谈同样与利益相关者的对话相同。我的目的是与大约10位用户交谈（肯定是雄心勃勃），但设法采访了7，他们都分享了令人难以置信的有用观点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户分享的最突出的疼痛点是与当前集成一起执行连接的复杂性。提到的另一个问题是由字符集限制引起的指标名称的不匹配，但我知道此后已经解决了这一点，因为最近的Prometheus版本现在支持UTF-8字符（尽管这引入了对Promql中更繁琐的引用选择器的概述的需求。&lt;/p&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;关于心理模型，许多用户（受访者和调查受访者）都没有区分资源属性和普罗米修斯标签。他们倾向于将它们视为同一件事。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我希望将资源属性通常与示踪剂，度量标准的属性完全相同的方式进行处理。我不会在它们之间划界。” - 面试参与者1 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我还了解了人们用来处理特定用例中资源属性问题的各种解决方法。有些将选定的资源属性促进标签，而另一些则在OpenTelemetry-Collector级别处理转换，以避免在Prometheus中处理它，而一些转换所有属性，尽管通常仅在属性数很小时才。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;调查见解&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这项调查帮助我量化了在采访中听到的内容，并吸引了更广泛的受众。在撰写本文时，我们有134个回复，我们的目标人群有61个 - 将Otel和Prometheus一起使用的人。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是关键发现：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;用户不会将资源属性概念化为与常规标签不同，但是当前的实现将它们视为单独的元数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;复杂的加入语法是采用的巨大障碍，普通的开发人员无法编写基本查询来访问资源属性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;手动属性促销创建的操作开销，随着团队规模和复杂性的缩小范围很差。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 78％的受访者发现文档差距是他们使用资源属性的挑战。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;调查模式与我的定性研究中出现的结果一致。有关详细结果，请参见&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/prometheus-community/ux-research/blob/main/main/main/prom-otel-research/survey-results.csv”&gt;匿名调查响应&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我没想到（但做过）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我开始了这项研究，以通过资源属性处理来了解用户痛点，但是我发现了一些意外而重要的发现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最令人惊讶的之一是意识到&lt;a href =“ https://opentelemetry.io/docs/docs/specs/specs/otel/resource/#telescoping”&gt; opentelemetry的资源检测功能&lt;/a&gt;允许用户基于相关模式选择性地或删除使用概念的模式来选择或删除资源属性。尽管具有潜力，但许多用户甚至是普罗米修斯社区的某些成员似乎都没有意识到这一点。缺乏意识可能有助于采用“联接”模式，此后事实证明这是有问题的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这突出了一个更广泛的问题：文档和教育差距是一个主要障碍。在我们的调查中，有78％的受访者将文件差距作为挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一个关键的认识是，像依赖加入的依赖一样，早期的集成决策是对每个工具能力的全面理解，这是普罗米修斯和欧普特群岛之间缺乏早期协作和交流的不可避免的结果。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;推荐的解决方案&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基于与利益相关者和最终用户的对话，以下是一些提议的解决方案，由短期中可行的与长期愿景的部分相分组：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-tearing”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;短期解决方案&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;改进了属性处理的文档&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since users find it easier to promote attributes than to join on target info, it may be worth de-emphasizing (or even phasing out) documentation around joins, while making &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/guides/opentelemetry/#promoting-resource-attributes&#34;&gt;attribute promotion docs&lt;/a&gt; more prominent for those not yet aware of the 选项。 Opentelemetry中资源检测的望远镜模式也值得更多可见性和适当的文档。此外，用户建议创建合并的Prometheus -opentelemetry文档，该文档清楚地说明了两个系统如何处理资源属性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;长期视觉&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;实体框架&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OpenTelemetry的发展概念可以帮助Prometheus区分识别与描述性属性。这将指导哪些属性成为标签，然后将其存储或过滤出来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;元数据存储&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; stAkeholders还讨论了将一流的元数据支持添加到Prometheus本身的想法。这将允许某些资源属性作为元数据（而非标签）存储，避免了基数成本，同时保持信息可用于查询或加入。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;扩展探索性遥测&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这可能是一个范围，但是普罗米修斯可以考虑扩大其范围以更好地支持探索性遥测用例。只要普罗米修斯的核心架构保持完好无损并且现有用户没有疏远，利益相关者就会表现出开放的变化。这表明可能有进化的空间，尤其是如果新功能可以补充而不是替换当前行为。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;我认为奥特尔和普罗米修斯是关于遥测应该如何运作的截然不同的假设。因此，尽管Prometheus在时间序列存储中非常有用……另一方面，Otel来自追踪背景，这意味着它比Prometheus更具探索性。因此，有了Prometheus，我有点知道我需要什么。 [使用] opentelemetry，我不知道我可能需要什么，所以我存储了所有内容。 - JuraciPaixãoKröhling&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;交叉信号相关&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户提到的是使用可以摄入所有遥测类型并在单个系统中关联的指标，迹线和日志的平台。尽管Prometheus可能只关注度量标准，但它可以实现将指标与存储在其他数据库中的遥测相关的工具。 Prometheus当前支持&lt;a href =“ https://prometheus.io/docs/specs/open_metrics_spec/#exemplars”&gt; exemplars &lt;/a&gt;，它允许链接指标追溯到追踪，但这与其范围的程度有关。他们依靠跟踪存在，这使得它们在没有痕迹或仪器的环境中降低了有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“ OpenCensus中的关键创新性事物之一是……您可以通过请求使用CPU并获得一个指标的CPU用法，并获得‘这是‘这是通过请求使用的CPU用法。’这是您可以在OpenCensus中完成的事情，因为这都是基于上下文的基于上下文的指标。” - 乔什（Josh）起诉&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仍然有工作要做。社区将需要时间来开发和测试解决方案。但是我为这项研究提供了以用户为中心的基础，我感到自豪。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in the ongoing discussions, proposals, and feedback around these ideas, you can check out the GitHub repository where everything is being documented: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus-community/ux-research/tree/main/prom-otel-research&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Resource Attributes in Prometheus UX Research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;确认&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果不承认我令人难以置信的导师，这篇文章将是不完整的：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/amy-super“&gt;艾米超级&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =” https://github.com/andrejkiri“&gt; andrej kiripolsky &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =” https：//github.com.com.com.com.com.com/arthursens“超级巨星。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;给所有花点时间的利益相关者和用户：感谢您参与这项工作，并以诚实的反馈信任我。您的见解使这项研究有意义。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我接下来是什么&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我很高兴继续在UX和Cloud Native Systems的交集。如果您知道与此指导类似的机会，我很想听听您的来信！我是一个勤奋的人 - 只是问我的导师。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How I Team Up with GenAI to Craft Conference Talk Proposals】我如何与Genai合作与会议会议谈话建议</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/22/how-i-team-up-with-genai-to-craft-conference-talk-proposals/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;TL;DR: GenAI can help you write conference abstracts, but if you use it without injecting your own curiosity and humanness, reviewers can tell. This post walks through my personal process for co-writing abstracts with GenAI in a way that preserves my voice and experience. I developed this process for technical talks, but it adapts well to other formats too.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve spoken at a lot of conferences, big and small. I’ve given keynotes. Breakouts. Workshops. I’ve been around the block and written many conference talk proposals. I’ve also been on program committees and reviewed others’ proposals. There’s always room for improvement, but I like to think I know what good is.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXc5Y4Sb_bZGi4hXTrNphLQoveDpqLLcK77iB6fyTehWRwupaeHgboPMy4wqOd75gEtw2jsaCIHtDGZhTcy2Ba8ESAdjAxSjiAuMU9KMQg-Wpup7Q2egNEib65e_n2CIYqCkjU3gwA?key=6rfoJ29BafNqZbLwsHq5dg&#34; style=&#34;&#34; alt=&#34;Image of Whitney speaking in front of a large audience.&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;In my view, here are some elements of a good talk proposal:&lt;br&gt;– A clear, engaging idea (or a run-of-the-mill idea with a compelling angle)&lt;br&gt;– Some clear details about the talk, like concrete examples or stories, or talk format and tools covered&lt;br&gt;– Clear audience&lt;br&gt;– Clear takeaways&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can imagine, the widespread use of GenAI to generate talk proposals has changed the game for both submitters and reviewers. As a submitter, you can type just one line into ChatGPT, for example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Write me a KubeCon + CloudNativeCon talk abstract on Validating Admission Policy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And it produces something that, on the surface, looks pretty good!*&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Enforcing What Matters: Building Safer Kubernetes with Validating Admission Policies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Kubernetes adoption continues to grow across organizations, ensuring workloads meet security, compliance, and operational standards before hitting the cluster is more critical than ever. Enter Validating Admission Policies—a powerful, built-in alternative to third-party admission controllers and dynamic webhook solutions.&lt;br&gt;In this talk, we’ll dive into the evolution and capabilities of Validating Admission Policies in Kubernetes, exploring how they provide a declarative, in-cluster mechanism for enforcing rules at admission time. We’ll cover practical use cases like blocking privileged containers, restricting image registries, and enforcing labeling conventions—all without the overhead of managing external webhooks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attendees will learn:&lt;br&gt;– How Validating Admission Policies work under the hood&lt;br&gt;– The differences between validating policies and mutating policies&lt;br&gt;– How to write and deploy policies using the Common Expression Language (CEL)&lt;br&gt;– Best practices for policy testing and gradual rollout&lt;br&gt;– Real-world scenarios and lessons from production use&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you’re a platform engineer aiming to harden your clusters, or a developer advocating for better guardrails, this session will help you move from theory to practice and adopt a more secure and manageable Kubernetes environment—using only what the API server gives you out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But as a submitter, you should be asking yourself: &lt;em&gt;If literally everyone can make a good-looking abstract this easily, why would a reviewer choose mine?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the truthful answer is: They wouldn’t. And they won’t.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“&lt;em&gt;But Whitney!&lt;/em&gt;” you might be saying, “&lt;em&gt;This strongly hits all 4 of your 4 criteria of a good conference talk proposal! A clear idea, clear details, clear audience, and clear takeaways!&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You’re right. You’re so right. Which is why you want to submit this &lt;strong&gt;so badly&lt;/strong&gt;, don’t you? But don’t do it!!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the age of GenAI, let’s add one more criteria to our list of what makes a good talk proposal:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;– A clear, engaging idea (or a run-of-the-mill idea with a compelling angle)&lt;br&gt;– Some clear details about the talk, like concrete examples or stories, or talk format and tools covered&lt;br&gt;– Clear audience&lt;br&gt;– Clear takeaways&lt;br&gt;– &lt;strong&gt;Not obviously written by GenAI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As someone who has looked at hundreds of talk proposals, I can spot one that is written by GenAI from a mile away. And you know what it tells me? &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This person did not put any effort into their proposal.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;And if they didn’t put any effort into their proposal, why should I believe that they’ll put effort into making their talk if they get accepted?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But what are these &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:WikiProject_AI_Cleanup/AI_catchphrases&#34;&gt;AI tells&lt;/a&gt; that experienced reviewers see? Let’s go over some of them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An Incomplete List of GenAI Tells&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How many of these do you see in the abstract above?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;– Heavy use of em dashes&lt;br&gt;– Repeated “from ___ to ___” constructions&lt;br&gt;– Paired adjectives (humans usually use one)&lt;br&gt;– “In this talk, we’ll…”&lt;br&gt;– Generic three-part lists&lt;br&gt;– Long, dense sentences&lt;br&gt;– Bullet lists&lt;br&gt;– “Whether you’re ___ or ___, this session will ___”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But more than these tells, GenAI abstracts give off a &lt;em&gt;feeling&lt;/em&gt;. Like, this abstract is too smooth, and it has no indication that the author has any actual experience in tech. Or, come to think of it, there’s no indication that the author has any actual experience at &lt;em&gt;being a human&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So let’s amend our “what makes a good talk proposal” criteria one more time and add:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;– A clear, engaging idea (or a run-of-the-mill idea with a compelling angle)&lt;br&gt;– Some clear details about the talk, like concrete examples or stories, or talk format and tools covered&lt;br&gt;– Clear audience&lt;br&gt;– Clear takeaways&lt;br&gt;– &lt;strong&gt;Not obviously written by GenAI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;– &lt;strong&gt;Human emotion and personality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The last two are admittedly similar. But you can manually write a proposal that is devoid of emotion and personality, you don’t need GenAI for that. And humanness is EVERYTHING, especially now with GenAI in the mix.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXep6a3XHHn4Zg14utY00bpesiKuCjLlWbwUn9_Sz1buBouVTZdoCNwJdOYJBeVdbsgt3ZNtpH8nF_E_8w6vRqHTFQvGUCZf1kIjsNhoxx6kCWQy6_QTREDRX0L1dGmpLABMVWfb2g?key=6rfoJ29BafNqZbLwsHq5dg&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic: the human element of GenAI&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now I’m not saying to abandon GenAI altogether when working on that proposal. That’s not reasonable. GenAI is truly helpful sometimes, and we’ve all got important lives to live. I’m all for outsourcing what we can!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To make a conference talk abstract, here’s the process I work through. I use GenAI interactively and use it more like a teammate who can help tease a talk/story idea out of my lived experience and interests.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Using this process, I transformed my ‘Kubernetes Validating Admission Policies’ talk idea from a perfectly fine (but soulless) GenAI draft into something that is closer to my voice and interests. See the prompts below!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step One: Brainstorm Buddy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ask your GenAI tool to ask you questions to explore possible talk subjects, choose one, and discuss what makes it interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Two: Shape the Story&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take your chosen talk idea and make it into a talk outline. Use this process to verify that you would feel happy to give this talk, and to give feedback and examples. Also—save this outline! If your talk gets accepted, here you have a great starting point from which to build your talk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Three: Write the Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Generate the abstract! But first give GenAI context, guidance, and guardrails.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Four: Iterate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;No matter how awesome this process is, and how awesome you are, GenAI probably won’t get it completely right on the first try. Be prepared to do some critiquing and iteration.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step Five: Review Like a Reviewer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Before you submit, ask GenAI to role-play as a program committee member. Ask it to read your abstract and give honest feedback. Is it clear? Does it stand out? Would it get selected? Why or why not?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Okay, Whitney, stop talking and give me the prompts already!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;I hear you, friend. Let’s do this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prompt 1: Brainstorm Buddy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Use this prompt to explore raw, personal ideas through conversation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want to come up with a compelling conference talk idea, but I’m not starting from a fully formed concept.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ask me one question at a time to help surface something human, specific, and worth exploring in public.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This might come from:&lt;br&gt;– Something I’ve been working on&lt;br&gt;– A moment I learned something the hard way&lt;br&gt;– A pattern I’ve noticed&lt;br&gt;– A question I haven’t answered yet&lt;br&gt;– A decision I’m wrestling with&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Don’t just ask what I know. Ask what I’m curious about, what I’m drawn to, or what I’d like to learn more about.&lt;br&gt;Follow up when something seems alive. Stay conversational.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ask me if a live demo might help tell the story. Would it clarify something? Make it more engaging? Help the audience connect? If I say yes, explore what that demo might look like and how it would fit into the flow.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We’re not building a talk outline yet. When we’ve landed on a promising angle or thread, write up a short, natural-language summary of what we surfaced. Then ask if I’m ready to move on to shaping the talk, or whether I want to add more details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prompt 2: Shape the Story&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Use this prompt to turn an idea into a talk outline without losing voice or vulnerability. (Feel free to adjust the target talk length if needed)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s shape this idea into a talk outline—but I want to keep the voice, questions, and human moments we uncovered during the brainstorm.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That doesn’t mean keeping everything. Focus on what supports the core idea. Clarity is more important than completeness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Help me build a structure that:&lt;br&gt;– Reflects my point of view and lived experience&lt;br&gt;– Highlights emotional or technical tension&lt;br&gt;– Builds toward a moment of insight, reflection, or takeaway&lt;br&gt;– Stays focused enough for a 30-minute talk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keep the voice personal, thoughtful, and exploratory. Don’t sand off the edges to sound overly polished or generic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prompt 3: Write the Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Use this to generate a conference-ready abstract that doesn’t sound AI-written. Add the name of the conference that you’re submitting to.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Write a talk proposal abstract based on the outline we’ve developed so far.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is for &amp;lt;&amp;lt;Conference Name&amp;gt;&amp;gt;. Please look up the conference online to understand:&lt;br&gt;– The tone and style of accepted talks from recent years&lt;br&gt;– The CFP format, character limits, and content expectations&lt;br&gt;– The kind of audience this conference attracts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Write in third person, using the speaker’s point of view (e.g., “This session explores…” is fine—but avoid first person like “I” or “we”).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aim for a tone that is grounded, curious, and human. It should feel like a thoughtful engineer exploring a real question—not like a marketing blurb or a how-to guide.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avoid these common GenAI tells:&lt;br&gt;– Overused em dashes—use varied punctuation&lt;br&gt;– “From ___ to ___” constructions&lt;br&gt;– Paired adjectives like “clear, actionable insights”&lt;br&gt;– Generic three-part lists&lt;br&gt;– Robotic transitions like “we’ll also look at…”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Instead:&lt;br&gt;– Start with a relatable tension, question, or moment&lt;br&gt;– Include specific, technical grounding—not just abstract vibes&lt;br&gt;– Convey a strong sense of what actionable takeaway(s) the audience will explore, gain, or reflect on&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rhetorical questions are welcome if they spark curiosity—but tie them to something concrete.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enjoy the Result!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This process transformed my ‘Validating Admission Policy’ talk idea and abstract from this:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Enforcing What Matters: Building Safer Kubernetes with Validating Admission Policies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;As Kubernetes adoption continues to grow across organizations, ensuring workloads meet security, compliance, and operational standards before hitting the cluster is more critical than ever. Enter Validating Admission Policies—a powerful, built-in alternative to third-party admission controllers and dynamic webhook solutions.&lt;br&gt;In this talk, we’ll dive into the evolution and capabilities of Validating Admission Policies in Kubernetes, exploring how they provide a declarative, in-cluster mechanism for enforcing rules at admission time. We’ll cover practical use cases like blocking privileged containers, restricting image registries, and enforcing labeling conventions—all without the overhead of managing external webhooks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Attendees will learn:&lt;br&gt;– How Validating Admission Policies work under the hood&lt;br&gt;– The differences between validating policies and mutating policies&lt;br&gt;– How to write and deploy policies using the Common Expression Language (CEL)&lt;br&gt;– Best practices for policy testing and gradual rollout&lt;br&gt;– Real-world scenarios and lessons from production use&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you’re a platform engineer aiming to harden your clusters, or a developer advocating for better guardrails, this session will help you move from theory to practice and adopt a more secure and manageable Kubernetes environment—using only what the API server gives you out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;to this**:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes Validating Admission Policies and Kyverno: Competitors or Comrades?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enforcing policies in Kubernetes often begins with a simple question: What do we need to enforce, and why? For many, the answer starts with Kubernetes’ native Validating Admission Policies (VAP)—a lightweight, declarative approach that feels intuitive and clean. But as platform teams scale, the question evolves: Is this enough?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This session explores that very question through a real-world lens. The speaker, currently building a proof-of-concept platform, began by implementing basic policies using VAP. However, as the platform’s needs grew, so did the complexity of the policies. This led to an exploration of Kyverno, a policy engine designed specifically for Kubernetes, to understand its capabilities and whether it offered advantages that VAP did not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through live demonstrations, the audience will see the same policy implemented first with VAP and then with Kyverno. The session will highlight differences in developer experience, observability, and the tools’ approaches to policy enforcement. By comparing these tools side by side, the speaker aims to provide insights into when each is appropriate, without advocating for one over the other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Attendees will leave with a clearer understanding of the trade-offs involved in choosing between VAP and Kyverno, equipped to make informed decisions about policy enforcement in their own Kubernetes environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before you Submit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Iterate on the abstract and make it your own. You’ll likely be messing with character count anyway since GenAI is terrible at that. As you iterate, don’t forget to ‘review like a reviewer.’ Ask GenAI to role play as a member of the program committee and tell you whether they’d accept your talk and why.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LMKWYT!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you try out my process, let me know what you think! And if you have any suggestions for improvements, I’m all ears! Let’s use GenAI to make us all more human, instead of more robotic. I firmly believe we can do it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;References&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;is-style-max-width-800 has-small-font-size&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;*I pinky swear that I only asked ChatGPT to “&lt;strong&gt;Write me a KubeCon + CloudNativeCon talk abstract on Validating Admission Policy&lt;/strong&gt;” one time and copy-pasted the first and only result&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;is-style-max-width-800 has-small-font-size&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;**This is the first output of Prompt 3, without any additional smoothing or iteration from me. I added the title later, after its own round of GenAI-assisted iteration.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; tl; dr：genai可以帮助您编写会议摘要，但是如果您不注入自己的好奇心和人性而使用它，审稿人可以告诉您。这篇文章介绍了我的个人过程，以与Genai共同编写摘要，以保留我的声音和经验。我为技术谈判开发了这个过程，但它也适合其他格式。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我在许多大小会议上都说了大小。我给了主题演讲。突破。讲习班。我去过街区，并写了许多会议谈话建议。我还曾参加过计划委员会，并审查了其他人的建议。总有改进的余地，但我想认为我知道什么是好的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4NXC5Y4SB_BZGI4HXTRNPHLQTRNPHLQCLCKLCK77IB6FYTEHWRWWRWPHWRWUPAEHGBOPMY 4WQOD75GETW2JSACIHTDGZHTCY2BA8SADJAXSJIAUMU9KMQG-WPUP7Q2EGNEIB65E_N2CIYQCCKJU3GWA = 6RFOJ29BAFNQZBAFNQZBLWSHQ5GDG“ style =“” alt =“惠特尼在大量观众面前说话的图像。” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;在我看来，以下是一个好的谈话建议的一些元素：&lt;br&gt;  - 一个清晰，引人入胜的想法（或具有令人信服的角度的普通想法）&lt;br&gt;  - 一些有关谈话的明确细节，例如具体的例子或故事，或说话形式和谈话形式和工具，或者涵盖了&lt;br&gt;  - 清晰的受众&lt;br&gt;  - 清晰的受众&lt;br&gt;  - 清晰的外卖&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以想象，Genai的广泛使用来生成谈话建议，已改变了提交者和审稿人的游戏。作为提交者，您只需在chatgpt中输入一行，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;给我写一个kubecon + cloudnativecon关于验证录取策略的摘要&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它产生的东西看起来很好！*&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;标题：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;强制执行重要的事情：使用验证的入学策略&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;建立更安全的kubernetes&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;随着Kubernetes的采用在整个组织之间继续增长，确保工作量达到安全性，合规性和运营标准，然后才达到集群比以往任何时候都更为重要。输入验证录取策略 - 一种强大的内置替代方案，是第三方录取控制器和动态网络钩解决方案的替代方案。&lt;br&gt;在本次演讲中，我们将深入研究Kubernetes中验证入学策略的演变和能力，探索他们如何在录取时间内提供声明性的，集群的内部群集机械机构。我们将介绍实用的用例，例如阻止特权容器，限制图像注册表以及执行标签惯例 - 所有这些都没有管理外部网络钩的开销。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;与会者将学习：&lt;br&gt;  -  &lt;br&gt;  - 验证录取策略如何在hood &lt;br&gt;下使用验证策略和突变策略之间的差异 -  &lt;br&gt;  -  &lt;br&gt;  -  drestion contruction ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting plotic &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;  - （CEL）&lt;br&gt;  - 政策测试的最佳实践NG和逐步推出&lt;br&gt;  - 现实世界中的场景和生产使用的经验&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;无论您是一名平台工程师，旨在旨在加强群集，还是一个倡导更好的护栏的开发人员，本届会议将帮助您从理论转向练习，并采用更安全和可管理的Kubernetes环境，只能使用Api Api Sivers-Off Api Sever-api Sever-api box。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，作为提交者，您应该问自己：&lt;em&gt;如果每个人都可以轻松地做一个好看的摘要，为什么审稿人选择我的？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;真实的答案是：他们不会。他们不会。你真好。这就是为什么您想提交此&lt;strong&gt;如此糟糕&lt;/strong&gt;的原因，不是吗？但是不要做！！！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the age of GenAI, let’s add one more criteria to our list of what makes a good talk proposal:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;– A clear, engaging idea (or a run-of-the-mill idea with a compelling angle)&lt;br&gt;– Some clear details about the talk, like concrete examples or stories, or talk format and tools covered&lt;br&gt;– Clear audience&lt;br&gt;– Clear takeaways&lt;br&gt;– &lt;strong&gt;Not obviously written by Genai &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为一个看过数百个谈话建议的人，我可以发现Genai从一英里外写的一个。你知道它告诉我什么吗？ &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;这个人没有在提案中付出任何努力。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;，如果他们没有在提案中付出任何努力，我为什么相信他们会付出努力，如果他们被接受了？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，这些是什么&lt;a href =“ https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/wikipedia:wikiproject_ai_cleanup/ai_catchphrases”&gt; AI告诉&lt;/a&gt;让我们介绍其中的一些。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;您在上面的摘要中看到了其中有多少个？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;– Heavy use of em dashes&lt;br&gt;– Repeated “from ___ to ___” constructions&lt;br&gt;– Paired adjectives (humans usually use one)&lt;br&gt;– “In this talk, we’ll…”&lt;br&gt;– Generic three-part lists&lt;br&gt;– Long, dense sentences&lt;br&gt;– Bullet lists&lt;br&gt;– “Whether you’re ___ or ___, this session will ___”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But more than these告诉我，Genai摘要散发出A &lt;em&gt;感觉&lt;/em&gt;。就像，这个摘要太流畅了，没有迹象表明作者在技术方面具有任何实际经验。或者，想一想，没有迹象表明作者在&lt;em&gt;上有任何实际经验。关于谈话的ils，例如具体的例子或故事，或说话格式和工具&lt;br&gt;  - 清晰的听众&lt;br&gt;  - 清晰的外卖&lt;br&gt;  -  &lt;brngr&gt;  -  &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;显然是由Genai &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;brong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;  -  &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;人类的情感和人格&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;是相似的。但是，您可以手动编写缺乏情感和个性的建议，因此您不需要Genai。人性就是一切，尤其是现在的Genai。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxep6a3xhhn4zg14uty00bppesikucjllwbwun9_sz1bubouvtzdocnwjd oyjbevdbsgt3zntph8nf_e_8w6vrqhtfqhtfqvguczf1kijsnhoxx6kcwqy6 kcwqy6_qtredrx0l1dgmplabmvwfb2g？ alt =“ graphic：genai的人类元素” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，我并不是说在提出该提案时完全放弃Genai。那是不合理的。 Genai有时确实很有帮助，而且我们都有重要的生活。我全都是为了外包我们能做的！&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;使会议谈话摘要，这是我工作的过程。我进行了交互式使用Genai，并更像是队友，他可以从我的生活经验和兴趣中挑逗谈话/故事的想法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我的过程&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;使用此过程，我将“ Kubernetes”从一个完美的（但不灵活的）Genai草稿中转变为与我的声音和兴趣更接近的东西。请参阅下面的提示！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第一步：头脑风暴伙伴&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要求您的Genai工具问您问题，以探索可能的谈话主题，选择一个，并讨论使它有趣的内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第二步：塑造故事&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以您选择的谈话想法并将其列入谈话大纲。使用此过程来验证您是否会很乐意发表此演讲，并提供反馈和示例。另外 - 避免此大纲！如果您的演讲被接受，那么您将有一个很好的起点来构建您的演讲。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第三步：写摘要&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;生成摘要！但是首先提供Genai上下文，指导和护栏。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第四步：迭代&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;，无论这个过程多么棒，以及您有多棒，Genai可能在第一次尝试时都不会完全正确。准备进行一些批评和迭代。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第五步：像审稿人一样审查&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;在您提交之前，请Genai扮演角色扮演计划委员会成员。要求它阅读您的摘要并提供诚实的反馈。清楚吗？它脱颖而出吗？会被选中吗？为什么或为什么不&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;好吧，惠特尼，停止说话并给我提示！&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/eM&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/em&gt;我听到了你，朋友。让我们这样做。&lt;br&gt; &lt;brong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;使用此提示来通过对话探索原始的个人想法&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want to come up with a compelling conference talk idea, but I’m not starting from a fully formed concept.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ask me one question at a time to help surface something human, specific, and worth exploring in public.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This might come from:&lt;br&gt;– Something I’ve been working on&lt;br&gt;– A moment I learned something the hard way&lt;br&gt;– A pattern I’ve noticed&lt;br&gt;– A question I haven’t answered yet&lt;br&gt;– A decision I’m wrestling使用&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;不要只是问我知道什么。询问我对什么，我所吸引的东西或我想了解的更多信息。保持对话。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;问我现场演示是否可能有助于讲述这个故事。它会澄清一下吗？使它更具吸引力？帮助观众建立联系？如果我说是的，请探索该演示的外观以及它如何适合流程。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;我们还没有构建谈话大纲。当我们以有希望的角度或线程降落时，写下了我们所浮出水面的简短，自然语言摘要。然后询问我是否准备继续进行演讲，还是要添加更多详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提示2：塑造故事&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;使用此提示将想法变成谈话大纲而不会失去声音或漏洞。 （如果需要，请随时调整目标谈话长度）&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们将这个想法塑造成谈话大纲，但我想在集思广益期间发现我们发现的声音，问题和人类时刻。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;这并不意味着要保留一切。专注于支持核心思想的因素。 Clarity is more important than completeness.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Help me build a structure that:&lt;br&gt;– Reflects my point of view and lived experience&lt;br&gt;– Highlights emotional or technical tension&lt;br&gt;– Builds toward a moment of insight, reflection, or takeaway&lt;br&gt;– Stays focused enough for a 30-minute talk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Keep the voice personal, thoughtful, and exploratory.不要将边缘打磨以听起来过分抛光或通用。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提示3：写摘要&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;使用它来生成一个听起来不写的会议摘要。添加您提交的会议的名称。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据我们到目前为止开发的大纲编写谈话提案摘要。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;这是针对&lt;&lt;会议名称&gt;&gt;。 Please look up the conference online to understand:&lt;br&gt;– The tone and style of accepted talks from recent years&lt;br&gt;– The CFP format, character limits, and content expectations&lt;br&gt;– The kind of audience this conference attracts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Write in third person, using the speaker’s point of view (e.g., “This session explores…” is fine—but avoid first person like “I” or “we”).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aim for a tone that is grounded, curious, and human. It should feel like a thoughtful engineer exploring a real question—not like a marketing blurb or a how-to guide.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Avoid these common GenAI tells:&lt;br&gt;– Overused em dashes—use varied punctuation&lt;br&gt;– “From ___ to ___”结构&lt;br&gt;  - 诸如“清晰，可行的见解”之类的配对形容词&lt;br&gt;  - 通用的三部分列表&lt;br&gt;  - 机器人过渡诸如“我们还将看……” &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;：&lt;br&gt;：&lt;br&gt;  -  &lt;br&gt;  -  &lt;br&gt;  - 从相关的紧张，问题或力学开始，包括特定的，包括特定的，技术接地的效果，可以播放abfors &lt;br apperiation formation formation-offers explore efans explore &lt;br emplore &lt;br emplore &lt;br-获得或反思&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;的修辞问题，如果它们激发好奇心，但是将它们绑在具体的东西上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;享受结果！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个过程改变了我的“验证录取政策”的谈话想法，并从中摘要：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;标题：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;强制执行重要的事情：建立更安全的Kubernetes，并具有验证录取政策&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;随着Kubernetes的采用在整个组织之间继续增长，确保工作量达到安全性，合规性和运营标准，然后才达到集群比以往任何时候都更为重要。输入验证录取策略 - 一种强大的内置替代方案，是第三方录取控制器和动态网络钩解决方案的替代方案。&lt;br&gt;在本次演讲中，我们将深入研究Kubernetes中验证入学策略的演变和能力，探索他们如何在录取时间内提供声明性的，集群的内部群集机械机构。我们将介绍实用的用例，例如阻止特权容器，限制图像注册表以及执行标签惯例 - 所有这些都没有管理外部网络钩的开销。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;与会者将学习：&lt;br&gt;  -  &lt;br&gt;  - 验证录取策略如何在hood &lt;br&gt;下使用验证策略和突变策略之间的差异 -  &lt;br&gt;  -  &lt;br&gt;  -  drestion contruction ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting ploting plotic &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;  -  (CEL)&lt;br&gt;– Best practices for policy testing and gradual rollout&lt;br&gt;– Real-world scenarios and lessons from production use&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Whether you’re a platform engineer aiming to harden your clusters, or a developer advocating for better guardrails, this session will help you move from theory to practice and adopt a more secure and manageable Kubernetes environment—using only what the API server gives you out of the box.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对此**：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;标题：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; kubernetes验证入学策略和kyverno：竞争对手还是同志？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;在Kubernetes中执行策略通常从一个简单的问题开始：我们需要执行什么，为什么？对于许多人来说，答案始于Kubernetes的本地验证允许政策（VAP） - 一种轻巧的声明性方法，感觉直觉和干净。但是随着平台团队的扩展，问题的发展：这足够了吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本届会议通过现实世界的镜头探讨了这个问题。当前建立概念验证平台的发言人首先使用VAP实施基本政策。但是，随着平台需求的增长，政策的复杂性也随之增长。这导致对专为Kubernetes设计的政策引擎Kyverno进行了探索，以了解其功能以及它是否提供了VAP没有的优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过现场演示，观众将看到首先使用VAP实施的相同政策，然后与Kyverno一起实施。该会议将突出开发人员的经验，可观察性和工具执法方法的差异。通过并排比较这些工具，演讲者的目的是提供有关何时适当的见解，而无需提倡一个。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与会者将更清楚地了解VAP和Kyverno之间涉及的权衡方案，并有能力在自己的Kubernetes环境中做出有关政策执法的明智决定。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提交之前&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在抽象上迭代并制作自己。无论如何，由于Genai对此很糟糕，您可能会弄乱角色数量。当您迭代时，请不要忘记“像评论者一样审核”。要求Genai作为计划委员会成员的角色扮演，并告诉您他们是否接受您的演讲以及为什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; lmkwyt！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您尝试我的过程，请让我知道您的想法！而且，如果您有任何改进建议，我全都是耳朵！让我们用Genai使我们所有人更加人性化，而不是更具机器人。我坚信我们可以做到。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;参考&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class =“ is style-max-width-800具有small-font-size”&gt; &lt;em&gt;*我只要求chatgpt的粉红发誓：“ &lt;strong&gt;给我写一个kubecon + cloubnativecon谈论摘要摘要验证录取策略&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&#39;&#39;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p class =“ IS风格的最大宽度800具有small-font-size”&gt; &lt;em&gt; **这是提示3的第一个输出，而没有我任何其他的平滑或迭代。我稍后添加了标题，之后是在其自己的Genai辅助迭代之后。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Celebrating 100 Golden Kubestronauts】庆祝100个金色kubestronauts</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/21/celebrating-100-golden-kubestronauts/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/&#34;&gt;Kubestronauts program&lt;/a&gt; has been growing at an incredible pace. We recently celebrated over &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/07/16/kubestronauts-celebrating-2000-achievements-and-an-exciting-new-chapter/&#34;&gt;2000 kubestronauts&lt;/a&gt; across the globe, and today we’re excited to celebrate another milestone: &lt;strong&gt;over 100 Golden Kubestronauts&lt;/strong&gt; have achieved Golden status in less than five months, thanks to their dedication and hard work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most inspiring aspects of the Golden Kubestronauts community is its global reach. With more than 100 Golden badges earned so far, we see representation from every corner of the world—spanning North and South America, Europe, Asia, and beyond. From &lt;strong&gt;Austria, Brazil, &lt;/strong&gt;and&lt;strong&gt; Canada&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;India, Japan, &lt;/strong&gt;and&lt;strong&gt; Singapore&lt;/strong&gt;, and from &lt;strong&gt;Germany, &lt;/strong&gt;the&lt;strong&gt; Netherlands, France &lt;/strong&gt;and the&lt;strong&gt; United States&lt;/strong&gt; to places like &lt;strong&gt;Bangladesh, Mongolia, &lt;/strong&gt;and&lt;strong&gt; Vietnam&lt;/strong&gt;, Golden Kubestronauts truly embody the global spirit of CNCF. This diversity highlights not only the worldwide adoption of cloud native technologies, but also the strength of a community that learns, grows, and achieves together—regardless of geography.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXcgKcUoz3M53_75HIYJykati9Jx1uHSOA3wMGavlEWnGs5_8puSmFFFVIziIwWjd3GV2GsNSK8Ns7y61NzB4B_ko4V8dqKBIba-ayw5qta3Zh-8jsVdJk67kAscQGnZBW9I9NxnNQ?key=htDq5TvYFVQDzyUegoMkhA&#34; alt=&#34;Golden Kubestronaut Logo&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is a Golden Kubestronaut?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Becoming a Golden Kubestronaut is the highest level of recognition in the program. It requires completing all CNCF certifications as well as the Linux Foundation Certified Sysadmin (LFCS). Starting October 15th, the Certified Cloud Native Platform Engineering Associate (CNPA) will also be added as part of this journey—just as all future CNCF certifications will be included as the program continues to evolve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Golden Kubestronauts are proof of what’s possible when passion, knowledge, persistence, and a love of cloud native come together. They embody the breadth of skills across the ecosystem, from Kubernetes administration to observability, security, platform engineering, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once a Golden, Always a Golden&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s important to highlight that &lt;strong&gt;once you’ve earned Golden Kubestronaut status, it’s yours for life&lt;/strong&gt;. The more than 100 community members who have already achieved it will always be recognized for their accomplishment—even if new certifications are added later.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growing Together as a Community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just as we celebrated passing 2,000 Kubestronaut badges last month, reaching 100 Golden Kubestronauts shows how strong and engaged the community is becoming. We’re also seeing more and more Kubestronauts get involved locally—organizing meetups, sharing their stories, and encouraging others on their learning journey. This is exactly the spirit we hoped to inspire when the program was created.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thank You!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A huge thank you to everyone who has joined the program, whether you’re just getting started or already among the Goldens. Each badge earned represents a commitment to learning and to the open, vendor neutral values that CNCF stands for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can’t wait to see the next 100 Golden Kubestronauts, and beyond!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to start your journey?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more about the Kubestronauts program here.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curious about CNPA? Discover more &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/certified-cloud-native-platform-engineering-associate-cnpa/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/”&gt; kubestronauts程序&lt;/a&gt;一直以令人难以置信的速度增长。最近，我们通过&lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/07/16/kubestronauts-celebrating-2000-achievements-and-achievements-and-and-an-exciting-new-chapter/” Kubestronauts &lt;/strong&gt;得益于他们的奉献精神和辛勤工作，在不到五个月的时间内就达到了黄金地位。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;黄金kubestronauts社区最具启发性的方面之一就是它的全球影响力。到目前为止，我们看到了100多个黄金徽章，我们看到了来自世界各个角落的代表，包括北美和南美，欧洲，亚洲及其他地区。来自&lt;strong&gt;奥地利，巴西，&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;加拿大&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;到&lt;strong&gt;印度，日本，&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;新加坡&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; netherlands，netherlands，france &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; Golden Kubestronauts真正体现了CNCF的全球精神。这种多样性不仅强调了云土著技术的全球采用，而且还强调了一个学习，成长和成就的社区的力量 - 没有地理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxcgkcuoz3m53_75hiyjykati9jx1uhsoa3wmgavlewlewngs5_8pusmffffv iziiwwwjd3gv2gsnsk8nns7y61nzb4b_ko4v8dqkbiba-ayw5qta3zh-8jsvdjk67Kascqqqqnzbw9i9nxnxnxnnq？ alt =“ Golden Kubestronaut徽标” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是金kubestronaut？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成为黄金kubestronaut是该计划中最高的认可水平。它需要完成所有CNCF认证以及Linux Foundation认证的Sysadmin（LFCS）。从10月15日开始，经过认证的云原生平台工程助理（CNPA）也将作为这一旅程的一部分添加 - 随着该计划继续发展，所有未来的CNCF认证将包括在内。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;黄金kubestronauts证明了当激情，知识，持久性和对云本地人的热爱时的可能性。它们体现了整个生态系统的技能广度，从Kubernetes管理到可观察性，安全性，平台工程等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;一旦成为金色，总是金色&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;重要的是要强调，&lt;strong&gt;您获得了金色kubestronaut的身份，这就是您的生命&lt;/strong&gt;。已经实现的100多名社区成员将始终因其成就而得到认可 - 即使以后添加了新的证书。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;作为一个社区成长&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;就像我们C一样上个月催血的超过2,000个Kubestronaut徽章，达到100个Golden Kubestronauts，显示了社区的强大和敬业度。我们还看到越来越多的kubestronauts在当地参与其中 - 组织聚会，分享他们的故事并鼓励其他人学习旅程。这正是我们希望何时创建该程序的精神。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;谢谢！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您刚刚开始还是已经成为黄金人，都非常感谢加入该计划的每个人。获得的每个徽章都代表着对学习和开放的供应商中性价值观的承诺。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们迫不及待地想看到下一个100个金色kubestronauts及以后！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class =“ wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;想要开始您的旅程？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/training/kubestronaut/”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在此处了解有关Kubestronauts计划的更多信息。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;对CNPA感到好奇吗？发现更多&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://training.linuxfoundation.org/certification/certified-cloud-native-native-platform-egineering-associate-cnpa/&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在这里&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Uniting the Cloud Native Community at the Inaugural KCD SF Bay Area】在首届KCD SF湾地区团结云土著社区</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/20/uniting-the-cloud-native-community-at-the-inaugural-kcd-sf-bay-area/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The cloud native landscape is constantly evolving, and staying ahead of the curve means more than just reading documentation—it means connecting with the people who are shaping the future. That’s exactly what the &lt;strong&gt;inaugural Kubernetes Community Day (KCD) SF Bay Area&lt;/strong&gt; event is all about. This full-day gathering, proudly sponsored by the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), is the ultimate opportunity for enthusiasts, developers, and industry leaders to come together for a day of insightful talks and unparalleled networking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;On &lt;strong&gt;September 9th&lt;/strong&gt;, the historic Computer History Museum in Mountain View will open its doors to the Bay Area’s thriving cloud native community. This isn’t just a conference; it’s a celebration of collaboration and knowledge sharing. As an added bonus, your event registration grants you access to the museum’s fascinating exhibits, allowing you to explore the history of technology during your breaks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Day Packed with Industry Visionaries&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The KCD SF Bay Area event boasts an incredible lineup of speakers and visionaries. You’ll have the chance to hear directly from some of the most influential minds in the cloud native space. Confirmed speakers include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Solomon Hykes&lt;/strong&gt;, the founder of Docker and Dagger.io, whose work has fundamentally changed the way we build and deploy applications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jim Bugwadia&lt;/strong&gt;, founder of Nirmata and a key maintainer of the popular policy engine Kyverno.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ramiro Berrelleza&lt;/strong&gt;, founder of Okteto, who is dedicated to simplifying cloud native development workflows.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marina Moore&lt;/strong&gt;, the head of Edera Research, and a security expert data scientist.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dan Garfield&lt;/strong&gt;, co-founder of Codefresh and a maintainer of the Argo Project.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ron Petty&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Ricardo Aravena&lt;/strong&gt;, leads of the CNCF AI WG &amp;amp; TOC, who are at the forefront of integrating artificial intelligence with cloud native technologies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jonathan Bryce, &lt;/strong&gt;Executive Director of the CNCF, LF, and OIF.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;These are just a few of the thought leaders you can expect to learn from. The full schedule, which you can view at &lt;a href=&#34;https://schedule.kcdsfbayarea.com/&#34;&gt;https://schedule.kcdsfbayarea.com&lt;/a&gt;, is packed with sessions designed to expand your knowledge and inspire new ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Special Moment: Celebrating 10 Years of the CNCF&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year marks a special milestone for the cloud native community. We will take a moment during the event to celebrate the &lt;strong&gt;10th anniversary of the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF)&lt;/strong&gt;. The Computer History Museum holds a unique significance for us, as it was the very location where the CNCF was born. We are thrilled to be back at this historic venue to honor a decade of innovation, collaboration, and growth that has shaped the modern technological landscape. Join us as we recognize the achievements of the past ten years and look forward to the future of cloud native technology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hands-On Workshops and Demos&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the main talks, the event will feature hands-on workshops from some of the leading companies in the cloud native ecosystem. These sessions will give you a chance to dive deep into new tools and technologies with guidance from the experts who created them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroku:&lt;/strong&gt; Explore approaches to deploying and managing applications, with a focus on developer-friendly workflows, scalability, and best practices..&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Appscode:&lt;/strong&gt; Gain practical experience with running production-grade databases on Kubernetes through hands-on sessions covering popular open source projects.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nirmata:&lt;/strong&gt; Dive into Kubernetes governance and policy-as-code with the maintainers of Kyverno. These workshops are perfect for anyone looking to automate security and compliance in their clusters.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mirantis:&lt;/strong&gt; Whether you’re a developer or an administrator, Mirantis will offer sessions on cloud native solutions, including Docker and Kubernetes, designed to help you prepare for certifications or simply sharpen your skills.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Octopus Deploy:&lt;/strong&gt; Simplify your CI/CD pipeline with deployment automation. This workshop will show you how to build robust, repeatable processes for getting your software from commit to production.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hosted by Your Cloud Native Bay Area User Groups&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This event is brought to you by the passionate leaders of the Cloud Native Bay Area user groups: &lt;strong&gt;Lisa-Marie Namphy&lt;/strong&gt; (Intuit), &lt;strong&gt;Rey Lejano&lt;/strong&gt; (Red Hat), &lt;strong&gt;Jason Smith&lt;/strong&gt; (Google), and &lt;strong&gt;Natalie Lunbeck&lt;/strong&gt; (Shipyard). Their vision is to create a space that fosters collaboration and strengthens the local tech community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;The day will culminate in a vibrant &lt;strong&gt;evening social hour&lt;/strong&gt;, the perfect setting to relax, network, and connect with fellow attendees. It’s a great opportunity to continue conversations from the day and forge new friendships and professional connections.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Take Action Today!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;View the Schedule:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://schedule.kcdsfbayarea.com/&#34;&gt;https://schedule.kcdsfbayarea.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Tickets:&lt;/strong&gt; Use code &lt;strong&gt;FRIENDS25&lt;/strong&gt; for a 25% discount on either platform.&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.cncf.io/events/details/cncf-kcd-sf-bay-area-presents-kcd-san-francisco-bay-area/&#34;&gt;CNCF Community&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(requires a Linux Foundation account)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://lu.ma/y3s2jegu&#34;&gt;Lu.ma&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;(requires a Lu.ma account)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Don’t miss this chance to learn from the best, network with peers, and celebrate the dynamic spirit of the cloud native community. We look forward to seeing you on September 9th in Mountain View!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;云原生景观在不断发展，并且在曲线领先不仅意味着不仅仅是阅读文档，还意味着与塑造未来的人们建立联系。这正是&lt;strong&gt;首届Kubernetes社区日（KCD）SF湾区&lt;/strong&gt;活动的全部内容。这次由Cloud Native Computing Foundation（CNCF）赞助的全天聚会是爱好者，开发人员和行业领导者的最终机会，可以团结一致，进行一天的见解和无与伦比的网络。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;在&lt;strong&gt; 9月9日&lt;/strong&gt;上，历史悠久的计算机历史博物馆将为海湾地区蓬勃发展的云土著社区打开大门。这不仅仅是一次会议；这是对合作和知识共享的庆祝活动。作为额外的奖励，您的活动注册会授予您进入博物馆迷人展览的访问，从而使您可以在休息期间探索技术的历史。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;em&gt;一日充满行业有远见的人&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; KCD SF湾地区活动拥有令人难以置信的扬声器和有远见的人。您将有机会直接听到云原生空间中一些最具影响力的思想。确认的扬声器包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Solomon Hykes &lt;/strong&gt;，Docker and Dagger.io的创始人，其工作从根本上改变了我们构建和部署应用程序的方式。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;吉姆·布格瓦迪亚（Jim Bugwadia）&lt;/strong&gt;，尼尔马塔（Nirmata）的创始人，流行的政策引擎的主要维护者kyverno。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Ramiro Berrelleza &lt;/strong&gt;，Okteto的创始人，他致力于简化云的本地发展工作流程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Marina Moore &lt;/strong&gt;，Edera Research的负责人和安全专家数据科学家。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Dan Garfield &lt;/strong&gt;，CodeFresh的联合创始人，Argo项目的维护者。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Ron Petty &lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt; Ricardo Aravena &lt;/strong&gt;，CNCF AI WG和TOC的潜在客户，他们处于将人工智能与云本地技术集成的最前沿。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;乔纳森·布莱斯（Jonathan Bryce），&lt;/strong&gt; CNCF，LF和OIF的执行董事。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;这些只是您可以期望学习的一些思想领袖。完整的时间表，您可以在&lt;a href =“ https://schedule.kcdsfbayarea.com/”&gt; https://schedule.kcdsfbayarea.com &lt;/a&gt;中都包含旨在扩展您的知识和激发新想法的会话。&lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class =“ wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;em&gt;一个特殊的时刻：庆祝CNCF &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;的10年&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年标志着云土著社区的特殊里程碑。我们将在活动中花点时间庆祝云原生计算基金会（CNCF）&lt;强&gt; 10周年&lt;/strong&gt;。公司Mputer历史博物馆对我们具有独特的意义，因为它是CNCF出生的地方。我们很高兴能回到这个历史悠久的场所，以纪念塑造现代技术景观的十年创新，合作和成长。加入我们，因为我们认识到过去十年的成就，并期待云土著技术的未来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class =“ wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;em&gt;动手研讨会和演示&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了主要会谈外，该活动还将举办来自Cloud Native生态系统中一些领先公司的动手研讨会。这些会议将使您有机会在创建它们的专家的指导下深入研究新的工具和技术。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Heroku：&lt;/strong&gt;探索部署和管理应用程序的方法，重点是开发人员友好的工作流，可伸缩性和最佳实践。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; AppScode：&lt;/strong&gt;通过涵盖流行的开源项目的动手会议，在Kubernetes上运行生产级数据库获得实践经验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; nirmata：&lt;/strong&gt;与Kyverno的维护者一起探讨了Kubernetes的治理和政策。这些研讨会非常适合任何希望在群集中自动化安全和合规性的人。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Mirantis：&lt;/strong&gt;无论您是开发人员还是管理员，Mirantis都会在包括Docker和Kubernetes在内的Cloud Native Solutions上提供会议，旨在帮助您准备认证或简单地提高您的技能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;章鱼部署：&lt;/strong&gt;使用部署自动化简化了您的CI/CD管道。该研讨会将向您展示如何构建可重复的可重复过程以使您的软件从投入生产。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class =“ wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt; &lt;em&gt;由您的云本地海湾区域用户组托管&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这项活动是由云土著湾地区用户群体的热情领导者带给您的：&lt;strong&gt; lisa-marie namphy &lt;/strong&gt;（intuit），&lt;strong&gt; rey ley lejano &lt;/strong&gt;（red&gt; jason jason smith&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;（google）和&lt;strong&gt; natalie natalie lunbeck &lt;/strong&gt; shipyd&gt; shipyard）。他们的愿景是创造一个促进协作并加强当地技术社区的空间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;这一天将在充满活力的&lt;strong&gt;晚上社交时光&lt;/strong&gt;中达到顶峰，这是放松，网络和与同伴联系的理想场所。从一天开始继续对话并建立新的友谊和专业联系。&lt;/p&gt;是一个很好的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;立即采取行动！&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;查看时间表：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://schedule.kcdsfbayarea.com/”&gt; https://schedule.kcdsfbayarea.com &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol start =“ 2” class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;获得门票：&lt;/strong&gt;使用代码&lt;strong&gt; friends25 &lt;/strong&gt;在任一平台上获得25％的折扣。&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://community.cncf.io/events/details/cncf-kcd-kcd-sf-bay-area-area-area-presents-kcd-san-francisco-bay-area/&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://lu.ma/y3s2jegu”&gt; lu.ma &lt;/a&gt;（需要一个lu.ma帐户）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不要错过这个机会，与同龄人一起学习最好的网络，并庆祝云土著社区的动态精神。我们期待在9月9日在Mountain View中与您见面！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Celebrating 100 Days of Kagent】庆祝100天的Kagent</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/19/celebrating-100-days-of-kagent/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When we first &lt;a href=&#34;https://techstrong.ai/agentic-ai/solo-ios-kagent-brings-agentic-ai-to-cloud-native-operations/&#34;&gt;introduced kagent&lt;/a&gt; on March 17th, 2025, we had a bold vision: to bring agentic AI to cloud native—empowering platforms and DevOps engineers to harness AI agents for solving real operational challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fast forward 100 days, and today we’re celebrating a major milestone: &lt;strong&gt;100 days of the kagent project&lt;/strong&gt;! 🎉Thank you everyone for being part of this journey! 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Accepted into CNCF as a sandbox project&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What began as a tool to address our own customer challenges has grown into a thriving open-source project. Kagent is now a &lt;strong&gt;CNCF Sandbox project&lt;/strong&gt;, and it’s evolving into a powerful &lt;strong&gt;declarative agentic AI framework&lt;/strong&gt;—enabling like-minded engineers to run AI agents in Kubernetes, automating complex operations and streamlining troubleshooting workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfncOUQ6yZnCUWu5AwPIyNR8r4qz0kHAwAnpau4PGO4utPJHAUEzG4b-TtanfIATjlbCCMLAMFVIew3_ETbh1Au5z22CoIMTd6QiWt7Rwku4V02QAHxjYx1gu740ZQV4BbJBCa-JA?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Graphic of Peter Jausovec tweet&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/pjausovec_kagent-has-been-accepted-as-a-cncf-sandbox-activity-7331347027777216512-9VC_&#34;&gt;LinkedIn post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;🌟 100 Contributors &amp;amp; 1000+ GitHub Stars!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In just 100 days, kagent has hit two incredible milestones:&lt;br&gt;🚀 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kagent.devstats.cncf.io/d/66/developer-activity-counts-by-companies?orgId=1&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;100 contributors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, with over &lt;strong&gt;85% from outside Solo.io&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; ⭐ &lt;strong&gt;1000+ GitHub stars&lt;/strong&gt; from our amazing community!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve been actively connecting with contributors through &lt;strong&gt;GitHub, Discord, weekly community calls, livestreams,&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Contributor Spotlights&lt;/strong&gt;. We’re incredibly grateful for everyone who’s explored, supported, and contributed to kagent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;huge shoutout&lt;/strong&gt; to our &lt;strong&gt;top 20 contributors&lt;/strong&gt;, and a special thanks to our &lt;strong&gt;top 3&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@eitanya, @peterj, and @sbx03&lt;/strong&gt; — we deeply appreciate your dedication and impact!! 🙌&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfeXmVqqDJJHKz1EBqlt-iWF2xFG6HfDDfG9_3dPNTA18oEXY5iMwGFsVZn81XaD8gSfF3JpUtnMusQybNkpCVITY58mcEDiZpgNsQ-5R0Jm2jxnfGgjONhzoDHa4nYYgthzkuM?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Top 20 contributors of kagent&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: https://kagent.devstats.cncf.io/d/66/developer-activity-counts-by-companies?orgId=1&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Users advocating for kagent&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the past 100 days, we’ve been blown away by how our early adopters are using kagent in creative and powerful ways—including in &lt;strong&gt;production environments&lt;/strong&gt;! Across &lt;strong&gt;social media, community meetings&lt;/strong&gt;, and beyond, users are not just experimenting—they’re innovating. 💡&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are just a few examples of how the community is putting kagent to work:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Talk to Infrastructure using kagent, A2A, kgateway and others!&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfjfJqLAs-Mw5b2ljQMAcarEQVbc0uvFOM3U8aGcqKO0HQEcKNvEwtyuTP37WndR_XR3IM6QrYYfPhMklAKcIssdDqkPcbFnho8u8JPmMeKQkpxnXMa8m_0u0zW_r99wdHw_Qsp_A?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Denys Vasyliev Tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7331020451076308993&#34;&gt;Linkedin post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Integrate kagent with Argo MCP server&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfC-VBRsVFxlTM5a23NGmiaGhN_1PgSs2VU_ZZh5xRg32Nnno_FA3T4KO7ltJ0mi6rWo9lcy7aAvAokbB2Nr4FuP4gtJ6SmVFyl7UcNHmkM8msXPqSCnOoLdyOEtWcHohWqjoM9og?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Chris Matcham tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/christophermatcham_exploring-argocds-new-mcp-server-with-kagent-activity-7326612299459321856-ucyq?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=member_desktop&amp;amp;rcm=ACoAAABLihcBuozqLyftNtauegAdN2-QszsmqQQ&#34;&gt;Linkedin post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Integrate kagent with home labs and MCP servers&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfQBDyo9I7QK_Ue0JosClS_EV_b2YrquGUbb1Jgoz0VQuTbqnD-neB17LKzRCvoelBMGSnSqxjDL8leDp_5NeJ6mY5VgK7tanBOhKqgeEgv7_vGT7i82PbyJRzFizJRmjxFBlD32A?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; style=&#34;&#34; alt=&#34;Dmytrp Rashko tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7327684658475712515&#34;&gt;LinkedIn post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Use kagent for AI reliability engineering&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdo3DIrgL-pEH8WxHWgD6NUH2C6sOnGdy0QK0zUPgi5cUV3DijD405nPmSRdQXgN4-rBSErYexpzEsBtOMoHH9BdrNnV6_uDDDjNg1wbmUyDY8Lxi3HJgovNIAq8Le9G5_GFbsRXg?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Christian Posta tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7328046281916841985&#34;&gt;LinkedIn post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Fast delivery with kagent: A2A agent with discord:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfc-yI2vYcz88Qt5pcyjWTbnDFmdjvragaGNWpQ-Rczs9DBDdpNkarfEiIae6b4xEVKeKc4MqoPy0RMobChXVh7SXtiCMMHdN2MlivTAe0AC-J2c-197wXQqqbEjBCqvOGUf_AoaQ?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Marcin Kubica tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7340382418895368193&#34;&gt;LinkedIn post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;GCP terraform agent on kagent:&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeewrdKAA9o8kAVEu8TV9AHsnB6NwN3wAYdmgyJYaxBuk-G1zzzGSLeyadIDSnhyCGhC-r-xhVkWrfW7JeZWmKndnS1ke4dWDUeIagvQyyOo5HAOimxAXBdlE_By9LQHx58BA15?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Huzefa Hamdard tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/huzefa-hamdard_terraform-gcp-kubernetes-activity-7331957646113067010-7F7I?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=member_desktop&amp;amp;rcm=ACoAAABLihcBuozqLyftNtauegAdN2-QszsmqQQ&#34;&gt;LinkedIn post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;🌍 Kagent travels around the world&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In just 100 days, kagent has made its mark on the global stage. We’ve taken our vision of Agentic AI to some of the most prestigious conferences worldwide—sharing our belief that kagent is a key building block for the future of agentic AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;📢KubeCon + CloudNativeCon EU 2025&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This was where it all began—the first public announcement of kagent and our intention to donate it to the CNCF. The announcement was made during the Day 2 keynote by Idit Levine and Keith Babo. Later, Christian Posta delivered a live demo at the KubeCon + CloudNativeCon EU demo theater, showcasing kagent in action. 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;🇫🇷 GOSIM AI Paris 2025&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Eitan Yarmush took the stage in Paris to challenge attendees to rethink the open-source agent stack with kagent. Check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4uus0zf6OUQ&#34;&gt;recording&lt;/a&gt;—it’s a must-watch!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;🤠 KCD Texas 2025&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kagent was featured in KCD Texas keynote along with Headlamp, AI model pack and Dapr agent by Chris Aniszczyk. Later, I also did a live demo of kagent to help me with Istio ambient operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXeZ4iOD2uLVvR7xL_-DytvSgzZ2oOfsemdPwK5-P5lBO4KxJJhi0gD2YnPz3-qipho505kG0J1GgmBW4H74uQXI-uCqntGp-ODZs7HtMGiBmdHiVNXWf5Ahzg3X8eXP20RaWW7owQ?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Lin Sun tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7328804002693820419&#34;&gt;LinkedIn post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;🇬🇧London DevOps Meetup May 2025&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Denys Vasyliev presented using kagent for his custom controllers of Kubernetes and MCP servers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdgoW2ig_7yUy0BdZp9f4PWB-8Rz0Cd4bZRzFUqhe6PFZs_56yGNorngqGIwukyINvi9Zttj7pnWu4lBJlP2tuki_BA2SkCDeCRFHhoJAY7GcQrNcjIZKD3IrhlI2KovhM_luYuUw?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Tor H. tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/activity-7331419530239315968-fJ7j?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=member_desktop&amp;amp;rcm=ACoAAABLihcBuozqLyftNtauegAdN2-QszsmqQQ&#34;&gt;Linkedin post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;🇨🇳KubeCon + CloudNativeCon China 2025&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The excitement for kagent crossed continents as we shared it with the cloud native community in China.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfY_J2siBaFNg68xPqZPfz_kj0-f5ire5Ucqa6B6ei4V-ksZg_qj4Tp2BwOmFXnbBJeZ8LYwJXY43QI_q_v8XeoWzr1OO9vA3Qlv1xac_fJH_HBbLUryn2pFaDxrkrjwBgh3aZU4Q?key=qRZXOzXKu-A8HOMrTLESOw&#34; alt=&#34;Brent Leung tweet graphic&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7339255065632731136&#34;&gt;LinkedIn post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;🇯🇵 OpenSSF Community – Japan&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I connected with the open source security community in Japan to explore how agentic AI can help shape the future of cloud-native users, OpenSSF, and the broader open source ecosystem. I also showcased a live demo of kagent, highlighting the future impact of agentic AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;🇺🇸Open Source Summit NA&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a totally unplanned moment, I did a live demo of kagent alongside my generative AI application with Kubernetes, Argo and Istio—right in the middle of troubleshooting a Git mistake I had just made! 😅&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was amazing to have kagent acting like my buddy on stage, offering hints and helping me recover in real time. A great example of how powerful and practical agentic AI can be!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Beyond cloud native operations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While kagent was originally designed to tackle challenges in cloud-native operations, we’ve been excited to see users applying it far beyond that scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to its knowledge-based agent, kagent can be used to interact with and reason over any type of documentation—not just Kubernetes manifests or infrastructure logs. From internal wikis and runbooks to software manuals and onboarding guides, kagent is proving to be a powerful tool for making structured and unstructured knowledge accessible via simple conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🎉&lt;/strong&gt;Wrapping up&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To everyone who has starred the kagent repo, contributed code, filed issues, joined discussions, or simply helped spread the word—&lt;strong&gt;thank you&lt;/strong&gt; for being an essential part of this community! We’re super excited to keep growing and building together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We’re proud to collaborate within the CNCF community to shape the future of agentic AI with kagent—together.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class=&#34;wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want to join the kagent community? Check out the project at&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kagent.dev/&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;kagent.dev&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, star us on&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kagent-dev/kagent&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;GitHub&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and join our &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/Fu3k65f2k3&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Discord&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; or weekly community meeting. Whether you’re looking to build your first AI agent or contribute to the framework itself, we’d love to have you onboard.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当我们第一次&lt;a href =“ https://techstrong.ai/agentic-aio/solo-ios-ios-kagent-brings-brings-brings-brings-agentic-agentic-agent-to-cloud-native-operations/”&gt;介绍了kagent &lt;/a&gt;”真正的操作挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;快进100天，今天我们庆祝一个主要的里程碑：&lt;strong&gt; Kagent Project的100天&lt;/strong&gt;！ 🎉感谢大家参与这一旅程的一部分！ 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;被CNCF接受为沙盒项目&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最初是应对我们自己的客户挑战的工具，已经发展成为一个蓬勃发展的开源项目。 Kagent现在是一个&lt;strong&gt; cncf沙盒项目&lt;/strong&gt;，它正在发展为强大的&lt;strong&gt;声明性的代理AI框架&lt;/strong&gt;  - 使志趣相投的工程师在Kubernetes中运行AI代理，自动化复杂操作并简化了疑虑的工作流程。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfncouq6yzncuwu5awpiynr8r4r4r4qz0khawanpau4pgo4bgo4utpjhauezg4b---- ttanfiatjlbccmlamfview3_etbh1au5z22coimtd6qiwt7rwku4v02qahxjyx1gu740zqv4bbjbca-ja？ alt =“ Peter Jausovec Tweet的图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/pjausovec_kagent-has-been-accepted-as-a-cncf-sandbox-activity-7331347027777216512-9VC_&#34;&gt;LinkedIn post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在短短100天内，Kagent达到了两个令人难以置信的里程碑：&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kagent.devstats.cncf.io/develiper-66/develiveer-activity-countivity-counts-counts-counts-bby-companies-companies-companies-companies？ Solo.io &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1000+ github星星&lt;/strong&gt;来自我们惊人的社区！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们一直通过&lt;strong&gt; github，Discord，每周社区电话，直播，&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;贡献者聚光灯&lt;/strong&gt;积极地与贡献者建立联系。我们非常感谢探索，支持和为Kagent做出贡献的每个人。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; a &lt;strong&gt;大喊大叫&lt;/strong&gt;我们的&lt;strong&gt;前20名贡献者&lt;/strong&gt;，并特别感谢我们的&lt;strong&gt; top 3 &lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;strong&gt; @eitanya，@peterj和 @sbx03 &lt;/strong&gt;  - 我们非常感谢您的奉献精神和影响力！ 🙌&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfexmvqqqdjjhkz1ebqlt-iwf2xf2xfg6hfg6hfddfg9_3dpndpnta18oexy5imwgf SVZN81XAD8GSFF3JPUTNMUSQYBNKPCVITY58MCEDIZPGNSQ-5R0JM2JXNFGGJONHZODHA4NYYGTHZKUM？ alt =“ Kagent的前20个贡献者” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figifer&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：https：//kagent.devstats.cncf.io/d/66/developer-activity-counts-by-companies?orgid=1 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;提倡Kagent &lt;/h2&gt;的用户&lt;p&gt;在过去的100天中，我们的早期采用者如何在&lt;strong&gt;生产环境中使用Kagent如何使用Kagent &lt;/strong&gt;！在&lt;strong&gt;社交媒体，社区会议&lt;/strong&gt;及以后，用户不仅在尝试，而且在创新。 💡&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这里只是社区如何使Kagent工作的一些例子：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;使用Kagent，A2A，Kgateway等与基础架构交谈！&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfjfjqlas-mw5b2ljqmacareqvbc0uvfom3u8agcqko0hqeckecknvyu tp37wndr_xr3im6qryyfphmklakcissddqkpcbfnho8u8jpmmekqkpxnxma8m_0zw_r99wdhw_qsp_a？ alt =“ denys vasyliev tweet graphic” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:li：activity:73310451076308993”&gt; LinkedIn Post &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;将Kagent与Argo MCP服务器集成&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfc-vbrsvffxltm5a23ngmiaghn_1pgss2vu_zzh5xrg32nnnnnnnno_fa3t4k O7LTJ0MI6RWO9LCY7AAVAOKBBBB2NR4FUP4GTJ6SMVFYL7UCNHMKMKMKMMKMKMM8MSXPQSPQSCNOOLDYOOLDYOETWCHOHWQJOM9OG？ alt =“ Chris Matcham Tweet Graphic” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/posts/christophermatcham_exploring-argocds-new-mcp-server-with-kagent-actact-activity-73266 12299459321856-ucyq？utm_source = share＆utm_medium = member_desktop＆rcm = acoaaabablihcbuozqlyfftntauegadn2-qszssmqqQ发布&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;将Kagent与家庭实验室和MCP服务器集成&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;img解码=“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfqbdyo9i7qk_ue0joscls_ev_b2yrquggubb1jgoz0vqutbqnd-neb17 lkzrcvoelbmgsnsqxjdl8ledp_5nej6my5vgk7tanbohkqgeegv7_vgt7i82pbyjrzfizjrmjxfbld32a？ style =“” alt =“ dmytrp rashko tweet图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-referrer”&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:li：activity:7327684658475712515”&gt; LinkedIn Post &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;使用kagent进行AI可靠性工程&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdo3dirgl-peh8wxhwgd6nuh2c6nuh2c6nupdy0qk0zupgi5cki5cuv3dijd405np MSRDQXGN4-RBSERYEXPZESBTOMOHH9BDRNNV6_UDDDJNG1WBMUYDY8LXI3HJGOVNIAQ8LE9G5_GFBSRXG？ alt =“ Christian Posta Tweet图形” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; source：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:li：activity:7328046281916841985”&gt; LinkedIn Post &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-heading”&gt;与Kagent快速交付：A2A代理不和谐：&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在NWPQ-RCZS9DBDDPNKARFEIIAE6B4XEVKEKC4MQOPY0RMOBCHXVH7SXTICMMHDN2MLIVTAE0AC-J2C-197WXQQQQQQQQQBCBCQBCQBCQVOGUF_AOAQ？ referrerpolicy =“ no-the Referrer”&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:li:li：activity:7340382418895368193”&gt; LinkedIn Post &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; kagent上的GCP Terraform代理：&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxeewrdkaa9o8kaveu8tv9ahsnb6nwnwnwnwwaydmgyjyaxbuk-g1zzzgsle yadidsnhycghc-r-xhvkwrfw7jezwmkndns1ke4dwdueiagvqyyoo5hoimxaxbdle_by9lqhx58ba15？ alt =“ Huzefa Hamdard Tweet图形” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/posts/huzefa-hamdard_terraform-gcp-kubernetes-activity-73319576461130670 10-7f7i？utm_source = share＆utm_medium = member_desktop＆rcm = acoaaablihcbuozqlyfftntauegadn2-qszsmqqq&gt; linkedIn发布&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;🌍kagent环游世界&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在短短100天内，Kagent在全球舞台上取得了成功。我们已经将代理AI的愿景带到了全球一些最负盛名的会议上，这表明我们相信Kagent是代理AI的未来的关键基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一切开始的地方，这是Kagent的首次公开宣布以及我们将其捐赠给CNCF的意图。这一消息是在第2天在IDIT Levine和Keith Babo的主题演讲中提出的。后来，克里斯蒂安·波斯塔（Christian Posta）在库贝肯（Kubecon） + Cloudnativecon欧盟演示剧院进行了现场演示，展示了Kagent的行动。 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;🇫🇷gosim ai paris 2025 &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; eitan Yarmush在巴黎上台，挑战与会者与Kagent重新考虑开源代理商Stack。请查看&lt;a href =“ https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4UUS0ZF6OUQ”&gt;录制&lt;/a&gt;  - 这是必不可少的！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;🤠KCDTexas 2025 &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Kagent与Chris Aniszczyk一起在KCD Texas主题演讲中与HeadLamp，AI模型包和DAPR代理一起出现。后来，我还进行了Kagent的现场演示，以帮助我进行ISTIO环境操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxez4iod2ulvvr7xl_-dytvsgzz2oofsemdpwk5p5lbo4kxjjjhi0gd2y NPZ3-QIPHO505KG0J1GGMBW4H74UQXI-UCQNTGP-ODZS7HTMGIBMDHIVNXWF5AHZG3X8X8X8X8 EXP20RAWW7OWQ？ alt =“ Lin Sun Tweet Graphic” referrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:li：activity:7328804002693820419”&gt; LinkedIn Post &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt; london DevOps Meetup 2025年5月&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; denys vasyliev使用Kagent为Kubernetes和MCP服务器的定制控制器提出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figie class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https：//lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4NXDGOW2IG_7YUY0BDZP9F4PWB-8RZ0CD4BZRZFUQHE6PFZS_56YGNERNGQGIWUKYINVI9ZT tj7pnwu4lbjlp2tuki_ba2skcdecrfhhojay7gcqrncjizkd3irhli2kovhm_luyuuw？ alt =“ tor H. Tweet Graphic” referrerPolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/posts/activity-7331419530239315968-fj7j？utm_source = share＆utm_medium = mmedium = mmedium = membem_desktop间发布&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们与中国的云土著社区分享时，Kagent越过大陆的兴奋。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxfy_j2sibafng68xpqzpfz_kj0-f5ire5ucqa6b6b6ei4v-kszg_qj4tp2 BWOMFXNBBJEZ8LYWJXY43QI_Q_V8XEOWZR1OO9VA3QLV1XAC_FJH_FJH_HBBLURYN2PFADXRKRKRJWBGH3AZU4Q？ alt =“ Brent Leung Tweet图形” reverrerpolicy =“ no-treferrer”&gt; &lt;/figife&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;来源：&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:li:li：activity:733925506565632731136”&gt; LinkedIn Post &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; i与日本的开源安全社区连接，以探讨Admitiic AI如何帮助塑造云本地用户，OpenSSF和更广泛的开源生态系统的未来。我还展示了Kagent的现场演示，强调了代理AI的未来影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; open源峰会&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在一个非常计划的时刻，我与Kubernetes，Argo和Istio一起进行了Kagent的现场演示，正好在解决我刚刚犯的Git错误的过程中！ 😅&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让Kagent像我的伙伴一样在舞台上表演，提供提示并帮助我实时康复。一个很好的例子，说明&lt;/p&gt;有多大和实用的代理AI！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;超越云本机操作&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然Kagent最初是为了应对云原生操作中的挑战而设计的，但我们很高兴看到用户将其应用于该范围之外。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于其基于知识的代理，Kagent可用于与任何类型的文档进行交互和理由，而不仅仅是Kubernetes表现出来或基础架构日志。从内部Wiki和Runbooks到软件手册和入职指南，Kagent被证明是通过简单的对话访问结构化和非结构化知识的强大工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;总结&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于所有主演Kagent Repo，贡献代码，提出问题，加入讨论或简单地帮助传播词的人来说，&lt;strong&gt;谢谢您&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;是这个社区的重要组成部分！我们很高兴能够继续成长和建设。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;我们很荣幸能在CNCF社区中合作，以塑造一个未来gentic ai与kagent  - 偶然。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr class =“ wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity”&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;想加入Kagent社区吗？在&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://kagent.dev/”中查看该项目&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; github &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;，并加入我们的&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://discord.gg/fu3k65f2k3”&gt; &lt;em&gt; discord &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;或每周社区会议。无论您是想建立第一个AI代理还是为框架本身做出贡献，我们都希望让您加入。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Combining GenAI &amp; Agentic AI to build scalable, autonomous systems】将Genai＆Agesic AI相结合以构建可扩展的自主系统</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/18/combining-genai-agentic-ai-to-build-scalable-autonomous-systems/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A common pattern in today’s AI adoption is that businesses are investing heavily in GenAI capabilities, yet many are leaving significant value on the table by failing to pair it with Agentic AI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This matters because while GenAI can generate content, ideas, or responses, it can’t act on them. However, when combined with Agentic AI, your systems shift from being reactive and prompt-driven to autonomous and outcome-oriented.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article aims to help senior technology leaders better understand the value Agentic AI can add to existing AI infrastructure, while outlining key considerations to determine whether its implementation aligns with your business needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Understanding Agentic AI&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXdK_MTJsDbf-762dNxU9eeSNBT3MNJaoPxFvS8z3GqUeDcUbpuSI1dfo3sw6NSIvLJ_LaMarkzvCDtMVvSnrrWrwvSHj9OvfxWcUeAE5rkbzcQ1HzjX4hetnrrqbX35C5r1Gx_CXQ?key=xgu2lQTqMaowWCibuTxnzqRW&#34; alt=&#34;Image caption: Core components of an Agentic AI Architecture from Markovate.&amp;nbsp;&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image caption: Core components of an Agentic AI Architecture from &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://markovate.com/blog/agentic-ai-architecture/?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Markovate.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Agentic AI systems are designed to operate autonomously, perceiving their environment, making decisions, and executing actions without continuous human oversight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This autonomy enables businesses to streamline operations, reduce costs, and enhance scalability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The image above illustrates how the following systems function:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perception layer:&lt;/strong&gt; This layer involves collecting data from various sources i.e. sensors, cameras, microphones, and digital inputs, to understand the current state of the environment. For businesses, this means real-time monitoring of operations, customer interactions, and market trends, facilitating proactive decision-making and rapid response to changing conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognition layer:&lt;/strong&gt; Once data is collected, the cognition layer processes this information to interpret context, recognise patterns, and determine the best course of action. This analysis automates complex decision-making processes and reduces reliance on manual interventions, minimising the risk of human error.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Action layer: &lt;/strong&gt;After determining the appropriate response, the action layer executes the decision i.e. adjusting system parameters, initiating workflows, or communicating with stakeholders. This capability ensures quick implementation of decisions to enhance operational efficiency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, Agentic AI systems are equipped with learning mechanisms that improve over time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through techniques like reinforcement learning, where the system learns from the outcomes of its actions, and supervised or unsupervised learning, where it identifies patterns in data, the AI adapts to new situations and refines its decision-making processes.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;GenAI is great at creation, while Agentic AI brings decision-making and execution&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most disruptive AI solutions over the next few years will combine GenAI with Agentic AI, and the key to achieving better business outcomes is knowing when to use one, the other, or both.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not every use case requires a full agentic system, but many businesses will be surprised at how many should.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GenAI alone:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GenAI excels at generating new content from existing data patterns, significantly boosting creativity and productivity across various domains. In software engineering, tools like GitHub Copilot are increasingly used to automate routine tasks such as generating boilerplate code. This enables engineers to avoid repetitive work and focus on more complex, high-impact challenges. While a human-in-the-loop remains essential to ensure code quality and alignment, GenAI is already improving engineering efficiency and accelerating delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In data science and engineering, GenAI supports teams facing surging data demands by improving accessibility and streamlining processing. Large language models (LLMs) help optimise how data is queried and managed, enabling faster and more accurate insights.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GenAI tools also enhance data analysis and application development by allowing users to interact with data through natural language processing (NLP), unlocking insights without requiring SQL expertise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the case of Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG), GenAI can efficiently access relevant data sources to assist customer service agents, or any customer-facing teams in responding to user queries with greater speed and accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agentic AI Alone for autonomous decision-making and actions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Agentic AI is best suited for automating complex, multi-step processes like supply chain management or customer service workflows.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tasks that require real-time decision-making and adaptation to changing environments benefit from Agentic AI.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, a logistics company can implement Agentic AI to autonomously manage inventory levels, reorder supplies, and optimise delivery routes based on real-time data. This leads to improved operational efficiency, reduced errors, and faster response times.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Merging GenAI and Agentic AI:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The combined approach is best used when your business requires systems that generate content and autonomously act upon it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The goal is to create end-to-end automated solutions that handle creation and execution, enhancing customer experiences through personalised interactions and proactive services.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example is when an e-commerce platform uses GenAI to create personalised product recommendations. Agentic AI automatically adjusts pricing and inventory based on customer behaviour and purchasing trends.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This combined approach delivers better customer engagement through personalised and timely interactions, helping the business achieve greater agility in responding to market demands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why human oversight matters in enterprise-scale AI systems:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In high-risk decision-making environments like finance or healthcare, AI systems aren’t always the right decision, but when they do make sense to implement, it’s essential to maintain a human-in-the-loop approach. This is especially important for models prone to errors or “hallucinations,” as inaccuracies can have significant consequences in these sectors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Industries governed by strict regulations often face challenges when implementing AI systems that lack transparency. The opaque nature of some AI models can hinder compliance efforts and erode stakeholder trust.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, deploying and maintaining advanced AI systems, such as GenAI and Agentic AI can be resource-intensive, requiring substantial computational power and specialised expertise. This complexity reinforces the need for human oversight to ensure smooth implementation and to mitigate potential risks that could strain organisational resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For organisations with limited resources, adopting simpler AI solutions that address specific needs without the complexity of full integration may be more practical. Certain tasks inherently require human intuition, empathy, and ethical judgment, which are qualities that AI currently cannot replicate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Strategic considerations for tech leaders&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As technology leaders, it’s essential to move beyond static GenAI chatbots and assess whether integrating GenAI and Agentic AI aligns with your organisation’s objectives. Evaluate the specific operational tasks within your organisation to determine if a combined AI approach is necessary or if a more straightforward solution would be more appropriate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ensure your organisation possesses the appropriate infrastructure and expertise to support complex AI systems. This includes robust data architectures, scalable computing resources, and a skilled workforce adept in AI technologies. Equally important is the prioritisation of AI solutions that offer transparency and explainability. In regulated industries, understanding the decision-making processes of AI systems is crucial to maintaining compliance and building trust with stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当今AI采用的一种普遍模式是，企业在Genai的功能上投资了大量投资，但是许多人未能将其与Agentic AI配对，在桌面上留下了巨大的价值。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这很重要，因为尽管Genai可以产生内容，想法或响应，但它不能对它们作用。但是，当与代理AI结合使用时，您的系统从反应性和及时驱动到以自主性和结果为导向。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文旨在帮助高级技术领导者更好地了解价值代理AI可以添加到现有的AI基础架构中，同时概述了关键注意事项以确定其实施是否符合您的业务需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;了解代理AI &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figig class =“ wp-block-image”&gt; &lt;img decoding =“ async” src =“ https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/ad_4nxdk_mtjsdbf-762dnxu9eesnbt3mnjaopxfvs8z3gquedcubpusi1dfo3 sw6nsivlj_lamarkzvcdtmvvsnrrwrwvshj9ovfxwcueae5rkbzcq1hzjx4hetnrrqbx35c5r1gx_cxq_ke = key = xgu2lqtqmaowwcmaowwcmaowwcmaowwcibutxnzqrw oke alt =“图像字幕：来自Markovate的代理AI架构的核心组件。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;图像标题：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a的代理AI架构的核心组件href =“ https://markovate.com/blog/agentic-ai-Architecture/?utm_source=chatgpt.com”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; markovate&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;代理AI系统旨在自主操作，感知他们的环境，做出决定并执行行动而无需连续的人类监督。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种自主权使企业能够简化运营，降低成本并提高可扩展性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上图说明了以下系统的功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;感知层：&lt;/strong&gt;该层涉及从各种来源（即传感器，相机，麦克风和数字输入）收集数据，以了解环境的当前状态。对于企业而言，这意味着对运营，客户互动和市场趋势的实时监控，促进积极的决策和对变化条件的快速响应。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;认知层：&lt;/strong&gt;一旦收集数据，认知层就会处理此信息以解释上下文，识别模式并确定最佳的作用方案。该分析可自动化复杂的决策过程，并减少对手动干预的依赖，从而最大程度地减少人为错误的风险。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;动作层：&lt;/strong&gt;确定适当的响应后，操作层执行决策，即调整系统参数，启动工作流或与利益相关者进行通信。这种能力可确保快速实施决策以提高运营效率。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终，代理AI系统配备了随着时间的推移改善的学习机制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过技术就像加强学习一样，系统从其行动的结果中学习，监督或无监督的学习，在此识别数据中的模式，AI也适应了新的情况并完善了其决策过程。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class =“ wp-block-heading”&gt; genai擅长创建，而代理AI带来了决策和执行&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;未来几年中最具破坏性的AI解决方案将与Genai与代理AI结合使用，实现更好的业务成果的关键是知道何时使用一种，另一个或两者兼而有之。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;并非每种用例都需要一个完整的代理系统，但是许多企业会对多少企业感到惊讶。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; genai：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Genai擅长从现有数据模式中生成新内容，从而显着提高各个领域的创造力和生产力。在软件工程中，诸如GitHub Copilot之类的工具越来越多地用于自动执行常规任务，例如生成样板代码。这使工程师能够避免重复的工作，并专注于更复杂，高影响力的挑战。尽管人类在确保代码质量和对齐方面仍然至关重要，但Genai已经在提高工程效率和加速交付。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在数据科学和工程学中，Genai通过改善可访问性和简化处理来支持面临飙升数据需求的团队。大型语言模型（LLMS）有助于优化如何查询和管理数据，从而更快，更准确。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; genai工具还通过允许用户通过自然语言处理（NLP）与数据进行交互，解锁见解而无需SQL专业知识来增强数据分析和应用程序的开发。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在检索功能生成（RAG）的情况下，Genai可以有效访问相关的数据源以帮助客户服务代理商或任何面向客户的团队以更高的速度和准确性响应用户查询。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;仅用于自主决策和行动的代理AI：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;代理AI最适合自动化复杂的多步骤过程，例如供应链管理或客户服务工作流程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需要实时决策和适应不断变化环境的任务受益于代理AI。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，物流公司可以实施代理AI来自主管理库存级别，重新订购供应并根据实时数据优化交货路线。这会提高操作效率，降低错误和更快的响应时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;合并Genai和Agent AI：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您的业务需要生成内容并自主对其作用的系统时，最好使用合并的方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目标是创建端到端自动化解决方案，以处理创建和执行，通过个性化INT增强客户体验磨难和主动服务。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个例子是，当电子商务平台使用Genai创建个性化产品建议时。代理AI会根据客户行为和购买趋势自动调整定价和库存。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种合并的方法通过个性化和及时的互动来提供更好的客户参与度，帮助企业在响应市场需求方面实现了更大的敏捷性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么人类的监督在企业规模的AI系统中很重要：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在金融或医疗保健等高风险的决策环境中，AI系统并不总是正确的决定，但是当它们确实有意义地实施时，维护人类的方法至关重要。这对于容易出现错误或“幻觉”的模型尤其重要，因为不准确可能会对这些部门产生重大影响。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;受严格法规管辖的行业在实施缺乏透明度的AI系统时通常会面临挑战。某些AI模型的不透明性质可以阻止合规性并侵蚀利益相关者的信任。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，部署和维护高级AI系统，例如Genai和AgentIC AI可能是资源密集的，需要实质性的计算能力和专业知识。这种复杂性加强了对人类监督的需求，以确保平稳的实施并减轻可能损害组织资源的潜在风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于资源有限的组织而言，采用更简单的AI解决方案，这些解决方案在没有完全集成的情况下解决特定需求可能更实用。某些任务固有地需要人类的直觉，同理心和道德判断，这是AI当前无法复制的素质。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;H3 class =“ WP-block-neading”&gt;技术领导者的战略考虑&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为技术领导者，必须超越静态Genai聊天机器人，并评估将Genai和Agent AI整合到您组织的目标中是否一致。评估组织内的特定操作任务，以确定合并的AI方法是否需要，或者更直接的解决方案更合适。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确保您的组织拥有适当的基础架构和专业知识来支持复杂的AI系统。这包括强大的数据体系结构，可扩展的计算资源以及熟练的AI技术熟练劳动力。同样重要的是提供透明度和解释性的AI解决方案的优先级。在受管制的行业中，了解AI系统的决策过程对于维持与利益相关者的合规性和建立信任至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Gear Up for the 5th Annual KCD Washington DC!】为第五届KCD华盛顿特区准备好准备！</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2025/08/16/gear-up-for-the-5th-annual-kcd-washington-dc/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We’re so thrilled to be organizing another year of cloud native community in the Nation’s Capital.&amp;nbsp; Past years have witnessed amazing presentations ranging from core Kubernetes topics to emerging trends in ML/AI, sustainability, virtual clusters and more.&amp;nbsp; This year promises to be even more amazing.&amp;nbsp; Our program is set, and includes two new innovations for our KCD:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For the first time, we’re offering a &lt;strong&gt;hands-on workshop&lt;/strong&gt; covering basic and intermediate topics on using &lt;strong&gt;Prometheus&lt;/strong&gt; in your observability practice. The curriculum covers 20-25% of the Linux Foundation’s Prometheus Certified Associate (PCA) course.&amp;nbsp; While this workshop does not lead to certification, and is not a substitute for the PCA course, it will give you a solid working knowledge for getting started and perhaps help you decide if you’d like to pursue certification separately – if you do, you’ll be ahead of the game with this solid foundation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We’re adding a &lt;strong&gt;government-focused cybersecurity keynote&lt;/strong&gt; by our special guest, Ashley Jones, Cybersecurity Advisor for Region III of the Department of Homeland Security, Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special Government &amp;amp; Cybersecurity Focus – and free admission for our government employee community members!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You won’t want to miss Ashley Jones’ keynote if you’re a cybersecurity professional or involved in government technology in any way. A limited number of free tickets will be available soon for our community members working for federal, state or local government agencies. You can request a free government ticket here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/aLNfRwpvFn3vQ5Vo8&#34;&gt;https://forms.gle/aLNfRwpvFn3vQ5Vo8&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plus our regular program is amazing!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;All of that rests on top of our regular program that includes presentations like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industry perspective: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Scaling Cloud Native: Reaching the Next 10 Million Users&lt;/em&gt; by Lin Sun at Solo.io&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;K8s in the Enterprise: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Silos to SIGs: Building Kubernetes Community in the Enterprise&lt;/em&gt; by Jason Stryker&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inclusivity: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unleash Your Inner Ally: Let’s Make Open Source Radically Welcoming!&lt;/em&gt; by Catherine Paganini and Christopher Khanoyan advocate for inclusivity in open source. (This talk willwith be interpreted for the hearing-impaired)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI):&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;AI on Lockdown: Deploying ML Pipelines in Controlled Government Spaces&lt;/em&gt; by Kumuda Sreenivasa&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;….and a whole lot more, which you can see in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://kcd-washington-dc-2025.sessionize.com/&#34;&gt;Full Schedule&lt;/a&gt; [https://kcd-washington-dc-2025.sessionize.com/]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And there’s plenty of food, drinks and networking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once again, we plan on hosting an evening &lt;strong&gt;Social Hour&lt;/strong&gt; free for all attendees where you can meet fellow attendees, speakers, and sponsors, in a relaxed, community environment while enjoying drinks and appetizers.&amp;nbsp; And, of course, you can enjoy all-day snacks, beverages (tea, coffee, soft drinks) and a nutritious lunch, all included with your one-day ticket.&amp;nbsp; That’s a pretty good value for $75, and to make it even more inviting, we’re offering 25% for all CNCF readers using code FRIENDS25 when you &lt;a href=&#34;https://bit.ly/KCDDC2025&#34;&gt;Get Tickets&lt;/a&gt; [https://bit.ly/KCDDC2025] today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;True community&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, we know the current job market and economic times are difficult for many of our most vulnerable community members.&amp;nbsp; We also want to encourage participation from under-represented minority (URM) groups.&amp;nbsp; Therefore, we’re proud to offer a number of free tickets to community members in need or who are in URM groups. You can request a free community ticket here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/aLNfRwpvFn3vQ5Vo8&#34;&gt;https://forms.gle/aLNfRwpvFn3vQ5Vo8&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we have been collaborating with the CNCF Deaf and Hard of Hearing Working Group to ensure this year’s event has live captioning throughout the day and interpretation services for our special presentation on inclusivity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;This year’s KCD Washington DC promises to be our biggest and best yet, packed with insightful sessions, hands-on workshops, inclusive community and invaluable networking opportunities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re also once again co-locating with DevOpsDays DC for their auspicious 10&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; editioniteration in the DMV, and third annual event joining forces with us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We look forward to seeing you on September 16&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; at the historic American Red Cross headquarters!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴在美国首都组织另一年的云土著社区。  过去几年见证了从核心库伯尼（Kubernetes）主题到ML/AI的新兴趋势，可持续性，虚拟集群等的惊人演讲。  今年有望变得更加惊人。  我们的程序已设置，并为我们的KCD提供了两个新的创新：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;第一次，我们提供了&lt;strong&gt;动手研讨会&lt;/strong&gt;涵盖有关在您的可观察性实践中使用&lt;strong&gt; Prometheus &lt;/strong&gt;的基本和中间主题。该课程涵盖了Linux基金会的Prometheus认证合伙人（PCA）课程的20-25％。  虽然该研讨会不会导致认证，也不能代替PCA课程，但它将为您提供扎实的工作知识，以便您开始分别寻求认证 - 如果您这样做，那么您将获得此坚实的基础。&lt;/li&gt;，您将领先于游戏。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我们正在添加&lt;strong&gt;政府以政府为中心的网络安全主题演讲&lt;/strong&gt;由我们的特别嘉宾，Ashley Jones，国土安全部，网络安全和基础设施安全局（CISA。）的网络安全顾问Ashley Jones，&lt;/li&gt;）&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;特别政府和网络安全重点 - 我们的政府员工社区成员免费入场！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您是网络安全专业人员或以任何方式参与政府技术，您将不想错过Ashley Jones的主题演讲。在联邦，州或地方政府机构工作的社区成员很快将提供有限的免费门票。您可以在此处要求免费的政府票：&lt;a href =“ https://forms.gle/alnfrwpvfn3vq5vo8”&gt; https://forms.gle/alnfrwpvfn3vq5vq5vo8 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;加上我们的常规程序很棒！&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;所有这些都取决于我们的常规计划，其中包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class =“ wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;行业视角：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;缩放云本机：lin sun in solo.io &lt;/li&gt;触及接下来的1000万用户&lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; k8s企业中的K8：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;从孤岛到信号：在企业中建立kubernetes社区&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; by Jason Stryker &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;包容性：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;释放了您的内在盟友：让凯瑟琳·帕加尼尼（Catherine Paganini）和克里斯托弗·哈诺诺（Christopher Khanoyan）倡导开源的开源欢迎！&lt;/em&gt;。 （这次演讲将以听力受损的解释）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;人工智能（AI）：锁定：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; ai：在受控的政府空间中部署ML管道&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; by kumuda sreenivasa &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;…。还有很多，您可以在&lt;a href =“ https://kcd-washington-dc-20255.sessionize.com/”&gt;完整的时间表&lt;/a&gt; [https://kcd-washington-dc-20255.sessionize.com/] &lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;和很多食物，D溜冰场和网络&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;再次，我们计划举办夜晚&lt;strong&gt;社交时光&lt;/strong&gt;免费的所有与会者，您可以在轻松的社区环境中与同伴，演讲者和赞助商见面，同时享受饮料和开胃菜。  而且，当然，您可以享受全天的小吃，饮料（茶，咖啡，软饮料）和营养午餐，全部包括一日票。  75美元的价值是一个相当不错的价值，为了使其更具吸引力，当您&lt;a href =“ https://bit.ly/kcddc2025”时，我们将为所有CNCF读取器提供25％的价格，以提供25％的读者。&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;真正的社区&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后但并非最不重要的一点是，我们知道当前的就业市场和经济时代对于许多最脆弱的社区成员来说都是困难的。  我们还希望鼓励来自代表性不足的少数民族（URM）群体的参与。  因此，我们很自豪地为有需要的社区成员或在URM团体中提供许多免费门票。您可以在此处请求免费的社区票：&lt;A href =“ https://forms.gle/alnfrwpvfn3vq5vo8”&gt; https://forms.gle/alnfrwpvfn3vq5vo8 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，我们还与CNCF聋哑人合作，并难以听力工作组，以确保今年的活动全天都有现场字幕，并为包容性的特别演讲提供了解释服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在结论中&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt;今年的KCD华盛顿特区有望成为我们迄今为止最大，最好的，充满有见地的会议，动手讲习班，包容性社区和宝贵的网络机会。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还再次与DevOpsdays DC共同订立了他们的吉祥10 &lt;sup&gt; th &lt;/sup&gt;在DMV中的版本，以及与我们的第三次年度活动。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们期待在9月16日与您与历史悠久的美国红十字会总部见面！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>