<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>CNCF - Blog</title>
    <link>http://rsshub.rssforever.com/cncf</link>
    <description>CNCF - Blog - Powered by RSSHub</description>
    <managingEditor>contact@rsshub.app (RSSHub)</managingEditor>
    <item>
      <title>【A look at the Cilium CNCF project journey report】看一下 Cilium CNCF 项目历程报告</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/12/a-look-at-the-cilium-cncf-project-journey-report/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We’re excited to share the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/cilium-project-journey-report/&#34;&gt;Cilium project journey report&lt;/a&gt;!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cilium.io/&#34;&gt;Cilium&lt;/a&gt; is an open source platform designed for cloud-native networking, security, and observability, leveraging &lt;a href=&#34;https://ebpf.io/&#34;&gt;eBPF&lt;/a&gt; technology. It provides secure, high-performance network connectivity and deep visibility for Kubernetes and other cloud environments. Cilium allows for complex and detailed network policies, load balancing, service mesh integration, and comprehensive network observability. It is widely used in production environments by companies like Adobe, Capital OneCapitolOne, and Google, offering robust support for large-scale deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since joining as an Incubating project in October 2021, Cilium has grown tremendously, graduating in under a year in 2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of the highlights of the report include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The number of contributing companies has increased by 90% since Cilium joined CNCF, from 533 to 1,011. This growth corresponds to a rise in individual contributors from 1,269 when it joined to 4,464 today, representing a 252% increase.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All time contributions to Cilium total over 506,400, an increase of 124% from 225,900 when it joined CNCF.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To date, more than 350 contributors from many backgrounds and motivations have added to and polished Cilium’s documentation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@eBPFCilium&#34;&gt;eBPF &amp;amp; Cilium Community YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt; offers 364 videos and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@cncf/search?query=Cilium&#34;&gt;CNCF’s YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt; offers a treasure trove of past Cilium content.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have a look at the full &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/cilium-project-journey-report/&#34;&gt;Cilium Project Journey Report&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about these accomplishments in more detail.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴分享&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/cilium-project-journey-report/&#34;&gt;Cilium 项目历程报告&lt;/a&gt;！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cilium.io/&#34;&gt;Cilium&lt;/a&gt; 是一个开源平台，专为云原生网络、安全性和可观察性而设计，利用&lt;a href=&#34;https:// ebpf.io/&#34;&gt;eBPF&lt;/a&gt; 技术。它为 Kubernetes 和其他云环境提供安全、高性能的网络连接和深度可见性。 Cilium 允许复杂而详细的网络策略、负载平衡、服务网格集成和全面的网络可观察性。它被 Adob​​e、Capital OneCapitolOne、Google 等公司广泛应用于生产环境，为大规模部署提供强大支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自 2021 年 10 月作为孵化项目加入以来，Cilium 取得了巨大发展，并于 2023 年在不到一年的时间内毕业。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;报告的一些要点包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自 Cilium 加入 CNCF 以来，贡献公司的数量增加了 90%，从 533 家增加到 1,011 家。这一增长对应于个人贡献者从加入时的 1,269 人增加到如今的 4,464 人，增长了 252%。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cilium 的所有贡献总数超过 506,400，比加入 CNCF 时的 225,900 增加了 124%。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;迄今为止，已有超过 350 位来自不同背景和动机的贡献者对 Cilium 的文档进行了补充和完善。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@eBPFCilium&#34;&gt;eBPF 和 Cilium 社区 YouTube 频道&lt;/a&gt;提供 364 个视频和&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube. com/@cncf/search?query=Cilium&#34;&gt;CNCF 的 YouTube 频道&lt;/a&gt; 提供过去 Cilium 内容的宝库。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查看完整的&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/reports/cilium-project-journey-report/&#34;&gt;Cilium 项目历程报告&lt;/a&gt;，了解有关这些成就的更多信息更详细地说。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 Day 0: Co-located events】KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 北美 2024 年第 0 天：同地举办活动</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/12/kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2024-day-0-co-located-events/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Thousands of KubeCon + CloudNativecon North America attendees braved cold rain – and even snow – to attend 16 co-located events in the Salt Palace Convention Center in Salt Lake City. With talks aimed at every level from beginner to expert covering a broad swath of cloud native technologies including AI, observability, eBPF, WebAssembly and Istio, the always popular co-located events were filled with enthusiastic participants.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a slice of how the day unfolded. Want to follow KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024 in real time? We’re on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/cloudnativecomputingfoundation/&#34;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/KubeCon_&#34;&gt;X (for KubeCon)&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/CloudNativeFdn&#34;&gt;X (for CNCF)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform Engineering Day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The advent of internal developer platforms promises to revolutionize every step of the development process and the excitement around IDPs was the focus of the Platform Engineering Day co-located presentations this year. In &lt;em&gt;Portals and platforms, two Ps in a pod? How great interfaces make for good operabilty&lt;/em&gt;, Abby Bangser, principal engineer, Syntasso, and Jorge Lainfiesta, reliability advocate, Rootly, talked about the universal challenges around creating development templates that can grow, scale and adapt to future needs. They also discussed the equally tough hurdle of getting developers to actually use those templates once they were created.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To ensure long term success, build templates that have “operability” in mind but also keep other “ilities” on the list including maintainability, usability and extensibility. Maintainability is achieved by looking at the past, while usability is how to allow for present adoption and extensibility will ensure developers can build something in the future they can’t even imagine today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wondering what your team should be demanding of your platform and tooling? Compare efforts with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-app-delivery.cncf.io/whitepapers/platform-eng-maturity-model/&#34;&gt;CNCF Platform Engineering Model&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native + Kubernetes AI Day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence can challenge everything we’ve come to believe about cloud native, and Autumn Moulder, director of infrastructure &amp;amp; security at Cohere, tackled that head on in her presentation, &lt;em&gt;From Supercomputing to serving: a case study delivering cloud native foundation models.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moulder offered her company’s story – taking an ML infrastructuring from one cloud to multi-cloud and many clusters in less than six months – as object lessons in how to take cloud native learnings and apply them in the AI world.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Five challenges made the company stronger, she explained. Cohere had to overcome GPU capacity constraints, GPU high failure rates, the reality of tightly coupled software and hardware, complex multi-team deployments, and managing allocation and utilization. Her team had to get creative and was particularly successful using &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/04/introducing-kueue/&#34;&gt;Kueue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native Startup Fest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To kick off an afternoon targeted at entrepreneurs, Kelsey Hightower, retired distinguished engineer and Megan Reynolds, VC at Vertex Ventures, hosted a fireside chat, &lt;em&gt;Startup resilience in a post-ZIRP (zero interest rate policy world)&lt;/em&gt;. To get things rolling, Hightower suggested founders ask some hard questions beginning with something super basic:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Does the product work? To answer this, have a customer try it out without any input at all; if they can’t get it up and running, it’s clear the product doesn’t work. Also, it’s important to be careful with the term customer, Hightower said. The word needs to be reserved for those who’ve paid for the product, he emphasized. Also, he said he’s a big believer in early stage companies taking field trips to potential customers and really immersing themselves in the business. Ask those potential customers what you should build, and how much they’d pay for it. And, of course, look to open source because it’s got a proven track record as a great place to start new businesses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Istio Day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For those wondering what it would be like to finally embrace service mesh, Confluent shared their experience during &lt;em&gt;Confluent’s service mesh journey – building security and reliability one sidecar at a time&lt;/em&gt;, with Adam Sayah,&lt;a href=&#34;http://solo.io/&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;Solo.io and Cody Ray, Confluent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The driving force behind Confluence’s decision to move to service mesh was a combination of factors, starting with the compliance fed ramp, as well as an internal push for zero trust, Ray explained. The company had a lot of moving parts to deal with including tens of thousands of Kubernetes clusters, hundreds of services and almost 5,000 connections that needed continuous security monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With such vast scale – and a need for increased productivity and security – Ray felt the time was right to make the case for service mesh, and his ROI calculations showed an expected savings of $3.5 million + per year, not to mention centralized observability, improved compliance and faster delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Watch the highlight reel from Day 0 of KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Get&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtube.com/watch?v=bHEBxXf7t6U%3Fsi%3DnO7aLMMwTi1jZst4&#34;&gt; the first look&lt;/a&gt; at some of the fun, networking, and learning that went on today!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数千名 KubeCon + CloudNativecon 北美与会者冒着冷雨甚至大雪参加了在盐湖城盐宫会议中心举办的 16 场同期活动。演讲针对从初学者到专家的各个级别，涵盖了广泛的云原生技术，包括人工智能、可观测性、eBPF、WebAssembly 和 Istio，这些一直很受欢迎的同地举办的活动充满了热情的参与者。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是这一天的部分内容。想要实时关注 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon North America 2024？我们在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.instagram.com/cloudnativecomputingfoundation/&#34;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/KubeCon_&#34;&gt;X（针对 KubeCon） &lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/CloudNativeFdn&#34;&gt;X（针对 CNCF）&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;平台工程日&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;内部开发者平台的出现有望彻底改变开发过程的每一步，而围绕 IDP 的兴奋是今年平台工程日同期演讲的焦点。在门户和平台中，一个 Pod 中有两个 P？ Syntasso 首席工程师 Abby Bangser 和 Rootly 可靠性倡导者 Jorge Lainfiesta 讨论了创建可扩展、扩展和适应未来需求的开发模板所面临的普遍挑战。他们还讨论了让开发人员在创建模板后实际使用这些模板的同样困难的障碍。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了确保长期成功，构建的模板应牢记“可操作性”，但也要保留列表中的其他“功能”，包括可维护性、可用性和可扩展性。可维护性是通过回顾过去来实现的，而可用性是如何允许当前的采用，而可扩展性将确保开发人员能够在未来构建他们今天无法想象的东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想知道您的团队应该对您的平台和工具提出什么要求？与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-app-delivery.cncf.io/whitepapers/platform-eng-maturity-model/&#34;&gt;CNCF 平台工程模型&lt;/a&gt;进行比较。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云原生 + Kubernetes 人工智能日&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能可以挑战我们对云原生的一切认知，Cohere 基础设施和安全总监 Autumn Moulder 在她的演讲中正面解决了这个问题，&lt;em&gt;从超级计算到服务：案例研究交付云原生基础模型。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moulder 讲述了她公司的故事——在不到六个月的时间内将机器学习基础设施从一个云转变为多云和多个集群——作为如何获取云原生知识并将其应用到人工智能世界的实例课程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;她解释说，五项挑战使公司变得更加强大。 Cohere 必须克服 GPU 容量限制、GPU 高故障率、软件和硬件紧密耦合的现实、复杂的多团队部署以及人为因素。老化分配和利用。她的团队必须发挥创造力，并且使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2022/10/04/introducing-kueue/&#34;&gt;Kueue&lt;/a&gt; 取得了特别成功。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云原生创业节&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了拉开针对企业家的下午的序幕，退休杰出工程师 Kelsey Hightower 和 Vertex Ventures 的风险投资人 Megan Reynolds 主持了一场炉边谈话，&lt;em&gt;后 ZIRP（零利率政策世界）中的初创企业复原力&lt; /em&gt;。为了让事情顺利进行，海塔尔建议创始人从一些非常基本的问题开始提出一些棘手的问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该产品有效吗？要回答这个问题，请让客户在没有任何输入的情况下尝试一下；如果他们无法启动并运行，很明显该产品不起作用。海托尔说，此外，谨慎对待“客户”一词也很重要。他强调说，这个词需要保留给那些已经为该产品付费的人。此外，他还表示，他坚信早期公司应该对潜在客户进行实地考察，并真正沉浸在业务中。询问那些潜在客户您应该构建什么，以及他们愿意为此支付多少钱。当然，还要关注开源，因为它作为开展新业务的好地方有着良好的记录。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Istio 日&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于那些想知道最终拥抱服务网格会是什么样子的人，Confluence 与 Adam Sayah 分享了他们在 Confluence 服务网格之旅中的经验 - 一次构建一个 sidecar 的安全性和可靠性&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;http://solo.io/&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Solo.io 和 Cody Ray，Confluence。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ray 解释道，Confluence 决定转向服务网格的驱动力是多种因素综合作用的结果，首先是合规性的提升，其次是内部对零信任的推动。该公司有许多移动部件需要处理，包括数万个 Kubernetes 集群、数百个服务和近 5,000 个需要持续安全监控的连接。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;鉴于规模如此之大，而且需要提高生产力和安全性，Ray 认为是时候提出服务网格的理由了，他的 ROI 计算显示每年预计可节省 350 万美元以上，更不用说集中化了可观察性、更高的合规性和更快的交付。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;观看 2024 年 KubeCon + CloudNativeCon 北美大会第 0 天的精彩片段！&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtube.com/watch?v=bHEBxXf7t6U%3Fsi%3DnO7aLMMwTi1jZst4&#34;&gt;抢先了解&lt;/a&gt;今天发生的一些有趣的事情、社交和学习！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A beginners guide to contributing to CNCF open source projects】为 CNCF 开源项目做出贡献的初学者指南</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/11/a-beginners-guide-to-contributing-to-cncf-open-source-projects/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redpill-linpro.com/en/blogs/agile-it-operations-cloud-and-devops/beginners-guide-contributing-cncf-open-source-projects&#34;&gt;Redpill Linpro blog&lt;/a&gt; by Amelie Löwe&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Open source is not just a way of building software; it’s a philosophy that promotes collaboration, transparency, and community. Many of us use open source every day either in our professional life or in our hobby projects. By sharing code openly, developers from all over the world can contribute their skills, knowledge, and creativity to projects that impact millions of users daily.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, we’ll explore how to get involved in&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;CNCF (Cloud Native Computing Foundation)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;open source projects, what knowledge you need to contribute, and how to become part of this community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;First of all, what’s in it for me?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are a few perks of contributing to open source, aside from making a positive global impact and ensuring software remains freely accessible for anyone:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Gaining important skills, knowledge and learning from a global community of developers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fixing that irritating bug or translation issue that has been bugging you for ages.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Being able to add needed features to the software you’ve been using.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Rather than implementing workarounds in your software, which relies on an open-source project, consider addressing the issue at its root. By fixing the underlying problem, you can ensure that your software remains stable for the foreseeable future.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Participating in open-source projects can significantly enhance your personal growth and may also bolster your prospects in job hunting or exploring intriguing opportunities in the tech field.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;But I’m not a developer, can I still help?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, there are several important aspects of open source that Non-Code Contributors can help with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documentation and Guides:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Writing clear and comprehensive documentation can significantly impact a project’s usability and is an important part of the software’s lifecycle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UX/UI Design:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Elevate the user experience by enhancing the visual and interactive aspects of the project. Designing user interfaces, improving accessibility, and ensuring a seamless, intuitive experience not only boosts overall software quality but also aids developers in coding new features more effectively.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bug Reports and Issue Management:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;By creating, filing, and updating bug reports you help developers with the testing of the software and make sure that annoying bugs get fixed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Translation services:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Translating project documentation, user interfaces, and other communication materials into different languages enhances accessibility and extends the global reach of the open source project.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Engagement:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Actively participate in community discussions, welcome new members, and contribute to a positive and inclusive atmosphere. Your input can be invaluable in shaping the project’s direction and fostering a collaborative environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderation and Civility:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Volunteer to moderate discussions and ensure a civil and respectful tone within the community. This encourages a welcoming space for everyone.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Okay, now I can finally get started, right?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not quite, there are still some important prerequisites to keep in mind before contributing to open source projects:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Both technical and non-technical contributors should understand some basic&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-for-beginners/&#34;&gt;Git&lt;/a&gt;, pull requests, and issues. Version control management tools are usually used to manage contributions and track changes of contributors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You need programming language proficiency and familiarity with testing frameworks if you would like to become a technical contributor. What kind of programming language is needed depends on the project you are interested in.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It’s great to have some knowledge about basic security measures like SSH keys and 2FA(two-factor authentication). These measures ensure secure contributions in the projects. You can usually find information about the security measures in the project documentation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Already familiar with this? Then let’s go!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are the 5 steps of getting started with contributing to CNCF technologies:&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join the Community&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;– The first step to contribute to open source is to join the community around the technology. Most open source projects have slack or GitHub repositories where you can find information on how to contribute. It’s important to read and follow the community’s guidelines, to ensure a successful collaboration.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose a Project&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;– Selecting the right project for you is critical. CNCF hosts numerous open source projects in the global&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;cloud-native ecosystem.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;Explore the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/contributors/projects/&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Contributor page&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to discover an extensive list of projects available for your contribution, categorized by programming language and maturity level. Consider your interests and skill level when choosing a project. Being familiar or regularly using the open source project before contributing is essential. This helps you with the understanding of the architecture and software functionality. If you use the technology regularly you also gain insights into the project’s bugs, features and of course how to improve them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documentation&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;– Before contributing, take some time to properly read the project’s documentation, including all README files and contribution guidelines. Explore potential forums and open/closed issues and pull requests. This knowledge will provide insights into the project’s context, goals, and challenges, and will also guide you for example on the intricacies of writing effective pull requests.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborate with Others/Asking for Help&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;– Open source is all about coming together and working as a team. Reach out to other contributors for help or feedback if needed. Help other developers by reviewing code, providing feedback, and testing their changes. Building relationships with contributors and improving skills through collaboration is key. However it is important to remember to attempt to learn before seeking assistance. Many open source contributors do this in their spare time so try to limit seeking general mentoring of programming languages.&amp;nbsp;Don’t feel discouraged if you don’t get help immediately, usually there is a time zone difference and they might not have seen your requests just yet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contribute&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;– It’s time to do the work! Brew yourself a large cup of coffee and dive right in. It’s best to quickly rip off that bandage and start coding. Tackling a series of smaller issues or tasks will boost your confidence, enhancing your skills and knowledge along the way. Submitting a pull request for testing and general feedback, even if the problem isn’t fully resolved, is preferable to not submitting one at all. Other developers can pick up where you left off or help you continue on your journey.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Here are some other great tips and tricks:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start Small&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For beginners, starting small is crucial. Look for easier issues or small features to gain familiarity with the project’s codebase. As you gain experience, then you can tackle the more challenging tasks. Remember, every contribution counts!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Glossary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you stumble upon words or acronyms that seem outlandish to you then&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/resources/glossary/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;is a great glossary that covers frequently used CNCF-specific terms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explore and join a Mentoring WG (Mentoring Working Group)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Through the&lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/about/mentoring/&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;Mentoring WG,&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;individuals can explore various mentorship opportunities. Mentors, who are typically experienced contributors in the CNCF community, offer guidance and support to mentees looking to enhance their skills.&lt;br&gt;This is a great opportunity if you are new to contributing to Open source and cloud-native technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mentoring WG also manages the following mentorship initiatives:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mentorship.lfx.linuxfoundation.org/&#34;&gt;LFX Mentorship (ex-CommunityBridge)&lt;/a&gt;: mentoring initiative by the Linux Foundation –&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/mentoring/tree/main/programs/lfx-mentorship#readme&#34;&gt;details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/&#34;&gt;Google Summer of Code&lt;/a&gt;: mentoring program for the open source beginners –&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/mentoring/tree/main/programs/summerofcode#readme&#34;&gt;details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/season-of-docs&#34;&gt;Google Season of Docs&lt;/a&gt;: mentoring initiative for the technical writers –&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/mentoring/tree/main/programs/seasonofdocs#readme&#34;&gt;details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.outreachy.org/&#34;&gt;Outreachy&lt;/a&gt;: mentoring initiative for the communities traditionally underrepresented in tech –&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/mentoring/tree/main/programs/outreachy#readme&#34;&gt;details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Embarking on the CNCF open source journey opens doors to collaborative innovation. Whether a developer or non-code contributor, the benefits extend beyond the technical realm, fostering skill growth and global learning. Collaboration is key, so seek assistance and contribute at your own pace. Each contribution contributes to the collective progress of open source. Embrace the journey, as well as the learning experiences, and become an integral part of this dynamic ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Happy contributing!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://www.redpill-linpro.com/sites/default/files/styles/square/public/2024-02/Amelie-lowe%20copy.jpg?itok=4H-KYFEG&#34; alt=&#34;head shot&#34; style=&#34;width:115px;height:auto&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Written by&amp;nbsp;Amelie Löwe&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初发布于&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redpill-linpro.com/en/blogs/agile-it-operations-cloud-and-devops/beginners-guide-contributing -cncf-open-source-projects&#34;&gt;Redpill Linpro 博客&lt;/a&gt; 作者：Amelie Löwe&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;开源不仅仅是构建软件的一种方式；这是一种促进协作、透明度和社区的理念。我们中的许多人每天都在职业生活或业余爱好项目中使用开源。通过公开共享代码，来自世界各地的开发者可以将他们的技能、知识和创造力贡献给每天影响数百万用户的项目。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇博文中，我们将探讨如何参与&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;CNCF（云原生计算基金会）&lt;/a&gt;开源项目、什么您需要贡献的知识，以及如何成为这个社区的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;首先，这对我来说有什么好处？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了产生积极的全球影响和确保任何人都可以免费访问软件之外，以下是为开源做出贡献的一些好处：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;从全球开发者社区获得重要的技能、知识和学习。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;修复困扰您多年的恼人错误或翻译问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;能够向您一直使用的软件添加所需的功能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;不要在依赖于开源项目的软件中实施变通办法，而是考虑从根本上解决问题。通过解决根本问题，您可以确保您的软件在可预见的未来保持稳定。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;参与开源项目可以显着促进您的个人成长，还可以增强您在技术领域求职或探索有趣机会的前景。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;但我不是开发者，我还能提供帮助吗？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当然，非代码贡献者可以在开源的几个重要方面提供帮助：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;文档和指南&lt;/strong&gt;：编写清晰、全面的文档可以显着影响项目的可用性，并且是软件生命周期的重要组成部分。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UX/UI 设计&lt;/strong&gt;：通过增强项目的视觉和交互方面来提升用户体验。设计用户界面、提高可访问性并确保无缝、直观的体验不仅可以提高整体软件质量，还可以帮助开发人员更有效地编写新功能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;错误报告和问题管理&lt;/strong&gt;：通过创建、归档和更新错误报告，您可以帮助开发人员测试软件并确保修复烦人的错误。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;翻译服务&lt;/strong&gt;：翻译将项目文档、用户界面和其他交流材料翻译成不同的语言可以增强可访问性并扩展开源项目的全球影响力。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;社区参与&lt;/strong&gt;：积极参与社区讨论、欢迎新成员并营造积极、包容的氛围。您的意见对于确定项目方向和营造协作环境非常宝贵。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;节制和文明&lt;/strong&gt;：自愿主持讨论并确保社区内保持文明和尊重的基调。这为每个人提供了一个欢迎的空间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;好吧，现在我终于可以开始了，对吧？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不完全是，在为开源项目做出贡献之前，仍然需要牢记一些重要的先决条件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;技术和非技术贡献者都应该了解一些基本的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-for-beginners/&#34;&gt;Git&lt;/a&gt;、pull请求和问题。版本控制管理工具通常用于管理贡献并跟踪贡献者的变更。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果您想成为技术贡献者，您需要精通编程语言并熟悉测试框架。需要哪种编程语言取决于您感兴趣的项目。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果能够了解 SSH 密钥和 2FA（双因素身份验证）等基本安全措施的知识，那就太好了。这些措施确保了项目的安全贡献。您通常可以在项目文档中找到有关安全措施的信息。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;已经熟悉这个了吗？那我们走吧！&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是开始为 CNCF 技术做出贡献的 5 个步骤：&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol类=“wp-block-list”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;加入社区&lt;/strong&gt; – 为开源做出贡献的第一步是加入技术社区。大多数开源项目都有 Slack 或 GitHub 存储库，您可以在其中找到有关如何贡献的信息。为了确保成功的合作，阅读并遵循社区指南非常重要。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;选择项目&lt;/strong&gt; - 选择适合您的项目至关重要。 CNCF 在全球&lt;a href=&#34;https://landscape.cncf.io/&#34;&gt;云原生生态系统&lt;/a&gt;中托管着众多开源项目。探索&lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf。 io/contributors/projects/&#34;&gt;云原生贡献者页面&lt;/a&gt;，查找可供您贡献的详细项目列表，按编程语言和成熟度级别进行分类。选择项目时请考虑您的兴趣和技能水平。在做出贡献之前熟悉或定期使用开源项目至关重要。这可以帮助您对架构和软件功能的理解。如果您定期使用该技术，您还可以深入了解项目的错误、功能，当然还有如何改进它们。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;文档&lt;/strong&gt; – 在贡献之前，请花一些时间正确阅读项目的文档，包括所有自述文件和贡献指南。探索潜在的论坛以及开放/封闭的问题和拉取请求。这些知识将帮助您深入了解项目的背景、目标和挑战，并且还将指导您了解编写有效拉取请求的复杂性等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;与他人协作/寻求帮助&lt;/strong&gt; - 开源就是团结起来并作为一个团队工作。如果需要，请向其他贡献者寻求帮助或反馈。通过审查代码、提供反馈和测试他们的更改来帮助其他开发人员。与贡献者建立关系并通过协作提高技能是关键。然而，重要的是要记住在寻求帮助之前尝试学习。许多开源贡献者在业余时间这样做，因此尽量限制寻求编程语言的一般指导。 如果您没有立即获得帮助，请不要灰心，通常存在时区差异，他们可能还没有看到您的请求。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;贡献&lt;/strong&gt; – 是时候开始工作了！给自己泡一大杯咖啡，然后投入其中。最好快速撕掉绷带并开始编码。解决一系列较小的问题或任务将增强您的信心，并在此过程中增强您的技能和知识。即使问题没有完全解决，提交拉取请求以进行测试和一般反馈也比根本不提交要好。其他开发者可以从您上次停下的地方继续您的旅程，或者帮助您继续您的旅程。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;以下是一些其他很棒的提示和技巧：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;从小事做起&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于初学者来说，从小事做起至关重要。寻找更简单的问题或小功能来熟悉项目的代码库。当您获得经验时，您就可以解决更具挑战性的任务。请记住，每一次贡献都很重要！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;术语表&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您偶然发现一些对您来说很奇怪的单词或首字母缩略词，那么&lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/resources/glossary/&#34;&gt;这里&lt;/a&gt;是一个很棒的词汇表，涵盖了常用的术语CNCF 特定术语。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;探索并加入指导 WG（指导工作组）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过&lt;a href=&#34;https://contribute.cncf.io/about/mentoring/&#34;&gt;指导工作组&lt;/a&gt;，个人可以探索各种指导机会。导师通常是 CNCF 社区中经验丰富的贡献者，他们为希望提高技能的学员提供指导和支持。&lt;br&gt;这是一个很棒的机会如果您刚开始为开源和云原生技术做出贡献，那么这是一个机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;指导工作组还管理以下指导计划：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://mentorship.lfx.linuxfoundation.org/&#34;&gt;LFX 指导计划（前 CommunityBridge）&lt;/a&gt;：Linux 基金会的指导计划 - &lt;a href=&#34;https:// github.com/cncf/mentoring/tree/main/programs/lfx-mentorship#readme&#34;&gt;详细信息&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/&#34;&gt;Google Summer of Code&lt;/a&gt;：针对开源初学者的指导计划 - &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ cncf/mentoring/tree/main/programs/summerofcode#readme&#34;&gt;详细信息&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.google.com/season-of-docs&#34;&gt;Google 文档季&lt;/a&gt;：针对技术作家的指导计划 – &lt;a href=&#34;https:// github.com/cncf/mentoring/tree/main/programs/seasonofdocs#readme&#34;&gt;详细信息&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.outreachy.org/&#34;&gt;Outreachy&lt;/a&gt;：针对传统上在科技领域代表性不足的社区的指导计划 - &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf /mentoring/tree/main/programs/outreachy#readme&#34;&gt;详细信息&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;踏上 CNCF 开源之旅为协作创新打开了大门。无论是开发人员还是非代码贡献者，其好处都超出了技术领域，促进了技能增长和全球学习。协作是关键，因此请寻求帮助并按照自己的节奏做出贡献。每一项贡献都为开源的集体进步做出了贡献。拥抱这段旅程和学习经历，成为这个动态生态系统不可或缺的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;祝您贡献愉快！&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://www.redpill-linpro.com/sites/default/files/styles/square/public/2024 -02/Amelie-lowe%20copy.jpg?itok=4H-KYFEG&#34; alt=&#34;头像&#34; style=&#34;width:115px;height:auto&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作者：艾米莉·洛威&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to ace the Prometheus Certified Associate (PCA) exam】如何通过 Prometheus Certified Associate (PCA) 考试</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/07/how-to-ace-the-prometheus-certified-associate-pca-exam/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Community post originally published on &lt;a href=&#34;https://faun.pub/how-to-ace-pca-prometheus-certified-associate-exam-6485fbe5789f&#34;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt; by Giorgi Keratishvili&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*7qsoqjiCKrUx0-RDKKzfwg.png&#34; alt=&#34;PCA image&#34; style=&#34;width:900px;height:auto&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;7019&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;724c&#34;&gt;If you have worked on&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes production systems&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;at any time during the last&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;10 years&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and needed to check your pods or application uptime, resource consumption, HTTP error rates, and needed to observe them for a certain period of time, most probably you have been using the&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Prometheus&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;stack. If you want to extend your knowledge of&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;observability&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;monitoring&lt;/strong&gt;, then this exam is exactly for you because it does not focus only on Prometheus but also on general concepts such as SLA, SLO, SLI, how to structure alerting, and best practices for observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;3bf3&#34;&gt;Besides that, Prometheus is&amp;nbsp;one of the first open source projects&amp;nbsp;that joined the CNCF after Kubernetes and has since been one of the most preferred tools for monitoring and observability in containerized environments. It also incorporates other open source projects such as&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;for visualization and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;for observability, which greatly impact the whole industry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;0925&#34;&gt;Who should take this exam?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d6c1&#34;&gt;As mentioned above, the majority of the time we see Prometheus in Kubernetes or containerized environments, but nonetheless, it is not limited only to containerized scenarios. Overall, if we have any production system, we must have some kind of monitoring tool.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;If we don’t have observability, we are blind&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;and when things go wrong — and they will — it’s just a matter of time before it happens, you will appreciate that you could see more and on time everything.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;963e&#34;&gt;Regarding persons who would benefit&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;SysAdmins/Dev/Ops/SRE/Managers/Patform engineers&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;or anyone who is doing anything on production should consider it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*Cs7JWMoQKhLVkhkT.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34; style=&#34;width:465px;height:auto&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;af01&#34;&gt;Exam Format and PSI Proctored Exam Tips&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4549&#34;&gt;So, are we fired up like a torch, eager to spot any degradation in your systems and wanting to pass the exam? Then, we have a long path ahead until we reach this point. First, we need to understand what kind of exam it is compared to&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CKAD&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CKA&lt;/strong&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;CKS&lt;/strong&gt;. This is the first exam where the CNCF has adopted&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;multiple-choice questions&lt;/strong&gt;, and compared to other multiple-choice exams, this one, I would say, is not easy-peasy. However, it is still qualified as pre-professional, on par with the&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;KCNA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KCSA&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;6990&#34;&gt;This exam is conducted online, proctored similarly to other Kubernetes certifications, and is facilitated by&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;PSI&lt;/strong&gt;. As someone who has taken more than 15 exams with PSI, I can say that every time it’s a new journey. I&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;HIGHLY ADVISE joining the exam 30 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;before taking the test because there are pre-checks of ID, and the room in which you are taking it needs to be checked for exam criteria. Please check these two links for the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/exam-rules-and-policies&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;exam rules&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/taking-the-exam&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSI portal guide&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;2676&#34;&gt;You’ll have&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;90 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;to answer&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;60 questions&lt;/strong&gt;, which is generally considered sufficient time. Be prepared for some questions that can be quite tricky. I marked a couple of them for review and would advise doing the same because sometimes you could find a hint or partial answers in the next question. By this way, you could refer back to those questions. Regarding pricing, the exam costs&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;$250&lt;/strong&gt;, but you can&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;often&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;find it at a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;discount&lt;/strong&gt; during Black Friday promotions or near dates for CNCF events like KubeCon, Open Source Summit, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*mLVgSUK5oX-UDIzD.png&#34; alt=&#34;Prometheus logo&#34; style=&#34;width:343px;height:auto&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;7a6d&#34;&gt;The Path of Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;2765&#34;&gt;At this point, we understand what we have signed up for and are ready to dedicate time to training, but where should we start? Before taking this exam, I had a good experience with Kubernetes and its ecosystem and had experience with Prometheus but only for things that I needed. I did not delve deeper, yet I still learned a lot from this exam.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;8f98&#34;&gt;Let break down&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Domains &amp;amp; Competencies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-preformatted&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Observability Concepts 18%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Metrics&lt;br&gt;    Understand logs and events&lt;br&gt;    Tracing and Spans&lt;br&gt;    Push vs Pull&lt;br&gt;    Service Discovery&lt;br&gt;    Basics of SLOs, SLAs, and SLIs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Prometheus Fundamentals 20%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    System Architecture&lt;br&gt;    Configuration and Scraping&lt;br&gt;    Understanding Prometheus Limitations&lt;br&gt;    Data Model and Labels&lt;br&gt;    Exposition Format&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**PromQL 28%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Selecting Data&lt;br&gt;    Rates and Derivatives&lt;br&gt;    Aggregating over time&lt;br&gt;    Aggregating over dimensions&lt;br&gt;    Binary operators&lt;br&gt;    Histograms&lt;br&gt;    Timestamp Metrics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Instrumentation and Exporters 16%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Client Libraries&lt;br&gt;    Instrumentation&lt;br&gt;    Exporters&lt;br&gt;    Structuring and naming metrics&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Alerting &amp;amp; Dashboarding 18%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;    Dashboarding basics&lt;br&gt;    Configuring Alerting rules&lt;br&gt;    Understand and Use Alertmanager&lt;br&gt;    Alerting basics (when, what, and why)&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;6e54&#34;&gt;At first glance, this list might seem too simple and easy; however, we need to learn the fundamentals of observability first in order to understand higher-level concepts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;9a60&#34;&gt;Understanding Observability&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;300e&#34;&gt;Observability is a measure of how well the internal states of a system can be inferred from knowledge of its external outputs. In the context of system engineering and IT operations, observability is crucial for diagnosing issues and ensuring that all parts of the system are functioning as expected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d86f&#34;&gt;The Pillars of Observability&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Logs: These are immutable records that describe discrete events that have happened over time. Logs are useful for understanding what happened in a system after an event.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Metrics: These are numerical values that measure some aspect of a system over intervals of time. Metrics are vital for understanding the performance of a system and for making comparisons over time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Traces: These are records of the full paths or sequences of events that occur as requests flow through a system. Tracing helps in identifying how requests propagate through a system and where delays or issues arise.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*fLO7pJnCaWwiIGxZ.png&#34; alt=&#34;bubble chart with observability, traces, logs and metrics&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;a58e&#34;&gt;Some Key Concepts to Remember:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLA (Service Level Agreement):&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;An SLA is the agreement you establish with your clients or users, defining the level of service they can expect.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLO (Service Level Objective):&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;SLOs are specific, measurable goals your team must achieve to meet the SLA. They represent the performance targets you aim to reach.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLI (Service Level Indicator)&lt;/strong&gt;: SLIs are the actual metrics or measurements that indicate the real-time performance of your system. They are used to assess compliance with SLOs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pull:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Metric scraping is initiated by Prometheus. Prometheus queries target endpoints to collect metrics at regular intervals.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Push:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Metrics are published by the application to an endpoint (e.g., Pushgateway). This method allows applications to push metrics when they are generated.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trace&lt;/strong&gt;: A trace represents a sequence of operations that together form a unique transaction handled by an application and its constituent services. Traces help in understanding the flow of requests and identifying bottlenecks or issues in your system.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Span&lt;/strong&gt;: A span, in the context of tracing, represents a single operation within a trace. It provides detailed information about the duration and context of that operation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rule Types:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;In Prometheus, there are two types of rules.&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Record rules&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;help precompute frequently needed or computationally expensive expressions, while&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;alert rule&lt;/strong&gt;s enable you to define alert conditions using PromQL queries.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meta-Monitoring:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Comprehend the concept of meta-monitoring, which involves monitoring the Prometheus instances themselves.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;f154&#34;&gt;Key Learning Objectives:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PromQL&lt;/strong&gt;: PromQL is pivotal you can put your skills to the test by exploring metrics&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/prometheus/latest/querying/examples/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and delving into Prometheus’s basic system architecture&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/introduction/overview/#architecture&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, grasp the fundamentals of Prometheus’s basic functions&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/prometheus/latest/querying/functions/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AlertManager&lt;/strong&gt;: You need to understand AlertManager and its functionalities are crucial. Gain insights into AlertManager features&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/alerting/latest/alertmanager/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and visualize your AlertManager routes&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/webtools/alerting/routing-tree-editor/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exporters&lt;/strong&gt;: Familiarize yourself with exporters like node_exporter and blackbox_exporter.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*yN90oQ-nfP8hbpxd.png&#34; alt=&#34;map&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b570&#34;&gt;You can explore and learn about PCA Certification and related topics freely through the following GitHub repositories which I have used&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/walidshaari/PrometheusCertifiedAssociate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;walidshaari/PrometheusCertifiedAssociate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/edgarpf/prometheus-certified-associate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;edgarpf/prometheus-certified-associate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Al-HusseinHameedJasim/prometheus-certified-associate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Al-HusseinHameedJasim/prometheus-certified-associate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/edgarpf/prometheus-certified-associate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://github.com/edgarpf/prometheus-certified-associate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;f0de&#34;&gt;For structured and comprehensive PCA exam preparation, consider investing in these paid course from KodeKloud where they providy play ground I used it in preparation and it helped a lot&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kodekloud.com/courses/prometheus-certified-associate-pca&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;KodeKloud PCA Certification Course&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.promlabs.com/trainings/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://training.promlabs.com/trainings/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://robustperception.teachable.com/p/introduction-to-prometheus&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://robustperception.teachable.com/p/introduction-to-prometheus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;0235&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ffa5&#34;&gt;The exam is not easy among other certs. I would rank it in this order&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/CGOA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS&lt;/strong&gt;. After conducting the exam, you will receive grading within 24 hours and after passing the exam it feels pretty satisfying. Overall, I hope it was informative and useful 🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*ENet0gQW5vbAyT1J9U-lwQ.png&#34; alt=&#34;PCA certificate&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/tag/prometheus?source=post_page-----6485fbe5789f--------------------------------&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;社区帖子最初由 Giorgi 在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://faun.pub/how-to-ace-pca-prometheus-certified-associate-exam-6485fbe5789f&#34;&gt;Medium&lt;/a&gt; 上发布克拉蒂什维利&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*7qsoqjiCKrUx0-RDKKzfwg.png &#34; alt=&#34;PCA 图像&#34; style=&#34;width:900px;height:auto&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;7019&#34;&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;724c&#34;&gt;如果您在过去&lt;strong&gt;10年&lt;/strong&gt;的任何时间都曾使用过&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes生产系统&lt;/strong&gt;，并且需要检查您的 Pod 或应用程序的正常运行时间、资源消耗情况、HTTP 错误率，并且需要在一段时间内观察它们，很可能您一直在使用 &lt;strong&gt;Prometheus&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;Grafana&lt;/strong&gt; 堆栈。如果您想扩展&lt;strong&gt;可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;监控&lt;/strong&gt;方面的知识，那么这项考试非常适合您，因为它不仅关注 Prometheus，还关注诸如 SLA、 SLO、SLI、如何构建警报以及可观察性的最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;3bf3&#34;&gt;除此之外，Prometheus 是继 Kubernetes 之后最早加入 CNCF 的开源项目之一，自此成为容器化环境中监控和可观察性最受欢迎的工具之一。它还整合了其他开源项目，例如用于可视化的 &lt;strong&gt;Grafana&lt;/strong&gt; 和用于可观察性的 &lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry &lt;/strong&gt;，这对整个行业产生了巨大影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;0925&#34;&gt;谁应该参加这项考试？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;d6c1&#34;&gt;如上所述，我们大多数时候在 Kubernetes 或容器化环境中看到 Prometheus，但它不仅限于容器化场景。总的来说，如果我们有任何生产系统，我们就必须有某种监控工具。 &lt;strong&gt;如果我们没有可观察性，我们就是盲目的&lt;/strong&gt;，当事情出错时（它们确实会出错），它发生只是时间问题，您会感激自己可以看到更多、准时的一切.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;963e&#34;&gt;对于&lt;strong&gt;SysAdmins/Dev/Ops/SRE/Managers/Patform 工程师&lt;/strong&gt;受益的人员或任何在生产中从事任何工作的人都应该考虑它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*Cs7JWMoQKhLVkhkT.jpg&#34; alt =&#34;图像&#34; style=&#34;width:465px;height:auto&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;af01&#34;&gt;考试格式和 PSI 监考考试提示&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;4549&#34;&gt;那么，我们是否像火炬一样兴奋，渴望发现您系统中的任何退化并希望通过考试？然后，在到达这一点之前，我们还有很长的路要走。首先，我们需要了解一下它与&lt;strong&gt;CKAD&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;CKA&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;CKS&lt;/strong&gt;相比是一种考试。这是 CNCF 第一次采用&lt;strong&gt;多项选择题&lt;/strong&gt;的考试，与其他多项选择题考试相比，我想说，这次考试并不容易。不过，它仍然具有与&lt;strong&gt;朝中社&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;KCSA&lt;/strong&gt;同等的预科资格。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;6990&#34;&gt;此考试在线进行，监考方式与其他 Kubernetes 认证类似，并由 &lt;strong&gt;PSI&lt;/strong&gt; 提供协助。作为参加过超过 15 次 PSI 考试的人，我可以说每次都是新的旅程。我&lt;strong&gt;强烈建议在考试前 30 分钟参加考试&lt;/strong&gt;，因为需要预先检查身份证件，并且需要检查您参加考试的房间是否符合考试标准。请检查这两个链接以获取 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/exam-rules-and-policies&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank &#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;考试规​​则&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.linuxfoundation.org/tc-docs/certification/lf-handbook2/take-the-exam&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PSI 门户指南&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;2676&#34;&gt;您将有&lt;strong&gt;90 分钟&lt;/strong&gt;时间来回答&lt;strong&gt;60 个问题&lt;/strong&gt;，这通常被认为是足够的时间。为一些可能相当棘手的问题做好准备。我标记了其中几个以供审查，并建议您也这样做，因为有时您可以在下一个问题中找到提示或部分答案。这样你就可以回过头来看看这些问题了。关于定价，考试费用&lt;strong&gt; 250 美元&lt;/strong&gt;，但您&lt;strong&gt;通常&lt;/strong&gt;可以在黑色星期五促销期间或临近 CNCF 活动（例如 KubeCon）期间以&lt;strong&gt;折扣&lt;/strong&gt;找到它、开源峰会等&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image is-resized&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*mLVgSUK5oX-UDIzD.png &#34; alt=&#34;普罗米修斯标志&#34; style=&#34;width:343px;height:auto&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;7a6d&#34;&gt;学习之路&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;2765&#34;&gt;至此，我们了解了自己注册的目的，并准备好投入时间进行培训，但我们应该从哪里开始呢？在参加这次考试之前，我对 Kubernetes 及其生态系统有很好的体验，并且对 Prometheus 有很好的体验，但仅限于我需要的东西。我没有深入研究，但我还是从这次考试中学到了很多东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;8f98&#34;&gt;让我们分解一下&lt;strong&gt;领域和能力&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-preformatted&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**可观测性概念 18%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 指标&lt;br&gt; 了解日志和事件&lt;br&gt; 跟踪和跨度&lt;br&gt; 推与拉&lt;br&gt; 服务发现&lt;br&gt; SLO、SLA 和 SLI 基础知识&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Prometheus 基础知识 20%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 系统架构&lt;br&gt; 配置和抓取&lt;br&gt; 了解 Prometheus 限制&lt;br&gt; 数据模型和标签&lt;br&gt; 说明格式&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong &gt;**PromQL 28%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 选择数据&lt;br&gt; 汇率和导数&lt;br&gt; 随时间聚合&lt;br&gt; 维度聚合&lt;br&gt; 二进制运算符&lt;br&gt; 直方图&lt;br&gt; 时间戳指标&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**仪表和导出器 16%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 客户端库&lt;br&gt; 仪表&lt;br&gt; 导出器&lt;br&gt; 结构化和命名指标&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**警报和仪表板 18%**&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; 仪表板基础知识&lt;br&gt; 配置警报规则&lt;br&gt; 了解和使用Alertmanager&lt;br&gt; 警报基础知识（时间、内容和原因）&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;6e54&#34;&gt;乍一看，这个列表似乎过于简单和容易；然而，我们需要首先学习可观察性的基础知识，才能理解更高层次的概念。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;9a60&#34;&gt;了解可观察性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;300e&#34;&gt;可观测性是衡量系统内部状态如何根据其外部输出的知识推断出来的指标。在系统工程和 IT 运营的背景下，可观察性对于诊断问题和确保系统所有部分按预期运行至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;d86f&#34;&gt;可观察性的支柱&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;日志：这些是不可变的记录，描述随着时间的推移发生的离散事件。日志对于了解事件发生后系统中发生的情况很有用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;指标：这些是在一段时间内衡量系统某些方面的数值。指标对于了解系统的性能以及随时间进行比较至关重要。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;跟踪：这些是请求流经系统时发生的完整路径或事件序列的记录。跟踪有助于识别请求如何在系统中传播以及出现延迟或问题的位置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*fLO7pJnCaWwiIGxZ.png&#34; alt=&#34;bubble包含可观察性、痕迹、日志和指标的图表”referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;a58e&#34;&gt;一些需要记住的关键概念：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLA（服务级别协议）&lt;/strong&gt;：SLA 是您与客户或用户签订的协议，定义了他们可以期望的服务级别。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLO（服务级别目标）&lt;/strong&gt;：SLO 是您的团队为满足 SLA 必须实现的具体、可衡量的目标。它们代表您想要达到的绩效目标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLI（服务水平指标）&lt;/strong&gt;：SLI 是指示系统实时性能的实际指标或测量结果。他们习惯于作为确保遵守 SLO。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;拉动&lt;/strong&gt;：指标抓取由 Prometheus 发起。 Prometheus 查询目标端点以定期收集指标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;推送&lt;/strong&gt;：指标由应用程序发布到端点（例如 Pushgateway）。此方法允许应用程序在生成指标时推送指标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;跟踪&lt;/strong&gt;：跟踪表示一系列操作，这些操作共同形成由应用程序及其组成服务处理的唯一事务。跟踪有助于了解请求流并识别系统中的瓶颈或问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;跨度&lt;/strong&gt;：在跟踪上下文中，跨度表示跟踪中的单个操作。它提供有关该操作的持续时间和上下文的详细信息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;规则类型：&lt;/strong&gt;在 Prometheus 中，有两种类型的规则。 &lt;strong&gt;记录规则&lt;/strong&gt;有助于预先计算经常需要的或计算成本较高的表达式，而&lt;strong&gt;警报规则&lt;/strong&gt;使您能够使用 PromQL 查询定义警报条件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;元监控：&lt;/strong&gt;理解元监控的概念，其中涉及监控 Prometheus 实例本身。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;f154&#34;&gt;主要学习目标：&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PromQL&lt;/strong&gt;：PromQL 至关重要，您可以通过探索指标来测试您的技能&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/prometheus/latest/querying/examples/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;并深入研究 Prometheus 的基本系统架构&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/introduction/overview/#architecture&#34; target=&#34;_blank “ rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;。此外，&lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/prometheus/latest/querying/functions/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;掌握 Prometheus 基本功能的基础知识.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AlertManager&lt;/strong&gt;：您需要了解AlertManager，它的功能至关重要。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/alerting/latest/alertmanager/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;深入了解 AlertManager 功能，并可视化您的 AlertManager 路线&lt; a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/webtools/alerting/routing-tree-editor/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;导出器&lt;/strong&gt;：熟悉 node_exporter 和 blackbox_exporter 等导出器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*yN90oQ-nfP8hbpxd.png&#34; alt= “地图”referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;b570&#34;&gt;您可以通过我使用过的以下 GitHub 存储库自由探索和了解 PCA 认证及相关主题&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-块-列表&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/walidshaari/PrometheusCertifiedAssociate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;walidshaari/PrometheusCertifiedAssociate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/edgarpf/prometheus-certified-associate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;edgarpf/prometheus-certified-associate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Al-HusseinHameedJasim/prometheus-certified-associate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Al-HusseinHameedJasim/prometheus-certified-associate&lt;/a &gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/edgarpf/prometheus-certified-associate&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://github.com/edgarpf/prometheus-certified-同事&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;f0de&#34;&gt;对于结构化和全面的 PCA 考试准备，请考虑投资 KodeKloud 的这些付费课程，他们提供了游乐场，我在准备过程中使用了它，它很有帮助&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kodekloud.com/courses/prometheus-certified-associate-pca&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;KodeKloud PCA 认证课程&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://training.promlabs.com/trainings/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://training.promlabs.com/trainings/&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /里&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://robustperception.teachable.com/p/introduction-to-prometheus&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;https://robustperception.teachable.com/p/普罗米修斯简介&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;0235&#34;&gt;结论&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p id=&#34;ffa5&#34;&gt;与其他证书相比，考试并不容易。我会按以下顺序排列：&lt;strong&gt;KCNA/CGOA/CKAD/PCA/KCSA/CKA/CKS&lt;/strong&gt;。考试后，你会在24小时内收到评分，通过考试后的感觉非常满意。总的来说，我希望它内容丰富且有用🚀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:2000/1*ENet0gQW5vbAyT1J9U-lwQ.png&#34; alt= “PCA 证书”referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/tag/prometheus?source=post_page-----6485fbe5789f-------------------- -----------&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Jaeger v2 released: OpenTelemetry in the core!】Jaeger v2 发布：核心是 OpenTelemetry！</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/12/jaeger-v2-released-opentelemetry-in-the-core/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Project post by the Jaeger maintainers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/&#34;&gt;Jaeger&lt;/a&gt;, the popular open-source distributed tracing platform, has had a successful 9 year history as being one of the first graduated projects in the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF). After over 60 releases, Jaeger is celebrating a major milestone with the upcoming release of Jaeger v2. This new version is a new architecture for Jaeger components that utilizes &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/collector/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector&lt;/a&gt; framework as the base and extends it to implement Jaeger’s unique features. It brings significant improvements and changes, making Jaeger more flexible, extensible, and better aligned with the OpenTelemetry project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, we’ll dive into the details of Jaeger v2, exploring its design, features, and benefits. Sharing what users can expect from this exciting new release and what is next for the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Foundation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry is the de-facto standard for application instrumentation providing the foundation for observability. Jaeger is now based on the cornerstone of this project, the OpenTelemetry Collector. Jaeger is a complete tracing platform that includes storage and the UI. OpenTelemetry Collector is usually an intermediate component in the collection pipelines that are used to receive, process, transform, and export different telemetry types. The two systems have some overlaps, for example, `jaeger-agent` and `jaeger-collector` play a role similar to what can be done with OpenTelemetry Collector, but only for traces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Historically, both Jaeger and OpenTelemetry Collector reused each other’s code. Collector supports receivers for legacy Jaeger formats implemented by importing Jaeger packages. And Jaeger reuses Collector’s receivers and data model converters. Because of this synergy, it’s been our goal for a while to bring the two projects closer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector has a very flexible and extensible design, which makes it easy to extend with additional components needed for Jaeger use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Features and Benefits&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By aligning the Jaeger v2 architecture with OpenTelemetry Collector, we deliver several exciting features and benefits for users, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Native OpenTelemetry processing&lt;/strong&gt;: Jaeger v2 natively supports OTLP data format, eliminating the translation step from OTLP to Jaeger’s internal data format and improving performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Batched data processing&lt;/strong&gt;: the OpenTelemetry Collector pipelines operate on batches of data, which can be especially important for storage backends like ClickHouse that are much more performant with batch inserts. Jaeger v2 will be able to utilize this batch-based internal pipeline design.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Familiar developer experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Jaeger v2 follows the same configuration and deployment model as OpenTelemetry Collector, providing a more consistent developer experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Access to OpenTelemetry Collector features&lt;/strong&gt;: Jaeger v2 inherits all the core features of the Collector, including auth, cert reloading, internal monitoring, health checks, z-pages, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced sampling capabilities: &lt;/strong&gt;Jaeger v2 introduces the ability to perform tail-based sampling, using the upstream&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-collector-contrib/tree/main/processor/tailsamplingprocessor&#34;&gt; OpenTelemetry-contrib processor&lt;/a&gt;. It also fully supports Jaeger’s original&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/docs/1.62/sampling/#remote-sampling&#34;&gt; Remote&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/docs/1.62/sampling/#adaptive-sampling&#34;&gt; Adaptive&lt;/a&gt; head-based sampling methods.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Access to OpenTelemetry Collector ecosystem&lt;/strong&gt;: Jaeger v2 can use a multitude of extensions available for OpenTelemetry Collector, such as span-to-metric connector, telemetry rewriting processors, PII filtering, and many others. For example, we are able to reuse Kafka exporter and receiver and replicate the Jaeger v1 collector-ingester deployment model without maintaining any extra code.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The result is a leaner code base and more importantly the ability to future proof Jaeger as OpenTelemetry evolves to ensure Jaeger is always the first tracing system for open source users. Compatibility between OpenTelemetry and Jaeger will be supported on day 1 due to the tight integration between the projects. This will continue collaboration between both projects, getting more users to adopt open source technologies more quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Design and Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Overall, Jaeger v2 architecture is very similar to a standard OpenTelemetry Collector that has &lt;em&gt;pipelines&lt;/em&gt; for receiving and processing telemetry (a pipeline encapsulates &lt;em&gt;receivers&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;processors&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;exporters&lt;/em&gt;), and &lt;em&gt;extensions&lt;/em&gt; that perform functions not directly related to processing of telemetry. Jaeger v2 makes a few design decisions in how to use the Collector framework.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfszqCKRD0g9mKM8wOMI4xPbmtcZgZDXtnlTemCZITJZgOeaCcMmMiyN-WdCI3adoBVqavGYLn9axeVkI6sYiUe5nR2knuqpWgTqJGgWn4-KqQHqEgMpGvUoje7AChJ8yRrl2LbqhDvUPdaE6Tj4glGyBlv?key=7fldATYTFT0FJaOouEGZcm4g&#34; alt=&#34;pipeline&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Query Extension 🔎&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since Collector is primarily designed for data ingestion, querying for traces and presenting them in the UI is an example of functionality that is not in its remit. Jaeger v2 implements it as a Collector extension.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Single Binary&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger v1 provided multiple binaries for different purposes (agent, collector, ingester, query). Those binaries were hardwired to perform different functions and exposed different configuration options passed via command line. We realized that all that complexity was unnecessary in the v2 architecture as we achieve the same simply by enabling different components in the configuration file. We also did some benchmarking of executable size and noticed that if we bundle all possible Jaeger v2 components in a single binary, including ~3Mb (compressed) of UI assets, we end up with a container image of ~40Mb in size, versus ~30Mb in v1. As a result, Jaeger v2 ships just a single binary `jaeger`, and it will be configurable for different deployment roles via YAML configuration file, the same as the OpenTelemetry Collector.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Storage Implementation&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both Jaeger and OpenTelemetry Collector process telemetry data, but they differ in how they handle it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector:&lt;/strong&gt; Focuses on one-way data processing (receive, process, export). To store data, it uses specific exporters for each database (e.g., Elasticsearch Exporter).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jaeger:&lt;/strong&gt; Handles both writing and reading data, allowing queries and visualization through a UI. This requires a shared storage backend, unlike the Collector’s approach.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger v2 implements a storage extension to abstract the storage layer. This allows both the query component (read path) and a generic exporter (write path) to interact with various storage backends without dedicated implementations for each. This approach provides flexibility and maintains compatibility with Jaeger v1’s multi-storage capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What’s in v2&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ A single binary &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://hub.docker.com/r/jaegertracing/jaeger&#34;&gt;Docker image&lt;/a&gt; configurable to run in different roles, such as collector, ingester, query, and a collection of &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jaegertracing/jaeger/tree/main/cmd/jaeger&#34;&gt;configuration file templates&lt;/a&gt; for these roles.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Support for all official storage backends with full backwards compatibility with Jaeger v1.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Support for Kafka as intermediate queue, in both OTLP and Jaeger legacy data formats.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Support for primary and archive storage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Support for remote and adaptive head sampling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Support for tail sampling .&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Service Performance Management (SPM).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Internal observability integrated with OpenTelemetry Collector configuration.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ Refreshed documentation and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/docs/next-release-v2/migration/&#34;&gt;v1→v2 migration guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;▶️ Try Jaeger v2 today and check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/docs/next-release-v2/getting-started/&#34;&gt;Getting Started&lt;/a&gt; documentation for more options:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;docker run –rm –name jaeger \&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-p 16686:16686 \&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-p 4317:4317 \&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;-p 4318:4318 \&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;jaegertracing/jaeger:2.0.0&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;What’s Next&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Version 2.0.0 already supports all the core features of Jaeger, but the development will continue in 2025 to add remaining feature parity, improving performance, and enhancing the overall user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The roadmap for Jaeger v2 includes the following milestones:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🚧 Helm Chart for Jaeger v2.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🚧 Jaeger v2 support natively in the OpenTelemetry Operator.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;📅 Upgrading storage backend implementations to Storage v2 interface to use OpenTelemetry data natively.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;📅 Support ClickHouse as official storage backend.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🔮 Upgrading UI to use OpenTelemetry data natively.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🔮 Upgrading UI to normalize dependency views.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Leveraging Mentorship Programs 🎓&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Jaeger v2 roadmap was designed to minimize the amount of changes we needed to make to the project by avoiding a big-bang approach in favor of incremental improvements to the existing code base. Yet it was still a significant amount of new development, which is often difficult to sustain for a volunteer-driven project. We were able to attract new contributors and drive the Jaeger v2 roadmap by participating in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/mentorship/&#34;&gt;mentorship programs&lt;/a&gt; run by Linux Foundation, CNCF, and Google, such as LFX Mentorship and Google Summer of Code. This has been a rewarding and mutually beneficial engagement for both the project and the participating interns. Stay tuned for our next mentorships to build out the roadmap items.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger v2 represents a significant step forward for the Jaeger project, bringing improved flexibility, extensibility, and alignment with the OpenTelemetry project. With its native OTLP ingestion, simplified deployment model, and access to OpenTelemetry Collector features, Jaeger v2 promises to provide a more efficient and scalable distributed tracing solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the development of Jaeger v2 continues, we can expect to see a more robust and feature-rich system emerge. Stay tuned for updates and get ready to experience the next generation of distributed tracing with Jaeger v2!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jaeger 维护者发布的项目&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/&#34;&gt;Jaeger&lt;/a&gt;，流行的开源分布式跟踪平台，作为首批毕业项目之一，已经有 9 年的成功历史在云原生计算基金会 (CNCF) 中。在发布了 60 多个版本之后，Jaeger 即将发布 Jaeger v2，以庆祝一个重要的里程碑。这个新版本是 Jaeger 组件的新架构，它利用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/collector/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector&lt;/a&gt; 框架作为基础，并对其进行扩展以实现 Jaeger 的独特功能。它带来了重大改进和变化，使 Jaeger 更加灵活、可扩展，并且与 OpenTelemetry 项目更好地保持一致。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇博文中，我们将深入了解 Jaeger v2 的详细信息，探索其设计、功能和优势。分享用户对这个令人兴奋的新版本的期望以及该项目的下一步发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry 基金会&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry 是应用程序检测的事实上的标准，为可观察性提供了基础。 Jaeger 现在基于该项目的基石 OpenTelemetry Collector。 Jaeger 是一个完整的跟踪平台，包括存储和 UI。 OpenTelemetry Collector 通常是收集管道中的中间组件，用于接收、处理、转换和导出不同的遥测类型。这两个系统有一些重叠，例如，“jaeger-agent”和“jaeger-collector”的作用与 OpenTelemetry Collector 的作用类似，但仅用于跟踪。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从历史上看，Jaeger 和 OpenTelemetry Collector 都重用了彼此的代码。 Collector 支持通过导入 Jaeger 包实现的旧版 Jaeger 格式的接收器。 Jaeger 重用了 Collector 的接收器和数据模型转换器。由于这种协同作用，我们一段时间以来的目标就是让两个项目更加接近。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector 具有非常灵活和可扩展的设计，可以轻松地使用 Jaeger 用例所需的其他组件进行扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;功能和优点&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过将 Jaeger v2 架构与 OpenTelemetry Collector 相结合，我们为用户提供了多项令人兴奋的功能和优势，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;原生 OpenTelemetry 处理&lt;/strong&gt;：Jaeger v2 原生支持 OTLP 数据格式，消除了从 OTLP 到 Jaeger 内部数据格式的转换步骤并提高了性能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;批量数据处理&lt;/strong&gt;：OpenTelemetry Collector 管道对批量数据进行操作，这对于像 ClickHouse 这样的存储后端尤其重要，因为批量插入的性能要高得多。 Jaeger v2 将能够利用这种基于批处理的内部管道设计。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;熟悉的开发人员体验&lt;/strong&gt;：Jaeger v2遵循与OpenTelemetry Collector相同的配置和部署模型，提供更一致的开发者体验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;访问 OpenTelemetry Collector 功能&lt;/strong&gt;：Jaeger v2 继承了 Collector 的所有核心功能，包括身份验证、证书重新加载、内部监控、运行状况检查、z 页面等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高级采样功能：&lt;/strong&gt;Jaeger v2 引入了使用上游执行基于尾部采样的功能&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-collector- contrib/tree/main/processor/tailsamplingprocessor&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry-contrib 处理器&lt;/a&gt;。它还完全支持 Jaeger 的原始&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/docs/1.62/sampling/#remote-sampling&#34;&gt;远程&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/docs/1.62/sampling/#remote-sampling&#34;&gt;远程&lt;/a&gt;。 jaegertracing.io/docs/1.62/sampling/#adaptive-sampling&#34;&gt;自适应&lt;/a&gt;基于头部的采样方法。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;访问 OpenTelemetry Collector 生态系统&lt;/strong&gt;：Jaeger v2 可以使用 OpenTelemetry Collector 可用的多种扩展，例如跨度到公制连接器、遥测重写处理器、PII 过滤等等。例如，我们能够重用 Kafka 导出器和接收器，并复制 Jaeger v1 收集器-摄取器部署模型，而无需维护任何额外代码。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结果是一个更精简的代码库，更重要的是，随着 OpenTelemetry 的发展，Jaeger 能够在未来得到证明，以确保 Jaeger 始终是开源用户的第一个跟踪系统。由于项目之间的紧密集成，OpenTelemetry 和 Jaeger 之间的兼容性将在第一天得到支持。这将继续两个项目之间的合作，让更多用户更快地采用开源技术。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;设计与架构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;总体而言，Jaeger v2 架构与标准 OpenTelemetry Collector 非常相似，后者具有用于接收和处理遥测的&lt;em&gt;管道&lt;/em&gt;（管道封装&lt;em&gt;接收器&lt;/em&gt;、&lt;em&gt;处理器&lt;/em&gt; em&gt; 和 &lt;em&gt;导出器&lt;/em&gt;），以及执行与遥测处理不直接相关的功能的&lt;em&gt;扩展&lt;/em&gt;。 Jaeger v2 在如何使用 Collector 框架方面做出了一些设计决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://lh7-rt.googleusercontent.com/docsz/AD_4nXfszqCKRD0g9mKM8wOMI4xPbmtcZgZDXtnlTemCZITJZgOeaCcMmMiyN-WdCI3adoBVqavGYLn9axeVkI6sYiUe5nR2 knuqpWgTqJGgWn4-KqQHqEgMpGvUoje7AChJ8yRrl2LbqhDvUPdaE6Tj4glGyBlv?key=7fldATYTFT0FJaOouEGZcm4g&#34; alt=&#34;管道“referrerpolicy =“no-referrer”&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;查询扩展🔎&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于 Collector 主要是为数据摄取而设计的，因此查询跟踪并将其呈现在 UI 中是一个不属于其职权范围的功能示例。 Jaeger v2 将其实现为 Collector 扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;单个二进制文件&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger v1 专业版提供了用于不同目的的多个二进制文件（代理、收集器、摄取、查询）。这些二进制文件被硬连线以执行不同的功能，并公开通过命令行传递的不同配置选项。我们意识到，所有这些复杂性在 v2 架构中都是不必要的，因为我们只需在配置文件中启用不同的组件即可实现相同的目的。我们还对可执行文件大小进行了一些基准测试，并注意到，如果我们将所有可能的 Jaeger v2 组件捆绑在一个二进制文件中，包括 ~3Mb（压缩）的 UI 资产，我们最终会得到一个 ~40Mb 大小的容器映像，而不是 ~30Mb在 v1 中。因此，Jaeger v2 仅提供一个二进制“jaeger”，并且可以通过 YAML 配置文件为不同的部署角色进行配置，与 OpenTelemetry Collector 相同。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;存储实现&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger 和 OpenTelemetry Collector 都处理遥测数据，但它们的处理方式有所不同。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector&lt;/strong&gt;：专注于单向数据处理（接收、处理、导出）。为了存储数据，它为每个数据库使用特定的导出器（例如 Elasticsearch Exporter）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jaeger：&lt;/strong&gt;处理写入和读取数据，允许通过 UI 进行查询和可视化。这需要一个共享存储后端，与收集器的方法不同。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger v2 实现了存储扩展来抽象存储层。这允许查询组件（读取路径）和通用导出器（写入路径）与各种存储后端进行交互，而无需为每个后端提供专门的实现。这种方法提供了灵活性并保持了与 Jaeger v1 的多存储功能的兼容性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;v2 中有什么&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 单个二进制文件和&lt;a href=&#34;https://hub.docker.com/r/jaegertracing/jaeger&#34;&gt;Docker 映像&lt;/a&gt;可配置为以不同角色运行，例如收集器、摄取器、查询，以及这些角色的&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jaegertracing/jaeger/tree/main/cmd/jaeger&#34;&gt;配置文件模板&lt;/a&gt;集合。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 支持所有官方存储后端，并与 Jaeger v1 完全向后兼容。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 支持 Kafka 作为中间队列，采用 OTLP 和 Jaeger 旧数据格式。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 支持主存储和存档存储。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 支持远程和自适应头部采样。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 支持尾部采样。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 服务绩效管理 (SPM)。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 与 OpenTelemetry Collector 配置集成的内部可观察性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;✅ 更新了文档和&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/docs/next-release-v2/migration/&#34;&gt;v1→v2 迁移指南&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;▶️ 今天尝试 Jaeger v2 并查看 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jaegertracing.io/docs/next-release-v2/getting-started/&#34;&gt;入门&lt;/a&gt;文档以获取更多选项：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;docker run –rm –name jaeger \&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;  -p 16686:16686 \&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;  -p 4317:4317 \&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;  -p 4318:4318 \&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;  jaegertracing/jaeger:2.0.0&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;下一步是什么&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2.0.0 版本已经支持 Jaeger 的所有核心功能，但开发工作将在 2025 年继续进行，以添加剩余的功能奇偶校验、提高性能并增强整体用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger v2 的路线图包括以下里程碑：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🚧 Jaeger v2 的 Helm 图表。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🚧 OpenTelemetry Operator 中原生支持 Jaeger v2。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;📅 将存储后端实现升级到 Storage v2 接口，以原生使用 OpenTelemetry 数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;📅 支持 ClickHouse 作为官方存储后端。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🔮 升级 UI 以原生使用 OpenTelemetry 数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;🔮 升级 UI 以规范依赖关系视图。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;利用导师计划🎓&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger v2 路线图旨在通过避免采用有利于对现有代码库进行增量改进的大爆炸方法，最大限度地减少我们需要对项目进行的更改量。然而，这仍然是大量的新开发项目，对于志愿者驱动的项目来说往往难以维持。通过参与由 Linux 基金会、CNCF 和Google，例如 LFX Mentorship 和 Google Summer of Code。对于项目和参与的实习生来说，这都是一次有益且互惠互利的合作。请继续关注我们的下一次指导，以制定路线图项目。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;结论&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jaeger v2 代表了 Jaeger 项目向前迈出的重要一步，带来了更高的灵活性、可扩展性以及与 OpenTelemetry 项目的一致性。凭借其原生 OTLP 摄取、简化的部署模型以及对 OpenTelemetry Collector 功能的访问，Jaeger v2 有望提供更高效、可扩展的分布式跟踪解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着 Jaeger v2 的不断开发，我们预计会看到更强大、功能更丰富的系统的出现。请继续关注更新并准备好体验 Jaeger v2 的下一代分布式跟踪！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Managing threat intelligence in Falco】在 Falco 中管理威胁情报</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/12/managing-threat-intelligence-in-falco/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Falco has become a vital tool for security practitioners seeking to safeguard containerized and cloud-native environments. Leveraging the power of eBPF (Extended Berkeley Packet Filter), &lt;a href=&#34;https://falco.org/&#34;&gt;Falco&lt;/a&gt; monitors system calls and audit events, allowing it to detect malicious behavior in hosts and containers, no matter how large the infrastructure. Beyond its core detection capabilities, Falco offers critical integrations with industry-standard frameworks, such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://falco.org/about/use-cases/#threat-detection&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://falco.org/blog/falco-pci-controls/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PCI DSS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, to enforce regulatory compliance and security standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/announcements/2024/02/29/cloud-native-computing-foundation-announces-falco-graduation/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF Graduate Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; evolves to meet industry needs, one of the most pressing challenges practitioners face is ensuring that their instance of Falco stays ahead of evolving threats and regulatory requirements. With the complexity of managing and updating Falco rules, handling false positives, and keeping up with emerging threats, how can security teams efficiently manage their threat intelligence with Falco? In this blog post, we will explore various tools and approaches that help manage Falco’s rules and extend its capabilities to meet modern cybersecurity challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Falcosidekick&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Falcosidekick&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a lightweight solution that extends Falco’s capabilities by forwarding Falco event data to various third-party services. As organizations adopt more complex environments, they often need to centralize threat detection and responses across multiple systems. This is where Falcosidekick excels: it acts as a bridge between Falco and the extensive third-party ecosystem, including logging services, chat platforms, alerting tools, and observability systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By connecting Falco to these services, Falcosidekick enables:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich Contextual Alerts:&lt;/strong&gt; Falco events, enriched with metadata, can be sent to systems such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick/blob/master/docs/outputs/slack.md&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Slack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick/blob/master/docs/outputs/elasticsearch.md&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick?tab=readme-ov-file#prometheus&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prometheus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick?tab=readme-ov-file#siem&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIEM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; solutions, allowing teams to react quickly to suspicious behavior.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance and Digital Forensics:&lt;/strong&gt; Event data can be logged and stored for audits, digital forensics, or compliance purposes, enabling deeper investigation when threats arise.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automation and Response: &lt;/strong&gt;You can use Falcosidekick to automate &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick?tab=readme-ov-file#workflow&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;workflows&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in response to specific detections, or run arbitrary &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick?tab=readme-ov-file#faas--serverless&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FaaS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; scripts to mitigate risk.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, if Falco detects an unexpected process running in a container, the enriched alert can be sent to a chat platform like Slack, giving security teams the necessary context to assess the situation. This fan-out model ensures that you don’t miss critical alerts, and the ability to forward events to various platforms helps optimize your threat response strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Falco Talon&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An alternative approach would be to use &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falco-talon/falco-talon&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Falco Talon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; within a zero-trust model by automating real-time responses to unexpected system behavior based on predefined Falco rules. Instead of relying solely on known attack signatures, this approach focuses on detecting deviations from expected behavior within the system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this approach, you can define Falco rules for the normal behavior of operating systems, containers, and processes. If anything outside of the expected behavior occurs, a Falco Talon action can be triggered to mitigate the threat immediately, such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.falco-talon.org/docs/actionners/list/#kubernetesterminate&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gracefully terminating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a Kubernetes workload.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Isolating the pod networking with &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.falco-talon.org/docs/actionners/list/#kubernetesnetworkpolicy&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network Policies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Triggering additional monitoring or &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.falco-talon.org/docs/actionners/list/#kuberneteslog&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;logging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; based on the specific threat.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This approach is ideal for enforcing regulatory compliance in environments requiring strict control, such as PCI DSS or SOC 2. The benefit of this approach is that it requires less frequent updates to Falco rules, as it doesn’t rely heavily on threat feeds or lists of known behaviors. However, implementing this method requires a deep understanding of your system’s normal behavior to avoid unintended disruptions caused by over-aggressive rules.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Falcoctl: Streamlining Rules Management and Threat Intelligence&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcoctl&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Falcoctl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the command-line interface that simplifies the lifecycle management of Falco’s rules and plugins. Managing and updating Falco’s rules effectively is critical to staying ahead of evolving threats, and falcoctl allows practitioners to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install, update, or downgrade Falco rules&lt;/strong&gt;: Whether you need to update your rules in response to emerging threats or roll back to a previous version due to a false positive, falcoctl makes the process seamless.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage Falco plugins&lt;/strong&gt;: As the plugin ecosystem continues to grow, falcoctl helps install, upgrade, and manage plugins with minimal downtime, enabling Falco to integrate with more tools and data sources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Falcoctl supports &lt;a href=&#34;https://opencontainers.org/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OCI-compliant registries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for managing rules and plugins, allowing users to pull artifacts from custom or official sources. This is particularly useful for maintaining custom rules or curated threat feeds in larger organizations. For example, you can maintain a list of known malicious binaries within your Falco instance. If Falco Talon incorrectly blocks a legitimate process due to a false positive, falcoctl enables you to quickly revert to a previous version of the rule without disrupting your operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This flexibility makes falcoctl an essential tool for managing both threat intelligence and compliance requirements across dynamic, cloud-native environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;The Growing Need for Managed Falco Feeds&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Managing Falco’s rule lifecycle is essential for adapting to constantly changing security threats, compliance standards, and infrastructure needs. Yet, many practitioners face challenges in efficiently handling custom rules, updating threat feeds, and reducing noise in their production environments. To address these pain points, managed Falco Feeds can provide a solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Falco feeds allow users to maintain up-to-date rules for threat detection, compliance enforcement, and more. Instead of manually updating lists of IP addresses, complex macros, or regulatory compliance rules, managed Falco Feeds simplify this process by delivering continuous, curated rule updates. Managed feeds ensure that your Falco instance stays aligned with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evolving threat landscapes:&lt;/strong&gt; As new vulnerabilities, attack vectors, and threat operations are discovered, such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=swx-Kwyz410&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SCARLETEEL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://sysdig.com/blog/crystalray-rising-threat-actor-exploiting-oss-tools/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CRYSTALRAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, managed feeds help update your detection mechanisms without requiring manual intervention.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance standards:&lt;/strong&gt; For industries requiring compliance with frameworks like PCI DSS, SOC2, FedRAMP, NIS2, or GDPR, managed feeds can offer pre-built rulesets to enforce those standards automatically.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2024 Falco Survey: Understanding How You Manage Falco Rules&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As Falco matures post-CNCF graduation, we are eager to understand how the community manages its Falco instances, especially as threat landscapes and compliance requirements evolve. We’ve launched the &lt;a href=&#34;https://falco.org/blog/community-survey-2023/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2024 Falco Survey&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to gain insights into how Falco is being used in production environments, what tools (like Falcosidekick, Falco Talon, or falcoctl) are being adopted, and how custom rules are managed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now is the time to get involved—contribute to the Falco community, share your insights in the 2024 Falco survey, and help shape the future of this critical CNCF project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of the questions we aim to answer:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are users heavily relying on Falcosidekick for automated responses, or is Falco Talon taking the lead in real-time threat mitigation?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How do teams manage their custom rules updates?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How does Falco contribute to solving organizational pain points, particularly in Kubernetes security and compliance?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Falco is a powerful tool for securing cloud-native environments, but managing its rules and threat intelligence is an ongoing challenge for many organizations. Whether you’re integrating with third-party services via Falcosidekick, automating real-time response with Falco Talon, or streamlining lifecycle management with falcoctl, there are solutions available to meet the evolving needs of security practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we continue to build on the capabilities of Falco, fully managed Falco Feeds by Sysdig offers a way to stay ahead of emerging threats and complex compliance requirements without the friction of manual updates or configuration changes. &lt;a href=&#34;https://sysdig.com/opensource/falco/&#34;&gt;Falco Feeds&lt;/a&gt; equips users to harness the power and flexibility of open source Falco and exper-written detection rules fueled by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sysdig.com/threat-research/&#34;&gt;Sysdig Threat Research Team&lt;/a&gt; for real-time threat detection at enterprise scale.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Falco 已成为寻求保护容器化和云原生环境的安全从业者的重要工具。利用 eBPF（扩展伯克利数据包过滤器）的强大功能，&lt;a href=&#34;https://falco.org/&#34;&gt;Falco&lt;/a&gt; 监视系统调用和审核事件，使其能够检测主机和容器中的恶意行为，无论基础设施有多大。除了核心检测功能之外，Falco 还提供与行业标准框架的关键集成，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://falco.org/about/use-cases/#threat-detection&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MITRE ATT&amp;CK&lt;/ strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://falco.org/blog/falco-pci-controls/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PCI DSS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，以强制执行法规遵从性和安全性标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/announcements/2024/02/29/cloud-native-computing-foundation-announces-falco-graduation/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CNCF研究生项目&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 不断发展以满足行业需求，从业者面临的最紧迫的挑战之一是确保他们的 Falco 实例领先于不断变化的威胁和监管要求。由于管理和更新 Falco 规则、处理误报以及跟上新出现的威胁的复杂性，安全团队如何使用 Falco 有效管理威胁情报？在这篇博文中，我们将探索有助于管理 Falco 规则并扩展其功能以应对现代网络安全挑战的各种工具和方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Falcosidekick&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Falcosidekick&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 是一个轻量级解决方案，通过将 Falco 事件数据转发到各种第三方来扩展 Falco 的功能聚会服务。随着组织采用更复杂的环境，他们通常需要跨多个系统集中威胁检测和响应。这就是 Falcosidekick 的优势所在：它充当 Falco 与广泛的第三方生态系统之间的桥梁，包括日志服务、聊天平台、警报工具和可观测系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过将 Falco 连接到这些服务，Falcosidekick 可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;丰富的上下文警报：&lt;/strong&gt;富含元数据的 Falco 事件可以发送到诸如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick/blob/master/docs 等系统/outputs/slack.md&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;松弛&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick/blob/master/docs/outputs/elasticsearch.md&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https:// github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick?tab=readme-ov-file#prometheus&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;普罗米修斯&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，或 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick?tab=readme-ov-file#siem&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIEM&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 解决方案，使团队能够对可疑行为快速做出反应。&lt; /里&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;合规性和数字取证&lt;/strong&gt;：可以记录和存储事件数据，以供审核、数字取证或合规性使用。目的，以便在出现威胁时进行更深入的调查。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自动化和响应：&lt;/strong&gt;您可以使用 Falcosidekick 实现自动化&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick?tab=readme-ov-file#workflow&#34;&gt;&lt;strong &gt;工作流程&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;响应特定检测，或运行任意&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcosidekick?tab=readme-ov-file#faas--serverless&#34;&gt;用于降低风险的&lt;strong&gt;FaaS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;脚本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，如果 Falco 检测到容器中运行的意外进程，则丰富的警报可以发送到 Slack 等聊天平台，为安全团队提供必要的上下文来评估情况。这种扇出模型可确保您不会错过关键警报，并且将事件转发到各种平台的能力有助于优化您的威胁响应策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;隼爪&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一种方法是在零信任中使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falco-talon/falco-talon&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Falco Talon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;通过根据预定义的 Falco 规则自动实时响应意外系统行为来构建模型。这种方法不是仅仅依赖已知的攻击特征，而是专注于检测系统内与预期行为的偏差。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过这种方法，您可以为操作系统、容器和进程的正常行为定义 Falco 规则。如果发生任何超出预期行为的情况，可以触发 Falco Talon 操作以立即缓解威胁，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.falco-talon.org/docs/actionners/list/#kubernetesterminate&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;正常终止&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Kubernetes 工作负载。&lt;/li &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.falco-talon.org/docs/actionners/list/#kubernetesnetworkpolicy&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;网络策略&lt;/strong&gt;隔离 Pod 网络&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/李&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;根据具体情况触发额外监控或&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.falco-talon.org/docs/actionners/list/#kuberneteslog&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;日志记录&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;威胁。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此方法非常适合在需要严格控制的环境（例如 PCI DSS 或 SOC 2）中强制执行法规遵从性。此方法的优点是不需要频繁更新 Falco 规则，因为它不太依赖于威胁已知行为的提要或列表。但是，实施此方法需要深入了解系统的正常行为，以避免过度激进的规则造成意外中断。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Falcoctl：简化规则管理和威胁情报&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/falcosecurity/falcoctl&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Falcoctl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 是一个命令行界面，可简化 Falco 规则和插件的生命周期管理。有效管理和更新 Falco 规则对于领先于不断变化的威胁至关重要，并且 falcoctl 允许实践收件人：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安装、更新或降级 Falco 规则&lt;/strong&gt;：无论您是需要更新规则以应对新出现的威胁，还是需要因误报而回滚到之前的版本，falcoctl 都能使流程无缝衔接。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;管理 Falco 插件&lt;/strong&gt;：随着插件生态系统的不断发展，falcoctl 可帮助安装、升级和管理插件，同时最大限度地减少停机时间，使 Falco 能够与更多工具和数据源集成。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Falcoctl 支持&lt;a href=&#34;https://opencontainers.org/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;符合 OCI 的注册表&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;来管理规则和插件，允许用户从自定义或官方中提取工件来源。这对于在大型组织中维护自定义规则或策划的威胁源特别有用。例如，您可以在 Falco 实例中维护已知恶意二进制文件的列表。如果 Falco Talon 由于误报而错误地阻止了合法进程，falcoctl 使您能够快速恢复到规则的先前版本，而不会中断您的操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种灵活性使 falcoctl 成为跨动态云原生环境管理威胁情报和合规性要求的重要工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;对托管 Falco Feed 的需求不断增长&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;管理 Falco 的规则生命周期对于适应不断变化的安全威胁、合规标准和基础设施需求至关重要。然而，许多从业者在有效处理自定义规则、更新威胁源以及减少生产环境中的噪音方面面临挑战。为了解决这些痛点，托管 Falco Feed 可以提供解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Falco 源允许用户维护威胁检测、合规性执行等的最新规则。托管 Falco Feed 无需手动更新 IP 地址列表、复杂的宏或法规遵从性规则，而是通过提供持续、精心策划的规则更新来简化此过程。托管源可确保您的 Falco 实例与以下内容保持一致：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;不断变化的威胁形势&lt;/strong&gt;：随着新漏洞、攻击媒介和威胁操作的发现，例如&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=swx- Kwyz410&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SCARLETEEL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://sysdig.com/blog/crystalray-rising-threat-actor-exploiting-oss-tools/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CRYSTALRAY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，托管源可帮助您更新检测机制，而无需需要人工干预。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;合规标准&lt;/strong&gt;：对于需要遵守 PCI DSS、SOC2、FedRAMP、NIS2 或 GDPR 等框架的行业，托管 Feed 可以提供预构建的规则集来自动执行这些标准。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;2024 年 Falco 调查：了解如何管理 Falco 规则&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着 Falco 在 CNCF 毕业后逐渐成熟，我们渴望了解d 社区如何管理其 Falco 实例，特别是随着威胁形势和合规性要求的发展。我们发起了&lt;a href=&#34;https://falco.org/blog/community-survey-2023/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2024 年 Falco 调查&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，以深入了解 Falco 的现状生产环境中使用的工具、采用的工具（例如 Falcosidekick、Falco Talon 或 falcoctl）以及如何管理自定义规则。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在是参与其中的时候了 - 为 Falco 社区做出贡献，分享您在 2024 年 Falco 调查中的见解，并帮助塑造这一关键 CNCF 项目的未来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们旨在回答的一些问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;用户是否严重依赖 Falcosidekick 进行自动响应，或者 Falco Talon 是否在实时威胁缓解方面处于领先地位？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;团队如何管理自定义规则更新？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Falco 如何帮助解决组织痛点，特别是在 Kubernetes 安全性和合规性方面？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h1 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;结论&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Falco 是保护云原生环境的强大工具，但管理其规则和威胁情报对许多组织来说是一个持续的挑战。无论您是通过 Falcosidekick 与第三方服务集成、使用 Falco Talon 自动执行实时响应，还是使用 falcoctl 简化生命周期管理，都有可用的解决方案来满足安全从业者不断变化的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着我们继续构建 Falco 的功能，Sysdig 完全管理的 Falco Feed 提供了一种方法，可以领先于新出现的威胁和复杂的合规性要求，而无需手动更新或配置更改。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://sysdig.com/opensource/falco/&#34;&gt;Falco Feeds&lt;/a&gt; 使用户能够利用开源 Falco 的强大功能和灵活性以及由 &lt;a href= 推动的专家编写的检测规则&#34;https://sysdig.com/threat-research/&#34;&gt;Sysdig 威胁研究团队&lt;/a&gt;，用于企业规模的实时威胁检测。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fast, secure, and simple: Istio’s Ambient Mode reaches General Availability in v1.24】快速、安全且简单：Istio 的 Ambient 模式在 v1.24 中全面可用</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/07/fast-secure-and-simple-istios-ambient-mode-reaches-general-availability-in-v1-24/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Project post by Lin Sun, Solo.io, for the Istio Steering and Technical Oversight Committees&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Our latest release signals ambient mode – service mesh without sidecars – is ready for everyone.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce that Istio’s ambient data plane mode has reached General Availability, with the ztunnel, waypoints and APIs being marked as Stable by the Istio TOC. This marks the final stage in Istio’s&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/releases/feature-stages/&#34;&gt;feature phase progression&lt;/a&gt;, signaling that ambient mode is fully ready for broad production usage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ambient mesh — and its reference implementation with Istio’s ambient mode —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2022/introducing-ambient-mesh/&#34;&gt;was announced in September 2022&lt;/a&gt;. Since then, our community has put in 26 months of hard work and collaboration, with contributions from Solo.io, Google, Microsoft, Intel, Aviatrix, Huawei, IBM, Red Hat, and many others. Stable status in 1.24 indicates the features of ambient mode are now fully ready for broad production workloads. This is a huge milestone for Istio, bringing Istio to production readiness without sidecars, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/overview/dataplane-modes/&#34;&gt;offering users a choice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;why-ambient-mesh&#34;&gt;Why ambient mesh?&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#why-ambient-mesh&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the launch of Istio in 2017, we have observed a clear and growing demand for mesh capabilities for applications — but heard that many users found the resource overhead and operational complexity of sidecars hard to overcome. Challenges that Istio users shared with us include how sidecars can break applications after they are added, the large CPU and memory requirement for a proxy with every workload, and the inconvenience of needing to restart application pods with every new Istio release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a community, we designed ambient mesh from the ground up to tackle these problems, alleviating the previous barriers of complexity faced by users looking to implement service mesh. The new concept was named ‘ambient mesh’ as it was designed to be transparent to your application, with no proxy infrastructure collocated with user workloads, no subtle changes to configuration required to onboard, and no application restarts required. In ambient mode it is trivial to add or remove applications from the mesh. All you need to do is&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/add-workloads/&#34;&gt;label a namespace&lt;/a&gt;, and all applications in that namespace are instantly added to the mesh. This immediately secures all traffic within that namespace with industry-standard mutual TLS encryption — no other configuration or restarts required!. Refer to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2022/introducing-ambient-mesh/&#34;&gt;Introducing Ambient Mesh blog&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more information on why we built Istio’s ambient mode.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;how-does-ambient-mode-make-adoption-easier&#34;&gt;How does ambient mode make adoption easier?&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#how-does-ambient-mode-make-adoption-easier&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The core innovation behind ambient mesh is that it slices Layer 4 (L4) and Layer 7 (L7) processing into two distinct layers. Istio’s ambient mode is powered by lightweight, shared L4 node proxies and optional L7 proxies, removing the need for traditional sidecar proxies from the data plane. This layered approach allows you to adopt Istio incrementally, enabling a smooth transition from no mesh, to a secure overlay (L4), to optional full L7 processing — on a per-namespace basis, as needed, across your fleet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By utilizing ambient mesh, users bypass some of the previously restrictive elements of the sidecar model. Server-send-first protocols now work, most reserved ports are now available, and the ability for containers to bypass the sidecar — either maliciously or not — is eliminated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The lightweight shared L4 node proxy is called the&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/overview/#ztunnel&#34;&gt;ztunnel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;(zero-trust tunnel). ztunnel drastically reduces the overhead of running a mesh by removing the need to potentially over-provision memory and CPU within a cluster to handle expected loads. In some use cases, the savings can exceed 90% or more, while still providing zero-trust security using mutual TLS with cryptographic identity, simple L4 authorization policies, and telemetry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The L7 proxies are called&amp;nbsp;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/overview/#waypoint-proxies&#34;&gt;waypoints&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Waypoints process L7 functions such as traffic routing, rich authorization policy enforcement, and enterprise-grade resilience. Waypoints run outside of your application deployments and can scale independently based on your needs, which could be for the entire namespace or for multiple services within a namespace. Compared with sidecars, you don’t need one waypoint per application pod, and you can scale your waypoint effectively based on its scope, thus saving significant amounts of CPU and memory in most cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The separation between the L4 secure overlay layer and L7 processing layer allows incremental adoption of the ambient mode data plane, in contrast to the earlier binary “all-in” injection of sidecars. Users can start with the secure L4 overlay, which offers a majority of features that people deploy Istio for (mTLS, authorization policy, and telemetry). Complex L7 handling such as retries, traffic splitting, load balancing, and observability collection can then be enabled on a case-by-case basis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;rapid-exploration-and-adoption-of-ambient-mode&#34;&gt;Rapid exploration and adoption of ambient mode&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#rapid-exploration-and-adoption-of-ambient-mode&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ztunnel image on Docker Hub has reached over&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hub.docker.com/search?q=istio&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;1 million downloads&lt;/a&gt;, with ~63,000 pulls in the last week alone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/ztunnel-image.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/ztunnel-image.png&#34; alt=&#34;Docker Hub downloads of Istio ztunnel!&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We asked a few of our users for their thoughts on ambient mode’s GA:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio’s implementation of a service mesh with their ambient mesh design has been a great addition to our Kubernetes clusters to simplify the team responsibilities and overall network architecture of the mesh. In conjunction with the Gateway API project it has given me a great way to enable developers to get their networking needs met at the same time as only delegating as much control as needed. While it’s a rapidly evolving project it has been solid and dependable in production and will be our default option for implementing networking controls in a Kubernetes deployment going forth. —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://uk.linkedin.com/in/danielloader&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Daniel Loader&lt;/a&gt;, Lead Platform Engineer at Quotech&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is incredibly easy to install ambient mesh with the Helm chart wrapper. Migrating is as simple as setting up a waypoint gateway, updating labels on a namespace, and restarting. I’m looking forward to ditching sidecars and recuperating resources. Moreover, easier upgrades. No more restarting deployments! —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/raymond-wong-43baa8a2/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Raymond Wong&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Architect at Forbes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio’s ambient mode has served our production system since it became Beta. We are pleased by its stability and simplicity and are looking forward to additional benefits and features coming together with the GA status. Thanks to the Istio team for the great efforts! — &lt;strong&gt;Saarko Eilers&lt;/strong&gt;, Infrastructure Operations Manager at EISST International Ltd&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By Switching from AWS App Mesh to Istio in ambient mode, we were able to slash about 45% of the running containers just by removing sidecars and SPIRE agent DaemonSets. We gained many benefits, such as reducing compute costs or observability costs related to sidecars, eliminating many of the race conditions related to sidecars startup and shutdown, plus all the out-of-the-box benefits just by migrating, like mTLS, zonal awareness and workload load balancing. —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmad-al-masry-9ab90858/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Ahmad Al-Masry&lt;/a&gt;, DevSecOps Engineering Manager at Harri&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We chose Istio because we’re excited about ambient mesh. Different from other options, with Istio, the transition from sidecar to sidecar-less is not a leap of faith. We can build up our service mesh infrastructure with Istio knowing the path to sidecar-less is a two way door. —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/troydai/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Troy Dai&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Staff Software Engineer at Coinbase&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Extremely proud to see the fast and steady growth of ambient mode to GA, and all the amazing collaboration that took place over the past months to make this happen! We are looking forward to finding out how the new architecture is going to revolutionize the telcos world. —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/faseela-k-42178528/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Faseela K&lt;/a&gt;, Cloud Native Developer at Ericsson&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to see the Istio dataplane evolve with the GA release of ambient mode and are actively evaluating it for our next-generation infrastructure platform. Istio’s community is dynamic and welcoming, and ambient mesh is a testament to the community embracing new ideas and pragmatically working to improve developer experience operating Istio at scale. —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/tylerschade/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Tyler Schade&lt;/a&gt;, Distinguished Engineer at GEICO Tech&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Istio’s ambient mode reaching GA, we finally have a service mesh solution that isn’t tied to the pod lifecycle, addressing a major limitation of sidecar-based models. Ambient mesh provides a more lightweight, scalable architecture that simplifies operations and reduces our infrastructure costs by eliminating the resource overhead of sidecars. —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/bartoszsobieraj/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Bartosz Sobieraj&lt;/a&gt;, Platform Engineer at Spond&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our team chose Istio for its service mesh features and strong alignment with the Gateway API to create a robust Kubernetes-based hosting solution. As we integrated applications into the mesh, we faced resource challenges with sidecar proxies, prompting us to transition to ambient mode in Beta for improved scalability and security. We started with L4 security and observability through ztunnel, gaining automatic encryption of in-cluster traffic and transparent traffic flow monitoring. By selectively enabling L7 features and decoupling the proxy from applications, we achieved seamless scaling and reduced resource utilization and latency. This approach allowed developers to focus on application development, resulting in a more resilient, secure, and scalable platform powered by ambient mode. —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jdcmarques/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Jose Marques&lt;/a&gt;, Senior DevOps at Blip.pt&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are using Istio to ensure strict mTLS L4 traffic in our mesh and we are excited for ambient mode. Compared to sidecar mode it’s a massive save on resources and at the same time it makes configuring things even more simple and transparent. —&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrea-dolfi-58b427128/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Andrea Dolfi&lt;/a&gt;, DevOps Engineer&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-in-scope&#34;&gt;What is in scope?&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#what-is-in-scope&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The general availability of ambient mode means the following things are now considered stable:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/install/&#34;&gt;Installing Istio with support for ambient mode&lt;/a&gt;, with Helm or&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;istioctl&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/add-workloads/&#34;&gt;Adding your workloads to the mesh&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to gain mutual TLS with cryptographic identity,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/l4-policy/&#34;&gt;L4 authorization policies&lt;/a&gt;, and telemetry.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/waypoint/&#34;&gt;Configuring waypoints&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/l7-features/&#34;&gt;use L7 functions&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;such as traffic shifting, request routing, and rich authorization policy enforcement.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Connecting the Istio ingress gateway to workloads in ambient mode, supporting the Kubernetes Gateway APIs and all existing Istio APIs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Using waypoints for controlled mesh egress&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Using&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;istioctl&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;to operate waypoints, and troubleshoot ztunnel &amp;amp; waypoints.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refer to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/releases/feature-stages/#ambient-mode&#34;&gt;feature status page&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;roadmap&#34;&gt;Roadmap&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#roadmap&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are not standing still! There are a number of features that we continue to work on for future releases, including some that are currently in Alpha/Beta.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In our upcoming releases, we expect to move quickly on the following extensions to ambient mode:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Full support for sidecar and ambient mode interoperability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-cluster installations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-network support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;VM support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-about-sidecars&#34;&gt;What about sidecars?&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#what-about-sidecars&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sidecars are not going away, and remain first-class citizens in Istio. You can continue to use sidecars, and they will remain fully supported. While we believe most use cases will be best served with a mesh in ambient mode, the Istio project remains committed to ongoing sidecar mode support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;try-ambient-mode-today&#34;&gt;Try ambient mode today&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#try-ambient-mode-today&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the 1.24 release of Istio and the GA release of ambient mode, it is now easier than ever to try out Istio on your own workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Follow the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/getting-started/&#34;&gt;getting started guide&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to explore ambient mode.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Read our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/&#34;&gt;user guides&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to learn how to incrementally adopt ambient for mutual TLS &amp;amp; L4 authorization policy, traffic management, rich L7 authorization policy, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Explore the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/kialiproject/kiali-2-0-for-istio-2087810f337e&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;new Kiali 2.0 dashboard&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to visualize your mesh.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can engage with the developers in the #ambient channel on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.istio.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;the Istio Slack&lt;/a&gt;, or use the discussion forum on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/istio/discussions&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for any questions you may have.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Solo.io 的 Lin Sun 为 Istio 指导和技术监督委员会发布的项目帖子&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;我们的最新版本标志着环境模式 - 没有 sidecar 的服务网格 - 已经为所有人做好了准备。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很自豪地宣布，Istio 的环境数据平面模式已全面可用，ztunnel、路点和 API 被 Istio TOC 标记为稳定。这标志着 Istio &lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/releases/feature-stages/&#34;&gt;功能阶段进展&lt;/a&gt;的最后阶段，表明环境模式已完全准备好广泛的生产用途。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;环境网格 - 及其使用 Istio 环境模式的参考实现 - &lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2022/introducing-ambient-mesh/&#34;&gt;于 2022 年 9 月宣布&lt; /a&gt;.从那时起，我们的社区投入了 26 个月的辛勤工作和协作，其中包括 Solo.io、Google、Microsoft、Intel、Aviatrix、华为、IBM、Red Hat 和许多其他公司的贡献。 1.24 中的稳定状态表明环境模式的功能现已完全准备好用于广泛的生产工作负载。这对于 Istio 来说是一个巨大的里程碑，使 Istio 在没有 sidecar 的情况下进入生产就绪状态，并&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/overview/dataplane-modes/&#34;&gt;为用户提供了选择&lt;/一个&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;why-ambient-mesh&#34;&gt;为什么使用环境网格？&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches- ga/#why-ambient-mesh&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自 2017 年 Istio 推出以来，我们观察到应用程序对网格功能的需求明显且不断增长，但听说许多用户发现 sidecar 的资源开销和操作复杂性难以克服。 Istio 用户与我们分享的挑战包括 sidecar 在添加应用程序后如何破坏应用程序、每个工作负载对代理的大量 CPU 和内存需求，以及每个新的 Istio 版本都需要重新启动应用程序 Pod 带来的不便。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为一个社区，我们从头开始设计了环境网格来解决这些问题，减轻了希望实现服务网格的用户之前面临的复杂性障碍。新概念被命名为“环境网格”，因为它的设计对您的应用程序是透明的，没有与用户工作负载并置的代理基础设施，不需要对配置进行细微的更改，也不需要重新启动应用程序。在环境模式下，从网格中添加或删除应用程序很简单。您需要做的就是&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/add-workloads/&#34;&gt;标记一个命名空间&lt;/a&gt;，该命名空间中的所有应用程序都会立即添加到网格中。这会立即使用行业标准的双向 TLS 加密来保护该命名空间内的所有流量 - 无需其他配置或重新启动！请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2022/introducing-ambient-mesh/&#34;&gt;介绍 Ambient Mesh 博客&lt;/a&gt;，了解有关我们为何构建 Istio 环境模式的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;how-does-ambient-mode-make-adoption-easier&#34;&gt;环境模式如何让采用变得更容易？&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio. io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#how-does-ambient-mode-make-adoption-easier&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;环境网格背后的核心创新在于，它将第 4 层 (L4) 和第 7 层 (L7) 处理分割为两个不同的层。 Istio 的环境模式由轻量级共享 L4 节点代理和可选的 L7 代理提供支持，从而消除了数据平面对传统 sidecar 代理的需求。这种分层方法允许您逐步采用 Istio，实现从无网格到安全覆盖 (L4)，再到可选的完整 L7 处理的平滑过渡 - 根据需要，在整个队列中基于每个命名空间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过利用环境网格，用户绕过了 sidecar 模型之前的一些限制性元素。服务器发送优先协议现在可以工作，大多数保留端口现在可用，并且容器绕过 sidecar 的能力（无论是恶意还是非恶意）都被消除了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;轻量级共享 L4 节点代理称为 &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/overview/#ztunnel&#34;&gt;ztunnel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em &gt;（零信任隧道）。 ztunnel 无需在集群内过度配置内存和 CPU 来处理预期负载，从而大大降低了运行网格的开销。在某些使用案例中，节省的费用可以超过 90% 或更多，同时仍然使用具有加密身份的双向 TLS、简单的 L4 授权策略和遥测来提供零信任安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;L7 代理称为&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/overview/#waypoint-proxies&#34;&gt;路径点&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;。 Waypoints 处理 L7 功能，例如流量路由、丰富的授权策略实施和企业级弹性。路点在应用程序部署之外运行，并且可以根据您的需求独立扩展，这可以针对整个命名空间或命名空间内的多个服务。与 Sidecar 相比，每个应用程序 Pod 不需要一个路点，并且可以根据其范围有效地扩展路点，从而在大多数情况下节省大量 CPU 和内存。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;L4 安全覆盖层和 L7 处理层之间的分离允许增量采用环境模式数据平面，这与早期的 sidecar 二进制“全部”注​​入形成鲜明对比。用户可以从安全的 L4 覆盖开始，它提供了人们部署 Istio 的大部分功能（mTLS、授权策略和遥测）。然后可以根据具体情况启用复杂的 L7 处理，例如重试、流量分割、负载平衡和可观察性收集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;rapid-exploration-and-adoption-of-ambient-mode&#34;&gt;环境模式的快速探索和采用&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches- ga/#rapid-exploration-and-adoption-of-ambient-mode&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Docker Hub 上的 ztunnel 镜像下载量已超过&lt;a href=&#34;https://hub.docker.com/search?q=istio&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;100 万次&lt;/ a&gt;，仅上周就有约 63,000 次拉动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/ztunnel-image.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img 解码= &#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/ztunnel-image.png&#34; alt=&#34;Docker Hub 下载 Istio z隧道！” referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们询问了一些用户对环境模式的 GA 的看法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio 的服务网格实现及其环境网格设计对我们的 Kubernetes 集群来说是一个很好的补充，可以简化网格的团队职责和整体网络架构。与 Gateway API 项目相结合，它为我提供了一种很好的方法，使开发人员能够在只委托所需的控制权的同时满足他们的网络需求。虽然这是一个快速发展的项目，但它在生产中一直稳定可靠，并且将成为我们在未来的 Kubernetes 部署中实现网络控制的默认选项。 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://uk.linkedin.com/in/danielloader&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Daniel Loader&lt;/a&gt;，Quotech 首席平台工程师&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用 Helm 图表包装器安装环境网格非常容易。迁移就像设置路径点网关、更新命名空间上的标签以及重新启动一样简单。我期待着放弃边车并恢复资源。此外，升级更容易。不再需要重新启动部署！ — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/raymond-wong-43baa8a2/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Raymond Wong&lt;/a&gt;，福布斯高级架构师&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio 的环境模式自 Beta 版以来一直为我们的生产系统服务。我们对其稳定性和简单性感到满意，并期待着 GA 状态带来更多好处和功能。感谢 Istio 团队的付出！ — &lt;strong&gt;Saarko Eilers&lt;/strong&gt;，EISST International Ltd 基础设施运营经理&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过在环境模式下从 AWS App Mesh 切换到 Istio，我们只需删除 sidecar 和 SPIRE 代理 DaemonSet，就能减少大约 45% 的正在运行的容器。我们获得了许多好处，例如降低与 sidecar 相关的计算成本或可观测性成本，消除与 sidecar 启动和关闭相关的许多竞争条件，以及仅通过迁移即可获得的所有开箱即用的好处，例如 mTLS、区域感知和工作负载负载平衡。 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmad-al-masry-9ab90858/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Ahmad Al-Masry&lt;/a&gt;，DevSecOps 工程哈里经理&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们选择 Istio 是因为我们对环境网格感到兴奋。与其他选择不同，对于 Istio，从 sidecar 到无 sidecar 的转变并不是信仰的飞跃。我们可以使用 Istio 构建我们的服务网格基础设施，因为我们知道通往无 sidecar 的道路是双向的。 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/troydai/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Troy Dai&lt;/a&gt;，Coinbase 高级软件工程师&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;非常自豪地看到环境模式快速稳定地发展到正式版，以及过去几个月为实现这一目标而进行的所有令人惊叹的合作！我们期待着了解新架构将如何彻底改变电信世界。 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/faseela-k-42178528/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Faseela K&lt;/a&gt;，爱立信云原生开发人员&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们很高兴看到 Istio 数据平面随着环境模式的 GA 版本而不断发展，并正在积极评估它是否适合我们的下一代基础设施平台。 Istio 的社区充满活力且热情好客，环境网格证明了社区拥抱新想法并务实地致力于改善大规模操作 Istio 的开发人员体验。 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/tylerschade/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Tyler Schade&lt;/a&gt;，GEICO Tech 杰出工程师&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着 Istio 的环境模式达到 GA，我们终于有了一个与 Pod 生命周期无关的服务网格解决方案，解决了基于 Sidecar 的模型的主要限制。 Ambient Mesh 提供了更轻量级、可扩展的架构，通过消除 sidecar 的资源开销来简化操作并降低基础设施成本。 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/bartoszsobieraj/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Bartosz Sobieraj&lt;/a&gt;，Spond 平台工程师&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的团队选择 Istio 是因为它的服务网格功能以及与网关 API 的强大一致性，以创建强大的基于 Kubernetes 的托管解决方案。当我们将应用程序集成到网格中时，我们面临着 sidecar 代理的资源挑战，促使我们在 Beta 版中过渡到环境模式，以提高可扩展性和安全性。我们首先通过 ztunnel 实现 L4 安全性和可观察性，获得集群内流量的自动加密和透明的流量监控。通过有选择地启用 L7 功能并将代理与应用程序解耦，我们实现了无缝扩展并降低了资源利用率和延迟。这种方法使开发人员能够专注于应用程序开发，从而形成由环境模式支持的更具弹性、安全性和可扩展性的平台。 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jdcmarques/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Jose Marques&lt;/a&gt;，Blip.pt 高级开发运营&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;wp-block-quote is-style-smaller-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在使用 Istio 来确保网格中严格的 mTLS L4 流量，并且我们对环境模式感到兴奋。与 sidecar 模式相比，它可以节省大量资源，同时使配置变得更加简单和透明。 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrea-dolfi-58b427128/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Andrea Dolfi&lt;/a&gt;，DevOps 工程师&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-in-scope&#34;&gt;范围是什么？&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient -reaches-ga/#what-is-in-scope&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;环境模式的普遍可用性意味着以下内容现在被认为是稳定的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/install/&#34;&gt;使用 Helm 或 &lt;code&gt;istioctl&lt;/code 安装支持环境模式的 Istio&lt;/a&gt; &gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/add-workloads/&#34;&gt;将您的工作负载添加到网格&lt;/a&gt;以获取具有加密身份的相互 TLS， &lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/l4-policy/&#34;&gt;L4 授权策略&lt;/a&gt;和遥测。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/waypoint/&#34;&gt;将路径点配置&lt;/a&gt;至&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio. io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/l7-features/&#34;&gt;使用 L7 功能&lt;/a&gt;，例如流量转移、请求路由和丰富的授权策略实施。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在环境模式下将 Istio 入口网关连接到工作负载，支持 Kubernetes 网关 API 和所有现有的 Istio API。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用路径点控制网格出口&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用 &lt;code&gt;istioctl&lt;/code&gt; 操作路径点，并对 ztunnel 和路径点进行故障排除ts。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/releases/feature-stages/#ambient-mode&#34;&gt;功能状态页面&lt;/a&gt;了解更多信息。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;roadmap&#34;&gt;路线图&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches-ga/#roadmap&#34;&gt;&lt; /a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们没有坐以待毙！我们将继续在未来的版本中开发许多功能，包括目前处于 Alpha/Beta 版本的一些功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在即将发布的版本中，我们希望快速实现环境模式的以下扩展：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;全面支持 sidecar 和环境模式互操作性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多集群安装&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多网络支持&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;虚拟机支持&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-about-sidecars&#34;&gt;边车怎么样？&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-reaches- ga/#what-about-sidecars&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sidecar 不会消失，并且仍然是 Istio 中的一等公民。您可以继续使用 sidecar，它们将保持完全支持。虽然我们相信大多数用例最好在环境模式下使用网格，但 Istio 项目仍然致力于持续支持 Sidecar 模式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;try-ambient-mode-today&#34;&gt;立即尝试环境模式&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/blog/2024/ambient-到达-ga/#try-ambient-mode-today&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着 Istio 1.24 版本和环境模式的 GA 版本的发布，现在在您自己的工作负载上尝试 Istio 变得比以往更加容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;按照&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/getting-started/&#34;&gt;入门指南&lt;/a&gt;探索微光模式。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;阅读我们的&lt;a href=&#34;https://preliminary.istio.io/latest/docs/ambient/usage/&#34;&gt;用户指南&lt;/a&gt;，了解如何逐步采用环境来实现双向 TLS 和 L4 授权政策、流量管理、丰富的L7授权策略等等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;探索&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/kialiproject/kiali-2-0-for-istio-2087810f337e&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;新的 Kiali 2.0 仪表板&lt;/ a&gt; 可视化您的网格。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.istio.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;Istio Slack&lt;/a&gt;上的#ambient频道与开发者互动，或者使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/istio/istio/discussions&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; 上的讨论论坛解答您可能遇到的任何问题有。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【CNCF welcomes wasmCloud to the CNCF Incubator】CNCF 欢迎 wasmCloud 加入 CNCF 孵化器</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/12/cncf-welcomes-wasmcloud-to-the-cncf-incubator/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The CNCF Technical Oversight Committee (TOC) has voted to accept wasmCloud as a CNCF incubating project.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.com/&#34;&gt;wasmCloud&lt;/a&gt;, an open source project from the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), enables teams to build and run polyglot applications made up of reusable WebAssembly (Wasm) components. This allows applications to operate resiliently and efficiently across diverse environments—in the cloud, on Kubernetes, in data centers, or at the edge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By using Wasm as the application artifact, wasmCloud decouples applications from underlying infrastructure, freeing developers to focus on feature development. It provides the tools to run Wasm components securely and efficiently and—instead of forcing thousands of developers to maintain the same libraries and capabilities in their applications—create a &lt;strong&gt;single set of reusable core applications&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“wasmCloud is a platform for platform engineers. It orchestrates componentized applications in a way that complements Kubernetes,” said Liam Randall, wasmCloud co-founder and Cosmonic CEO. “While Kubernetes abstracts and manages infrastructure, wasmCloud functions as a distributed application control plane, managing applications at scale. It integrates with Kubernetes, allowing organizations to extend their Kubernetes deployments to remote edges which maximizes the value of existing investments. We are humbled by the end user adoption and excited to see wasmCloud make this big move to the Incubator.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The project was created by Liam Randall and Kevin Hoffman during their time at a top 10 US bank. The project is currently led by Cosmonic CTO and Bytecode Alliance Technical Steering Committee member Bailey Hayes. wasmCloud was designed to solve the friction that application teams face in every enterprise when writing software and it has grown in popularity since being accepted into the CNCF Sandbox; it is now being deployed and maintained by engineers working in a host of organizations including Adobe, Orange, MachineMetrics, TM Forum member CSPs, and Akamai.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since joining the CNCF Sandbox, wasmCloud has matured and grown in popularity:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enterprise-readiness:&lt;/strong&gt; Built around new standards, wasmCloud 1.0 was released in early 2024 as a stable, production-ready platform. The project has now reached release 1.4 and is full of DevEx improvements that bring parity to the Wasm developer experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Standards-first:&lt;/strong&gt; wasmCloud was one of the first to bring support for wasip2 and embrace the Wasm Component Model. This makes it the most open, secure, stable, and standards-led ecosystem for deploying and orchestrating distributed applications in production.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Native and CNCF integration:&lt;/strong&gt; wasmCloud integrates with a host of CNCF projects. wasmCloud is powered by &lt;strong&gt;NATS&lt;/strong&gt;; it also integrates with 20+ cloud native tools including &lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Open Policy Agent&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Argo&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Couchbase&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Kafka&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Grafana&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Azure blobstore&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.com/docs/integrations/&#34;&gt;and more&lt;/a&gt;. It is also possible to distribute artifacts using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-runtime.cncf.io/wgs/wasm/deliverables/wasm-oci-artifact/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open Container Initiative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (OCI).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Industrial adoption:&lt;/strong&gt; wasmCloud is deployed in a wide variety of sectors and use cases, from industrial IoT and automotive to digital services and banking, with more use cases emerging all the time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community growth&lt;/strong&gt;: In the last 12 months, the wasmCloud community has grown significantly. wasmCloud now has over 100 regular contributors, with overall contributions rising by 300% since 2021.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adoption is growing amongst engineering teams working in a variety of sectors, attracted by the possibility of simplifying the way they build, run, and maintain applications at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adobe&lt;/strong&gt;. With the aim to improve infrastructure efficiency, performance, and lower costs, Colin Murphy and Sean Isom conducted a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2022/11/17/better-together-a-kubernetes-and-wasm-case-study/&#34;&gt;successful project&lt;/a&gt; that brought wasmCloud together with Kubernetes to create agility and efficiency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TM Forum Catalyst Project.&lt;/strong&gt; A group of international CSPs and their integration partners &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/01/05/bringing-webassembly-to-telecoms-with-cncf-wasmcloud/&#34;&gt;brought wasmCloud to telecoms&lt;/a&gt;. WebAssembly Canvas Phase I proved that wasmCloud could be a credible alternative to Kubernetes in managing TM Forum’s estate of open APIs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MachineMetrics.&lt;/strong&gt; Industrial IoT engineers Jochen Rau and Tyle Schoppe completed a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/08/23/wasmcloud-on-the-factory-floor-efficient-and-secure-processing-of-high-velocity-machine-data/&#34;&gt;successful PoC&lt;/a&gt; proving the ability to run high-frequency data workloads as components, on edge devices running in wasmCloud.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orange&lt;/strong&gt;. Orange’s successful experiment showed wasmCloud to be capable of scaling applications to the edge and beyond. This &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1sWQqgK-79c&#34;&gt;Wasm Day talk&lt;/a&gt; explores the practical experiments undertaken.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BMW&lt;/strong&gt; has been testing machine learning applications with wasmCloud for some time. In &lt;a href=&#34;https://cfp.cloud-native.rejekts.io/cloud-native-rejekts-eu-valencia-2022/talk/NXLTRQ/&#34;&gt;early forays&lt;/a&gt;, engineers deployed a common code base, for use with inference engines like Tensorflow or ONNX, on embedded devices, LAN workstations, and the cloud.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Akamai&lt;/strong&gt;. Adobe’s Colin Murphy and Akamai’s Doug Rodrigues recently joined forces to explore the benefits of running wasmCloud at the edge. Check out their recent &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/B1Q_Xx5i6Ek&#34;&gt;appearance on Cloud Native Live&lt;/a&gt; for more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“wasmCloud is the most ambitious project around. It is attempting to revolutionize how software is developed, architected, and run, all while staying at the forefront of wider WebAssembly and WASI standards. I’m so proud of the team that has done so much over the past 4 years to get it to this point. The smartest and kindest group of people you’d ever want to work with.” – Colin Murphy, wasmCloud maintainer and Senior Software Engineer, Adobe&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“CNCF incubation is a confirmation of the strength of the wasmCloud project and community. It has taken a lot of work to gain the right reputation within the wider cloud native landscape, and it’s paying off in project maturity, integrations and success stories. I’m incredibly grateful to our industry partners who pioneered real-world Wasm use cases. Incubation is a real indicator that wasmCloud is ready to integrate into any cloud native stack. I truly believe that a successful community makes a successful project, and I’m so proud of where we are today.” – Brooks Townsend, wasmCloud maintainer and Senior Engineer at Cosmonic&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“As a longtime maintainer and contributor to CNCF projects, I am thrilled that wasmCloud has made it to incubating status. This is the culmination of 5 years of work from an ever-growing community that represents so many different parts of the technology landscape. The contributions that wasmCloud has made to the wider ecosystem and the adoption we see across software platforms, banking, IoT, and more is something that makes me extremely proud.”– Taylor Thomas, wasmCloud maintainer and engineering director, Cosmonic&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“wasmCloud helps us build complex systems with a new perspective; it gives us a way to distribute workloads, compute, and feature requests in a way that just wasn’t possible before. A team of any size can start to see benefits very early in the development cycle.” – Luke Jones, Lattica co-founder and developer&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I am so excited to see wasmCloud enter incubating and sit alongside other major incubating and graduated projects like Kubernetes and Knative in the scheduling and orchestration section of the CNCF landscape. Components offer a fundamentally finer-grained abstraction than containers, like Kubernetes for WebAssembly, so wasmCloud provides a Wasm-native orchestrator to best take advantage of the unique properties that WebAssembly components can provide. Wasm-native works with cloud-native and runs seamlessly on Kubernetes or any other container execution engine like AWS Fargate, Microsoft AKS, or Google Cloud Run.” – Bailey Hayes, TSC director for Bytecode Alliance foundation, W3C WASI SG chair, CTO at Cosmonic&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“wasmCloud’s acceptance into the CNCF incubator is a major milestone, marking the beginning of a new phase—one of collaboration, innovation, and the spread of WebAssembly across industries. It’s also a testament to the dedication of the entire community in pioneering the cloud-native Wasm space, and I’m proud to contribute towards expanding its ecosystem.”– Aditya Sal, wasmCloud contributor&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Components:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Declarative WebAssembly Orchestration.&lt;/strong&gt; The wasmCloud Application Deployment Manager (wadm) orchestrates the deployment and management of Wasm applications, at any scale or location.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seamless Distributed Networking.&lt;/strong&gt; Powered by NATS, wasmCloud network has a flat topology that enables application components to communicate exactly the same, whether they are running on a single machine or globally distributed at scale.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distributed Support with wRPC.&lt;/strong&gt; wRPC (WIT over Remote Procedure Call) is protocol agnostic and makes distributed computing in wasmCloud feel like composing components over the lattice.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Polished DevEx.&lt;/strong&gt; wash dev is a CLI tool that brings the hot reload experience developers expect.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support for Multiple Languages.&lt;/strong&gt; wasmCloud abstracts away vendor and language considerations from software development.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Completely OTEL Observable. &lt;/strong&gt;wasmCloud has full OTEL support for traces, logs and metrics, the 3 pillars of observability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure By-Default.&lt;/strong&gt; Having passed the &lt;a href=&#34;https://ostif.org/ostif-has-completed-a-security-audit-of-wasmcloud/&#34;&gt;OSTIF/Trail of Bits security audit&lt;/a&gt;, new features cement the commitment to security.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notable Milestones:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2,900+ GitHub Stars&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;100+ contributors representing 73 unique &lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.devstats.cncf.io/d/5/companies-table?orgId=1&#34;&gt;companies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Average 1500 monthly contributions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3,200 contributions in September 2024 alone&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Average 111 merged PRs per month&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Growing and active community:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;780+ community members engaging on Slack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;50% increase in Community Meeting attendance over 12 months&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;23,500 YouTube views over the last 3 months alone&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;wasmCloud has several features and functionalities on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/orgs/wasmCloud/projects/7/views/12&#34;&gt;roadmap&lt;/a&gt; for Q4 and beyond including mult-tenancy, standards alignment, and deeper language support. Previous roadmaps can be viewed in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.com/docs/roadmap/&#34;&gt;wasmCloud roadmap&lt;/a&gt; section in wasmCloud documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a CNCF-hosted project, wasmCloud is part of a neutral foundation aligned with its technical interests, as well as the larger Linux Foundation, which provides governance, marketing support, and community outreach. wasmCloud joins incubating technologies Artifact Hub, Backstage, Buildpacks, cert-manager, Chaos Mesh, CloudEvents, Container Network Interface (CNI), Contour, Cortex, CubeFS, Dragonfly, Emissary-Ingress, Falco, Flatcar, gRPC, in-toto, Keptn, Keycloak, Knative, Kubeflow, KubeVela, KubeVirt, Kyverno, Litmus, Longhorn, NATS, Notary, OpenCost, OpenFeature, OpenKruise, OpenMetrics, OpenTelemetry, Operator Framework, Thanos, and Volcano. For more information on maturity requirements for each level, please visit the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/blob/main/process/graduation_criteria.md&#34;&gt;CNCF Graduation Criteria&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;CNCF 技术监督委员会 (TOC) 已投票同意 wasmCloud 作为 CNCF 孵化项目。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.com/&#34;&gt;wasmCloud&lt;/a&gt; 是云原生计算基金会 (CNCF) 的开源项目，使团队能够构建和运行由可重用组成的多语言应用程序WebAssembly (Wasm) 组件。这使得应用程序能够在不同的环境中弹性、高效地运行——在云端、Kubernetes、数据中心或边缘。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过使用 Wasm 作为应用程序工件，wasmCloud 将应用程序与底层基础设施解耦，使开发人员能够专注于功能开发。它提供了安全、高效地运行 Wasm 组件的工具，并且创建&lt;strong&gt;一组可重用的核心应用程序&lt;/strong&gt;，而不是强迫成千上万的开发人员在其应用程序中维护相同的库和功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“wasmCloud 是一个面向平台工程师的平台。它以补充 Kubernetes 的方式编排组件化应用程序。”wasmCloud 联合创始人兼 Cosmonic 首席执行官 Liam Randall 说道。 “Kubernetes 抽象并管理基础设施，而 wasmCloud 则充当分布式应用程序控制平面，大规模管理应用程序。它与 Kubernetes 集成，允许组织将其 Kubernetes 部署扩展到远程边缘，从而最大限度地提高现有投资的价值。我们对最终用户的采用感到谦卑，并很高兴看到 wasmCloud 向孵化器迈出这一重大一步。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该项目由利亚姆·兰德尔 (Liam Randall) 和凯文·霍夫曼 (Kevin Hoffman) 在美国十大银行任职期间创建。该项目目前由 Cosmonic CTO 和字节码联盟技术指导委员会成员 Bailey Hayes 领导。 wasmCloud 旨在解决每个企业的应用程序团队在编写软件时面临的摩擦，自从被 CNCF 沙箱接受以来，它越来越受欢迎；它现在由 Adob​​e、Orange、MachineMetrics、TM 论坛成员 CSP 和 Akamai 等许多组织的工程师部署和维护。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自从加入 CNCF 沙箱以来，wasmCloud 已经成熟并越来越受欢迎：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;企业就绪&lt;/strong&gt;：wasmCloud 1.0 围绕新标准构建，于 2024 年初作为稳定的生产就绪平台发布。该项目现已发布 1.4 版本，并充满了 DevEx 改进，为 Wasm 开发者体验带来了同等的体验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标准优先：&lt;/strong&gt;wasmCloud 是最早支持 wasip2 并采用 Wasm 组件模型的公司之一。这使其成为用于在生产中部署和编排分布式应用程序的最开放、安全、稳定且以标准为主导的生态系统。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云原生和 CNCF 集成：&lt;/strong&gt;wasmCloud 与许多 CNCF 项目集成。 wasmCloud 由 &lt;strong&gt;NATS&lt;/strong&gt; 提供支持；它还集成了 20 多个云原生工具，包括 &lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;开放策略代理&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;Argo&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt; &gt;Couchbase&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;Kafka&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;Grafana&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;Azure blobstore&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https: //wasmcloud.com/docs/integrations/&#34;&gt;以及更多&lt;/a&gt;。还可以使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-runtime.cncf.io/wgs/wasm/deliverables/wasm-oci-artifact/&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;开放容器计划&lt;/strong&gt;来分发工件&lt;/a&gt;（OCI）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;工业采用：&lt;/strong&gt;wasmCloud 部署在各种行业和用例中，从工业物联网和汽车到数字服务和银行业，而且更多用例不断涌现。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;社区发展&lt;/strong&gt;：在过去 12 个月中，wasmCloud 社区发展显着。 wasmCloud 目前拥有 100 多名定期贡献者，自 2021 年以来总体贡献量增长了 300%。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于能够简化大规模构建、运行和维护应用程序的方式，各行业的工程团队越来越多地采用该技术。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adobe&lt;/strong&gt;。为了提高基础设施效率、性能并降低成本，Colin Murphy 和 Sean Isom 开展了一项&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2022/11/17/better-together-a- kubernetes-and-wasm-case-study/&#34;&gt;成功的项目&lt;/a&gt;，将 wasmCloud 与 Kubernetes 结合在一起，以创造敏捷性和效率。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TM Forum Catalyst 项目。&lt;/strong&gt;一组国际 CSP 及其集成合作伙伴&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/01/05/bringing-web assembly -to-telecoms-with-cncf-wasmcloud/&#34;&gt;将 wasmCloud 引入电信&lt;/a&gt;。 WebAssembly Canvas 第一阶段证明，在管理 TM Forum 的开放 API 资产方面，wasmCloud 可以成为 Kubernetes 的可靠替代方案。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MachineMetrics。&lt;/strong&gt;工业物联网工程师 Jochen Rau 和 Tyle Schoppe 完成了&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/08/23/wasmcloud-on-the -factory-floor-efficient-and-secure-processing-of-high-velocity-machine-data/&#34;&gt;成功的 PoC&lt;/a&gt; 证明能够在 wasmCloud 中运行的边缘设备上将高频数据工作负载作为组件运行。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;橙色&lt;/strong&gt;。 Orange 的成功实验表明 wasmCloud 能够将应用程序扩展到边缘甚至更远的地方。这个&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1sWQqgK-79c&#34;&gt;Wasm Day 演讲&lt;/a&gt;探讨了所进行的实际实验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BMW&lt;/strong&gt; 一直在使用 wasmCloud 测试机器学习应用程序。在&lt;a href=&#34;https://cfp.cloud-native.rejekts.io/cloud-native-rejekts-eu-valencia-2022/talk/NXLTRQ/&#34;&gt;早期尝试&lt;/a&gt;中，工程师部署了通用代码基础，与 Tensorflow 或 ONNX 等推理引擎一起使用，在嵌入式设备上，洛杉矶N 个工作站和云。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Akamai&lt;/strong&gt;。 Adobe 的 Colin Murphy 和 Akamai 的 Doug Rodrigues 最近联手探索在边缘运行 wasmCloud 的好处。查看他们最近&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtu.be/B1Q_Xx5i6Ek&#34;&gt;在 Cloud Native Live 上的亮相&lt;/a&gt;了解更多信息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“wasmCloud 是最雄心勃勃的项目。它试图彻底改变软件的开发、架构和运行方式，同时保持在更广泛的 WebAssembly 和 WASI 标准的前沿。我为这个团队感到非常自豪，他们在过去 4 年里付出了如此多的努力才取得了今天的成就。他们是你想与之共事的最聪明、最友善的一群人。” – Colin Murphy，wasmCloud 维护者兼 Adob​​e 高级软件工程师&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“CNCF 孵化是对 wasmCloud 项目和社区实力的确认。为了在更广泛的云原生环境中获得正确的声誉，我们付出了大量的努力，并且在项目成熟度、集成和成功案例方面得到了回报。我非常感谢我们的行业合作伙伴，他们开创了现实世界的 Wasm 用例。孵化是 wasmCloud 已准备好集成到任何云原生堆栈的真实指标。我坚信，一个成功的社区才能打造一个成功的项目，我为我们今天的成就感到非常自豪。” – Brooks Townsend，wasmCloud 维护者兼 Cosmonic 高级工程师&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“作为 CNCF 项目的长期维护者和贡献者，我很高兴 wasmCloud 已进入孵化状态。这是一个不断发展的社区 5 年工作的结晶，该社区代表了技术领域的许多不同部分。 wasmCloud 对更广泛的生态系统做出的贡献以及我们在软件平台、银行、物联网等领域看到的采用让我感到非常自豪。”——Taylor Thomas，wasmCloud 维护者兼 Cosmonic 工程总监&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“wasmCloud 帮助我们以新的视角构建复杂的系统；它为我们提供了一种以以前不可能的方式分配工作负载、计算和功能请求的方法。任何规模的团队都可以在开发周期的早期就开始看到好处。” – Luke Jones，Lattica 联合创始人兼开发人员&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我很高兴看到 wasmCloud 进入孵化阶段，并与 Kubernetes 和 Knative 等其他主要孵化和毕业项目并列 CNCF 领域的调度和编排部分。组件提供了比容器更细粒度的抽象，例如用于 WebAssembly 的 Kubernetes，因此 wasmCloud 提供了 Wasm 原生编排器，以最好地利用 WebAssembly 组件可以提供的独特属性。 Wasm-native 与云原生配合使用，并在 Kubernetes 或任何其他容器执行引擎（例如 AWS Fargate、Microsoft AKS 或 Google Cloud Run）上无缝运行。” – Bailey Hayes，字节码联盟 TSC 总监undation，W3C WASI SG 主席，Cosmonic 首席技术官&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“wasmCloud 被 CNCF 孵化器接受是一个重要的里程碑，标志着一个新阶段的开始——协作、创新以及 WebAssembly 跨行业的传播。这也证明了整个社区在开拓云原生 Wasm 领域的奉献精神，我很自豪能够为扩展其生态系统做出贡献。”——Aditya Sal，wasmCloud 贡献者&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;主要组件：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;声明式 WebAssembly 编排。&lt;/strong&gt; wasmCloud 应用程序部署管理器 (wadm) 编排任何规模或位置的 Wasm 应用程序的部署和管理。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;无缝分布式网络。&lt;/strong&gt;wasmCloud 网络由 NATS 提供支持，具有扁平拓扑，使应用程序组件能够进行完全相同的通信，无论它们是在单台计算机上运行还是大规模分布在全球。&lt;/李&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;wRPC 的分布式支持。&lt;/strong&gt;wRPC（基于远程过程调用的 WIT）与协议无关，使得 wasmCloud 中的分布式计算感觉就像在网格上组合组件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;完善了 DevEx。&lt;/strong&gt;wash dev 是一个 CLI 工具，可以带来开发人员期望的热重载体验。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;支持多种语言。&lt;/strong&gt;wasmCloud 从软件开发中抽象出了供应商和语言的考虑因素。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;完全 OTEL 可观察。 &lt;/strong&gt;wasmCloud 对跟踪、日志和指标（可观察性的三大支柱）提供全面的 OTEL 支持。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;默认安全。&lt;/strong&gt;已通过 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ostif.org/ostif-has-completed-a-security-audit-of-wasmcloud/&#34;&gt;OSTIF /Trail of Bits 安全审计&lt;/a&gt;，新功能巩固了对安全的承诺。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;值得注意的里程碑：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;超过 2,900 名 GitHub 明星&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;100 多名贡献者代表 73 家独特的&lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.devstats.cncf.io/d/5/companies-table?orgId=1&#34;&gt;公司&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;平均每月捐款 1500 美元&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;仅 2024 年 9 月就有 3,200 份捐款&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;每月平均合并 111 个 PR&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;不断发展且活跃的社区：&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;780 多名社区成员参与 Slack&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;12 个月内社区会议出席率增加了 50%&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;仅过去 3 个月就有 23,500 次 YouTube 观看次数&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;wasmCloud 在第四季度及以后的&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/orgs/wasmCloud/projects/7/views/12&#34;&gt;路线图&lt;/a&gt;上拥有多项特性和功能，包括多租户、标准一致和更深入的语言支持。之前的路线图可以在 wasmCloud 文档的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://wasmcloud.com/docs/roadmap/&#34;&gt;wasmCloud 路线图&lt;/a&gt;部分查看。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为 CNCF 托管的项目，wasmCloud是与其技术利益一致的中立基金会以及更大的 Linux 基金会的一部分，该基金会提供治理、营销支持和社区外展。 wasmCloud 加入孵化技术 Artifact Hub、Backstage、Buildpacks、cert-manager、Chaos Mesh、CloudEvents、容器网络接口 (CNI)、Contour、Cortex、CubeFS、Dragonfly、Emissary-Ingress、Falco、Flatcar、gRPC、in-toto、Keptn 、Keycloak、Knative、Kubeflow、KubeVela、KubeVirt、Kyverno、Litmus、Longhorn、NATS、Notary、OpenCost、OpenFeature、OpenKruise、OpenMetrics、OpenTelemetry、Operator Framework、Thanos 和 Volcano。有关每个级别的成熟度要求的更多信息，请访问&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/blob/main/process/graduation_criteria.md&#34;&gt;CNCF 毕业标准&lt;/a&gt;。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes RBAC: improve the K8s security posture】Kubernetes RBAC：改善 K8s 安全状况</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/08/kubernetes-rbac-improve-the-k8s-security-posture/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Member post originally published on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-rbac-improve-the-k8s-security-posture/&#34;&gt;Devtron blog &lt;/a&gt;by &lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/author/siddhant-khisty/&#34;&gt;Siddhant Khisty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;TL;DR: Secure your Kubernetes cluster with Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) to define granular permissions for users and applications. This guide explains how to implement RBAC in Kubernetes and introduces Devtron, a dashboard simplifying RBAC management.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While working with Kubernetes, the cluster has many tiny internal components that all work together to deploy and manage your business applications. Kubernetes itself is a distributed system, consisting of tons of different components that work together to provide the experience that we are all familiar with. To learn about all those different Kubernetes components, please check out our blog on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-architecture-the-ultimate-guide/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kubernetes Architecture&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and the different&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/what-are-kubernetes-workloads/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kubernetes Workloads&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a traditional monolithic application, your main concerns would be ensuring that your application code is written securely and that the environment where it is deployed is secure and has the necessary firewalls and security permissions set up. When talking about security in Kubernetes, the story gets a lot more distributed. Since many different components work together to create and operate a cluster, you need to ensure that each individual component is secure. You have to set up proper mTLS between all the different Kubernetes components.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you deploy your business applications, will have to once again ensure that it meets your security standards. You also need to ensure that only authorized users have access to the Kubernetes clusters and that they have the correct level of access to the cluster. Luckily, Kubernetes has a way to authenticate users to the cluster and restrict their level of access to the cluster as required.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Within the blog, you will be learning how you can authenticate users to your Kubernetes clusters, and how to restrict their access to the cluster using Role Based Access Control (RBAC).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-role-based-access-control-rbac&#34;&gt;What is Role Based Access Control (RBAC)?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whenever a user has access to any systems, in this case, Kubernetes, you do not want every single user to have super-admin levels of access to the cluster. This can pose a security risk. Imagine handing over super-admin access to the production cluster to someone who does not know all the ins and outs of a Kubernetes cluster. There is a possibility that they may unknowingly perform some action that takes the entire cluster offline.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To avoid the above scenario, you want only one or two super-admin users that have unrestricted access to the Kubernetes cluster. Every other user like the developers, should have limited access to the cluster for only the resources they require. For example, if the development team is working on developing a new microservice called backend-beta, they should have access to the specific namespace and resources that are related to the backend-beta application to avoid accidentally messing up any other workloads running in the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An additional benefit of using RBAC is to limit the impact of accidental credential leaks. In the unlikely event that a developer’s credentials are accidentally leaked, the attacker would have very limited access to the information within the cluster. Another step that can be taken to minimize the impact is to implement time-based access. After a certain amount of time, the access would expire and the token which was given to the developer would be rendered useless.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Implementing Role Based Access Control (RBAC) in your Kubernetes systems has multiple benefits such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Better security:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Limiting user access to the cluster, restricting access to only the required resources&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimize the impact of leaked credentials:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Minimizing the impact of leaked cluster credentials as the malicious party would have very limited access to the cluster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Enables organizations to follow set security compliance standards which improves a cluster’s overall security posture&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Granular Control:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Provides the ability to granularly control a user’s access to the cluster and provide only specific permissions that they require&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;levels-of-rbac-permissions-in-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Levels of RBAC Permissions in Kubernetes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whenever you want to allow a user to get access to the Kubernetes cluster, you do not want to give them super admin permissions. Doing so may lead to unintended deletions of resources or a change of configurations. You want to ensure that the user has access to only a few specific resources in the cluster. If you have a developer user, they should only be allowed to access the applications that they are developing in their particular namespace.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, if you had a node admin or a storage admin, they would require access to every single node or every single storage resource across all namespaces in the cluster. What if you have deployed an application to the Kubernetes cluster that requires some permissions to view a particular cluster resource? The application too would need to be assigned the correct level of permissions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes by default has several objects that help satisfy all of the above use cases. These objects include&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roles:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;A role defines a set of permissions that are allowed. It is a namespace-scoped resource. For example, creating and deleting a pod&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RoleBindings:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;A RoleBinding is used to assign the permissions defined in the role to a particular user or application&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ClusterRole:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Similar to a Role, with the key difference that it is a cluster-wide resource&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ClusterRoleBinging:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Same as RoleBinding, with the difference that the permission is applied to every namespace in the cluster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ServiceAccounts:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;When an application needs to be given some permissions, it uses a service account. The actual set of permissions is assigned to the service account object.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will be looking at all the above Kubernetes objects in detail later in this article. First, let us look at how you can add a user to the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;adding-a-user-to-the-cluster&#34;&gt;Adding a user to the Cluster&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before you can go ahead and assign permissions to the cluster, you will first need to authenticate(authN) the user to the Kubernetes cluster. To add the user to the cluster, you must create a Certificate Signing Request (CSR). The cluster signing key will use the user’s public key to authenticate with the cluster.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s say that we want to onboard a new developer named John to the cluster. He has provided us with his public key. Let us create a Certificate Signing Request (CSR) to add John to the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To create a Certificate Signing Request, you will need to paste John’s public key into the manifest file below under&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;spec.request&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: certificates.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: CertificateSigningRequest&#xA;metadata:&#xA; name: john&#xA;spec:&#xA; request: &amp;lt;request&amp;gt;&#xA; signerName: kubernetes.io/kube-apiserver-client&#xA; expirationSeconds: 86400  # one day&#xA; usages:&#xA; - client auth&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve created the above manifest file, go ahead and apply it using&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl apply -f csr.yaml&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upon applying the manifest, a CSR object will be created. You can check all the CSR’s made to the cluster by running&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl get csr&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You should be able to see that John’s CSR has been created, and is pending approval. Since we already know that John is our developer user, we want to accept this request. To do so, you can run the below command&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl csr approve john&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, the user John is authenticated to the cluster and has access to the cluster. The authorization permissions (authZ) still need to be set up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to add users to the cluster with ease, without creating a CSR, you can use an SSO to easily authenticate your users via their GitHub, Google, or Microsoft accounts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/sso-and-rbac-a-secure-access-strategy-for-your-kubernetes/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Please check out this blog to learn more about SSO&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;setting-user-permissions&#34;&gt;Setting User Permissions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that you have added a user to the cluster, it’s time to set up the appropriate level of permissions for the user. As we discussed before, you can set permissions at two levels&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Namespace Scopped permissions using Role &amp;amp; RoleBinding&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cluster Scopped Permissions using ClusterRole &amp;amp; ClusterRoleBinding.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will take a look at how you can create both types of permissions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;role-rolebinding&#34;&gt;Role &amp;amp; RoleBinding&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After a user has been added to the cluster, we can now go ahead and assign certain permissions to them. To do this, Kubernetes provides two objects called a&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;Role&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;RoleBinding&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As discussed earlier, the role defines the set of permissions, and the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;role-binding&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;assigns the role to a particular user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s say that you have a new developer called John who has joined your organization to work on a sensitive project called Project Gamma. In your existing setup, you have a separate namespace called&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;project-gamma&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;for all the resources of the project. You want to allow John to create deployments and pods only in the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;project-gamma&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;namespace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To enforce these rules, you have to create the proper role and role-binding resources. Let’s take a look at how you can create the two objects and assign the correct permissions to John.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Create a role called&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;gamma-developer-role&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;and assign it the proper set of permissions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This can be done imperatively using&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;kubectl&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;or declaratively by using a YAML file. We will be looking at creating the file declaratively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The YAML file below can be used to create the role with the required permissions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: Role&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  namespace: project-gamma&#xA;  name: gamma-developer-role&#xA;rules:&#xA;- apiGroups: [&#34;&#34;]&#xA;  resources: [&#34;pods&#34;]&#xA;  verbs: [&#34;create&#34;, &#34;get&#34;, &#34;list&#34;, &#34;delete&#34;]&#xA;- apiGroups: [&#34;&#34;]&#xA;  resources: [&#34;deployment&#34;]&#xA;  verbs: [&#34;create&#34;, &#34;get&#34;, &#34;list&#34;]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s understand some of the important configuration fields that are described in the above manifest&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Name of the role&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Namespace:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The will be created in this namespace and the permissions and will be limited to it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rules:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;These are the actual permissions that are defined. We can define multiple permissions as needed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API groups:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The API group used for targeting the specific resource. This is useful when there are multiple custom resources&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The particular type of resource that you wish to assign the permissions on.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Verbs:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The particular permission that you wish to allow for the defined resources. You can select between the following verbs: get, create, delete, list, patch, update, watch.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Create a RoleBinding called&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;gamma-developer-binding&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;and configure it to use the correct role and assign the correct user&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the role has been created, it also needs to be assigned to a user. Similar to the role, the RoleBinding can also be created imperatively with the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;kubectl create rolebinding&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;command. We will look at how to make it declaratively using a YAML file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The below YAML file will create the RoleBinding and assign the permissions to John.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: RoleBinding&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: gamma-developer-binding&#xA;  namespace: project-gamma&#xA;subjects:&#xA;- kind: User&#xA;  name: John&#xA;roleRef:&#xA;  kind: Role &#xA;  name: gamma-developer-role&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the above manifest, some of the important configuration fields are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Name of the RoleBinding&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Namespace:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The NameSpace where the RoleBinding will be created. The permissions will be limited to that namespace.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subjects:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The subjects to which the roles should be applied&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;roleRef:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;The permissions of the specific role that should be applied to the Subject.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note:- The Role and RoleBinding are Namespace-scoped resources. They will only work in the namespace where they have been created.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Validate the permissions&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After creating the role and assigning it to the correct user using RoleBinding, it’s time to make sure that the permission works correctly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can use the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;kubectl auth can-i&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;command to ensure that the permissions work correctly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The command will show you if the action that you are trying to run will be successful or not. For example, John should be able to get the pods in the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;project-gamma&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;namespace. But he should not be able to get the pods in the default namespace. We can verify this by running the below two commands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl auth can-i get pods -nproject-gamma --as=John&#xA;&#xA;kubectl auth can-i get pods --as=John&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/1.-k-auth-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;kubectl auth&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig.1] kubectl auth&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see from the above image, John can get the pods in the project-gamma namespace, but cannot get the pods in the default namespace. This is the exact permissions that we wanted to create.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;clusterrole-clusterrolebinding&#34;&gt;ClusterRole &amp;amp; ClusterRoleBinding&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Similar to the Roles and RoleBindings, ClusterRoles, and ClusterRoleBindings can allow certain permissions for a user. The key difference is that the ClusterRole and ClusterRoleBinding will be applied across the entire cluster i.e it will work in every namespace in the cluster. The Roles and RoleBindings on the other hand are limited to the particular namespace they exist in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s look at how to create and assign a ClusterRole and ClusterRoleBinding with an example. Imagine that you have an application called DeploymentManager which is responsible for managing all the Deployments in the cluster. For this application to perform its functions, it needs to have admin permissions for all the Deployments in the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s look at the step-by-step process for how we can assign the right level of permissions for this application&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Create a Service Account&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When we want to assign permissions to a user, we can directly assign it to them. However, when permission has to be applied to an application, it cannot be directly applied to the pod or deployment of the application. Kubernetes has a resource called a Service Account which is a non-human account with a distinct identity. When an application needs certain permissions within the cluster, it is assigned to them via a service account.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let us create a ServiceAccount called&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-sa&lt;/code&gt;. You can create the service account imperatively using the below command.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl create serviceaccount deploy-manager-sa&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You also want to ensure that the application is using this new ServiceAccount. Edit the application’s manifest and update the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;serviceAccount&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;field so that it uses the new service account that has been created.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Creating the ClusterRole&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the application is responsible for managing every single deployment in the cluster, it will require permission to perform all actions on the deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Similar to what we discussed with Roles, ClusterRoles can be created imperatively as well as declaratively. We saw how to create Roles in a declarative manner. Let us create the ClusterRole named&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-cr&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;with the imperative method. You can use the below command to create the ClusterRole with the correct permissions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl create clusterrole deploy-manager-cr --verb=’*’ --resource=deployments&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The above command will allow the Service Account to perform any actions on only the deployment objects. It will not be able to perform any action on any other resource type.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you wish to run the same command using the declarative commands, you can use the following YAML manifest:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: ClusterRole&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: deploy-manager-cr&#xA;rules:&#xA;- apiGroups: [&#34;&#34;]&#xA;  resources: [&#34;deployment&#34;]&#xA;  verbs: [&#34;*&#34;]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 3:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Create the ClusterRoleBinding&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, we want to create a ClusterRoleBinding to assign the ClusterRole to the Service account that we had created. Let us call this ClusterRoleBinding as&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-crb&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will create the ClusterRoleBinding imperatively with&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;kubectl&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;commands. You can use the below command to create the ClusterRoleBinding such that it will use the permissions defined in the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-cr&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;and assign it to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-sa&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;service account&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl create clusterrolebinding deploy-manager-crb --clusterrole=deploy-manager-cr --serviceaccount=default:deploy-manager-sa&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The above command ClusterRoeBinding can also be created declaratively. You can use the following YAML manifest to create the same role using the declarative method.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: ClusterRoleBinding&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: deploy-manager-crb&#xA;subjects:&#xA;- kind: ServiceAccount&#xA;  name: default:deploy-manager-sa&#xA;roleRef:&#xA;  kind: ClusterRole &#xA;  name: deploy-manager-cr&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 4:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Validate the permissions&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Similar to how we validated the permissions for the Roles and ClusterRoles, we also want to validate the permissions for the ClusterRole and ClusterRoleBinding using the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;kubectl auth can-i&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;commands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s see if the ServiceAccount can get the deployments, as well as if it can get individual pods or not. You can use the below commands to try it out&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl auth can-i get deployments --as=system:serviceaccount:default:deploy-manager-sa&#xA;&#xA;kubectl auth can-i get pods --as=system:serviceaccount:default:deploy-manager-sa&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/2.-k-auth-cluster-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;kubectl auth clusterrole&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[Fig.2] kubectl auth clusterrole&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see, the service account can perform actions on deployments, but cannot perform actions on any other resource such as pods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;user-accounts-service-accounts&#34;&gt;User Accounts &amp;amp; Service Accounts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While we were creating the roles and role bindings in the above examples, you may have noticed that when we were assigning the permissions to a user, we directly assigned the permission to the user. However, when we wanted to give some permissions to an application, we had to do it through a service account.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Accounts:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;A user account is an account used by a human. They are intended to be a global resource i.e. they must have a unique name across all namespaces in the cluster. A user account belongs to a cluster operator such as a DevOps engineer or Developer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Accounts:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;A service account is an account used by a non-human i.e it is used by an application. It is a namespace-scoped resource i.e. multiple service accounts can have the same name across different namespaces. A service account is used to assign a set of permissions to applications running inside the pod.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog, you’ve seen the entire process of adding a user to the Kubernetes cluster and adding fine-grained permissions for them using Roles, RoleBindings, ClusterRoles, and ClusterRoleBindings. Kubernetes provides a robust and flexible way to define the permissions for different users and applications. However, certain limitations and challenges do arise when creating the permissions with just the Kubernetes resources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of the challenges with implementing RBAC in Kubernetes are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of Visibility:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;To assign permissions to any user, you need to create multiple resources such as Roles and RoleBindings. It becomes very difficult to understand which role is mapped to which RoleBinding which makes it difficult to properly manage the permissions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manual role assignment:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Whenever a new user is onboarded on the Kubernetes cluster, the roles have to be manually created and assigned to the user. You cannot assign the same set of permissions to a group of users such as the developer users.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Time-based access:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;If you wish to allow access to the cluster for only a limited time, you need to manually assign the permissions, and remove them after a set period. The access does not automatically expire, and the cluster administrator needs to manually remove the permissions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficult to manage at scale:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;As organizations grow, the number of users that have access to the cluster increases. This in turn increases the number of Roles, RoleBindings, ClusterRoles, and ClusterRoleBindings. It becomes very difficult to manage these resources at scale as there are hundreds of them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty in onboarding users:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;When you want to onboard a new user to the cluster, you need to obtain their public keys and create a Certificate Signing Request (CSR). This CSR then needs to be approved by the cluster admin, which becomes a lengthy process. Moreover, the cluster admin needs to ensure that the correct CSR is being approved and no malicious actors get access to the cluster.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron is a robust Kubernetes dashboard that makes it much easier to add users to your Kubernetes cluster by using an SSO service. It also helps you fine-grain the level of access you wish to assign to all your users. Devtron’s permissions groups can help you assign the same permissions to different users, such as all Developer users or Operations users. It also provides the option to set a time-based access to the cluster which ensures that the user has access only for a limited period.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additional reading on how Devtron helps with Kubernetes RBAC:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/sso-and-rbac-a-secure-access-strategy-for-your-kubernetes/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Using SSO for RBAC in Kubernetes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/control-and-secure-kubectl-access/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Securing access to a cluster&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-access-management-made-easy/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kubernetes Access Management made easy with Devtron&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes Security has multiple aspects to it. One of the most important aspects of Kubernetes Security is properly setting up role based access control. Kubernetes RBAC is useful to limit the actions that a user can perform in the Kubernetes cluster. A user is first added to the cluster by creating a CSR request which authenticates(authN) the user with the Kubernetes cluster.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the authentication is done, the user needs to be assigned the proper authorization(authZ) permissions to ensure that they have access only to the resources they require. To set up the authorization permissions in the cluster, Kubernetes provides users with Roles, RoleBindings, ClusterRoles, and ClusterRoleBindings which are useful for setting authorization permissions either at the namespace level or the cluster level.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron is a Kubernetes Dashboard that takes Kubernetes Security one step further by making it easier to create and assign permissions to different users. It also provides permission groups to assign the same set of permissions to a group of users such as the developers. It also helps provide time-based access to particular resources in the cluster and revokes access once the set period has expired.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have any queries, don’t hesitate to&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rebrand.ly/devtron-demo?ref=blog&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;connect with us&lt;/a&gt;. Join the lively discussions and shared knowledge in our actively growing&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rebrand.ly/Devtron-Discord?ref=devtron.ai&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Discord Community&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;成员帖子最初由 &lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-rbac-improve-the-k8s-security-posture/&#34;&gt;Devtron 博客&lt;/a&gt;发布&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/author/siddhant-khisty/&#34;&gt;Siddhant Khisty&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;TL;DR：使用基于角色的访问控制 (RBAC) 保护您的 Kubernetes 集群，为用户和应用程序定义精细的权限。本指南介绍了如何在 Kubernetes 中实现 RBAC，并介绍了 Devtron，这是一个简化 RBAC 管理的仪表板。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在使用 Kubernetes 时，集群具有许多微小的内部组件，它们一起工作来部署和管理您的业务应用程序。 Kubernetes 本身是一个分布式系统，由大量不同的组件组成，这些组件协同工作以提供我们都熟悉的体验。要了解所有这些不同的 Kubernetes 组件，请查看我们的博客：&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-architecture-the-ultimate-guide/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kubernetes 架构&lt;/u &gt;&lt;/a&gt; 以及不同的&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/what-are-kubernetes-workloads/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kubernetes 工作负载&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p &gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在传统的整体应用程序中，您主要关心的是确保应用程序代码的编写安全、部署环境的安全以及设置必要的防火墙和安全权限。当谈论 Kubernetes 中的安全性时，故事变得更加分散。由于许多不同的组件一起工作来创建和操作集群，因此您需要确保每个单独组件的安全。您必须在所有不同的 Kubernetes 组件之间设置正确的 mTLS。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您部署业务应用程序时，将不得不再次确保它满足您的安全标准。您还需要确保只有授权用户才能访问 Kubernetes 集群，并且他们对集群具有正确的访问级别。幸运的是，Kubernetes 有一种方法可以对集群的用户进行身份验证，并根据需要限制他们对集群的访问级别。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在博客中，您将了解如何对 Kubernetes 集群的用户进行身份验证，以及如何使用基于角色的访问控制 (RBAC) 限制他们对集群的访问。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;what-is-role-based-access-control-rbac&#34;&gt;什么是基于角色的访问控制 (RBAC)？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每当用户有权访问任何系统（在本例中为 Kubernetes）时，您不希望每个用户都拥有对集群的超级管理员级别的访问权限。这可能会带来安全风险。想象一下，将对生产集群的超级管理员访问权限移交给不了解 Kubernetes 集群所有细节的人。他们有可能在不知不觉中执行某些操作，导致整个集群脱机。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了避免上述情况，您只需要一两个超级可以不受限制地访问 Kubernetes 集群的管理员用户。其他每个用户（例如开发人员）应该对集群具有有限的访问权限，仅获取他们所需的资源。例如，如果开发团队正在开发一个名为 backend-beta 的新微服务，他们应该有权访问与 backend-beta 应用程序相关的特定命名空间和资源，以避免意外搞乱集群中运行的任何其他工作负载.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用 RBAC 的另一个好处是限制意外凭据泄露的影响。万一开发人员的凭据意外泄露，攻击者对集群内信息的访问权限将非常有限。可以采取的最小化影响的另一个步骤是实施基于时间的访问。一段时间后，访问权限将过期，并且提供给开发者的令牌将变得无用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Kubernetes 系统中实施基于角色的访问控制 (RBAC) 有多种好处，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;更高的安全性：&lt;/strong&gt;限制用户对集群的访问，仅限制对所需资源的访问&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;最大限度地降低凭据泄露的影响&lt;/strong&gt;：最大限度地降低集群凭据泄露的影响，因为恶意方对集群的访问权限非常有限&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;合规性&lt;/strong&gt;：使组织能够遵循既定的安全合规性标准，从而改善集群的整体安全状况&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;精细控制&lt;/strong&gt;：能够精细控制用户对集群的访问，并仅提供他们所需的特定权限&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;levels-of-rbac-permissions-in-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 中的 RBAC 权限级别&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每当您想要允许用户访问 Kubernetes 集群时，您都不希望授予他们超级管理员权限。这样做可能会导致意外删除资源或更改配置。您希望确保用户只能访问集群中的少数特定资源。如果您有开发人员用户，则应仅允许他们访问他们在其特定命名空间中开发的应用程序。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一方面，如果您有节点管理员或存储管理员，他们将需要访问集群中所有命名空间中的每个节点或每个存储资源。如果您已将应用程序部署到 Kubernetes 集群，并且需要某些权限才能查看特定集群资源，该怎么办？该应用程序也需要被分配正确的权限级别。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 默认有几个对象可以帮助满足上述所有用例。这些对象包括&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;角色&lt;/strong&gt;：角色定义一组角色f 允许的权限。它是命名空间范围的资源。例如创建和删除 Pod&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RoleBindings&lt;/strong&gt;：RoleBinding 用于将角色中定义的权限分配给特定用户或应用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ClusterRole：&lt;/strong&gt;与角色类似，主要区别在于它是集群范围的资源&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ClusterRoleBinging：&lt;/strong&gt;与 RoleBinding 相同，不同之处在于权限应用于集群中的每个命名空间&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;服务帐户&lt;/strong&gt;：当应用程序需要获得某些权限时，它会使用服务帐户。实际的权限集分配给服务帐户对象。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将在本文后面详细介绍上述所有 Kubernetes 对象。首先，让我们看看如何将用户添加到集群。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;adding-a-user-to-the-cluster&#34;&gt;将用户添加到集群&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在继续向集群分配权限之前，您首先需要对 Kubernetes 集群的用户进行身份验证 (authN)。要将用户添加到集群，您必须创建证书签名请求 (CSR)。集群签名密钥将使用用户的公钥对集群进行身份验证。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设我们想要将一位名为 John 的新开发人员加入集群。他向我们提供了他的公钥。让我们创建一个证书签名请求 (CSR) 以将 John 添加到集群。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要创建证书签名请求，您需要将 John 的公钥粘贴到下面的清单文件中的 &lt;code&gt;spec.request&lt;/code&gt; 下。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：certificates.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类：证书签名请求&#xA;元数据：&#xA; 姓名：约翰&#xA;规格：&#xA; 请求：&lt;请求&gt;&#xA; 签名者名称：kubernetes.io/kube-apiserver-client&#xA; expirationSeconds: 86400 #一天&#xA; 用途：&#xA; - 客户端授权&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建上述清单文件后，请继续使用&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl apply -f csr.yaml&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;应用清单后，将创建一个 CSR 对象。您可以通过运行来检查对集群所做的所有 CSR&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl 获取 csr&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您应该能够看到 John 的 CSR 已创建，并且正在等待批准。由于我们已经知道 John 是我们的开发人员用户，因此我们希望接受此请求。为此，您可以运行以下命令&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl csr 批准约翰&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，用户 John 已通过集群身份验证并有权访问集群。授权权限（authZ）仍需要设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您想轻松地将用户添加到集群中，而不需要创建 CSR，您可以使用 SSO 通过用户的 GitHub 轻松验证用户身份，Google 或 Microsoft 帐户。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/sso-and-rbac-a-secure-access-strategy-for-your-kubernetes/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;请查看此博客以了解有关 SSO 的更多信息&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;setting-user-permissions&#34;&gt;设置用户权限&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在您已将用户添加到集群中，是时候为该用户设置适当的权限级别了。正如我们之前讨论的，您可以设置两个级别的权限&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用 Role 和 RoleBinding 的命名空间范围权限&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用 ClusterRole 和 ClusterRoleBinding 的集群范围权限。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将了解如何创建这两种类型的权限。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;role-rolebinding&#34;&gt;角色和角色绑定&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将用户添加到集群后，我们现在可以继续为他们分配某些权限。为此，Kubernetes 提供了两个对象，称为 &lt;code&gt;Role&lt;/code&gt; 和 &lt;code&gt;RoleBinding&lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如前所述，角色定义权限集，并且&lt;code&gt;角色绑定&lt;/code&gt;将角色分配给特定用户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设您有一位名叫 John 的新开发人员，他加入了您的组织，负责一个名为 Project Gamma 的敏感项目。在现有设置中，您有一个名为 &lt;code&gt;project-gamma&lt;/code&gt; 的单独命名空间，用于存储项目的所有资源。您希望允许 John 仅在 &lt;code&gt;project-gamma&lt;/code&gt; 命名空间中创建部署和 Pod。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要执行这些规则，您必须创建适当的角色和角色绑定资源。让我们看一下如何创建这两个对象并为 John 分配正确的权限。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 1 步：&lt;/strong&gt;创建一个名为 &lt;code&gt;gamma-developer-role&lt;/code&gt; 的角色，并为其分配适当的权限集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这可以使用 &lt;code&gt;kubectl&lt;/code&gt; 命令式完成，也可以使用 YAML 文件以声明式完成。我们将考虑以声明方式创建文件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下面的 YAML 文件可用于创建具有所需权限的角色。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类：角色&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  命名空间：project-gamma&#xA;  名称：gamma-开发人员角色&#xA;规则：&#xA;- api 组：[&#34;&#34;]&#xA;  资源：[“豆荚”]&#xA;  动词：[“创建”、“获取”、“列表”、“删除”]&#xA;- api 组：[&#34;&#34;]&#xA;  资源：[“部署”]&#xA;  动词：[“创建”、“获取”、“列表”]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们了解上面清单中描述的一些重要配置字段&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;名称：&lt;/strong&gt; 角色名称&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;命名空间&lt;/strong&gt;：将在此命名空间中创建，并且权限将受到限制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;规则&lt;/strong&gt;：这些是定义的实际权限。我们可以根据需要定义多个权限&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API 组&lt;/strong&gt;：用于定位特定资源的 API 组。当有多个自定义资源时这非常有用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;资源&lt;/strong&gt;：您希望分配权限的特定资源类型。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;动词&lt;/strong&gt;：您希望为已定义的资源授予的特定权限。您可以在以下动词之间进行选择：获取、创建、删除、列出、修补、更新、监视。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 2 步：&lt;/strong&gt;创建一个名为 &lt;code&gt;gamma-developer-binding&lt;/code&gt; 的 RoleBinding，并将其配置为使用正确的角色并分配正确的用户&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建角色后，还需要将其分配给用户。与角色类似，RoleBinding 也可以使用 &lt;code&gt;kubectl create RoleBinding&lt;/code&gt; 命令强制创建。我们将了解如何使用 YAML 文件以声明方式实现它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下面的 YAML 文件将创建 RoleBinding 并将权限分配给 John。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类：角色绑定&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称： 伽马-开发人员-绑定&#xA;  命名空间：project-gamma&#xA;科目：&#xA;- 种类：用户&#xA;  姓名：约翰&#xA;角色参考：&#xA;  种类：角色 &#xA;  名称：gamma-开发人员角色&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在上面的清单中，一些重要的配置字段如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;名称：&lt;/strong&gt; RoleBinding 的名称&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;命名空间：&lt;/strong&gt;将在其中创建 RoleBinding 的命名空间。权限将仅限于该命名空间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;主题：&lt;/strong&gt;应应用角色的主题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;roleRef：&lt;/strong&gt; 应应用于主题的特定角色的权限。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意：- Role 和 RoleBinding 是命名空间范围内的资源。它们只能在创建它们的命名空间中工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 3 步：&lt;/strong&gt;验证权限&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建角色并使用 RoleBinding 将其分配给正确的用户后，需要确保权限正常工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以使用&lt;code&gt;kubectl auth can-i&lt;/code&gt;命令确保权限正常工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该命令将显示您尝试运行的操作是否成功。例如，John 应该能够获取 &lt;code&gt;project-gamma&lt;/code&gt; 命名空间中的 Pod。但他不应该能够获取默认命名空间中的 Pod。我们可以通过运行以下两个命令来验证这一点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl auth can-i get pods -nproject-gamma --as=John&#xA;&#xA;kubectl auth can-i get pods --as=John&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/1.-k-auth-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;kubectl auth&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[图1] kubectl auth&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt; /图&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从上图中可以看到，John 可以获取project-gamma 命名空间中的 pod，但无法获取 default 命名空间中的 pod。这正是我们想要创建的权限。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;clusterrole-clusterrolebinding&#34;&gt;ClusterRole 和 ClusterRoleBinding&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与 Roles 和 RoleBindings 类似，ClusterRoles 和 ClusterRoleBindings 可以为用户授予某些权限。关键区别在于 ClusterRole 和 ClusterRoleBinding 将应用于整个集群，即它将在集群中的每个命名空间中工作。另一方面，角色和角色绑定仅限于它们所在的特定命名空间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们通过示例了解如何创建和分配 ClusterRole 和 ClusterRoleBinding。想象一下，您有一个名为 DeploymentManager 的应用程序，它负责管理集群中的所有 Deployment。为了使该应用程序执行其功能，它需要拥有集群中所有部署的管理员权限。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们看一下如何为此应用程序分配正确级别的权限的分步过程&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 1 步：&lt;/strong&gt;创建服务帐户&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们想给某个用户分配权限时，可以直接分配给他们。但是，当权限必须应用于应用程序时，不能直接应用于应用程序的 Pod 或部署。 Kubernetes 有一种称为服务帐户的资源，它是具有独特身份的非人类帐户。当应用程序需要集群内的某些权限时，会通过服务帐户分配给它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们创建一个名为 &lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-sa&lt;/code&gt; 的 ServiceAccount。您可以使用以下命令强制创建服务帐户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl 创建服务帐户部署管理器-sa&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您还想确保应用程序正在使用这个新的 ServiceAccount。编辑应用程序的清单并更新 &lt;code&gt;serviceAccount&lt;/code&gt; 字段，以便它使用已创建的新服务帐户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 2 步：&lt;/strong&gt;创建 ClusterRole&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于应用程序负责管理集群中的每个部署，因此需要权限才能对部署执行所有操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与我们讨论的角色类似，ClusterRoles 可以命令式和声明式创建。我们了解了如何以声明方式创建角色。让我们使用命令式方法创建名为 &lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-cr&lt;/code&gt; 的 ClusterRole。您可以使用以下命令创建具有正确权限的 ClusterRole。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl create clusterrole deploy-manager-cr --verb=&#39;*&#39; --resource=deployments&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上述命令将允许服务帐户仅对部署对象执行任何操作。它将无法对任何其他资源类型执行任何操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您希望使用声明性命令运行相同的命令，可以使用以下 YAML 清单：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类：集群角色&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：部署管理器-cr&#xA;规则：&#xA;- api 组：[&#34;&#34;]&#xA;  资源：[“部署”]&#xA;  动词：[“*”]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 3 步：&lt;/strong&gt;创建 ClusterRoleBinding&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，我们要创建一个 ClusterRoleBinding 以将 ClusterRole 分配给我们创建的服务帐户。我们将此 ClusterRoleBinding 称为 &lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-crb&lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将使用 &lt;code&gt;kubectl&lt;/code&gt; 命令强制创建 ClusterRoleBinding。您可以使用以下命令创建 ClusterRoleBinding，以便它将使用 &lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-cr&lt;/code&gt; 中定义的权限并将其分配给 &lt;code&gt;deploy-manager-sa&lt;/code&gt; 服务帐户&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl 创建集群角色绑定部署管理器-crb --clusterrole=deploy-manager-cr --serviceaccount=default:deploy-manager-sa&lt;/code &gt;&lt;/前&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上述命令 ClusterRoeBinding 也可以以声明方式创建。您可以使用以下 YAML 清单通过声明性方法创建相同的角色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：rbac.authorization.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类：ClusterRoleBinding&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：部署管理器-crb&#xA;科目：&#xA;- 种类：服务帐户&#xA;  名称：默认：deploy-manager-sa&#xA;角色参考：&#xA;  种类：集群角色 &#xA;  名称：部署管理器-cr&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 4 步：&lt;/strong&gt;验证权限&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与验证 Roles 和 ClusterRoles 权限的方式类似，我们还希望使用 &lt;code&gt;kubectl auth can-i&lt;/code&gt; 命令验证 ClusterRole 和 ClusterRoleBinding 的权限。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们看看 ServiceAccount 是否可以获得部署，以及是否可以获得单独的 Pod。您可以使用以下命令来尝试一下&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;kubectl auth 可以获取部署 --as=system:serviceaccount:default:deploy-manager-sa&#xA;&#xA;kubectl auth can-i get pods --as=system:serviceaccount:default:deploy-manager-sa&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/content/images/2024/10/2.-k-auth-cluster-1 .png&#34; alt=&#34;kubectl auth clusterrole&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;wp-element-caption&#34;&gt;[图2] kubectl auth clusterrole&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如您所见，服务帐户可以对部署执行操作，但无法对 Pod 等任何其他资源执行操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;user-accounts-service-accounts&#34;&gt;用户帐户和服务帐户&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们在上面的示例中创建角色和角色绑定时，您可能已经注意到，当我们为用户分配权限时，我们直接将权限分配给用户。但是，当我们想要向应用程序授予某些权限时，我们必须通过服务帐户来完成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;用户帐户：&lt;/strong&gt;用户帐户是由人类使用的帐户。它们旨在成为全局资源，即它们必须在集群中的所有命名空间中具有唯一的名称。用户帐户属于集群操作员，例如 DevOps 工程师或开发人员。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;服务帐户：&lt;/strong&gt;服务帐户是非人类使用的帐户，即由应用程序使用的帐户。它是一个命名空间范围的资源，即多个服务帐户可以在不同的命名空间中具有相同的名称。服务帐户用于向 Pod 内运行的应用程序分配一组权限。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本博客中，您了解了将用户添加到 Kubernetes 集群并使用 Roles、RoleBindings、ClusterRoles 和 ClusterRoleBindings 为其添加细粒度权限的整个过程。 Kubernetes 提供了一种强大而灵活的方式来定义不同用户和应用程序的权限。但是，仅使用 Kubernetes 资源创建权限时，确实会出现某些限制和挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Kubernetes 中实施 RBAC 的一些挑战如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;缺乏可见性&lt;/strong&gt;：要向任何用户分配权限，您需要创建多个资源，例如角色和 RoleBindings。很难理解哪个角色映射到哪个 RoleBinding，这使得正确管理权限变得困难。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;手动角色分配&lt;/strong&gt;：每当新用户加入 Kubernetes 集群时，都必须手动创建角色并将其分配给该用户。您不能将同一组权限分配给一组用户（例如开发人员用户）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;无基于时间的访问：&lt;/strong&gt;如果您希望仅允许在有限的时间内访问集群，则需要手动分配权限，并在设定的时间段后将其删除。访问权限不会自动过期，需要集群管理员手动移除权限。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;难以大规模管理&lt;/strong&gt;：随着组织的发展，有权访问集群的用户数量也会增加。这反过来会增加 Roles、RoleBindings、ClusterRoles 和 ClusterRoleBindings 的数量。由于这些资源有数百个，因此大规模管理这些资源变得非常困难。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;引导用户遇到困难：&lt;/strong&gt;当您想要引导用户时新用户加入集群后，您需要获取其公钥并创建证书签名请求 (CSR)。然后，此 CSR 需要得到集群管理员的批准，这将成为一个漫长的过程。此外，集群管理员需要确保正确的 CSR 得到批准，并且没有恶意行为者可以访问集群。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron 是一个强大的 Kubernetes 仪表板，可以更轻松地使用 SSO 服务将用户添加到 Kubernetes 集群。它还可以帮助您细化希望分配给所有用户的访问级别。 Devtron 的权限组可以帮助您将相同的权限分配给不同的用户，例如所有开发人员用户或操作用户。它还提供了设置基于时间的集群访问权限的选项，确保用户只能在有限的时间内进行访问。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关 Devtron 如何帮助 Kubernetes RBAC 的其他阅读内容：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/sso-and-rbac-a-secure-access-strategy-for-your-kubernetes/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;在 Kubernetes 中使用 SSO 进行 RBAC&lt; /u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/control-and-secure-kubectl-access/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;保护对集群的访问&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://devtron.ai/blog/kubernetes-access-management-made-easy/&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;Devtron 让 Kubernetes 访问管理变得轻松&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/李&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;结论&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 安全性有多个方面。 Kubernetes 安全性最重要的方面之一是正确设置基于角色的访问控制。 Kubernetes RBAC 对于限制用户可以在 Kubernetes 集群中执行的操作非常有用。首先通过创建 CSR 请求将用户添加到集群，该请求使用 Kubernetes 集群对用户进行身份验证 (authN)。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成身份验证后，需要为用户分配适当的授权 (authZ) 权限，以确保他们只能访问所需的资源。为了在集群中设置授权权限，Kubernetes 为用户提供了 Roles、RoleBindings、ClusterRoles 和 ClusterRoleBindings，这些对于在命名空间级别或集群级别设置授权权限非常有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Devtron 是一个 Kubernetes 仪表板，它使创建权限并向不同用户分配权限变得更加容易，从而使 Kubernetes 安全性更进一步。它还提供权限组，将同一组权限分配给一组用户（例如开发人员）。它还有助于提供对集群中特定资源的基于时间的访问，并在设定的期限到期后撤销访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您有任何疑问，请随时&lt;a href=&#34;https://rebrand.ly/devtron-demo?ref=blog&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34;&gt;与我们联系&lt;/a&gt;。加入我们积极发展的活跃讨论和共享知识&lt;a href=&#34;https://rebrand.ly/Devtron-Discord?ref=devtron.ai&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Discord 社区&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Kyverno release 1.13!】宣布 Kyverno 版本 1.13！</title>
      <link>https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/11/07/announcing-kyverno-release-1-13/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Project post originally published on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/&#34;&gt;Kyverno blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 released with Sigstore bundle verification, exceptions for validatingAdmissionPolicies, new assertion trees, generate enhancments, enhanced ValidatingAdmissionPolicy and PolicyException support, and tons more!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wednesday, October 30, 2024&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 contains&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/compare/release-1.12...v1.13.0-rc.3&#34;&gt;over 700 changes from 39 contributors&lt;/a&gt;! In this blog, we will highlight some of the major changes and enhancements for the release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img decoding=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/kyverno.png&#34; alt=&#34;kyverno&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;major-features&#34;&gt;Major Features&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#major-features&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;sigstore-bundle-verification&#34;&gt;Sigstore Bundle Verification&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#sigstore-bundle-verification&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 introduces support for verifying container images signatures that use the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sigstore/protobuf-specs/blob/main/protos/sigstore_bundle.proto&#34;&gt;sigstore bundle format&lt;/a&gt;. This enables seamless support for&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.github.com/en/actions/security-for-github-actions/using-artifact-attestations&#34;&gt;GitHub Artifact Attestations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;to be verified using verification type&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;SigstoreBundle&lt;/code&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following example verifies images containing SLSA Provenance created and signed using GitHub Artifact Attestation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is an example policy:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;kind: ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt; name: sigstore-image-verification&lt;br&gt;spec:&lt;br&gt; validationFailureAction: Enforce&lt;br&gt; webhookTimeoutSeconds: 30&lt;br&gt; rules:&lt;br&gt; - match:&lt;br&gt;     any:&lt;br&gt;     - resources:&lt;br&gt;         kinds:&lt;br&gt;         - Pod&lt;br&gt;   name: sigstore-image-verification&lt;br&gt;   verifyImages:&lt;br&gt;   - imageReferences:&lt;br&gt;     - &#34;*&#34;&lt;br&gt;     type: SigstoreBundle&lt;br&gt;     attestations:&lt;br&gt;     - type: https://slsa.dev/provenance/v1&lt;br&gt;       attestors:&lt;br&gt;       - entries:&lt;br&gt;         - keyless:&lt;br&gt;             issuer: https://token.actions.githubusercontent.com&lt;br&gt;             subject: https://github.com/nirmata/github-signing-demo/.github/workflows/build-attested-image.yaml@refs/heads/main&lt;br&gt;             rekor:&lt;br&gt;                 url: https://rekor.sigstore.dev&lt;br&gt;             additionalExtensions:&lt;br&gt;               githubWorkflowTrigger: push&lt;br&gt;               githubWorkflowName: build-attested-image&lt;br&gt;               githubWorkflowRepository: nirmata/github-signing-demo&lt;br&gt;       conditions:&lt;br&gt;       - all:&lt;br&gt;         - key: &#34;{{ buildDefinition.buildType }}&#34;&lt;br&gt;           operator: Equals&lt;br&gt;           value: &#34;https://actions.github.io/buildtypes/workflow/v1&#34;&lt;br&gt;         - key: &#34;{{ buildDefinition.externalParameters.workflow.repository }}&#34;&lt;br&gt;           operator: Equals&lt;br&gt;           value: &#34;https://github.com/nirmata/github-signing-demo&#34;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The demo repository is available at:&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nirmata/github-signing-demo&#34;&gt;https://github.com/nirmata/github-signing-demo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;exceptions-for-validatingadmissionpolicies&#34;&gt;Exceptions for ValidatingAdmissionPolicies&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#exceptions-for-validatingadmissionpolicies&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 introduces the ability to leverage PolicyException declarations while auto-generating Kubernetes ValidatingAdmissionPolicies directly from Kyverno policies that use the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;validate.cel&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;subrule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The resources specified within the PolicyException are then used to populate the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;matchConstraints.excludeResourceRules&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;field of the generated ValidatingAdmissionPolicy, effectively creating exclusions for those resources. This functionality is illustrated below with an example of a Kyverno ClusterPolicy and a PolicyException, along with the resulting ValidatingAdmissionPolicy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno policy:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;kind: ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt;  name: disallow-host-path&lt;br&gt;spec:&lt;br&gt;  background: false&lt;br&gt;  rules:&lt;br&gt;    - name: host-path&lt;br&gt;      match:&lt;br&gt;        any:&lt;br&gt;        - resources:&lt;br&gt;            kinds:&lt;br&gt;            - Deployment&lt;br&gt;            - StatefulSet&lt;br&gt;            operations:&lt;br&gt;            - CREATE&lt;br&gt;            - UPDATE&lt;br&gt;            namespaceSelector:&lt;br&gt;              matchExpressions:&lt;br&gt;                - key: type &lt;br&gt;                  operator: In&lt;br&gt;                  values: &lt;br&gt;                  - connector&lt;br&gt;      validate:&lt;br&gt;        failureAction: Audit&lt;br&gt;        cel:&lt;br&gt;          expressions:&lt;br&gt;            - expression: &#34;!has(object.spec.template.spec.volumes) || object.spec.template.spec.volumes.all(volume, !has(volume.hostPath))&#34;&lt;br&gt;              message: &#34;HostPath volumes are forbidden. The field spec.template.spec.volumes[*].hostPath must be unset.&#34;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PolicyException:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v2&#xA;kind: PolicyException&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: policy-exception&#xA;spec:&#xA;  exceptions:&#xA;  - policyName: disallow-host-path&#xA;    ruleNames:&#xA;    - host-path&#xA;  match:&#xA;    any:&#xA;    - resources:&#xA;        kinds:&#xA;        - Deployment&#xA;        names:&#xA;        - important-tool&#xA;        operations:&#xA;        - CREATE&#xA;        - UPDATE&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The generated ValidatingAdmissionPolicy and its binding are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: admissionregistration.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: ValidatingAdmissionPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  labels:&#xA;    app.kubernetes.io/managed-by: kyverno&#xA;  name: disallow-host-path&#xA;  ownerReferences:&#xA;  - apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&#xA;    kind: ClusterPolicy&#xA;    name: disallow-host-path&#xA;spec:&#xA;  failurePolicy: Fail&#xA;  matchConstraints:&#xA;    resourceRules:&#xA;    - apiGroups:&#xA;      - apps&#xA;      apiVersions:&#xA;      - v1&#xA;      operations:&#xA;      - CREATE&#xA;      - UPDATE&#xA;      resources:&#xA;      - deployments&#xA;      - statefulsets&#xA;    namespaceSelector:&#xA;      matchExpressions:&#xA;      - key: type&#xA;        operator: In&#xA;        values:&#xA;        - connector&#xA;    excludeResourceRules:&#xA;    - apiGroups:&#xA;      - apps&#xA;      apiVersions:&#xA;      - v1&#xA;      operations:&#xA;      - CREATE&#xA;      - UPDATE&#xA;      resourceNames:&#xA;      - important-tool&#xA;      resources:&#xA;      - deployments&#xA;  validations:&#xA;  - expression: &#39;!has(object.spec.template.spec.volumes) || object.spec.template.spec.volumes.all(volume,&#xA;      !has(volume.hostPath))&#39;&#xA;    message: HostPath volumes are forbidden. The field spec.template.spec.volumes[*].hostPath&#xA;      must be unset.&#xA;---&#xA;apiVersion: admissionregistration.k8s.io/v1&#xA;kind: ValidatingAdmissionPolicyBinding&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  labels:&#xA;    app.kubernetes.io/managed-by: kyverno&#xA;  name: disallow-host-path-binding&#xA;  ownerReferences:&#xA;  - apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&#xA;    kind: ClusterPolicy&#xA;    name: disallow-host-path&#xA;spec:&#xA;  policyName: disallow-host-path&#xA;  validationActions: [Audit, Warn]&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, Kyverno policies targeting resources within a specific namespace will now generate a ValidatingAdmissionPolicy that utilizes the&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;matchConstraints.namespaceSelector&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;field to scope its enforcement to that namespace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Policy snippet:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;match:&#xA;  any:&#xA;  - resources:&#xA;      kinds:&#xA;      - Deployment&#xA;      operations:&#xA;      - CREATE&#xA;      - UPDATE&#xA;      namespaces:&#xA;      - production&#xA;      - staging&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The generated ValidatingAdmissionPolicy:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;matchConstraints:&lt;br&gt;  namespaceSelector:&lt;br&gt;    matchExpressions:&lt;br&gt;    - key: kubernetes.io/metadata.name&lt;br&gt;      operator: In&lt;br&gt;      values:&lt;br&gt;      - production&lt;br&gt;      - staging&lt;br&gt;  resourceRules:&lt;br&gt;  - apiGroups:&lt;br&gt;    - apps&lt;br&gt;    apiVersions:&lt;br&gt;    - v1&lt;br&gt;    operations:&lt;br&gt;    - CREATE&lt;br&gt;    - UPDATE&lt;br&gt;    resources:&lt;br&gt;    - deployments&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;validation-rules-with-assertion-trees&#34;&gt;Validation Rules with Assertion Trees&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#validation-rules-with-assertion-trees&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno-JSON allows Kyverno policies to be used anywhere, even for non-Kubernetes workloads. It introduces the powerful concept of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2023/12/13/kyverno-chainsaw-exploring-the-power-of-assertion-trees/&#34;&gt;assertion trees&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Previously the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/kyverno-cli/assertion-trees/&#34;&gt;Kyverno CLI added support for assertion trees&lt;/a&gt;, and now in Release 1.13 assertion trees can also be used in validation rules as a sub-type.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is an example of a policy that uses an assertion tree to deny pods from using the default service account:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;kind: ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt; name: disallow-default-sa&lt;br&gt;spec:&lt;br&gt; validationFailureAction: Enforce&lt;br&gt; rules:&lt;br&gt; - match:&lt;br&gt;     any:&lt;br&gt;     - resources:&lt;br&gt;         kinds:&lt;br&gt;         - Pod&lt;br&gt;   name: disallow-default-sa&lt;br&gt;   validate:&lt;br&gt;     message: default ServiceAccount should not be used&lt;br&gt;     assert:&lt;br&gt;       object:&lt;br&gt;         spec:&lt;br&gt;           (serviceAccountName == ‘default’): false&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;other-features-and-enhancements&#34;&gt;Other Features and Enhancements&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#other-features-and-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;generate-changes&#34;&gt;Generate Changes&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#generate-changes&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;foreach&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;declaration allows the generation of multiple target resources of sub-elements in resource declarations. Each&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;foreach&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;entry must contain a list attribute, written as a JMESPath expression without braces, that defines sub-elements it processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is an example of creating networkpolicies for a list of Namespaces, the namespaces are stored in a ConfigMap which can be easily configured dynamically.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;kind: ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt; name: foreach-generate-data&lt;br&gt;spec:&lt;br&gt; rules:&lt;br&gt; - match:&lt;br&gt;     any:&lt;br&gt;     - resources:&lt;br&gt;         kinds:&lt;br&gt;         - ConfigMap&lt;br&gt;   name: k-kafka-address&lt;br&gt;   generate:&lt;br&gt;     generateExisting: false&lt;br&gt;     synchronize: true&lt;br&gt;     orphanDownstreamOnPolicyDelete: false&lt;br&gt;     foreach:&lt;br&gt;       - list: request.object.data.namespaces | split(@, ‘,’)&lt;br&gt;         apiVersion: networking.k8s.io/v1&lt;br&gt;         kind: NetworkPolicy&lt;br&gt;         name: my-networkpolicy-{{element}}-{{ elementIndex }}&lt;br&gt;         namespace: ‘{{ element }}’&lt;br&gt;         data:&lt;br&gt;           metadata:&lt;br&gt;             labels:&lt;br&gt;               request.namespace: ‘{{ request.object.metadata.name }}’&lt;br&gt;               element: ‘{{ element }}’&lt;br&gt;               elementIndex: ‘{{ elementIndex }}’&lt;br&gt;           spec:&lt;br&gt;             podSelector: {}&lt;br&gt;             policyTypes:&lt;br&gt;             - Ingress&lt;br&gt;             - Egress&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The triggering ConfigMap is defined as follows, the data contains a namespaces field that defines multiple namespaces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;kind: ConfigMap&lt;br&gt;apiVersion: v1&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt;  name: default-deny&lt;br&gt;  namespace: default&lt;br&gt;data:&lt;br&gt;  namespaces: foreach-ns-1,foreach-ns-2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, below is an example of a clone source type of&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;foreach&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;declaration that clones the source Secret into a list of matching existing namespaces which is stored in the same ConfigMap as above.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;kind: ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt;  name: foreach-clone&lt;br&gt;spec:&lt;br&gt;  rules:&lt;br&gt;  - match:&lt;br&gt;      any:&lt;br&gt;      - resources:&lt;br&gt;          kinds:&lt;br&gt;          - ConfigMap&lt;br&gt;   namespaces:&lt;br&gt;          - default&lt;br&gt;    name: k-kafka-address&lt;br&gt;    generate:&lt;br&gt;      generateExisting: false&lt;br&gt;      synchronize: true&lt;br&gt;      foreach:&lt;br&gt;        - list: request.object.data.namespaces | split(@, &#39;,&#39;)&lt;br&gt;          apiVersion: v1&lt;br&gt;          kind: Secret&lt;br&gt;          name: cloned-secret-{{ elementIndex }}-{{ element }}&lt;br&gt;          namespace: &#39;{{ element }}&#39;&lt;br&gt;          clone:&lt;br&gt;            namespace: default&lt;br&gt;            name: source-secret&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, each&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;foreach&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;declaration supports the following declarations: Contex and Preconditions. For more information please see&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/writing-policies/generate/#foreach&#34;&gt;Kyverno documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release also allows updates to the generate rule pattern. In addition to deletion, if the triggering resource is altered in a way such that it no longer matches the definition in the rule, that too will cause the removal of the downstream resource.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;api-call-enhancements&#34;&gt;API call enhancements&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#api-call-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;default-values&#34;&gt;Default Values&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#default-values&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the case where the API server returns an error,&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;apiCall.default&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;can be used to provide a fallback value for the API call context entry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following example shows how to add default value to context entries:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;    context:&#xA;    - name: currentnamespace&#xA;      apiCall:&#xA;        urlPath: “/api/v1/namespaces/{{ request.namespace }}”&#xA;        jmesPath: metadata.name&#xA;        default: default&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;custom-headers&#34;&gt;Custom Headers&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#custom-headers&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno Service API calls now also support custom headers. This can be useful for authentication or adding other HTTP request headers. Here is an example of adding a token in the HTTP Authorization header:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;     context:&#xA;        - name: result&#xA;          apiCall:&#xA;            method: POST&#xA;            data:&#xA;              - key: foo&#xA;                value: bar&#xA;              - key: namespace&#xA;                value: &#34;{{ `{{ request.namespace }}` }}&#34;&#xA;            service:&#xA;              url: http://my-service.svc.cluster.local/validation&#xA;              headers:&#xA;                - key: &#34;UserAgent&#34;&#xA;                  value: &#34;Kyverno Policy XYZ&#34;&#xA;                - key: &#34;Authorization&#34;&#xA;                  value: &#34;Bearer {{ MY_SECRET }}&#34;&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;policy-report-enhancements&#34;&gt;Policy Report Enhancements&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#policy-report-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;reports-for-mutate-and-generate-rules&#34;&gt;Reports for Mutate and Generate rules&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#reports-for-mutate-and-generate-rules&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to validate and verifyImages rules, Kyverno 1.13 supports reporting for generate and mutate, including mutate existing policies, to record policy results. The container flag&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;--enableReporting&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;can be used to enable or disable reports for specific rule types. It allows the comma-separated values, validate, mutate, mutateExisting, generate, and imageVerify. See details&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/installation/customization/#container-flags&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A result entry will be audited in the policy report for rule decision:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;apiVersion: wgpolicyk8s.io/v1alpha2&lt;br&gt;kind: PolicyReport&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt;  labels:&lt;br&gt;    app.kubernetes.io/managed-by: kyverno&lt;br&gt;  namespace: default&lt;br&gt;results:&lt;br&gt;- message: mutated Pod/good-pod in namespace default&lt;br&gt;  policy: add-labels&lt;br&gt;  result: pass&lt;br&gt;  rule: add-labels&lt;br&gt;  scored: true&lt;br&gt;  source: kyverno&lt;br&gt;scope:&lt;br&gt;  apiVersion: v1&lt;br&gt;  kind: Pod&lt;br&gt;  name: good-pod&lt;br&gt;  namespace: default&lt;br&gt;...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note that the proper permissions need to be granted to the reports controller, a warning message will be returned upon policy admission if no RBAC permission is configured.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;custom-data-in-reports&#34;&gt;Custom Data in Reports&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#custom-data-in-reports&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A new field&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;reportProperties&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;is introduced to custom data in policy reports. For example, a validate rule below adds two additional entries operation and objName to the policy reports:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;kind: ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;metadata:&lt;br&gt;  name: require-owner&lt;br&gt;spec:&lt;br&gt;  background: false&lt;br&gt;  rules:&lt;br&gt;  - match:&lt;br&gt;      any:&lt;br&gt;      - resources:&lt;br&gt;          kinds:&lt;br&gt;          - Namespace&lt;br&gt;    name: check-owner&lt;br&gt;    context:&lt;br&gt;    - name: objName&lt;br&gt;      variable:&lt;br&gt;        jmesPath: request.object.metadata.name&lt;br&gt;    reportProperties:&lt;br&gt;      operation: ‘{{ request.operation }}’&lt;br&gt;      objName: ‘{{ objName }}’&lt;br&gt;    validate:&lt;br&gt;      validationFailureAction: Audit&lt;br&gt;      message: The `owner` label is required for all Namespaces.&lt;br&gt;      pattern:&lt;br&gt;        metadata:&lt;br&gt;          labels:&lt;br&gt;            owner: ?*&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can find the two custom entries added to&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;results.properties&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: wgpolicyk8s.io/v1alpha2&#xA;kind: ClusterPolicyReport&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  ownerReferences:&#xA;  - apiVersion: v1&#xA;    kind: Namespace&#xA;    name: bar&#xA;results:&#xA;- message: validation rule ‘check-owner’ passed.&#xA;  policy: require-owner&#xA;  result: pass&#xA;  rule: check-owner&#xA;  scored: true&#xA;  source: kyverno&#xA;  properties:&#xA;    objName: bar&#xA;    operation: CREATE&#xA;scope:&#xA;  apiVersion: v1&#xA;  kind: Namespace&#xA;  name: bar&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;globalcontextentries-enhancements&#34;&gt;GlobalContextEntries Enhancements&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#globalcontextentries-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;api-call-retry&#34;&gt;API Call Retry&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#api-call-retry&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno’s GlobalContextEntry provides a powerful mechanism to fetch external data and use it within policies. When leveraging the apiCall feature to retrieve data from an API, transient network issues can sometimes hinder successful retrieval.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address this, Kyverno now offers built-in retry logic for API calls within GlobalContextEntry. You can now optionally specify a retryLimit for your API calls:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: kyverno.io/v2alpha1&#xA;kind: GlobalContextEntry&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: gctxentry-apicall-correct&#xA;spec:&#xA;  apiCall:&#xA;    urlPath: &#34;/apis/apps/v1/namespaces/test-globalcontext-apicall-correct/deployments&#34;&#xA;    refreshInterval: 1h&#xA;    retryLimit: 3&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;retryLimit&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;field determines the number of times Kyverno will attempt to make the API call if it initially fails. This field is optional and defaults to 3, ensuring a reasonable level of resilience against temporary network hiccups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By incorporating this retry mechanism, Kyverno further strengthens its ability to reliably fetch external data, ensuring your policies can function smoothly even in the face of occasional connectivity issues. This enhancement improves the overall robustness and dependability of your Kubernetes policy enforcement framework.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;cli-based-injection-of-global-context-entries&#34;&gt;CLI-based Injection of Global Context Entries&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#cli-based-injection-of-global-context-entries&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno CLI now allows you to dynamically inject global context entries using a Values file. This feature facilitates flexible policy testing and execution by simulating different scenarios without modifying GlobalContextEntry resources in your cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now define global values and rule-specific values within the Values file, providing greater control over policy evaluation during testing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: cli.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;kind: Value&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: values&#xA;globalValues:&#xA;  request.operation: CREATE&#xA;policies:&#xA;  - name: gctx&#xA;    rules:&#xA;      - name: main-deployment-exists&#xA;        values:&#xA;          deploymentCount: 1&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this example,&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;request.operation&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;is set as a global value, and deploymentCount is set for a specific rule in the gctx policy. When using the Kyverno CLI, you can reference this Values file to inject these global context entries into your policy evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;security-hardening&#34;&gt;Security Hardening&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#security-hardening&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Kyverno project strives to be secure and production-ready, while providing ease of use. This release contains important changes to further enhance the security of the project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;removal-of-wildcard-roles&#34;&gt;Removal of wildcard roles&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#removal-of-wildcard-roles&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prior versions of Kyverno included wildcard view permissions. These have been removed in 1.13 and replaced with a role binding to the system view role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This change does not impact policy behaviors during admission controls, but may impact users with mutate and generate policies for custom resources, and may impact reporting of policy results for validation rules on custom resources A Helm option was added to upgrade Kyverno without breaking existing policies, see the upgrade guidance&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/installation/upgrading/#upgrading-to-kyverno-v113&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;removal-of-insecure-configuration-for-exceptions&#34;&gt;Removal of insecure configuration for exceptions&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#removal-of-insecure-configuration-for-exceptions&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In prior versions, policy exceptions were allowed in all namespaces. This creates a potential security issue, as any user with permission to create a policy exception can bypass policies, even in other namespaces. See&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/security/advisories/GHSA-qjvc-p88j-j9rm&#34;&gt;CVE-2024-48921&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for more details.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This release changes the defaults to disable the policy exceptions and only allows exceptions to be created in a specified namespace. To maintain backward compatibility follow the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/installation/upgrading/#upgrading-to-kyverno-v113&#34;&gt;upgrade guidance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;warnings-for-policy-violations-and-mutations&#34;&gt;Warnings for Policy Violations and Mutations&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#warnings-for-policy-violations-and-mutations&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A warning message can now be returned along with admission responses by the policy setting&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;spec.emitWarning&lt;/code&gt;, this can be used to report policy violations as well as mutations upon admission events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;shallow-evaluation-of-variables&#34;&gt;Shallow evaluation of Variables&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#shallow-evaluation-of-variables&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno performs nested variable substitution by default, this may not be desirable in certain situations. Take the following ConfigMap as an example, it defines a&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;.hcl&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;string content using the same&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;{{ }}&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;notation which is used in Kyverno for variable syntax. In this case, Kyverno needs to be instructed to not attempt to resolve variables in the HCL, this can be achieved by&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;{{- ... }}&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;notation for shallow (one time only) substitution of variables.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: v1&#xA;data:&#xA;  config: |-&#xA;    from_string&#xA;    {{ some hcl tempalte }}    &#xA;kind: ConfigMap&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  annotations:&#xA;  labels:&#xA;    argocd.development.cpl.&amp;lt;removed&amp;gt;.co.at/app: corp-tech-ap-team-ping-ep&#xA;  name: vault-injector-config-http-echo&#xA;  namespace: corp-tech-ap-team-ping-ep&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To only substitute the rule data with the HCL, and not perform nested substitutions, the following policy uses the declaration&amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;{{- hcl }}&lt;/code&gt;&amp;nbsp;for shallow substitution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;apiVersion: cli.kyverno.io/v1alphaapiVersion: kyverno.io/v1&#xA;kind: ClusterPolicy&#xA;metadata:&#xA;  name: vault-auth-backend&#xA;spec:&#xA;  validationFailureAction: Audit&#xA;  background: true&#xA;  mutateExistingOnPolicyUpdate: true&#xA;  rules:&#xA;  - name: vault-injector-config-blue-to-green-auth-backend&#xA;    context:&#xA;    - name: hcl&#xA;      variable:&#xA;        jmesPath: replace_all( ‘{{ request.object.data.config }}’, ‘from_string’,‘to_string’)&#xA;    match:&#xA;      any:&#xA;      - resources:&#xA;          kinds:&#xA;          - ConfigMap&#xA;          names:&#xA;          - test-*&#xA;          namespaces:&#xA;          - corp-tech-ap-team-ping-ep&#xA;    mutate:&#xA;      patchStrategicMerge:&#xA;        data:&#xA;          config: ‘{{- hcl }}’&#xA;      targets:&#xA;      - apiVersion: v1&#xA;        kind: ConfigMap&#xA;        name: ‘{{ request.object.metadata.name }}’&#xA;        namespace: ‘{{ request.object.metadata.namespace }}’&#xA;    name: vault-injector-config-blue-to-green-auth-backend&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;improved-argocd-integration&#34;&gt;Improved ArgoCD Integration&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#improved-argocd-integration&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno-managed webhook configurations are auto-cleaned up upon uninstallation. This behavior could be broken if Kyverno loses RBAC permissions to do so given the random resources deletion order. This release introduces a finalizer-based cleanup solution to ensure webhooks are removed successfully.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature is in&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/installation/uninstallation/#clean-up-webhooks&#34;&gt;beta stage&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;and will be used as the default cleanup strategy in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;api-version-management&#34;&gt;API Version Management&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#api-version-management&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 introduces new changes in the policy CRDs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Both Policy Exceptions and Cleanup Policies have graduated to a stable version (v2).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Several policy settings are deprecated:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.validationFailureAction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.validationFailureActionOverrides&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.mutateExistingOnPolicyUpdate&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.generateExisting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;These are replaced by more granular controls within the rule itself:&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[*].validate.failureAction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[*].validate.failureActionOverrides&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[&lt;em&gt;].verifyImages[&lt;/em&gt;].failureAction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[*].mutate.mutateExisting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[*].generate.generateExisting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note that the deprecated fields will be removed in a future release, so migration to the new settings is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#conclusion&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 promises to be a great release, with many new features, enhancements, and fixes. To get started with Kyverno try the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/introduction/quick-start/&#34;&gt;quick start guides&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;or head to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/installation/methods/&#34;&gt;installation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;section of the docs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get the most value out of Kyverno, and check out the&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/support/&#34;&gt;available enterprise solutions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;项目帖子最初发布于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/&#34;&gt;Kyverno 博客&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 发布，包含 Sigstore 捆绑验证、validateAdmissionPolicies 例外、新断言树、生成增强功能、增强的 ValidatingAdmissionPolicy 和 PolicyException 支持等等！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2024 年 10 月 30 日星期三&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 包含&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/compare/release-1.12...v1.13.0-rc.3&#34;&gt;来自 39 位贡献者的 700 多项更改&lt;/a&gt; ！在本博客中，我们将重点介绍该版本的一些主要更改和增强功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;wp-block-image&#34;&gt;&lt;img解码=&#34;async&#34; src=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/kyverno.png&#34; alt=&#34;kyverno&#34;referrerpolicy=&#34;no-referrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;major-features&#34;&gt;主要功能&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/ #主要功能&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;sigstore-bundle-verification&#34;&gt;Sigstore 捆绑包验证 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release -1.13/#sigstore-bundle-verification&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 引入了对验证使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sigstore/protobuf-specs/blob/main/protos/sigstore_bundle.proto&#34;&gt;sigstore 捆绑包格式的容器映像签名的支持&lt;/一个&gt;。这样可以无缝支持 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.github.com/en/actions/security-for-github-actions/using-artifact-attestations&#34;&gt;GitHub Artifact Attestations&lt;/a&gt;验证类型&lt;code&gt;SigstoreBundle&lt;/code&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下示例验证包含使用 GitHub Artifact Attestation 创建和签名的 SLSA Provenance 的图像。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是政策示例：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;种类：ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;名称： sigstore-image-verification&lt;br&gt;规范：&lt;br&gt;validationFailureAction：强制&lt;br&gt;webhookTimeoutSeconds：30&lt;br&gt;规则：&lt;br&gt; - 匹配：&lt;br&gt;任何：&lt;br&gt; - 资源：&lt;br&gt; 种类：&lt;br&gt; - Pod&lt;br&gt; 名称：sigstore-image-verification&lt;br&gt; verifyImages：&lt;br&gt; - imageReferences：&lt;br&gt; - &#34;*&#34;&lt;br&gt; 类型：SigstoreBundle&lt;br&gt; 证明：&lt;br&gt; - 类型：https://slsa.dev/provenance/v1&lt;br&gt; 证明者：&lt;br&gt; - 条目：&lt;br&gt; - 无密钥：&lt;br&gt;发行者：https://token.actions.githubusercontent.com&lt;br&gt;主题：https://github.com/nirmata/github-signing-demo/.github/workflows/build-attested-image.yaml@refs/heads /main&lt;br&gt; rekor:&lt;br&gt; url: https://rekor.sigstore.dev&lt;br&gt; extraExtensions:&lt;br&gt; githubWorkflowTrigger: Push&lt;br&gt; githubWorkflowName:构建证明图像&lt;br&gt; githubWorkflowRepository：nirmata/github-signing-demo&lt;br&gt; 条件：&lt;br&gt; - 全部：&lt;br&gt; - 键：“{{ buildDefinition.buildType }}”&lt;br&gt; 运算符：等于&lt;br&gt; 值：“https://actions.github.io/buildtypes/workflow /v1&#34;&lt;br&gt; - 键：“{{ buildDefinition.externalParameters.workflow.repository }}”&lt;br&gt; 运算符：等于&lt;br&gt; 值： “https://github.com/nirmata/github-signing-demo”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno -release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;演示存储库位于：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nirmata/github-signing-demo&#34;&gt;https://github.com/nirmata/github-signing-demo&lt;/a &gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;exceptions-for-validatingadmissionpolicies&#34;&gt;ValidatingAdmissionPolicies 的例外情况 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release -1.13/#exceptions-for-validatingadmissionpolicies&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 引入了利用 PolicyException 声明的功能，同时直接从使用 &lt;code&gt;validate.cel&lt;/code&gt; 子规则的 Kyverno 策略自动生成 Kubernetes ValidatingAdmissionPolicies。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，使用 PolicyException 中指定的资源填充生成的 ValidatingAdmissionPolicy 的 &lt;code&gt;matchConstraints.excludeResourceRules&lt;/code&gt; 字段，从而有效地为这些资源创建排除项。下面通过 Kyverno ClusterPolicy 和 PolicyException 以及生成的 ValidatingAdmissionPolicy 示例说明了此功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 政策：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;种类：ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;名称： disallow-host-path&lt;br&gt;规范：&lt;br&gt; 背景： false&lt;br&gt; 规则：&lt;br&gt; - 名称：主机路径&lt;br&gt; 匹配：&lt;br&gt; 任何：&lt;br&gt; - 资源：&lt;br&gt; 种类:&lt;br&gt;-部署&lt;br&gt; - StatefulSet&lt;br&gt; 操作：&lt;br&gt; - CREATE&lt;br&gt; - UPDATE&lt;br&gt; 命名空间选择器：&lt;br&gt; matchExpressions：&lt;br&gt; - 键：类型 &lt;br&gt; 运算符：In&lt;br&gt; 值：&lt; br&gt; - 连接器&lt;br&gt; 验证：&lt;br&gt; failureAction：审核&lt;br&gt; cel:&lt;br&gt; 表达式：&lt;br&gt; - 表达式：&#34;!has(object.spec.template.spec.volumes) || object.spec.template.spec.volumes.all(volume, !has(volume.hostPath))&#34;&lt;br&gt; 消息：“禁止使用 HostPath 卷。spec.template.spec.volumes[*].hostPath 字段必须为禁止的。取消设置。”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;策略异常：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：kyverno.io/v2&#xA;种类：PolicyException元数据：&#xA;  名称：策略例外&#xA;规格：&#xA;  例外情况：&#xA;  - 策略名称：禁止主机路径&#xA;    规则名称：&#xA;    - 主机路径&#xA;  匹配：&#xA;    任何：&#xA;    - 资源：&#xA;        种类：&#xA;        - 部署&#xA;        名称：&#xA;        - 重要工具&#xA;        运营：&#xA;        - 创造&#xA;        - 更新&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;生成的ValidatingAdmissionPolicy及其绑定如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：admissionregistration.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类：ValidatingAdmissionPolicy&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  标签：&#xA;    app.kubernetes.io/管理者：kyverno&#xA;  名称：禁止主机路径&#xA;  业主参考资料：&#xA;  - api版本：kyverno.io/v1&#xA;    种类：集群策略&#xA;    名称：禁止主机路径&#xA;规格：&#xA;  失败策略：失败&#xA;  匹配限制：&#xA;    资源规则：&#xA;    - api 组：&#xA;      - 应用程序&#xA;      api版本：&#xA;      - v1&#xA;      运营：&#xA;      - 创造&#xA;      - 更新&#xA;      资源：&#xA;      - 部署&#xA;      - 有状态集&#xA;    命名空间选择器：&#xA;      匹配表达式：&#xA;      - 键：类型&#xA;        运算符：In&#xA;        价值观：&#xA;        - 连接器&#xA;    排除资源规则：&#xA;    - api 组：&#xA;      - 应用程序&#xA;      api版本：&#xA;      - v1&#xA;      运营：&#xA;      - 创造&#xA;      - 更新&#xA;      资源名称：&#xA;      - 重要工具&#xA;      资源：&#xA;      - 部署&#xA;  验证：&#xA;  - 表达式： &#39;!has(object.spec.template.spec.volumes) || object.spec.template.spec.volumes.all(体积，&#xA;      !has(volume.hostPath))&#39;&#xA;    消息：HostPath 卷被禁止。字段spec.template.spec.volumes[*].hostPath&#xA;      必须取消设置。&#xA;---&#xA;api版本：admissionregistration.k8s.io/v1&#xA;种类：ValidatingAdmissionPolicyBinding&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  标签：&#xA;    app.kubernetes.io/管理者：kyverno&#xA;  名称：禁止主机路径绑定&#xA;  业主参考资料：&#xA;  - api版本：kyverno.io/v1&#xA;    种类：集群策略&#xA;    名称：禁止主机路径&#xA;规格：&#xA;  策略名称：禁止主机路径&#xA;  验证操作：[审核、警告]&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，针对特定命名空间内的资源的 Kyverno 策略现在将生成一个 ValidatingAdmissionPolicy，该策略利用 &lt;code&gt;matchConstraints.namespaceSelector&lt;/code&gt; 字段将其强制执行范围限制在该命名空间内。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;政策片段：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;匹配：&#xA;  任何：&#xA;  - 资源：&#xA;      种类：&#xA;      - 部署&#xA;      运营：&#xA;      - 创造&#xA;      - 更新&#xA;      命名空间：&#xA;      - 生产&#xA;      - 分期&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;生成的ValidatingAdmissionPo莉西：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;matchConstraints:&lt;br&gt; 命名空间选择器:&lt;br&gt; matchExpressions:&lt;br&gt; - key: kubernetes.io/metadata .name&lt;br&gt; 运算符：In&lt;br&gt; 值：&lt;br&gt; - 生产&lt;br&gt; - 暂存&lt;br&gt; 资源规则：&lt;br&gt; - apiGroups：&lt;br&gt; - 应用程序&lt;br&gt; api版本：&lt;br&gt; - v1&lt;br&gt; 操作：&lt;br&gt; - 创建&lt;br&gt; - 更新&lt;br&gt;资源：&lt;br&gt; - 部署&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https:// kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;validation-rules-with-assertion-trees&#34;&gt;使用断言树的验证规则&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30 /announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#validation-rules-with-assertion-trees&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno-JSON 允许在任何地方使用 Kyverno 策略，甚至适用于非 Kubernetes 工作负载。它引入了&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2023/12/13/kyverno-chainsaw-exploring-the-power-of-assertion-trees/&#34;&gt;断言树&lt;/a的强大概念&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;之前 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/kyverno-cli/assertion-trees/&#34;&gt;Kyverno CLI 添加了对断言树的支持&lt;/a&gt;，现在在版本 1.13 中断言树可以也可以在验证规则中用作子类型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是使用断言树拒绝 Pod 使用默认服务帐户的策略示例：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;种类：ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;名称： disallow-default-sa&lt;br&gt;规范：&lt;br&gt;validationFailureAction：强制&lt;br&gt;规则：&lt;br&gt;-匹配：&lt;br&gt;任何：&lt;br&gt;-资源：&lt;br&gt;种类：&lt;br&gt;- Pod&lt;br&gt; 名称：disallow-default-sa&lt;br&gt; 验证：&lt;br&gt; 消息：不应使用默认 ServiceAccount&lt;br&gt; 断言：&lt;br&gt; 对象：&lt;br&gt; 规格：&lt;br&gt; (serviceAccountName == &#39;默认&#39;): false&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024 /10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;other-features-and-enhancements&#34;&gt;其他功能和增强功能 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing- kyverno-release-1.13/#other-features-and-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;generate-changes&#34;&gt;生成更改&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/ #generate-changes&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;foreach&lt;/code&gt; 声明允许在资源声明中生成子元素的多个目标资源。每个 &lt;code&gt;foreach&lt;/code&gt; 条目必须包含一个列表属性，以不带大括号的 JMESPath 表达式编写，用于定义它处理的子元素。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是为列表创建网络策略的示例命名空间，命名空间存储在 ConfigMap 中，可以轻松动态配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;种类：ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;名称： foreach-generate-data&lt;br&gt;规范：&lt;br&gt; 规则：&lt;br&gt; - 匹配：&lt;br&gt; 任何：&lt;br&gt; - 资源：&lt;br&gt; 种类：&lt;br&gt; - ConfigMap&lt;br&gt; 名称：k-kafka -address&lt;br&gt; 生成：&lt;br&gt; 生成现有：假&lt;br&gt; 同步：真&lt;br&gt; orphanDownstreamOnPolicyDelete：假&lt;br&gt; foreach：&lt;br&gt; - 列表：request.object.data.namespaces | split(@, &#39;,&#39;)&lt;br&gt; api版本：networking.k8s.io/v1&lt;br&gt; 种类：NetworkPolicy&lt;br&gt; 名称：my-networkpolicy-{{element}}-{{ elementIndex }}&lt;br&gt; 命名空间: &#39;{{ element }}&#39;&lt;br&gt; data:&lt;br&gt; 元数据:&lt;br&gt; labels:&lt;br&gt; request.namespace: &#39;{{ request.object.metadata.name }}&#39;&lt;br&gt; element: &#39;{ { element }}&#39;&lt;br&gt; elementIndex: &#39;{{ elementIndex }}&#39;&lt;br&gt; 规格:&lt;br&gt; podSelector: {}&lt;br&gt; 策略类型:&lt;br&gt; - 入口&lt;br&gt; - 出口&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno. io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;触发的ConfigMap定义如下，数据中包含一个namespaces字段，该字段定义了多个命名空间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;种类：ConfigMap&lt;br&gt;api版本：v1&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;名称：default-deny&lt; br&gt; 命名空间：默认&lt;br&gt;数据：&lt;br&gt; 命名空间：foreach-ns-1,foreach-ns-2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/ 2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/ #&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;类似地，下面是 &lt;code&gt;foreach&lt;/code&gt; 声明的克隆源类型的示例，它将源 Secret 克隆到匹配的现有命名空间列表中，该命名空间存储在与上面相同的 ConfigMap 中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;种类：ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;名称： foreach-clone&lt;br&gt;规范：&lt;br&gt; 规则：&lt;br&gt; - 匹配：&lt;br&gt; 任意：&lt;br&gt; - 资源：&lt;br&gt; 种类：&lt;br&gt; - ConfigMap&lt;br&gt; 命名空间：&lt;br&gt; - 默认&lt;br&gt;名称：k-kafka-address&lt;br&gt;生成：&lt;br&gt;generateExisting：false&lt;br&gt;同步：true&lt;br&gt;foreach：&lt;br&gt;-列表：request.object.data.namespaces | split(@, &#39;,&#39;)&lt;br&gt; apiVersion: v1&lt;br&gt; kind: Secret&lt;br&gt; name: cloned-secret-{{ elementIndex }}-{{ element }}&lt;br&gt; 命名空间: &#39;{{ element } }&#39;&lt;br&gt; 克隆：&lt;br&gt; 命名空间：默认&lt;br&gt; 名称：源秘密&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30 /announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，每个 &lt;code&gt;foreach&lt;/code&gt; 声明都支持以下声明：Contex 和 Preconditions。有关更多信息，请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/writing-policies/generate/#foreach&#34;&gt;Kyverno 文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本还允许更新生成规则模式。除了删除之外，如果触发资源发生更改，使其不再符合规则中的定义，也会导致下游资源被删除。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;api-call-enhancements&#34;&gt;API 调用增强 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release -1.13/#api-call-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;default-values&#34;&gt;默认值 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/ #默认值&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果 API 服务器返回错误，&lt;code&gt;apiCall.default&lt;/code&gt; 可用于为 API 调用上下文条目提供后备值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下示例演示如何向上下文条目添加默认值：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt; 上下文：&#xA;    - 名称：当前命名空间&#xA;      api调用：&#xA;        urlPath: “/api/v1/namespaces/{{ request.namespace }}”&#xA;        jmesPath: 元数据.name&#xA;        默认：默认&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;custom-headers&#34;&gt;自定义标头 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/ #custom-headers&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 服务 API 调用现在也支持自定义标头。这对于身份验证或添加其他 HTTP 请求标头非常有用。以下是在 HTTP 授权标头中添加令牌的示例：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt; 上下文：&#xA;        - 名称：结果&#xA;          api调用：&#xA;            方法：POST&#xA;            数据：&#xA;              - 键：foo&#xA;                值： 酒吧&#xA;              - 键：命名空间&#xA;                值：“{{`{{request.namespace}}`}}”&#xA;            服务：&#xA;              网址：http://my-service.svc.cluster.local/validation&#xA;              标题：&#xA;                - 键：“用户代理”&#xA;                  值：“Kyverno 策略 XYZ”&#xA;                - 键：“授权”&#xA;                  值：“承载{{ MY_SECRET }}”&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;policy-report-enhancements&#34;&gt;政策报告增强功能 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release -1.13/#policy-report-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;reports-for-mutate-and-generate-rules&#34;&gt;突变和生成规则的报告&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/ 10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#reports-for-mutate-and-generate-rules&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了验证和验证图像规则之外，Kyverno 1.13还支持生成和变异报告，包括变异现有策略，以记录策略结果。容器标志&lt;code&gt;--enableReporting&lt;/code&gt;可用于启用或禁用特定规则类型的报告。它允许使用逗号分隔值、validate、mutate、mutateExisting、generate 和 imageVerify。请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/installation/customization/#container-flags&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结果条目将在策略报告中进行审核以进行规则决策：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;&#34;&gt;api版本：wgpolicyk8s.io/v1alpha2&lt;br&gt;种类：PolicyReport&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;标签：&lt;br&gt;app.kubernetes.io /托管者：kyverno&lt;br&gt;命名空间：默认&lt;br&gt;结果：&lt;br&gt;-消息：命名空间默认&lt;br&gt;策略中突变的Pod/good-pod&lt;br&gt;策略：添加标签&lt;br&gt;结果：通过&lt;br&gt;规则: add-labels&lt;br&gt; 评分：true&lt;br&gt; 来源：kyverno&lt;br&gt;范围：&lt;br&gt; apiVersion: v1&lt;br&gt; 种类：Pod&lt;br&gt; 名称：good-pod&lt;br&gt; 命名空间：default&lt;br&gt; ...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请注意，需要向报告控制器授予适当的权限，如果未配置 RBAC 权限，则策略准入时将返回警告消息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;custom-data-in-reports&#34;&gt;报告中的自定义数据&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing- kyverno-release-1.13/#custom-data-in-reports&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为政策报告中的自定义数据引入了新字段&lt;code&gt;reportProperties&lt;/code&gt;。例如，下面的验证规则向策略报告中添加了两个附加条目“操作”和“objName”：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：kyverno.io/v1&lt;br&gt;种类：ClusterPolicy&lt;br&gt;元数据：&lt;br&gt;名称： require-owner&lt;br&gt;规范：&lt;br&gt; 背景： false&lt;br&gt; 规则：&lt;br&gt; - 匹配：&lt;br&gt; 任何：&lt;br&gt; - 资源：&lt;br&gt; 种类：&lt;br&gt; - 命名空间&lt;br&gt; 名称: check-owner&lt;br&gt; 上下文:&lt;br&gt; - 名称: objName&lt;br&gt; 变量:&lt;br&gt; jmesPath: request.object.metadata.name&lt;br&gt; reportProperties:&lt;br&gt; 操作: &#39;{{ request.operation } }&#39;&lt;br&gt; objName: &#39;{{ objName }}&#39;&lt;br&gt; validate:&lt;br&gt;validationFailureAction: Audit&lt;br&gt; 消息: 所有命名空间都需要 `owner` 标签。&lt;br&gt; 模式:&lt;br&gt; 元数据：&lt;br&gt;标签：&lt;br&gt;所有者：？*&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13 /#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以找到添加到 &lt;code&gt;results.properties&lt;/code&gt; 中的两个自定义条目：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：wgpolicyk8s.io/v1alpha2&#xA;种类：ClusterPolicyReport&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  业主参考资料：&#xA;  - api版本：v1&#xA;    种类：命名空间&#xA;    名称： 酒吧&#xA;结果：&#xA;- 消息：验证规则“check-owner”已通过。&#xA;  政策：要求所有者&#xA;  结果：通过&#xA;  规则：检查所有者&#xA;  得分：真实&#xA;  资料来源：基维尔诺&#xA;  特性：&#xA;    对象名称： 酒吧&#xA;    操作：创建&#xA;范围：&#xA;  api版本：v1&#xA;  种类：命名空间&#xA;  名称： 酒吧&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;globalcontextentries-enhancements&#34;&gt;GlobalContextEntries 增强&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/ #globalcontextentries-enhancements&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;api-call-retry&#34;&gt;API 调用重试 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release -1.13/#api-call-retry&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 的 GlobalContextEntry 提供了一种强大的机制来获取外部数据并在策略中使用它。当利用 apiCall 功能从 API 检索数据时，短暂的网络问题有时会阻碍成功检索。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了解决这个问题，Kyverno 现在为 GlobalContextEntry 中的 API 调用提供内置重试逻辑。您现在可以选择为 API 调用指定 retryLimit：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：kyverno.io/v2alpha1&#xA;种类：GlobalContextEntry&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：gctxentry-apicall-正确&#xA;规格：&#xA;  api调用：&#xA;    urlPath: &#34;/apis/apps/v1/namespaces/test-globalcontext-apicall- Correct/deployments&#34;&#xA;    刷新间隔：1h&#xA;    重试次数限制：3&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;retryLimit&lt;/code&gt; 字段确定 Kyverno 在最初失败时尝试进行 API 调用的次数。该字段是可选的，默认为 3，确保针对临时网络故障的合理恢复能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过整合此重试机制，Kyverno 进一步增强了其可靠获取外部数据的能力，确保您的策略即使在偶尔出现连接问题的情况下也能顺利运行。此增强功能提高了 Kubernetes 策略执行框架的整体稳健性和可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;cli-based-injection-of-global-context-entries&#34;&gt;基于 CLI 的全局上下文条目注入&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/博客/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#cli-based-injection-of-global-上下文条目&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno CLI 现在允许您使用值文件动态注入全局上下文条目。此功能通过模拟不同的场景，无需修改集群中的 GlobalContextEntry 资源，可以促进灵活的策略测试和执行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您现在可以在值文件中定义全局值和特定于规则的值，从而在测试期间更好地控制策略评估。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：cli.kyverno.io/v1alpha1&#xA;种类：价值&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：值&#xA;全局价值观：&#xA;  请求.操作：创建&#xA;政策：&#xA;  - 名称：gctx&#xA;    规则：&#xA;      - 名称：主部署存在&#xA;        价值观：&#xA;          部署数量：1&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此示例中，&lt;code&gt;request.operation&lt;/code&gt; 设置为全局值，并为 gctx 政策中的特定规则设置部署计数。使用 Kyverno CLI 时，您可以引用此值文件将这些全局上下文条目注入到您的策略评估中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;security-hardening&#34;&gt;安全强化&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/ #安全强化&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 项目致力于确保安全和生产就绪，同时提供易用性。此版本包含进一步增强项目安全性的重要更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;removal-of-wildcard-roles&#34;&gt;移除通配符角色 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing- kyverno-release-1.13/#removal-of-wildcard-roles&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 的早期版本包含通配符查看权限。这些已在 1.13 中删除，并替换为绑定到系统视图角色的角色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此更改不会影响准入控制期间的策略行为，但可能会影响使用 mutate 的用户并为自定义资源生成策略，并且可能会影响自定义资源验证规则的策略结果的报告 添加了 Helm 选项以升级 Kyverno 而不会破坏现有政策，请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/installation/upgrading/#upgrading-to-kyverno-v113&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;的升级指南。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h4 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;removal-of-insecure-configuration-for-exceptions&#34;&gt;删除异常的不安全配置&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/ 10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#removal-of-insecure-configuration-for-exceptions&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在之前的版本中，所有命名空间都允许策略例外。这会产生潜在的安全问题，因为任何有权创建策略例外的用户都可以绕过策略，即使在其他命名空间中也是如此。请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kyverno/kyverno/security/advisories/GHSA-qjvc-p88j-j9rm&#34;&gt;CVE-2024-48921&lt;/a&gt; 了解更多详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此版本更改了默认设置以禁用策略异常，并且仅允许在指定命名空间中创建异常。要保持向后兼容性，请遵循&lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/installation/upgrading/#upgrading-to-kyverno-v113&#34;&gt;升级指南&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;warnings-for-policy-violations-and-mutations&#34;&gt;政策违规和变更警告&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/ 10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#warnings-for-policy-violations-and-mutations&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在可以通过策略设置 &lt;code&gt;spec.emitWarning&lt;/code&gt; 返回一条警告消息以及准入响应，这可用于报告政策违规行为以及准入事件的突变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;shallow-evaluation-of-variables&#34;&gt;变量的浅评估&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing- kyverno-release-1.13/#shallow-evaluation-of-variables&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 默认执行嵌套变量替换，这在某些情况下可能并不理想。以下面的 ConfigMap 为例，它使用与 Kyverno 中变量语法相同的 &lt;code&gt;{{ }}&lt;/code&gt; 表示法定义 &lt;code&gt;.hcl&lt;/code&gt; 字符串内容。在这种情况下，需要指示 Kyverno 不要尝试解析 HCL 中的变量，这可以通过变量浅（仅一次）替换的 &lt;code&gt;{{- ... }}&lt;/code&gt; 表示法来实现.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：v1&#xA;数据：&#xA;  配置：|-&#xA;    来自字符串&#xA;    {{ 一些 hcl 模板 }}    &#xA;种类：ConfigMap&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  注释：&#xA;  标签：&#xA;    argocd.development.cpl.&lt;已删除&gt;.co.at/app: corp-tech-ap-team-ping-ep&#xA;  名称：vault-injector-config-http-echo&#xA;  命名空间：corp-tech-ap-team-ping-ep&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了仅用 HCL 替换规则数据，而不执行嵌套替换，以下策略使用声明 &lt;code&gt;{{- hcl }}&lt;/code&gt; 进行浅替换。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre class=&#34;wp-block-code&#34;&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;yaml&#34; class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;api版本：cli.kyverno.io/v1alphaapi版本：kyverno.io/v1&#xA;种类：集群策略&#xA;元数据：&#xA;  名称：vault-auth-backend&#xA;规格：&#xA;  validationFailureAction：审核&#xA;  背景：真实&#xA;  mutateExistingOnPolicyUpdate：true&#xA;  规则：&#xA;  - 名称：vault-injector-config-blue-to-green-auth-backend&#xA;    语境：&#xA;    - 名称：hcl&#xA;      多变的：&#xA;        jmesPath：replace_all(&#39;{{request.object.data.config }}&#39;,&#39;from_string&#39;,&#39;to_string&#39;)&#xA;    匹配：&#xA;      任何：&#xA;      - 资源：&#xA;          种类：&#xA;          - 配置映射&#xA;          名称：&#xA;          - 测试-*&#xA;          命名空间：- corp-tech-ap-team-ping-ep&#xA;    变异：&#xA;      补丁策略合并：&#xA;        数据：&#xA;          配置：&#39;{{- hcl }}&#39;&#xA;      目标：&#xA;      - api版本：v1&#xA;        种类：ConfigMap&#xA;        名称：&#39;{{ request.object.metadata.name }}&#39;&#xA;        命名空间：&#39;{{ request.object.metadata.namespace }}&#39;&#xA;    名称：vault-injector-config-blue-to-green-auth-backend&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog /2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;improved-argocd-integration&#34;&gt;改进的 ArgoCD 集成&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release -1.13/#improved-argocd-integration&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;卸载时，Kyverno 管理的 Webhook 配置会自动清理。如果 Kyverno 在给定随机资源删除顺序的情况下失去 RBAC 权限，则此行为可能会被破坏。此版本引入了基于终结器的清理解决方案，以确保成功删除 Webhook。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能处于&lt;a href=&#34;https://main.kyverno.io/docs/installation/uninstallation/#clean-up-webhooks&#34;&gt;测试阶段&lt;/a&gt;，将用作默认清理功能未来的战略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;api-version-management&#34;&gt;API 版本管理 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release -1.13/#api-版本管理&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 引入了策略 CRD 的新变化：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;政策例外和清理政策均已升级为稳定版本 (v2)。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多项政策设置已弃用：&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.validationFailureAction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.validationFailureActionOverrides&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.mutateExistingOnPolicyUpdate&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.generateExisting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;这些规则已被规则本身内更精细的控制所取代：&#xA;&lt;ul class=&#34;wp-block-list&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[*].validate.failureAction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[*].validate.failureActionOverrides&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[&lt;em&gt;].verifyImages[&lt;/em&gt;].failureAction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[*].mutate.mutateExisting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;spec.rules[*].generate.generateExisting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请注意，已弃用的字段将在未来版本中删除，因此建议迁移到新设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;结论 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/blog/2024/10/30/announcing-kyverno-release-1.13/#conclusion&#34; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kyverno 1.13 有望成为一个出色的版本，包含许多新功能、增强功能和修复。要开始使用 Kyverno，请尝试&lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/docs/introduction/quick-start/&#34;&gt;快速入门指南&lt;/a&gt;或前往&lt;a href=&#34;https:// kyverno.io/docs/installation/methods/&#34;&gt;文档的安装&lt;/a&gt;部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要充分发挥 Kyverno 的价值，请查看e &lt;a href=&#34;https://kyverno.io/support/&#34;&gt;可用的企业解决方案&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;height:80px&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; class=&#34;wp-block-spacer is-style-80-120&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>