<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes Debugging Recipe: Practical Steps to Diagnose Pods Like a Pro】Kubernetes 调试秘诀：像专业人士一样诊断 Pod 的实用步骤</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/debugging-kubernetes-pods-like-a-pro</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Automation isn’t optional at enterprise scale. It’s resilient by design. Kubernetes provides remarkable scalability and resilience , but when pods crash, even seasoned engineers struggle to translate complex and cryptic logs and events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide walks you through the spectrum of AI-powered root cause analysis and manual debugging, combining command-line reproducibility and predictive observability approaches.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;自动化在企业规模上不是可选的。它的设计具有弹性。 Kubernetes 提供了卓越的可扩展性和弹性，但是当 Pod 崩溃时，即使是经验丰富的工程师也很难翻译复杂且神秘的日志和事件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南将引导您完成人工智能驱动的根本原因分析和手动调试，结合命令行再现性和预测可观察性方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Distributed Monolith to Composable Architecture on AWS】从分布式整体架构到 AWS 上的可组合架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/from-distributed-monolith-to-composable-architecture-on-aws</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;You adopted microservices for independence and agility. Instead, every deployment requires coordinating multiple teams and testing the entire system. What you built is a distributed monolith, complexity spread across systems, but still bound by monolithic coupling. The shift from technical boundaries to business-driven boundaries is the only path to true agility. Many organizations discover too late that microservices alone do not guarantee independence. Domain-Driven Composable Architecture (DDCA) provides a methodology to escape this rigidity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article is a practical playbook for decomposing services into Packaged Business Capabilities (PBCs) aligned with business domains and mapped to AWS patterns such as EventBridge, Step Functions, and DynamoDB Streams. It explains when DDCA fits and when it does not, and covers security, anti-patterns, and operational realities, so you can adopt composability with a clear view of the investment required.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;您采用微服务是为了实现独立性和敏捷性。相反，每次部署都需要协调多个团队并测试整个系统。您构建的是一个分布式整体，复杂性分布在各个系统中，但仍然受到整体耦合的束缚。从技术边界到业务驱动边界的转变是实现真正敏捷的唯一途径。许多组织发现微服务本身并不能保证独立性，但为时已晚。领域驱动可组合架构（DDCA）提供了一种摆脱这种僵化的方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文是一本实用手册，用于将服务分解为与业务领域保持一致并映射到 AWS 模式（例如 EventBridge、Step Functions 和 DynamoDB Streams）的打包业务功能 (PBC)。它解释了 DDCA 何时适合、何时不适合，并涵盖安全性、反模式和操作现实，以便您可以采用可组合性，并清楚地了解所需的投资。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unhandled Promise Rejections: The Tiny Mistake That Crashed Our Node.js App】未处理的 Promise 拒绝：导致 Node.js 应用程序崩溃的小错误</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unhandled-promise-rejections-nodejs-crash</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Imagine deploying a Node.js backend service that works flawlessly in development, only to have it mysteriously crash in production. Everything ran fine on your laptop, but on the live server, the process keeps shutting down unexpectedly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In our case, the culprit was a single unhandled promise rejection — one missing &lt;code data-end=&#34;410&#34; data-start=&#34;400&#34;&gt;.catch()&lt;/code&gt; in our code caused Node to exit abruptly whenever an error occurred. That one “tiny” mistake made the difference between a stable service and frequent downtime. In this article, we’ll explore how a misconfigured error handling in a Node/Express API can bring down an application, and how to diagnose and fix it to prevent future crashes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;想象一下，部署一个在开发中完美运行的 Node.js 后端服务，却在生产中神秘地崩溃了。在您的笔记本电脑上一切运行良好，但在实时服务器上，进程不断意外关闭。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们的例子中，罪魁祸首是一个未处理的 Promise 拒绝 - 我们的代码中缺少一个 &lt;code data-end=&#34;410&#34; data-start=&#34;400&#34;&gt;.catch()&lt;/code&gt; 导致 Node 在发生错误时突然退出。正是这个“小”错误导致了稳定的服务和频繁的停机。在本文中，我们将探讨 Node/Express API 中配置错误的错误处理如何导致应用程序崩溃，以及如何诊断和修复它以防止将来发生崩溃。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Performance Testing 101: A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Building Robust Applications】性能测试 101：构建健壮应用程序的初学者指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/performance-testing-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Welcome! This guide is for anyone who has built an application and wants to ensure it doesn&#39;t fall over when real people start using it. We&#39;ll walk through the essentials of performance testing without the complicated jargon, focusing on practical steps you can take to make your app robust and reliable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You may find this article too abstract, but be sure the next time we will go over the real example of making a performance test with Java, Gatling, and Docker Compose.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;欢迎！本指南适用于已经构建了应用程序并希望确保当真人开始使用它时它不会崩溃的任何人。我们将介绍性能测试的要点，不使用复杂的术语，重点关注您可以采取的实际步骤，以使您的应用程序健壮可靠。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可能会发现本文过于抽象，但请确保下次我们将讨论使用 Java、Gattle 和 Docker Compose 进行性能测试的真实示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Strategic Domain-Driven Design: The Forgotten Foundation of Great Software】战略领域驱动设计：伟大软件被遗忘的基础</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/strategic-domain-driven-design</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;When teams talk about d&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;omain-driven design (DDD)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;, the conversation often jumps straight to code — entities, value objects, and aggregates. Yet, this is where most projects begin to lose direction. The essence of DDD is not in the tactical implementation, but in its&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;strategic foundation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;— the part that defines&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;why&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;where&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;we apply the patterns in the first place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;The strategic aspect of DDD is often overlooked because many people do not recognize its importance. This is a significant mistake when applying DDD. Strategic design provides context for the model, establishes clear boundaries, and fosters a shared understanding between business and technology. Without this foundation, developers may focus on modeling data rather than behavior, create isolated microservices that do not represent the domain accurately, or implement design patterns without a clear purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;当团队讨论&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;域驱动设计 (DDD)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; 时，对话通常会直接跳转到代码 — 实体、值对象和聚合。然而，这就是大多数项目开始失去方向的地方。 DDD 的本质不在于战术实施，而在于其战略基础&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; - 定义&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;原因&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;和&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span的部分 data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;我们首先在何处应用模式。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;我们首先应用这些模式。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;DDD 的战略方面经常被忽视，因为许多人没有认识到它的重要性。这是应用 DDD 时的一个重大错误。战略设计为模型提供了背景，建立了清晰的界限，并促进了业务和技术之间的共同理解。如果没有这个基础，开发人员可能会专注于对数据建模而不是行为，创建不能准确表示领域的孤立的微服务，或者在没有明确目的的情况下实现设计模式。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build a Dynamic Web Form Using Camunda BPMN and DMN】使用 Camunda BPMN 和 DMN 构建动态 Web 表单</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dynamic-web-form-using-camunda-dmn</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Business Process Model and Notation (BPMN) is the universal standard for visually modeling and automating business processes. It is used to design and automate workflows, defining the sequence of tasks, approvals, and user interactions. Whereas Decision Model and Notation (DMN) models the complex decision logic that can be embedded within those processes to automate business rules in a structured, reusable way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Camunda&#39;s process orchestration platform provides a collaborative environment for Business and IT developers via an intuitive visual Modeler that adheres to BPMN and DMN standards. Modeling with Camunda reduces the time it takes to develop and maintain real-world business processes through automation. Beyond automation, combining BPMN and DMN allows us to create dynamic web forms where the fields, validations, and even flow of the form adapt real-time business rules, instead of being hardcoded. This makes applications more flexible, easier to maintain, and business-driven.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;业务流程模型和表示法 (BPMN) 是可视化建模和自动化业务流程的通用标准。它用于设计和自动化工作流程，定义任务、批准和用户交互的顺序。而决策模型和表示法 (DMN) 对复杂的决策逻辑进行建模，可以嵌入到这些流程中，以结构化、可重用的方式自动化业务规则。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Camunda 的流程编排平台通过符合 BPMN 和 DMN 标准的直观可视化建模器为业务和 IT 开发人员提供了协作环境。使用 Camunda 进行建模可减少通过自动化开发和维护实际业务流程所需的时间。除了自动化之外，结合 BPMN 和 DMN 使我们能够创建动态 Web 表单，其中字段、验证甚至表单流程适应实时业务规则，而不是进行硬编码。这使得应用程序更加灵活、更易于维护且业务驱动。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud Agnostic MLOps: How to Build and Deploy AI Models Across Azure, AWS, and Open Source】与云无关的 MLOps：如何跨 Azure、AWS 和开源构建和部署 AI 模型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-agnostic-mlops-ai-model-deployment</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence has become the centerpiece of every digital strategy. What began as isolated proof-of-concepts running on data scientists’ laptops is now expected to scale across clouds, business units, and continents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Enterprises quickly discover that the challenge is not building AI models. It’s operationalizing them sustainably.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能已成为每个数字战略的核心。最初是在数据科学家的笔记本电脑上运行的孤立的概念验证，现在预计可以跨云、业务部门和大陆扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;企业很快发现挑战不在于构建人工智能模型。它正在可持续地实施它们。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Diagnosing and Fixing a Page Fault Performance Issue With Arm64 Atomics】诊断和修复 Arm64 Atomics 的页面错误性能问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/arm64-atomics-page-fault-performance-issue</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;While running a synthetic benchmark that pre-warmed the cache, we noticed an abnormal performance impact on Ampere CPUs. Digging deeper, we found that there were many more page faults happening with Ampere CPUs when compared to x86 CPUs. We isolated the issue to the use of certain atomic instructions like ldadd, which load a register, add a value to it, and store data in a register in a single instruction. This triggered two “page faults” under certain conditions, even though this is logically an all-or-nothing operation, which is guaranteed to be completed in one step.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, we will summarize how to qualify this kind of problem, how memory management in Linux works in general, explain how an atomic Arm64 instruction can generate multiple page faults, and show how to avoid performance slowdowns related to this behavior.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在运行预热缓存的综合基准测试时，我们注意到 Ampere CPU 出现异常性能影响。深入挖掘后，我们发现与 x86 CPU 相比，Ampere CPU 发生的页面错误要多得多。我们将该问题与某些原子指令（例如 ldadd）的使用隔离开来，这些指令会加载寄存器、向其添加值，然后在单个指令中将数据存储在寄存器中。这在某些条件下触发了两次“页面错误”，尽管这在逻辑上是一种全有或全无的操作，保证一步完成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将总结如何限定此类问题、Linux 中内存管理的一般工作原理、解释原子 Arm64 指令如何生成多个页面错误，并展示如何避免与此行为相关的性能下降。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【I Built a Full Stack App Using Only Vibe Coding Prompts: Here’s What Happened】我仅使用 Vibe 编码提示构建了一个全栈应用程序：这就是发生的事情</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/full-stack-app-with-vibe-coding-prompts</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;You know that moment when you stare at your screen and think, &lt;em&gt;“What if I just let the vibes lead?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; &amp;nbsp;That’s exactly what I did.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I decided to build a &lt;strong&gt;full-stack app&lt;/strong&gt;, not with a strict roadmap, not with a pre-decided stack, and not even with a design in Figma, but by coding my way through it by vibe. I used AI tools, intuition, and years of muscle memory to go with the flow. No formal planning, no architecture diagrams, no syntax lookups, just prompts, patterns, and pure gut feel.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您知道当您盯着屏幕思考的那一刻，&lt;em&gt;“如果我只是让共鸣引导怎么办？”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  这正是我所做的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我决定构建一个&lt;strong&gt;全栈应用程序&lt;/strong&gt;，没有严格的路线图，没有预先决定的堆栈，甚至没有Figma中的设计，而是通过vibe进行编码。我利用人工智能工具、直觉和多年的肌肉记忆来顺应潮流。没有正式的规划，没有架构图，没有语法查找，只有提示、模式和纯粹的直觉。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Evolving Golden Paths: Upgrades Without Disruption】不断发展的黄金之路：不间断升级</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/evolving-golden-paths-upgrades-without-disruption</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The platform team had done it again — a new version of the golden path was ready. Cleaner templates, better guardrails, smoother CI/CD. But as soon as it rolled out, messages started flooding in: &lt;em&gt;“My pipeline broke!”&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;“The new module isn’t compatible with our setup!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sound familiar? Every platform engineer knows that delicate balance — driving innovation while ensuring developer stability. Golden paths promise simplicity and speed, but without careful version management, they can easily turn from enablers into disruptors.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;平台团队再次做到了——新版本的黄金之路已经准备好了。更干净的模板、更好的护栏、更流畅的 CI/CD。但它一推出，消息就开始涌入：&lt;em&gt;“我的管道坏了！”&lt;/em&gt;、&lt;em&gt;“新模块与我们的设置不兼容！”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;听起来很熟悉吗？每个平台工程师都知道这种微妙的平衡——推动创新，同时确保开发人员的稳定性。黄金路径承诺简单性和速度，但如果没有仔细的版本管理，它们很容易从推动者变成破坏者。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>