<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering DynamoDB: A Developer&#39;s Guide】掌握 DynamoDB：开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-dynamodb-a-developers-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the ever-evolving landscape of database technologies, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-access-control-in-amazon-dynamodb-impleme&#34;&gt;Amazon DynamoDB&lt;/a&gt; stands out as a robust, fully managed &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-nosql-database-1&#34;&gt;NoSQL database service&lt;/a&gt; designed for applications requiring consistent, single-digit millisecond response times at any scale. From startups to large enterprises, DynamoDB is the go-to choice for handling high-velocity data needs. In this guide, we&#39;ll explore the fundamentals, advanced features, and best practices to help you master DynamoDB.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why Choose DynamoDB?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Seamless Scalability&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DynamoDB automatically scales up and down to handle the throughput of your application without downtime. Whether you&#39;re managing a small workload or scaling to millions of requests per second, DynamoDB adjusts to your needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在不断发展的数据库技术领域，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-access-control-in-amazon-dynamodb-impleme&#34;&gt;Amazon DynamoDB&lt;/a&gt; 脱颖而出作为一个强大的、完全托管的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-nosql-database-1&#34;&gt;NoSQL 数据库服务&lt;/a&gt;，专为需要一致、个位数毫秒的应用程序而设计任何规模的响应时间。从初创公司到大型企业，DynamoDB 是处理高速数据需求的首选。在本指南中，我们将探讨基础知识、高级功能和最佳实践，以帮助您掌握 DynamoDB。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么选择 DynamoDB？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;无缝可扩展性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DynamoDB 自动扩展和缩小以处理应用程序的吞吐量，而无需停机。无论您是管理小型工作负载还是扩展到每秒数百万个请求，DynamoDB 都会根据您的需求进行调整。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Penetration Testing for Beginners: A Step-By-Step Guide】初学者渗透测试：分步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/penetration-testing-for-beginners-a-step-by-step</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In an era where digital transformation is rapidly advancing, the importance of cybersecurity cannot be overstated. One of the essential aspects of maintaining robust security is penetration testing, commonly known as pentesting. This guide aims to provide beginners with a comprehensive understanding of penetration testing, offering a step-by-step approach to getting started in this critical field.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction to Penetration Testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Penetration testing is a simulated cyber attack against a computer system, network, or web application to identify security vulnerabilities that an attacker could exploit. The primary goal is to find and fix these vulnerabilities before they can be leveraged by malicious actors. Penetration testing can be manual or automated and typically involves various methods and tools to evaluate the security of an organization’s IT infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在数字化转型快速推进的时代，网络安全的重要性怎么强调都不为过。维护强大安全性的重要方面之一是渗透测试，通常称为渗透测试。本指南旨在帮助初学者全面了解渗透测试，并提供在这一关键领域入门的分步方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;渗透测试简介&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;渗透测试是针对计算机系统、网络或 Web 应用程序的模拟网络攻击，旨在识别攻击者可能利用的安全漏洞。主要目标是在这些漏洞被恶意行为者利用之前找到并修复它们。渗透测试可以是手动或自动的，通常涉及各种方法和工具来评估组织 IT 基础设施的安全性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Questioning an Image Database With Local AI/LLM on Ollama and Spring AI】在 Ollama 和 Spring AI 上使用本地 AI/LLM 质疑图像数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/questioning-an-image-database-with-local-aillm</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Angular2Guy/AIDocumentLibraryChat&#34;&gt;AIDocumentLibraryChat&lt;/a&gt; project has been extended to include an image database that can be questioned for images. It uses the &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/library/llava&#34;&gt;LLava&lt;/a&gt; model of &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com&#34;&gt;Ollama&lt;/a&gt;, which can analyze images. The image search uses embeddings with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pgvector/pgvector&#34;&gt;PGVector&lt;/a&gt; extension of PostgreSQL.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Angular2Guy/AIDocumentLibraryChat&#34;&gt;AIDocumentLibraryChat&lt;/a&gt; project has this architecture:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Angular2Guy/AIDocumentLibraryChat&#34;&gt;AIDocumentLibraryChat&lt;/a&gt; 项目已扩展为包含可以查询图像的图像数据库。它使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/library/llava&#34;&gt;Ollama&lt;/a&gt; 的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/library/llava&#34;&gt;LLava&lt;/a&gt; 模型，它可以分析图像。图像搜索使用带有 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pgvector/pgvector&#34;&gt;PGVector&lt;/a&gt; PostgreSQL 扩展的嵌入。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;架构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Angular2Guy/AIDocumentLibraryChat&#34;&gt;AIDocumentLibraryChat&lt;/a&gt; 项目具有以下架构：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Choosing the Best CSS Frameworks for Enterprise Web Applications】为企业 Web 应用程序选择最佳 CSS 框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/choosing-the-best-css-frameworks-for-enterprise</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The heart of the web application is Cascading Style Sheets (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/corecss-part1&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;), which allows you to style your web pages and make them look better and richer. There are many CSS frameworks available for you to choose from when architecting an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/guides/dynamic-web-and-mobile-application-development&#34;&gt;enterprise web application&lt;/a&gt;. These frameworks often provide you with responsive standard styles that are pre-built for the same purpose. When choosing a particular framework, look for specific product requirements; it also allows for more customization and the ability to scale and perform when tied to the web app. I will be making a detailed analysis of some popular CSS frameworks like Bootstrap CSS, Tailwind CSS, Chakra UI, and Next UI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;1. Tailwind CSS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As per its definition, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/theme-based-front-end-architecture-leveraging&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tailwind CSS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a utility-first CSS framework for rapidly building modern websites without ever leaving your HTML. This allows the developers to directly inject the classes into the respective HTML elements. This takes away all the groundwork that the developer has to do to spin the web page with proper styling. In short, there is no need to maintain an external style sheet. It&#39;s easy to customize and scale.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Web 应用程序的核心是层叠样式表 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/corecss-part1&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;)，它允许您设置网页样式并让他们看起来更好、更富有。在构建&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/guides/dynamic-web-and-mobile-application-development&#34;&gt;企业 Web 应用程序&lt;/a&gt;时，有许多 CSS 框架可供您选择。这些框架通常为您提供出于相同目的而预先构建的响应式标准样式。选择特定框架时，​​请考虑特定的产品需求；它还允许更多的定制以及在与网络应用程序绑定时扩展和执行的能力。我将对一些流行的 CSS 框架进行详细分析，例如 Bootstrap CSS、Tailwind CSS、Chakra UI 和 Next UI。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;1。顺风CSS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;概述&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据其定义，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/theme-based-front-end-architecture-leveraging&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tailwind CSS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 是实用程序优先的 CSS 框架，用于快速构建现代网站，而无需离开 HTML。这允许开发人员直接将类注入到相应的 HTML 元素中。这消除了开发人员为使用正确的样式旋转网页所必须做的所有基础工作。简而言之，不需要维护外部样式表。易于定制和扩展。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Alluxio Enterprise AI 3.2: Enhancing GPU Utilization and Data Access for AI Workloads】Alluxio Enterprise AI 3.2：增强AI工作负载的GPU利用率和数据访问</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/alluxio-enterprise-ai-32-enhancing-gpu-utilization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In an era where AI and machine learning are pushing the boundaries of computational power, efficient GPU utilization, and data access have become critical bottlenecks. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.alluxio.com&#34;&gt;Alluxio&lt;/a&gt;, a pioneer in data orchestration for analytics and AI, has unveiled its latest offering, Alluxio Enterprise AI 3.2, to address these challenges head-on. This release promises to transform how organizations leverage their &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/applications-for-gpu-based-ai-and-machine-learning&#34;&gt;GPU&lt;/a&gt; resources and manage data for AI workloads, offering a blend of performance, flexibility, and ease of use that could reshape the landscape of AI infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Unleashing GPU Power: Anywhere, Anytime&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;One of the standout features of Alluxio Enterprise AI 3.2 is its ability to enable GPU utilization anywhere. This capability is a game-changer in a world where GPU resources are often scarce and distributed across various environments. Organizations can now run AI workloads wherever GPUs are available, whether on-premises, in the cloud, or in a hybrid setup.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在人工智能和机器学习不断突破计算能力界限的时代，高效的 GPU 利用率和数据访问已成为关键瓶颈。 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.alluxio.com&#34;&gt;Alluxio&lt;/a&gt; 是分析和人工智能数据编排领域的先驱，推出了最新产品 Alluxio Enterprise AI 3.2，以应对这些挑战。此版本有望改变组织利用其 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/applications-for-gpu-based-ai-and-machine-learning&#34;&gt;GPU&lt;/a&gt; 资源和管理数据的方式针对人工智能工作负载，提供性能、灵活性和易用性的结合，可以重塑人工智能基础设施的格局。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;释放 GPU 能力：随时随地&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Alluxio Enterprise AI 3.2 的突出功能之一是能够在任何地方启用 GPU 利用率。在 GPU 资源通常稀缺且分布在各种环境中的世界中，此功能将彻底改变游戏规则。现在，组织可以在任何可用 GPU 的地方运行 AI 工作负载，无论是在本地、云端还是混合设置中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Creating Wrapper Classes for Component Libraries Is a Great Idea in Web Development】为什么为组件库创建包装类是 Web 开发中的一个好主意</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-wrapper-classes-for-component-libraries</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;No wonder there are tons of third-party &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/web-component-solutions-a-comparison&#34;&gt;component libraries&lt;/a&gt; available that can be integrated into your project to speed up the development process. Libraries like Angular Material UI, Bootstrap, Chakra UI, Next UI, and others offer various other rich features that are lightweight, fast, and adhere to accessibility norms. However, direct access to library components without an abstraction layer could lead to numerous inconsistencies and maintainability issues in the future. This is the primary reason I insist on creating classes that encapsulate the original composition, which I refer to as wrapper classes. These classes are easy to create and allow more flexibility and consistency when building an enterprise web application.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of Creating Wrapper Classes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Consistency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to consistency, I mean the look and feel of the components throughout the web application. Would you allow dropdowns or radio buttons to appear differently? The answer is no. Wrapping ensures uniformity and consistency across the app, enabling the components to seamlessly integrate with the product&#39;s specific branding. Here, branding refers to the themes and skins of the common components that you will use throughout the app.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;难怪有大量的第三方&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/web-component-solutions-a-comparison&#34;&gt;组件库&lt;/a&gt;可以集成到加快您的项目的开发进程。 Angular Material UI、Bootstrap、Chakra UI、Next UI 等库提供了各种其他丰富的功能，这些功能轻量、快速且符合可访问性规范。然而，在没有抽象层的情况下直接访问库组件可能会在未来导致许多不一致和可维护性问题。这是我坚持创建封装原始组合的类的主要原因，我将其称为包装类。这些类很容易创建，并且在构建企业 Web 应用程序时具有更大的灵活性和一致性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;创建包装类的好处&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;1。 &lt;strong&gt;一致性&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;说到一致性，我指的是整个 Web 应用程序中组件的外观和感觉。您是否允许下拉菜单或单选按钮以不同的方式显示？答案是不。包装可确保整个应用程序的统一性和一致性，使组件能够与产品的特定品牌无缝集成。在这里，品牌是指您将在整个应用程序中使用的常见组件的主题和外观。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Argo Rollout and Deployment Strategies】Argo 推出和部署策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/argo-rollout-and-deployment-strategies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/stress-free-deployment-options-with-argo-rollouts&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts&lt;/a&gt; is a Kubernetes controller and a part of the Argo project that provides advanced deployment capabilities for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-rise-of-kubernetes-reshaping-the-future&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;. It enhances the deployment process by offering advanced strategies such as blue-green deployments, canary releases, and experimentation. Argo Rollouts allows you to manage the release process of your applications more effectively, ensuring minimal downtime and better control over how updates are rolled out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts (optionally) integrates with ingress controllers and service meshes, leveraging their traffic shaping abilities to gradually shift traffic to the new version during an update. Additionally, Rollouts can query and interpret metrics from various providers to verify key KPIs and drive automated promotion or rollback during an update.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/stress-free-deployment-options-with-argo-rollouts&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts&lt;/a&gt; 是 Kubernetes 控制器和是 Argo 项目的一部分，为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-rise-of-kubernetes-reshaping-the-future&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; 提供高级部署功能。它通过提供蓝绿部署、金丝雀发布和实验等高级策略来增强部署过程。 Argo Rollouts 使您能够更有效地管理应用程序的发布流程，确保最短的停机时间并更好地控制更新的推出方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts（可选）与入口控制器和服务网格集成，利用其流量整形功能在更新期间逐渐将流量转移到新版本。此外，推出可以查询和解释来自各个提供商的指标，以验证关键 KPI 并在更新期间推动自动升级或回滚。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Faster Startup With Spring Boot 3.2 and CRaC, Part 1: Automatic Checkpoint】使用 Spring Boot 3.2 和 CRaC 加快启动速度，第 1 部分：自动检查点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/faster-startup-with-spring-boot-32-and-crac-part-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With Spring Boot 3.2 and Spring Framework 6.1, we get support for &lt;strong&gt;Coordinated Restore at Checkpoint&lt;/strong&gt; (CRaC), a mechanism that enables Java applications to start up faster. With Spring Boot, we can use CRaC in a simplified way, known as &lt;strong&gt;Automatic Checkpoint/Restore at startup&lt;/strong&gt;. Even though not as powerful as the standard way of using CRaC, this blog post will show an example where the Spring Boot applications startup time is decreased by 90%. The sample applications are from chapter 6 in my book on building microservices with Spring Boot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The blog post is divided into the following sections:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;借助 Spring Boot 3.2 和 Spring Framework 6.1，我们获得了对&lt;strong&gt;检查点协调还原&lt;/strong&gt; (CRaC) 的支持，这是一种使 Java 应用程序能够更快启动的机制。借助 Spring Boot，我们可以以一种简化的方式使用 CRaC，即&lt;strong&gt;启动时自动检查点/恢复&lt;/strong&gt;。尽管不如使用 CRaC 的标准方式那么强大，但本博客文章将展示一个示例，其中 Spring Boot 应用程序启动时间减少了 90%。示例应用程序来自我关于使用 Spring Boot 构建微服务的书的第 6 章。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;博客文章分为以下部分：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GBase 8s Database Locking Issues and Performance Optimization Strategies】GBase 8s数据库锁定问题及性能优化策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gbase-8s-database-locking-issues-and-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Database locking issues have always been a challenging aspect of database management. In the GBase 8s database, table locks can lead to the locking of table headers, data rows, and other components, which can result in various error messages. This article provides an in-depth understanding of the locking situations in GBase 8s and offers a series of effective resolution strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;1-locking-situations&#34; href=&#34;https://dev.to/new#1-locking-situations&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;1. Locking Situations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 8s locking issue can lock components such as table headers and specific data rows. Different lock conflicts will trigger different error messages, such as &lt;code&gt;244: Could not do a physical-order read to fetch next row&lt;/code&gt;. These are essentially lock conflict issues.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据库锁定问题一直是数据库管理中一个具有挑战性的方面。在GBase 8s数据库中，表锁会导致表头、数据行和其他组件被锁定，从而导致各种错误消息。本文深入了解GBase 8s中的锁定情况，并提供一系列有效的解决策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;1-locking-situations&#34; href=&#34;https://dev.to/new#1-locking-situations&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;1.锁定情况&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;8s 锁定问题可以锁定表头和特定数据行等组件。不同的锁冲突会触发不同的错误消息，例如&lt;code&gt;244：无法执行物理顺序读取以获取下一行&lt;/code&gt;。这些本质上是锁冲突问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SBOMs in Action: Securing Your Golden AMIs From Build to Runtime】SBOM 的实际应用：从构建到运行时保护您的黄金 AMI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sboms-in-action-securing-your-golden-amis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;5:1-5:373&#34;&gt;Golden Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) are the foundation for launching consistent and efficient instances in your AWS cloud environment. Ensuring their security and immutability is paramount. This guide delves into how Software Bill of Materials (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/software-supply-chain-security-checklist&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SBOMs&lt;/a&gt;), cryptographic signing, and runtime validation create a robust framework for building and maintaining secure golden AMIs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Steps Involved in Building Golden AMIs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34; style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;table class=&#34;fr-alternate-rows fr-dashed-borders&#34; style=&#34;max-width: 100%; width: auto; table-layout: fixed; display: table;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th class=&#34;fr-highlighted&#34; style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start with a Trusted Base Image&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Begin by selecting a minimal, reputable base image, such as AWS-provided base AMIs that are regularly updated with the latest security patches.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Necessary Packages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Install required packages using package managers like yum, apt, or pip. Ensure that packages are sourced from trusted repositories and specify version numbers for consistency.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configure Users and Permissions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Follow the Principle of Least Privilege when creating user accounts, removing unnecessary default users and groups. Configure SSH for key-based authentication and restrict root access.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Functional Testing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Verify the functionality of installed software and applications, including network connectivity and essential system services, to ensure everything works as expected.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Scanning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Utilize tools such as Amazon Inspector or Grype to scan the AMI for vulnerabilities. Address any critical findings promptly to mitigate potential security risks.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA; &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding Drift and Its Causes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AMI drift occurs when a running instance diverges from its original AMI configuration. This can result from ad-hoc administrator modifications, automated patching, configuration management tools like Puppet or Chef, and changes by application users. These deviations emphasize the need for ongoing monitoring and management of AMI configurations in cloud environments to maintain system consistency and security.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;5:1-5:373&#34;&gt;黄金亚马逊系统映像 (AMI) 是在 AWS 云环境中启动一致且高效的实例的基础。确保它们的安全性和不变性至关重要。本指南深入探讨了软件物料清单 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/software-supply-chain-security-checklist&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SBOM&lt;/ a&gt;)、加密签名和运行时验证创建了一个用于构建和维护安全黄金 AMI 的强大框架。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;构建黄金 AMI 涉及的步骤&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34; style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;table class=&#34;fr-alternate-rows fr-dashed-borders&#34; style=&#34;max-width: 100%; width: auto; table-layout:fixed; display: table;&#34;宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;标题&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;步数&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th class=&#34;fr-highlighted&#34; style=&#34;overflow-wrap:break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;描述&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/标题&gt;&#xA;  &lt;正文&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;从可信的基础镜像开始&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;首先选择一个最小的、信誉良好的基础映像，例如定期使用最新安全补丁进行更新的 AWS 提供的基础 AMI。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;添加必要的包&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;使用 yum、apt 或 pip 等包管理器安装所需的包。确保包来自受信任的存储库并指定版本号以保持一致性。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;配置用户和权限&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;创建用户帐户时遵循最小权限原则，删除不必要的默认用户和组。配置 SSH 以进行基于密钥的身份验证并限制 root 访问。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;功能测试&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;验证已安装软件和应用程序的功能，包括网络连接和基本系统服务，以确保一切按预期工作。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;漏洞扫描&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;利用 Amazon Inspector 或 Grype 等工具扫描 AMI 是否存在漏洞。及时解决任何关键问题，以减轻潜在的安全风险。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA; &lt;/表&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解漂移及其原因&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当正在运行的实例偏离其原始 AMI 配置时，就会发生 AMI 漂移。这可能是由临时管理员修改、自动修补、Puppet 或 Chef 等配置管理工具以及应用程序用户的更改造成的。这些偏差强调需要在云环境中持续监控和管理 AMI 配置，以保持系统的一致性和安全性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>