<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Industrial IoT: Exploring Microcontrollers for Robust Applications】工业物联网：探索稳健应用的微控制器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/industrial-iot-exploring-microcontrollers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When we think of the Internet of Things (IoT), our imaginations are often limited to consumer applications: smart homes, smart transportation, smart offices, etc. However, these account for just the tip of the iceberg when it comes to IoT. Just beneath the surface lies a sprawling world of industrial IoT and industrial microcontrollers (MCUs).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But just like an industrial solvent requires a formula special and distinct from your ordinary kitchen hand soap, the technical components of industrial IoT devices are starkly different from those that make your smart home HVAC system run smoothly. Nowhere is this distinction more sharp than when it comes to MCUs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当我们想到物联网 (IoT) 时，我们的想象力往往仅限于消费类应用：智能家居、智能交通、智能办公室等。然而，这些只是物联网的冰山一角。物联网。就在表面之下，是一个庞大的工业物联网和工业微控制器 (MCU) 世界。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，就像工业溶剂需要特殊且不同于普通厨房洗手液的配方一样，工业物联网设备的技术组件与使智能家居 HVAC 系统平稳运行的技术组件截然不同。这种区别在 MCU 方面最为明显。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Criticality in Data Stream Processing and a Few Effective Approaches】数据流处理的关键性和一些有效的方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/criticality-and-approaches-data-stream-processing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the current fast-paced digital age, many data sources generate an unending flow of information: a never-ending torrent of facts and figures that, while perplexing when examined separately, provide profound insights when examined together. Stream processing can be useful in this situation. It fills the void between real-time data collecting and actionable insights. It&#39;s a data processing practice that handles continuous data streams from an array of sources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;About Stream Processing&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Opposite to traditional batch data processing techniques, here, processing works on the data as it is produced in real time. In simple words, we can say processing data to get actionable insights when it is in motion before stationary on the repository. Data streaming processing is a continuous method of ingestion, processing, and, eventually, analyzing the data as it is generated from various sources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当前快节奏的数字时代，许多数据源都会产生源源不断的信息流：永无休止的事实和数据洪流，虽然单独检查时令人困惑，但放在一起检查时却提供了深刻的见解。流处理在这种情况下很有用。它填补了实时数据收集和可操作的见解之间的空白。这是一种数据处理实践，处理来自一系列源的连续数据流。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;关于流处理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与传统的批量数据处理技术相反，这里的处理是在实时生成的数据上进行的。简而言之，我们可以说，当数据在存储库中处于静止状态之前处于运动状态时，我们可以对数据进行处理以获得可操作的见解。数据流处理是一种持续摄取、处理并最终分析从各种来源生成的数据的方法。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The C̶a̶k̶e̶ User Location Is a Lie!!!】C̶a̶k̶e̶ 用户位置是一个谎言！</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-user-location-is-a-lie</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I recently sat in on a discussion about programming based on user location. Folks that are way smarter than me covered technical limitations, legal concerns, and privacy rights. It was nuanced, to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, I thought I’d share some details.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我最近参加了关于基于用户位置的编程的讨论。比我聪明得多的人涵盖了技术限制、法律问题和隐私权。至少可以说，这是微妙的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所以，我想分享一些细节。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【3 Reasons Why VPs of Engineering Are Choosing Low-Code】工程副总裁选择低代码的 3 个原因</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/3-reasons-vps-of-engineering-are-choosing-low-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I often hear the phrases &#34;Low code is not flexible&#34; and &#34;Scaling is the major issue with low code&#34; when talking to developers who have used it to build complex use cases like food ordering apps, e-commerce apps, and tools like that. For any type of application building, it&#39;s important to understand who you are developing it for, what is the ROI, and what they are going to achieve.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/low-code-application-development&#34;&gt;Low code&lt;/a&gt; is something that can be best used when you want to build apps for internal use, rich data dashboards, CMS apps, or any app for operational needs within your organization. Developers, the primary creators, benefit hugely from pre-built UI components, ready databases, and API integrations. Important stat: &lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-11-10-gartner-says-cloud-will-be-the-centerpiece-of-new-digital-experiences&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;70% of new applications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; created by enterprises are expected to utilize low-code or no-code technologies, stats Gartner findings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在与使用它构建复杂用例（例如食品订购应用程序、电子商务应用程序和应用程序）的开发人员交谈时，我经常听到“低代码不灵活”和“扩展是低代码的主要问题”这样的说法。之类的工具。对于任何类型的应用程序构建，重要的是要了解您正在为谁开发它、投资回报率是多少以及他们将实现什么目标。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/low-code-application-development&#34;&gt;低代码&lt;/a&gt;是当您想要构建供内部使用的应用程序时最好使用的东西，丰富的数据仪表板、CMS 应用程序或满足组织内运营需求的任何应用程序。开发人员（主要创建者）可以从预构建的 UI 组件、现成的数据库和 API 集成中获益匪浅。重要统计数据：&lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-11-10-gartner-says-cloud- will-be-the-centerpiece-of-new-digital-experiences&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;70% 的企业创建的新应用&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;预计将Gartner 调查结果显示，利用低代码或无代码技术。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Navigating BNPL Integration: Key Steps and Best Practices for Developers】BNPL 集成导航：开发人员的关键步骤和最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/bnpl-integration-key-steps-and-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-buy-now-pay-later-payment-solution&#34;&gt;Buy Now, Pay Later (BNPL) solutions&lt;/a&gt; are altering the way in which clients connect to payment systems by offering financial flexibility and enhancing the checkout experience. This guide offers developers and architects comprehensive knowledge on integrating your checkout process with BNPL as well as technical details, best practices, and common challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Importance of BNPL for Developers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Enhanced Conversion Rates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The abandonment of carts is reduced by the use of BNPL solutions that provide flexible payment options; hence, making it possible for users to complete their transactions. Users will not easily abandon their carts due to high upfront costs whenever payments can be broken down into small manageable amounts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-buy-now-pay-later- payment-solution&#34;&gt;先买后付 (BNPL) 解决方案&lt;/a&gt;正在改变通过提供财务灵活性和增强结账体验，客户连接支付系统的方式。本指南为开发人员和架构师提供了有关将结账流程与 BNPL 集成的全面知识，以及技术细节、最佳实践和常见挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;BNPL 对开发者的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;提高转化率&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;使用提供灵活支付选项的 BNPL 解决方案可以减少购物车的废弃情况；因此，使用户可以完成交易。只要可以将付款分解为可管理的小额金额，用户就不会因为高昂的前期成本而轻易放弃购物车。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The One-Pixel Threat: How Minuscule Changes Can Fool Deep Learning Systems】单像素威胁：微小的变化如何欺骗深度学习系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-one-pixel-threat</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI vulnerabilities: From medical diagnostics to autonomous vehicles, discover how changing a single pixel can compromise advanced deep learning models and explore the critical challenges to securing our AI-powered future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-ai-machine-learning-and-deep-learning&#34;&gt;Deep learning (DL)&lt;/a&gt; is a fundamental component of Artificial Intelligence (AI). It aims to enable machines to perform tasks that require decision-making mechanisms that tend to approximate those of human reasoning. DL models are at the heart of many advanced applications, such as medical diagnostics and autonomous vehicle driving.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能漏洞：从医疗诊断到自动驾驶汽车，了解改变单个像素如何影响先进的深度学习模型，并探索确保人工智能驱动的未来面临的关键挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-ai-machine-learning-and-deep-learning&#34;&gt;深度学习 (DL)&lt;/a&gt; 是人工智能的基本组成部分 (人工智能）。它的目的是使机器能够执行需要接近人类推理机制的决策机制的任务。深度学习模型是许多高级应用的核心，例如医疗诊断和自动驾驶汽车。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software Testing Errors To Look Out For (With Examples)】需要注意的软件测试错误（附示例）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-testing-errors-to-look-out-for-with-examp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Software will never be &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/along-came-a-bug&#34;&gt;bug&lt;/a&gt;-free. However, it’s important to minimize the number of bugs such that the impact on the functionality and user experience of an application is minimized. Bugs could come up due to different reasons. In this article, we will discuss them from the perspective of software errors. These are the errors that also need attention during the testing phase.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can divide the errors during software development into two sections for easy understanding:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;软件永远不会&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/along-came-a-bug&#34;&gt;没有错误&lt;/a&gt;。然而，重要的是要尽量减少错误的数量，以便最大限度地减少对应用程序功能和用户体验的影响。由于不同的原因，可能会出现错误。在这篇文章中，我们将从软件错误的角度来讨论它们。这些都是测试阶段也需要注意的错误。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了便于理解，我们可以将软件开发过程中的错误分为两部分：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【My Journey to Master SQL Data Analysis】我的 SQL 数据分析之旅</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/my-journey-to-master-sql-data-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Dealing with sales data can feel like a task especially when you&#39;re trying to extract insights for important business decisions. In this article, we&#39;ll delve into the experience of a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-data-analytics-understanding-data-analytic&#34;&gt;data analyst&lt;/a&gt; tackling these challenges and delve into why &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sql-commands-a-brief-guide&#34;&gt;mastering SQL&lt;/a&gt; is key to achieving success. By the end, you&#39;ll grasp the role that data analysts play and how they can transform data into actionable information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the Role of a Data Analyst&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data analysts often go unnoticed in organizations. They play a role. Their job involves sorting through volumes of data to identify patterns, trends, and insights that drive decision-making processes. Whether it&#39;s analyzing sales figures, customer feedback, or market research findings, data analysts are responsible for making sense of this information. However, this isn&#39;t a task. This demands a specific skill set that includes a solid grasp of SQL (Structured Query Language).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;处理销售数据感觉像是一项任务，尤其是当您尝试提取重要业务决策的见解时。在本文中，我们将深入探讨&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-data-analytics-understanding-data-analytic&#34;&gt;数据分析师&lt;/a&gt;处理问题的经验这些挑战并深入探讨为什么&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sql-commands-a-brief-guide&#34;&gt;掌握 SQL&lt;/a&gt; 是取得成功的关键。最后，您将了解数据分析师所扮演的角色以及他们如何将数据转换为可操作的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解数据分析师的角色&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据分析师在组织中经常被忽视。他们发挥作用。他们的工作包括对大量数据进行排序，以识别驱动决策过程的模式、趋势和见解。无论是分析销售数据、客户反馈还是市场研究结果，数据分析师都有责任理解这些信息。然而，这不是一个任务。这需要一套特定的技能，其中包括对 SQL（结构化查询语言）的扎实掌握。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging Open-Source Contributions To Boost Your Freelancing Profile】利用开源贡献来提升您的自由职业者形象</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/leveraging-open-source-contributions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Building your reputation as a freelance developer means diligently &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-boost-your-software-engineer-carrier-code-a&#34;&gt;improving your skills&lt;/a&gt; and reputation through real-world efforts. One of the best ways to do that is to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-developers-should-contribute-to-open-source&#34;&gt;contribute to open-source projects&lt;/a&gt;. How can you maximize that strategy for the best results?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Align Projects With Skills and Professional Goals&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Developer communities and the internet at large are full of open-source projects that need developers’ expertise. Narrow the abundant possibilities by focusing on those that match your skills and career goals. Then, you will stay more motivated because the work gets you closer to long-term aspirations while increasing your marketability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;建立自由开发者的声誉意味着勤奋&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-boost-your-software-engineer-carrier-code-a&#34; &gt;通过现实世界的努力提高您的技能&lt;/a&gt;和声誉。最好的方法之一是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-developers-should-contribute-to-open-source&#34;&gt;为开源项目做出贡献&lt;/a&gt; 。如何最大化该策略以获得最佳结果？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;使项目与技能和职业目标保持一致&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;开发者社区和整个互联网充满了需要开发者专业知识的开源项目。通过专注于那些与您的技能和职业目标相匹配的可能性来缩小丰富的可能性。然后，您将保持更有动力，因为这项工作让您更接近长期愿望，同时提高您的市场竞争力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Compound Interest in Software】软件复利</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/compound-interest-in-software</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Many articles and posts online show how regular, small, incremental changes result in much larger gains over time. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/consistency-101365-compounding-effect-unleashing-power-scott-jeffers-ueeoe/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;This article&lt;/a&gt; applies &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/c/compoundinterest.asp&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;compound interest&lt;/a&gt; calculations to show that a 1% daily increase provides a 37.8-times improvement/growth/whatever over the year &lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt; the power of compound interest! Frustrating at first, but the gains grew each day &lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; in the end very pleasing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Software engineers make decisions daily about the design and implementation of the solution being worked on: functionality, code structure, data validation, flow, error handling, security, performance, reliability, external dependencies, configurability, and more. Expected functionality and time-to-market often prioritize what is included and what is deferred/ignored: certain failures/errors are accepted, edge cases require manual implementation, etc. It&#39;s feature/implementation/tech debt that likely needs future remediation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;许多在线文章和帖子都表明，随着时间的推移，定期的、小的、渐进的变化如何带来更大的收益。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/consistency-101365-compounding-effect-unleashing-power-scott-jeffers-ueeoe/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;本文&lt;/a&gt; 应用&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/c/compoundinterest.asp&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;复利&lt;/a&gt;计算来表明每天 1% 的增长可提供 37.8 倍的改善/增长/全年&lt;strong&gt;-&lt;/strong&gt;复利的力量！一开始令人沮丧，但收益每天都在增长&lt;strong&gt;-&lt;/strong&gt;，最终非常令人高兴。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;软件工程师每天就正在开发的解决方案的设计和实现做出决策：功能、代码结构、数据验证、流程、错误处理、安全性、性能、可靠性、外部依赖性、可配置性等等。预期的功能和上市时间通常会优先考虑包含的内容和推迟/忽略的内容：接受某些失败/错误，边缘情况需要手动实现等。功能/实现/技术债务可能需要未来的补救。&lt;/ p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>