<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring the Evolution of Transformers: From Basic To Advanced Architectures】探索 Transformer 的演变：从基础架构到高级架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-the-evolution-of-transformers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In their seminal 2017 paper, &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1706.03762&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Attention Is All You Need&lt;/a&gt;,&#34; Vaswani et al. introduced the Transformer architecture, revolutionizing not only speech recognition technology but many other fields as well. This blog post explores the evolution of Transformers, tracing their development from the original design to the most advanced models, and highlighting significant advancements made along the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Original Transformer&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The original Transformer model introduced several groundbreaking concepts:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在他们 2017 年的开创性论文中，“&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1706.03762&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;注意力就是你所需要的&lt; /a&gt;”，Vaswani 等人。推出了 Transformer 架构，不仅彻底改变了语音识别技术，还彻底改变了许多其他领域。这篇博文探讨了变形金刚的演变，追溯了它们从最初的设计到最先进模型的发展，并强调了这一过程中取得的重大进步。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;原始变压器&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最初的 Transformer 模型引入了几个突破性的概念：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Meet Bun.js and Vite, Two Web-Development Turbochargers】认识一下 Bun.js 和 Vite，这两个 Web 开发涡轮增压器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/meet-bunjs-and-vite-two-web-development-turbocharg</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-message-author-role=&#34;assistant&#34; data-message-id=&#34;820364ce-e572-4b19-89ae-17572f9203d6&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;What about boosting your bicycle with a jet engine? That&#39;s the kind of speed &lt;a href=&#34;https://bun.sh/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bun.js&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://vitejs.dev/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Vite&lt;/a&gt; bring to web development. Let&#39;s dive into these two tools and see what they offer. Two experienced developers of Valletta, Alexander, and Oleg, helped me with this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2&gt;Bun.js: The Speed Boost for JavaScript&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;Remember when we thought Node.js was fast? Well, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-first-look-at-bun-will-it-take-nodes-crown&#34;&gt;Bun.js&lt;/a&gt; makes it look slow in comparison.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-message-author-role=&#34;助理&#34; data-message-id=&#34;820364ce-e572-4b19-89ae-17572f9203d6&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;用喷气发动机来增强你的自行车怎么样？这就是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://bun.sh/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bun.js&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://vitejs. dev/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Vite&lt;/a&gt; 带来 Web 开发。让我们深入研究这两个工具，看看它们提供什么。瓦莱塔的两位经验丰富的开发人员 Alexander 和 Oleg 为我提供了帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2&gt;Bun.js：JavaScript 的速度提升&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;还记得我们认为 Node.js 很快吗？好吧， &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-first-look-at-bun-will-it-take-nodes-crown&#34;&gt;Bun.js&lt;/a&gt; 让它看起来很慢比较。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Implement a Gateway With Spring Cloud】如何使用 Spring Cloud 实现网关</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-implement-a-gateway-with-spring-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A microservice system could have a high number of components with complex interactions. It is important to reduce this complexity, at least from the standpoint of the clients interacting with the system. A gateway hides the microservices from the external world. It represents a unique entrance and implements common cross requirements. In this article, you will learn how to configure a gateway component for a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-framework-tutorials&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt; application, using the Spring Cloud Gateway package.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Spring Cloud Gateway&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-brief-overview-of-the-spring-cloud-framework&#34;&gt;Spring Cloud&lt;/a&gt; provides a gateway implementation by the Spring Cloud Gateway project. It is based on Spring Boot, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/embracing-reactive-programming-with-spring-webflux&#34;&gt;Spring WebFlux&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reactive-programming-with-project-reactor&#34;&gt;Reactor&lt;/a&gt;. Since it is based on Spring WebFlux, it must run on a Netty environment, not a usual servlet container.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;微服务系统可能具有大量具有复杂交互的组件。至少从客户端与系统交互的角度来看，降低这种复杂性非常重要。网关向外部世界隐藏微服务。它代表了一个独特的入口并实现了共同的交叉要求。在本文中，您将了解如何使用 Spring 为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-framework-tutorials&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt; 应用程序配置网关组件云网关包。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Spring 云网关&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-brief-overview-of-the-spring-cloud-framework&#34;&gt;Spring Cloud&lt;/a&gt;通过Spring Cloud Gateway提供了网关实现项目。它基于 Spring Boot、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/embracing-reactive-programming-with-spring-webflux&#34;&gt;Spring WebFlux&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https: //dzone.com/articles/reactive-programming-with-project-reactor&#34;&gt;反应堆&lt;/a&gt;。由于它是基于Spring WebFlux，所以它必须运行在Netty环境上，而不是通常的servlet容器上。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Practitioner’s Guide to Deep Learning】深度学习从业者指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/practitioners-guide-to-deep-learning-projects</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Our world is undergoing an AI revolution powered by very deep &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/basic-convolutional-neural-network-architectures&#34;&gt;neural networks&lt;/a&gt;. With the advent of Apple Intelligence and Gemini, AI has reached the hands of every human being with a mobile phone. Apart from consumer AI, we also have deep learning models being used in several industries like automobile, finance, medical science, manufacturing, etc. This has motivated many engineers to learn deep learning techniques and apply them to solve complex problems in their projects. In order to help these engineers, it becomes imperative to lay down certain guiding principles to prevent common pitfalls when building these &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/black-box-tester-in-python&#34;&gt;black box&lt;/a&gt; models.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Any &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-ai-machine-learning-and-deep-learning&#34;&gt;deep learning&lt;/a&gt; project involves five basic elements: data, model architecture, loss functions, optimizer, and evaluation process. It is critical to design and configure each of these appropriately to ensure proper convergence of models. This article shall cover some of the recommended practices and common problems and their solutions associated with each of these elements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我们的世界正在经历一场由深度神经网络推动的人工智能革命&lt;/a &gt;。随着Apple Intelligence和Gemini的出现，人工智能已经通过手机到达了每个人的手中。除了消费者人工智能之外，我们还有深度学习模型应用于汽车、金融、医疗、制造等多个行业。这促使许多工程师学习深度学习技术，并将其应用于解决项目中的复杂问题。为了帮助这些工程师，必须制定某些指导原则，以防止在构建这些&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/black-box-tester-in-python&#34;&gt;黑色盒模型。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;任何&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-ai-machine-learning-and-deep-learning&#34;&gt;深度学习&lt;/a&gt;项目都涉及五个基本要素：数据、模型架构、损失函数、优化器和评估过程。适当地设计和配置其中每一个以确保模型的正确收敛至关重要。本文将涵盖一些推荐的实践和常见问题及其与每个元素相关的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【5 Innovative Cybersecurity Measures App Developers Should Incorporate in the Digital Transformation Race】应用程序开发人员应纳入数字化转型竞赛的 5 项创新网络安全措施</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/5-innovative-cybersecurity-measures</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Digital transformation initiatives are ongoing processes for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-influence-of-vpn-on-software-development&#34;&gt;software developers&lt;/a&gt; in particular, and organizations at large must constantly adapt while enabling seamless workplace-cultural shifts and enhancing relevance to global users. With the increasing sophistication of cyber threats and the growing reliance on digital technologies, it has become crucial for app developers to incorporate innovative cybersecurity measures to enhance digital transformation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.walkme.com/blog/digital-transformation/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Digital transformation&lt;/a&gt; entails integrating technology, such as apps and tools, to create new business processes; it can involve changing existing systems or building relatively new ones. To harness the expected outcome of digital transformation, organizations must change their operational mode by moving traditional tasks to digital formats.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;数字化转型计划是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-influence-of-vpn-on-software-development&#34;&gt;软件开发人员持续进行的过程&lt;/a &gt; 尤其是，整个组织必须不断适应，同时实现无缝的工作场所文化转变并增强与全球用户的相关性。随着网络威胁的日益复杂以及对数字技术的日益依赖，应用程序开发人员采用创新的网络安全措施来加强数字化转型变得至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.walkme.com/blog/digital-transformation/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;数字化转型&lt;/a&gt;需要整合用于创建新业务流程的技术，例如应用程序和工具；它可能涉及改变现有系统或构建相对较新的系统。为了实现数字化转型的预期成果，组织必须通过将传统任务转变为数字格式来改变其运营模式。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Secure Your Angular Apps: End-To-End Encryption of API Calls】如何保护您的 Angular 应用程序：API 调用的端到端加密</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-angular-apps-end-to-end-encryption-api-calls</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-id=&#34;6b3b72d5-21ec-4f01-9455-c674114616f5&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;When it comes to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/secure-coding-practices-for-web-applications&#34;&gt;secure web applications&lt;/a&gt;, we must keep sensitive data secure during the communication period. Sadly, while HTTPS encrypts data as it moves from point A to point B, the information is still exposed in a browser&#39;s network tab and can leak out this way. In this post, I will give you an example of implementing end-to-end encryption of API calls in your secure web app built with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/angularjs-essentials&#34;&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-id=&#34;84dbd79a-ced0-45f3-b57a-ec3e1cda8b05&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Encryption Workflow&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;84dbd79a-ced0-45f3-b57a-ec3e1cda8b05&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Weak protections have traditionally been obfuscation with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/base-32-and-base-64-encoding&#34;&gt;Base64 encoding&lt;/a&gt; or custom schemes. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/encryption-part-2-public-key-private-key-encryptio&#34;&gt;Public key cryptography&lt;/a&gt; (PKC) is considered a modern solution to be more secure. It uses a key pair one public key for encryption, and the other private key for decryption. A public key is distributed and a private key is kept on the server.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-id=&#34;6b3b72d5-21ec-4f01-9455-c674114616f5&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;当涉及&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/secure -coding-practices-for-web-applications&#34;&gt;安全Web应用&lt;/a&gt;，我们必须保证通信期间敏感数据的安全。遗憾的是，虽然 HTTPS 在数据从 A 点移动到 B 点时对数据进行加密，但信息仍然暴露在浏览器的网络选项卡中，并且可能会以这种方式泄漏。在这篇文章中，我将向您提供一个在使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/angularjs-essentials&#34;&gt;Angular&lt; 构建的安全 Web 应用程序中实现 API 调用端到端加密的示例/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-id=&#34;84dbd79a-ced0-45f3-b57a-ec3e1cda8b05&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;加密工作流程&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;84dbd79a-ced0-45f3-b57a-ec3e1cda8b05&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;传统上，弱保护是通过 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ 进行混淆的articles/base-32-and-base-64-encoding&#34;&gt;Base64 编码&lt;/a&gt; 或自定义方案。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/encryption-part-2-public-key-private-key-encryptio&#34;&gt;公钥加密&lt;/a&gt; (PKC) 被认为是一种更现代的解决方案安全的。它使用密钥对，一个公钥用于加密，另一个私钥用于解密。公钥被分发，私钥保存在服务器上。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introduction to Polymorphism With Database Engines in NoSQL Using Jakarta NoSQL】使用 Jakarta NoSQL 介绍 NoSQL 中数据库引擎的多态性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/intro-to-polymorphism-with-db-engines-in-nosql</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/learning-java-what-vs-why&#34;&gt;Polymorphism&lt;/a&gt;, a fundamental concept in object-oriented programming, allows objects of different types to be treated as instances of a common superclass. This flexibility is essential for creating systems that can be easily extended and maintained. While traditional SQL databases in combination with Jakarta Persistence (JPA) can handle polymorphic data, NoSQL databases offer distinct advantages. Unlike SQL databases, which require strict schema definitions, NoSQL databases take a schema-less approach, inherently supporting dynamic and flexible data structures. This flexibility becomes especially appealing when integrated with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/jakarta-nosql-100-b5-how-to-make-your-life-easier&#34;&gt;Jakarta NoSQL&lt;/a&gt;, a tool that provides robust support for defining and managing polymorphic fields through custom converters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In many enterprise applications, there is a common need to manage different types of data objects. For example, an e-commerce platform may handle various payment methods such as credit cards, digital wallets, and bank transfers, each with specific attributes. Similarly, asset management systems in large corporations deal with different types of assets like real estate, machinery, and intellectual property, each with unique properties. Healthcare systems must accommodate various data types, from personal information to medical records and test results. Utilizing NoSQL databases with polymorphic fields can store and manage these diverse data types cohesively. The schema-less nature of NoSQL databases also makes it easier to adapt to changing requirements than relational databases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/learning-java-what-vs-why&#34;&gt;多态性&lt;/a&gt;是面向对象编程中的一个基本概念，它允许不同类型的对象被视为公共超类的实例。这种灵活性对于创建易于扩展和维护的系统至关重要。虽然传统 SQL 数据库与 Jakarta Persistence (JPA) 相结合可以处理多态数据，但 NoSQL 数据库具有明显的优势。与需要严格模式定义的 SQL 数据库不同，NoSQL 数据库采用无模式方法，本质上支持动态且灵活的数据结构。当与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/jakarta-nosql-100-b5-how-to-make-your-life-easier&#34;&gt;Jakarta NoSQL&lt;/a&gt; 集成时，这种灵活性变得特别有吸引力，一个为通过自定义转换器定义和管理多态字段提供强大支持的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在许多企业应用程序中，普遍需要管理不同类型的数据对象。例如，电子商务平台可以处理各种支付方式，例如信用卡、数字钱包和银行转账，每种方式都有特定的属性。同样，大公司的资产管理系统处理不同类型的资产，如房地产、机械和知识产权，每种资产都有独特的属性。医疗保健系统必须容纳各种数据类型，从个人信息到医疗记录和测试结果。利用具有多态字段的 NoSQL 数据库可以统一存储和管理这些不同的数据类型。 NoSQL 数据库的无模式特性也使其比关系数据库更容易适应不断变化的需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Roots of Test Smells】测试气味的根源</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/roots-of-test-smells</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Test smells are signs that something has gone bad in your code. Plenty of &lt;a href=&#34;http://xunitpatterns.com/TestSmells.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;great stuff&lt;/a&gt; has been written about them, and we at our team have contributed practical examples of how to spot smelly test code &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-smells-cleaning-up-unit-tests&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-smells-cleaning-up-e2e-tests&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While test smells may arise for a bunch of different reasons, there is one recurring theme that we&#39;d like to cover today, and it has to do with team structure. The point we&#39;d like to make is that a good automated test is an overlap of several different domain areas:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;测试气味是代码中出现问题的迹象。已经有很多关于它们的&lt;a href=&#34;http://xunitpatterns.com/TestSmells.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;精彩内容&lt;/a&gt;，我们团队也做出了贡献如何发现有异味的测试代码的实际示例&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-smells-cleaning-up-unit-tests&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;此处&lt; /a&gt; 和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-smells-cleaning-up-e2e-tests&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然测试异味可能因多种不同原因而出现，但我们今天想讨论一个反复出现的主题，它与团队结构有关。我们想要指出的一点是，一个好的自动化测试是几个不同领域的重叠：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Time Streaming Architectures: A Technical Deep Dive Into Kafka, Flink, and Pinot】实时流架构：从技术角度深入探讨 Kafka、Flink 和 Pinot</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-streaming-architectures-kafka-flink-pinot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-database-systems-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Database Systems: Modernization for Data-Driven Architectures&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Real-time streaming architectures are designed to ingest, process, and analyze data as it arrives continuously, enabling near real-time decision making and insights. They need to have low latency, handle high-throughput data volumes, and be fault tolerant in the event of failures. Some of the challenges in this area include:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-database-systems-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;数据库系统：数据驱动架构的现代化&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。 p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;实时流架构旨在摄取、处理和分析持续到达的数据，从而实现近乎实时的决策和洞察。它们需要具有低延迟、处理高吞吐量数据量，并且在发生故障时具有容错能力。该领域的一些挑战包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 12:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DB2 vs. Oracle for IBM Maximo: A Comparative Analysis】DB2 与 Oracle for IBM Maximo：比较分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/db2-vs-oracle-for-ibm-maximo-a-comparative</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-change-status-of-work-orders-in-maximo-usin&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-change-status-of-work-orders-in-maximo-usin&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-change-status-of-work-orders-in-maximo-usin&#34;&gt;IBM Maximo&lt;/a&gt;, an enterprise asset management solution, supports various database platforms, among which IBM DB2 and Oracle are prominent choices. Each database system has its strengths and capabilities, influencing system performance, scalability, and maintenance. This essay explores the differences between &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/db2-dte-pocdb2dmc&#34;&gt;DB2&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/oracle-sql-understanding-execution-plans&#34;&gt;Oracle&lt;/a&gt; in the context of their integration with IBM Maximo, focusing on aspects such as performance, scalability, ease of management, cost, and specific features that benefit Maximo environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Database Performance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DB2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DB2 is known for its high performance in data handling and retrieval efficiency, particularly in environments that are heavily integrated with other IBM software solutions. DB2 uses self-tuning memory allocation which adjusts the database buffer size dynamically based on the workload, thereby optimizing performance without manual intervention.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-change-status-of-work-orders-in-maximo-usin&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-change-status-of-work-orders-in-maximo-usin&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone .com/articles/how-to-change-status-of-work-orders-in-maximo-usin&#34;&gt;IBM Maximo&lt;/a&gt;，企业资产管理解决方案，支持各种数据库平台，其中包括 IBM DB2 和 Oracle都是突出的选择。每个数据库系统都有其优势和功能，影响系统性能、可扩展性和维护。本文探讨了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/db2-dte-pocdb2dmc&#34;&gt;DB2&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/oracle -sql-understanding-execution-plans&#34;&gt;Oracle&lt;/a&gt; 在与 IBM Maximo 集成的背景下，重点关注性能、可扩展性、易于管理、成本和有利于 Maximo 环境的特定功能等方面。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据库性能&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DB2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DB2 以其在数据处理和检索效率方面的高性能而闻名，特别是在与其他 IBM 软件解决方案高度集成的环境中。 DB2 使用自调整内存分配，根据工作负载动态调整数据库缓冲区大小，从而在无需人工干预的情况下优化性能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>