<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【From Zero to Local AI in 10 Minutes With Ollama + Python】使用 Ollama + Python 在 10 分钟内从零到本地 AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-local-ai-ollama-python</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Why Ollama (And Why Now)?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want production‑like experiments without cloud keys or per‑call fees, Ollama gives you a local‑first developer path:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zero friction&lt;/strong&gt;: Install once; pull models on demand; everything runs on &lt;code&gt;localhost&lt;/code&gt; by default.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One API, two runtimes&lt;/strong&gt;: The same API works for local and (optional) cloud models, so you can start on your laptop and scale later with minimal code changes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Batteries included&lt;/strong&gt;: Simple CLI (&lt;code&gt;ollama run&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;ollama pull&lt;/code&gt;), a clean REST API, an official Python client, embeddings, and vision support.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Repeatability&lt;/strong&gt;: A &lt;code&gt;Modelfile&lt;/code&gt; (think: Dockerfile for models) captures system prompts and parameters so teams get the same behaviour.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What’s New in Late 2025 (at a Glance)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud models (preview)&lt;/strong&gt;: Run larger models on managed GPUs with the same API surface; develop locally, scale in the cloud without code changes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenAI‑compatible endpoints&lt;/strong&gt;: Point OpenAI SDKs at Ollama (&lt;code&gt;/v1&lt;/code&gt;) for easy migration and local testing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows desktop app&lt;/strong&gt;: Official GUI for Windows users; drag‑and‑drop, multimodal inputs, and background service management.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safety/quality updates&lt;/strong&gt;: Recent safety‑classification models and runtime optimizations (e.g., flash‑attention toggles in select backends) to improve performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;How Ollama Works (Architecture in 90 Seconds)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Runtime&lt;/strong&gt;: A lightweight server listens on &lt;code&gt;localhost:11434&lt;/code&gt; and exposes REST endpoints for chat, generate, and embeddings. Responses stream token‑by‑token.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model format (GGUF)&lt;/strong&gt;: Models are packaged in quantized &lt;code&gt;.gguf&lt;/code&gt; binaries for efficient CPU/GPU inference and fast memory‑mapped loading.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inference engine&lt;/strong&gt;: Built on the &lt;code&gt;llama.cpp&lt;/code&gt; family of kernels with GPU offload via Metal (Apple Silicon), CUDA (NVIDIA), and others; choose quantization for your hardware.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configuration&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;code&gt;Modelfile&lt;/code&gt; pins base model, system prompt, parameters, adapters (LoRA), and optional templates — so your team’s runs are reproducible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Install in 60 Seconds&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;macOS / Windows / Linux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. Download and install Ollama from the official site (choose your OS).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;为什么选择 Ollama（以及为什么现在）？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您想要无需云密钥或每次调用费用的类似生产实验，Ollama 为您提供本地优先的开发者路径：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;零摩擦&lt;/strong&gt;：安装一次；按需拉取模型；默认情况下，一切都在 &lt;code&gt;localhost&lt;/code&gt; 上运行。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;一个 API，两个运行时&lt;/strong&gt;：相同的 API 适用于本地和（可选）云模型，因此您可以在笔记本电脑上开始，然后以最少的代码更改进行扩展。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;内含电池&lt;/strong&gt;：简单的 CLI（&lt;code&gt;ollama run&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;ollama pull&lt;/code&gt;）、干净的 REST API、官方 Python 客户端、嵌入和视觉支持。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可重复性&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;code&gt;模型文件&lt;/code&gt;（例如：模型的 Dockerfile）捕获系统提示和参数，以便团队获得相同的行为。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;2025 年末的新动态（概览）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云模型（预览版）&lt;/strong&gt;：在具有相同 API 界面的托管 GPU 上运行更大的模型；本地开发，在云中扩展，无需更改代码。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenAI 兼容端点&lt;/strong&gt;：将 OpenAI SDK 指向 Ollama (&lt;code&gt;/v1&lt;/code&gt;)，以便轻松迁移和本地测试。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows 桌面应用&lt;/strong&gt;：适用于 Windows 用户的官方 GUI；拖放、多模式输入和后台服务管理。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安全/质量更新&lt;/strong&gt;：最近的安全分类模型和运行时优化（例如，选定后端中的 flash-attention 切换）以提高性能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Ollama 的工作原理（90 秒构建架构）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;运行时&lt;/strong&gt;：轻量级服务器侦听 &lt;code&gt;localhost:11434&lt;/code&gt; 并公开用于聊天、生成和嵌入的 REST 端点。响应逐个令牌流式传输。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;模型格式 (GGUF)&lt;/strong&gt;：模型打包在量化的 &lt;code&gt;.gguf&lt;/code&gt; 二进制文件中，以实现高效的 CPU/GPU 推理和快速内存映射加载。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;推理引擎&lt;/strong&gt;：基于 &lt;code&gt;llama.cpp&lt;/code&gt; 系列内核构建，通过 Metal (Apple Silicon)、CUDA (NVIDIA) 等实现 GPU 卸载；为您的硬件选择量化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;配置&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;code&gt;模型文件&lt;/code&gt;固定基本模型、系统提示、参数、适配器 (LoRA) 和可选模板 - 因此您团队的运行是可重复的。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;60 秒内安装&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;macOS / Windows / Linux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.从官方网站下载并安装 Ollama（选择您的操作系统）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 20:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Create a Responsive Filter Component on React Guide】如何在 React 指南上创建响应式过滤器组件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/react-responsive-filter-component</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In web development, responsive and user-friendly components have never been more important. One of these is a filter component that enables web users to quickly filter the user interface (UI) and data elements and display only relevant fields. The challenge is creating a filter component that can fit any screen size.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article will demonstrate how to implement a responsive filter component using &lt;a href=&#34;https://react.dev/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;React&lt;/a&gt;. The tutorial explains how developers can build flexible filters into their web applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在 Web 开发中，响应式和用户友好的组件从未如此重要。其中之一是过滤器组件，它使 Web 用户能够快速过滤用户界面 (UI) 和数据元素并仅显示相关字段。挑战在于创建一个适合任何屏幕尺寸的过滤器组件。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文将演示如何使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://react.dev/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;React&lt;/a&gt; 实现响应式过滤器组件。本教程介绍了开发人员如何在其 Web 应用程序中构建灵活的过滤器。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Gateway Analytics: My Journey to Making API Traffic Data Useful】构建网关分析：我的 API 流量数据有用之旅</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gateway-analytics-api-traffic</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;APIs are everywhere today. Whether it&#39;s buying something online, logging into a mobile app, or streaming a movie, an API is always working behind the scenes. Over the last decade, APIs have become the backbone of modern software systems. As an application scales, the volume of API calls increases rapidly, and managing them becomes more complex. This is where API gateways come into action.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An API gateway acts as an entry point for all internal or external API traffic. It sits in front of the backend services and handles responsibilities such as authentications, routing, rate limiting, logging, performance monitoring, and more.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如今，API 无处不在。无论是在线购买商品、登录移动应用程序还是流式传输电影，API 始终在幕后工作。在过去的十年中，API 已成为现代软件系统的支柱。随着应用程序的扩展，API 调用量迅速增加，管理它们变得更加复杂。这就是 API 网关发挥作用的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;API 网关充当所有内部或外部 API 流量的入口点。它位于后端服务前面，负责处理身份验证、路由、速率限制、日志记录、性能监控等职责。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Embedding Ethics Into Multi-AI Agentic Self-Healing Data Pipelines】将道德规范嵌入到多人工智能代理自我修复数据管道中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ethical-ai-agentic-self-healing-data-pipelines</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The race to design a fully autonomous system is fostering innovations in the development of modern data systems. Developers are striving to create data ecosystems that are self-correcting and have minimal downtime so as to manage data movement effectively within their organizations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to such a drive for automation, the use of self-healing data pipelines has increased rapidly. &amp;nbsp;A conventional data pipeline consists of data processing elements connected in a relevant manner to move data between two different data systems. For example, extracting data from IoT devices, such as temperature sensors, and loading it into an analytical database for monitoring forms a simple ELT data pipeline. Such traditional pipelines are prone to limitations, including downtime, crashes, low scalability, and excessive monitoring overhead.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;设计完全自主系统的竞赛正在促进现代数据系统开发的创新。开发人员正在努力创建可自我纠正且停机时间最短的数据生态系统，以便有效管理组织内的数据移动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于这种自动化的推动，自我修复数据管道的使用迅速增加。  传统的数据管道由以相关方式连接的数据处理元件组成，以在两个不同的数据系统之间移动数据。例如，从温度传感器等物联网设备中提取数据，并将其加载到分析数据库中进行监控，形成一个简单的 ELT 数据管道。这种传统管道很容易受到限制，包括停机、崩溃、可扩展性低和监控开销过多。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【NVIDIA GPU Operator Explained: Simplifying GPU Workloads on Kubernetes】NVIDIA GPU Operator 解释：简化 Kubernetes 上的 GPU 工作负载</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/nvidia-gpu-operator-explained-simplifying-gpu-work</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;c961&#34;&gt;While GPUs have long been a staple in industries like gaming, video editing, CAD, and 3D rendering, their role has evolved dramatically over the years. Originally designed to handle graphics-intensive tasks, GPUs have proven to be powerful tools for a wide range of computationally demanding applications. Today, their ability to perform massive parallel processing has made them indispensable in modern fields such as data science, artificial intelligence and machine learning (AI/ML), robotics, cryptocurrency mining, and scientific computing. This shift was catalysed by the introduction of CUDA (Compute Unified Device Architecture) by NVIDIA in 2007, which unlocked the potential of GPUs for general-purpose computing. As a result, GPUs are no longer just graphics accelerators; they’re now at the heart of cutting-edge innovation across industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;c976&#34;&gt;In this blog post, we will discuss the NVIDIA GPU operator on Kubernetes and how to deploy it on the Kubernetes Cluster.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;c961&#34;&gt;虽然 GPU 长期以来一直是游戏、视频编辑、CAD 和 3D 渲染等行业的主要产品，但多年来它们的作用发生了巨大变化。 GPU 最初设计用于处理图形密集型任务，现已证明是适用于各种计算要求较高的应用程序的强大工具。如今，它们执行大规模并行处理的能力使其在数据科学、人工智能和机器学习 (AI/ML)、机器人、加密货币挖掘和科学计算等现代领域不可或缺。 NVIDIA 于 2007 年推出的 CUDA（统一计算设备架构）促进了这一转变，释放了 GPU 在通用计算方面的潜力。因此，GPU 不再仅仅是图形加速器；而是图形加速器。它们现在已成为跨行业尖端创新的核心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;c976&#34;&gt;在这篇博文中，我们将讨论 Kubernetes 上的 NVIDIA GPU Operator 以及如何将其部署在 Kubernetes 集群上。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Containerized Quarkus API on AWS ECS/Fargate With CDK】使用 CDK 在 AWS ECS/Fargate 上构建容器化 Quarkus API</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/quarkus-api-aws-ecs-fargate-cdk</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In a three-article series published recently on this site (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastructure-as-abstract-data-types&#34;&gt;Part 1&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastructure-as-abstract-data-types-pt-2&#34;&gt;Part 2&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastructure-as-abstract-data-types-3&#34;&gt;Part 3&lt;/a&gt;), I&#39;ve been demonstrating the power of the AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) in the Infrastructure as Code (IaC) area, especially when coupled with the ubiquitous Java and its supersonic/subatomic cloud-native stack: Quarkus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While focusing on the CDK fundamentals in Java, like Stack and Construct, together with their Quarkus implementations, this series was a bit frugal as far as the infrastructure elements were concerned. Indeed, for the sake of clarity and simplification, the infrastructure used to illustrate how to use the CDK with Java and Quarkus was inherently consensual. Hence, the idea for a new series, of which this article is the first, is a series less concerned with CDK internals and more dedicated to the infrastructure itself.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本网站最近发布的三篇文章系列中（&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastruct-as-abstract-data-types&#34;&gt;第 1 部分&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastruct-as-abstract-data-types-pt-2&#34;&gt;第 2 部分&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastruct-as-abstract-data-types-3&#34;&gt;第 3 部分&lt;/a&gt;)，我一直在演示 AWS 云开发套件 (CDK) 在基础设施即代码 (IaC) 领域的强大功能，尤其是与无处不在的 Java 及其超音速/亚原子云原生堆栈：Quarkus 结合使用时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然重点关注 Java 中的 CDK 基础知识（例如 Stack 和 Construct）以及它们的 Quarkus 实现，但就基础设施元素而言，本系列有点节俭。事实上，为了清楚和简单起见，用于说明如何将 CDK 与 Java 和 Quarkus 结合使用的基础设施本质上是一致同意的。因此，新系列的想法（本文是第一篇）是一个不太关心 CDK 内部结构而更致力于基础设施本身的系列。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Symptoms to Solutions: Troubleshooting Java Memory Leaks and OutOfMemoryError】从症状到解决方案：Java 内存泄漏和 OutOfMemoryError 故障排除</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/troubleshooting-java-memory-leaks-oom</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;Troubleshooting memory problems, such as&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heaphero.io/common-memory-leaks-in-java-how-to-fix-them/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;memory leaks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heaphero.io/types-of-outofmemoryerror/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OutOfMemoryError,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;can be an intimidating task even for experienced engineers.&lt;/span&gt; In this post, we would like to share simple tips, tools, and tricks so that even a novice engineer can isolate memory problems and resolve them quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Are Common Signs of a Java Memory Leak That Might Lead to OutOfMemoryError?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before your application throws an OutOfMemoryError, it usually gives you a few warning signs. If you catch them early, you can prevent downtime and customer impact. Here’s what you should keep an eye on:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;排查内存问题，例如&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heaphero.io/common-memory-leaks-in-java-how-to-fix-them/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;内存泄漏&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;和&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heaphero.io/types-of-outofmemoryerror/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OutOfMemoryError，&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;即使对于经验丰富的工程师来说也可能是一项令人生畏的任务。&lt;/span&gt;在这篇文章中，我们希望分享简单的提示、工具和技巧，以便即使是新手工程师也可以隔离内存问题并快速解决它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;可能导致 OutOfMemoryError 的 Java 内存泄漏的常见迹象是什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在您的应用程序抛出 OutOfMemoryError 之前，它通常会给您一些警告信号。如果您尽早发现它们，就可以防止停机和对客户的影响。以下是您应该注意的事项：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Aggregation Strategies for Scalable Data Insights: A Technical Perspective】可扩展数据洞察的聚合策略：技术视角</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aggregation-strategies-for-scalable-data-insights</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Elasticsearch is a cornerstone of our analytics infrastructure, and mastering its aggregation capabilities is essential for achieving optimal performance and accuracy. This blog explores our experiences comparing three essential Elasticsearch aggregation types: Sampler, Composite, and Terms. We’ll evaluate their strengths, limitations, and ideal use cases to help you make informed decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Power of Aggregation in Elasticsearch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Elasticsearch aggregations offer a powerful means of summarizing and analyzing data. They allow us to group documents into buckets based on specific criteria and then perform calculations on those buckets. This is essential for tasks like:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Elasticsearch 是我们分析基础设施的基石，掌握其聚合功能对于实现最佳性能和准确性至关重要。本博客探讨了我们比较三种基本 Elasticsearch 聚合类型的经验：采样器、组合和术语。我们将评估它们的优势、局限性和理想用例，以帮助您做出明智的决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elasticsearch 中聚合的力量&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Elasticsearch 聚合提供了一种强大的汇总和分析数据的方法。它们允许我们根据特定标准将文档分组到存储桶中，然后对这些存储桶执行计算。这对于以下任务至关重要：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Pinecone vs. Weaviate: The Trade-offs You Only Discover in Production】Pinecone 与 Weaviate：只有在生产中才能发现的权衡</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/pinecone-vs-weaviate-the-trade-offs-you-only-disco</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-line=&#34;2&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;When we built our first AI-powered semantic search system, choosing a vector database felt straightforward. &lt;strong&gt;Pinecone&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Weaviate&lt;/strong&gt; both looked great on paper — fast, scalable, and built for embeddings. We did what any team under time pressure would do: pick the one that promised the least friction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line=&#34;4&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;It worked beautifully ... until it didn&#39;t. That&#39;s when we learned the hard way that the biggest differences between vector databases don&#39;t show up in feature lists or benchmarks - they appear only after you&#39;ve gone live!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-line=&#34;2&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;当我们构建第一个人工智能驱动的语义搜索系统时，选择矢量数据库感觉很简单。 &lt;strong&gt;Pinecone&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;Weaviate&lt;/strong&gt; 在纸面上看起来都很棒 - 快速、可扩展且专为嵌入而构建。我们做了任何团队在时间压力下都会做的事情：选择摩擦最小的一个。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line=&#34;4&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;它工作得很好......直到它不起作用。就在那时，我们惨痛地认识到，矢量数据库之间的最大差异不会出现在功能列表或基准测试中 - 它们只有在上线后才会出现！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond the Vibe: Why AI Coding Workflows Need a Framework】超越氛围：为什么人工智能编码工作流程需要一个框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/beyond-vibe-ai-coding-frameworks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;For decades, software development has been a story of evolving methodologies. We moved from the rigid assembly line of Waterfall to the collaborative, iterative cycles of Agile and Scrum. Each shift was driven by a need to better manage complexity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we stand at a similar inflection point. A new, powerful collaborator has joined the team: Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;几十年来，软件开发一直是一个不断发展的方法论的故事。我们从瀑布式的严格装配线转向敏捷和 Scrum 的协作、迭代循环。每次转变都是由更好地管理复杂性的需求驱动的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们正处于类似的拐点。一个新的、强大的合作者加入了团队：人工智能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>