<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Best Gantt Chart Libraries for React】React 的最佳甘特图库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/best-gantt-chart-libraries-for-react</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Gantt chart is an advanced visualization solution for project management that considerably facilitates planning, scheduling, and controlling the progress of short-, mid-, and long-term projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-gantt-chart-how-and-when-to-use-a-gantt&#34;&gt;Gantt charts&lt;/a&gt; were invented more than a hundred years ago by Henry Gantt, who made a major contribution to the development of scientific management. Decades ago, the entire procedure of implementing Gantt charts in infrastructure projects was really time-consuming. Today, we are lucky to have modern tools that greatly speed up the process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;甘特图是一种先进的项目管理可视化解决方案，可极大地方便规划、安排和控制短期、中期和长期项目的进度。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-gantt-chart-how-and-when-to-use-a-gantt&#34;&gt;甘特图&lt;/a&gt; 是一百多年前由亨利·甘特发明的，他为科学管理的发展做出了重大贡献。几十年前，在基础设施项目中实施甘特图的整个过程非常耗时。今天，我们很幸运拥有可以大大加快这一过程的现代工具。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Feature Flags in .NET 8 and Azure】.NET 8 和 Azure 中的功能标志</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/feature-flags-in-net-8-and-azure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In an industry where fast, reliable, and iterative development cycles define success, the ability to deploy software while minimizing risks is invaluable. Feature flags have become an essential part of the modern developer’s toolkit, offering a flexible approach to enabling and disabling features dynamically.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s examine how the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-the-good-and-the-bad-of-net-developm&#34;&gt;Microsoft .NET&lt;/a&gt; team, in combination with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/cloud-computing-windows-azure&#34;&gt;Azure&lt;/a&gt;, manages new feature releases efficiently without reverting (redeploying) in case of regressions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在快速、可靠和迭代开发周期决定成功的行业中，部署软件同时最大限度降低风险的能力是非常宝贵的。功能标志已成为现代开发人员工具包的重要组成部分，提供了动态启用和禁用功能的灵活方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们来看看 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-the-good-and-the-bad-of-net-developm&#34;&gt;Microsoft .NET&lt;/a&gt; 团队如何，与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/cloud-computing-windows-azure&#34;&gt;Azure&lt;/a&gt; 结合使用，可以有效管理新功能发布，而无需在出现回归时恢复（重新部署）。&lt;/ p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Talk to Your Project: An LLM Experiment You Can Join and Build On】谈论您的项目：您可以加入并继续发展的法学硕士实验</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/talk-to-your-project-llm-experiment</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today, I want to share the story of a small open-source project I created just for fun and experimentation — ConsoleGpt. The process, results, and overall experience turned out to be fascinating, so I hope you find this story interesting and, perhaps, even inspiring. After all, I taught my project how to understand spoken commands and do exactly what I want.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This story might spark new ideas for you, encourage your own experiments, or even motivate you to build a similar project. And of course, I&#39;d be thrilled if you join me in developing &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/shcherbanich/symfony-console-gpt&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ConsoleGpt&lt;/a&gt; — whether by contributing new features, running it locally, or simply starring it on GitHub. Anyone who&#39;s ever worked on an open-source project knows how much even small support means.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;今天，我想分享一个我为了乐趣和实验而创建的小型开源项目的故事 - ConsoleGpt。整个过程、结果和整体体验都很有趣，所以我希望你觉得这个故事很有趣，甚至可能鼓舞人心。毕竟，我教我的项目如何理解口头命令并准确地执行我想要的操作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;这个故事可能会激发您的新想法，鼓励您自己进行实验，甚至激励您构建类似的项目。当然，如果您和我一起开发 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/shcherbanich/symfony-console-gpt&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ConsoleGpt&lt; /a&gt; — 无论是贡献新功能、在本地运行它，还是只是在 GitHub 上加注星标。任何参与过开源项目的人都知道即使是很小的支持也意味着多大的意义。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dark Data: Recovering the Lost Opportunities】暗数据：找回失去的机会</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dark-data-recovering-lost-opportunities</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Dark data may contain secret information that is valuable for corporate operations. Companies can lead the competition by gaining insights from dark data using the relevant tools and practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s check what dark data is all about and how to use it to make smarter decisions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;暗数据可能包含对企业运营有价值的秘密信息。公司可以使用相关工具和实践从暗数据中获取洞察，从而在竞争中处于领先地位。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们来看看暗数据是什么以及如何使用它来做出更明智的决策。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Your First Chrome Extension With Rust and WebAssembly】使用 Rust 和 WebAssembly 构建您的第一个 Chrome 扩展</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-chrome-extension-rust-webassembly</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Chrome extensions have traditionally been built using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. However, with the rise of WebAssembly (Wasm), we can now leverage Rust&#39;s performance, safety, and modern development features in browser extensions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, we will create a simple Chrome extension that uses &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rust-programming-language-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;Rust&lt;/a&gt; compiled to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-webassembly&#34;&gt;WebAssembly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Chrome 扩展程序传统上是使用 JavaScript、HTML 和 CSS 构建的。然而，随着 WebAssembly (Wasm) 的兴起，我们现在可以在浏览器扩展中利用 Rust 的性能、安全性和现代开发功能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本教程中，我们将创建一个简单的 Chrome 扩展程序，该扩展程序使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rust-programming-language-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;Rust&lt;/a&gt; 编译到 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-webassemble&#34;&gt;WebAssembly&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating Artificial Doubt Significantly Improves AI Math Accuracy】制造人工疑问可显着提高人工智能数学准确性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-artificial-doubt-improves-ai-math-accuracy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;b82c&#34;&gt;What makes an AI system good at math? Not raw computational power, but something that seems almost contradictory: being neurotically careful about being right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;0e04&#34;&gt;When AI researchers talk about mathematical reasoning, they typically focus on scaling up  —  bigger models, more parameters, and larger datasets. But in practice, mathematical ability isn’t about how much compute you have for your model. It’s actually about whether machines can learn to verify their own work, because at least 90% of reasoning errors come from models confidently stating wrong intermediate steps.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;b82c&#34;&gt;是什么让人工智能系统擅长数学？不是原始的计算能力，而是看起来几乎矛盾的东西：神经质地小心翼翼地追求正确。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;0e04&#34;&gt;当人工智能研究人员谈论数学推理时，他们通常关注扩大规模  —  更大的模型、更多的参数和更大的数据集。但在实践中，数学能力并不在于你的模型有多少计算能力。这实际上是关于机器能否学会验证自己的工作，因为至少 90% 的推理错误来自于模型自信地陈述错误的中间步骤。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Leaderless Replication for Distributed Data】了解分布式数据的无领导复制</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/leaderless-replication-for-distributed-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Leaderless replication is another fundamental replication approach for distributed systems. It alleviates problems of multi-leader replication while, at the same time, it introduces its own problems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Write conflicts in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/multi-leader-replication-for-distributed-data&#34;&gt;multi-leader replication&lt;/a&gt; are tackled in leaderless replication with quorum-based writes and systematic conflict resolution (e.g., version vectors). Cascading failures, synchronization overhead, and operational complexity can be handled in leaderless replication via its decentralized architecture. Removing leaders can simplify cluster management, failure handling,g and recovery mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;无领导者复制是分布式系统的另一种基本复制方法。它缓解了多领导者复制的问题，同时也引入了自己的问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/multi-leader-replication-for-distributed-data&#34;&gt;多领导复制&lt;/a&gt;中的写入冲突在无领导复制中通过仲裁解决基于写入和系统冲突解决（例如版本向量）。级联故障、同步开销和操作复杂性可以通过其去中心化架构在无领导者复制中得到处理。删除领导者可以简化集群管理、故障处理和恢复机制。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Schema Changes Are a Blind Spot】架构更改是一个盲点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/schema-changes-blind-spot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Schema changes and migrations can quickly spiral into chaos, leading to significant challenges. Overcoming these obstacles requires effective strategies for streamlining schema migrations and adaptations, enabling seamless database changes with minimal downtime and performance impact.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Without these practices, the risk of flawed schema migrations grows — &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.blog/news-insights/company-news/github-availability-report-november-2021/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_self&#34;&gt;just as GitHub experienced&lt;/a&gt;. Discover how to avoid similar pitfalls.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;架构更改和迁移可能会迅速陷入混乱，从而带来重大挑战。克服这些障碍需要有效的策略来简化模式迁移和适应，从而以最小的停机时间和性能影响实现无缝数据库更改。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;如果没有这些实践，有缺陷的架构迁移的风险就会增加 — &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.blog/news-insights/company-news/github- availability-report-november-2021/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_self&#34;&gt;正如 GitHub 所经历的&lt;/a&gt;。了解如何避免类似的陷阱。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Business Logic Database Agent】业务逻辑数据库代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/business-logic-database-agent</link>
      <description>【&lt;main&gt;&#xA; &lt;div data-scaffold-immersive-reader=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;article&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div data-scaffold-immersive-reader-content=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&#xA;     &lt;div data-artdeco-is-focused=&#34;true&#34; tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;In a recent interview, Satya Nadella prophesied the &#34;end of SaaS&#34; with &lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uGOLYz2pgr8&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Business Logic Database Agents&lt;/a&gt;. The vision was exciting and broad but indefinite. And, it sparked concerns — serious ones.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;In this article, we describe a&amp;nbsp;definite&amp;nbsp;(in fact, running) vision for such a system and how to deal with reasonable&amp;nbsp;concerns&amp;nbsp;raised in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;主要&gt;&#xA; &lt;div data-scaffold-immersive-reader=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;文章&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div data-scaffold-immersive-reader-content=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div 目录=“ltr”&gt;&#xA;     &lt;div data-artdeco-is-focused=&#34;true&#34; tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;在最近的一次采访中，Satya Nadella 预言“SaaS 的终结”&lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uGOLYz2pgr8 &#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;业务逻辑数据库代理&lt;/a&gt;。这个愿景令人兴奋、广阔但不确定。而且，它引发了担忧——严重的担忧。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们描述了此类系统的明确（实际上是正在运行的）愿景，以及如何处理评论中提出的合理担忧。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ArangoDB: Achieving Success With a Multivalue Database】ArangoDB：利用多值数据库取得成功</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/arangodb-success-through-multivalue-database</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Handling diverse database structures often introduces significant complexity to system architecture, especially when multiple database instances are required. This fragmentation can complicate operations, increase costs, and reduce efficiency. Multimodel databases like ArangoDB provide a unified solution to address these challenges. They simplify architecture and streamline data management by supporting multiple data models — key-value, document, and graph — within a single database instance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unlike relational databases, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-nosql-database-1&#34;&gt;NoSQL databases&lt;/a&gt; do not adhere to a universal standard like SQL. Instead, they are categorized based on their storage structure. Among the popular types are:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;处理不同的数据库结构通常会给系统架构带来极大的复杂性，特别是在需要多个数据库实例时。这种碎片化会使操作变得复杂、增加成本并降低效率。 ArangoDB 等多模型数据库提供了统一的解决方案来应对这些挑战。它们通过在单个数据库实例中支持多种数据模型（键值、文档和图形）来简化架构并简化数据管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与关系数据库不同，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-nosql-database-1&#34;&gt;NoSQL 数据库&lt;/a&gt;不遵守 SQL 等通用标准。相反，它们根据存储结构进行分类。流行的类型包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>