<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing SmallRye LLM: Injecting Langchain4J AI Services】介绍Smallrye LLM：注入Langchain4J AI服务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/smallrye-llm-langchain4j-ai-services</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’re a Java developer wanting to build AI agents or interface with various large language models (LLM) in Java, you will be familiar with Langchain4J.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-langchain4j-simplified&#34;&gt;What Is Langchain4J Simplified?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.langchain4j.dev/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;LangChain4J&lt;/a&gt; is essentially a toolbox for Java developers that makes it easier to add advanced language AI capabilities (like chatbots or text generators) to their applications, without having to deal with a ton of complicated details.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您是希望在Java中与各种大型语言模型（LLM）构建AI代理或接口的Java开发人员，那么您将熟悉Langchain4j。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“什么是langchain4j-simplified”&gt; langchain4j简化了什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.langchain4j.dev/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;LangChain4J&lt;/a&gt; is essentially a toolbox for Java developers that makes it easier to add advanced language AI capabilities (like chatbots or text generators) to their applications, without having to deal with a ton of complicated details.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Doris + Hudi Turned the Impossible Into the Everyday】多丽丝 + hudi如何将不可能的人变成日常</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/doris-hudi-making-impossible-possible</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the world of big data, there&#39;s a legend that goes like this: A data scientist, constantly worried about query performance and working late every night to optimize SQL, suddenly discovered the &#34;perfect match&#34; of Doris and Hudi, and immediately kicked into &#34;supersonic&#34; mode — query speeds so fast that even the boss couldn&#39;t believe it!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, this legend is widely circulated in the data community. Many data engineers jokingly say that processing data used to be like crossing a river in a canoe — slow and risky. Now, with the &#34;giant ship&#34; of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/integrate-apache-doris-hudi-data-querying-migration&#34;&gt;Doris + Hudi&lt;/a&gt;, they can not only sail smoothly but also elegantly travel through time to view every exciting moment of historical data.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在大数据的世界中，有一个传奇人物：一位数据科学家，经常担心查询性能并每天深夜工作以优化SQL，突然发现了多丽丝（Doris）和hudi的“完美匹配”，并立即踢入了“超音速”模式 - 甚至很快就可以相信它！&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，这个传说在数据界广泛流传。许多数据工程师开玩笑地说，处理数据曾经就像在独木舟中穿过河流一样 - 缓慢而风险。现在，有了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/integrate-apache-dori-hudi-data-querying migration”&gt; doris + hudi &lt;/a&gt;的“巨型船”。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Jira Restore And Disaster Recovery: Scenarios and Use Cases】JIRA还原和灾难恢复：方案和用例</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/jira-restore-disaster-recovery-scenarios-use-cases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to imagine the company managing its projects without issue-tracking tools. For example, Jira has probably become one of the most popular project management software solutions for organized teams. According to Atlassian, over 180k customers in about 190 countries use Jira in their daily work.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, what will they do if their Jira account suddenly fails to work? Every agile team, project management, product management, and software development team leader and member should consider a situation like that and have a plan to overcome any disaster with minimal impact.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;很难想象该公司在没有发行跟踪工具的情况下管理其项目。例如，JIRA可能已成为有组织团队最受欢迎的项目管理软件解决方案之一。根据Atlassian的说法，大约190个国家 /地区的超过18万客户在日常工作中使用JIRA。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那么，如果他们的Jira帐户突然无法正常工作，他们会怎么办？每个敏捷团队，项目管理，产品管理和软件开发团队负责人和成员都应考虑这样的情况，并计划以最小的影响来克服任何灾难。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Deep Dive into Apache Doris Indexes】深入研究Apache Doris索引</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-deep-dive-into-apache-doris-indexes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Developers in the big data field know that quickly retrieving data from a vast amount of information is like searching for a specific star in the constellations — extremely challenging. But don&#39;t worry! Database indexes are our “positioning magic tools,” capable of significantly boosting query efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-apache-doris-a-next-generation-rea&#34;&gt;Apache Doris&lt;/a&gt;, a popular analytical database, for example. It supports several types of indexes, each with its own unique features, enabling it to excel in various query scenarios. Today, let&#39;s explore Apache Doris indexes in detail and uncover the secrets behind their remarkable performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大数据字段中的开发人员知道，从大量信息中快速检索数据就像在星座中搜索特定的星星一样 - 极具挑战性。但是不用担心！数据库索引是我们的“定位魔术工具”，能够显着提高查询效率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以&lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-apache-doris-a-next-generation-rea-&gt; apache doris &lt;/a&gt;例如，流行的分析数据库。它支持几种类型的索引，每种索引具有自己独特的功能，使其能够在各种查询方案中表现出色。今天，让我们详细探讨Apache Doris索引，并发现其出色表现背后的秘密。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Critical Thinking In The Age Of AI-Generated Code】AI生成的代码时代的批判性思维</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-generated-code-critical-thinking</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;One of the first rules I learned about writing code is that you have to understand it line by line. Verify and validate instead of assuming and wishful thinking. The use of AI code assistants nowadays tends to make software developers forget this important rule.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest misconceptions about AI code assistants is that they simply “speed up” development. While they do increase the volume of code written, this doesn’t necessarily translate into better software. The more important question is: &lt;strong&gt;Does AI-generated code improve long-term maintainability&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我学到的有关编写代码的第一个规则之一是，您必须按行理解它。验证和验证，而不是假设和随意的思考。如今，使用AI代码助手的使用倾向于使软件开发人员忘记这一重要规则。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对AI代码助理的最大误解之一就是他们只是“加快”开发。尽管它们确实增加了编写的代码量，但这并不一定会转化为更好的软件。更重要的问题是：&lt;strong&gt; AI生成的代码是否可以改善长期可维护性&lt;/strong&gt;？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Overcoming MFA Test Automation Challenges】克服MFA测试自动化挑战</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/overcoming-mfa-test-automation-challenges</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Multi-factor authentication (MFA) has become an essential tool for safeguarding sensitive systems. As businesses strive to comply with regulatory requirements, the integration of MFA into workflows is now standard practice. However, automating tests for MFA-enabled systems poses unique challenges for QA teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will focus on a critical topic: what challenges arise when testing workflows with MFA, and what strategies can help overcome them?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;多因素身份验证（MFA）已成为维护敏感系统的必不可少的工具。随着企业努力遵守法规要求，将MFA集成到工作流程中现在是标准实践。但是，对支持MFA的系统的自动测试对质量检查团队构成了独特的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将重点介绍一个关键主题：在测试MFA的工作流程时会出现什么挑战，哪些策略可以帮助克服它们？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Generative AI and Data Streaming Are Replacing Visual Coding With Low-Code/No-Code Platforms】为什么生成的AI和数据流替换为低代码/无代码平台的视觉编码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/genai-replacing-visual-coding-low-code-no-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;This blog explores the evolution of low-code/no-code tools, their challenges, when (not) to use visual coding, and how generative AI and data streaming with Apache Kafka and Flink are reshaping the software and data engineering landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;Low-code/no-code tools have been praised as transformative for software development and data engineering, providing visual interfaces that democratize technology access for non-technical users. However, the&amp;nbsp;low-code / no-code space — saturated with hundreds of vendors and tools — faces challenges in scalability, consistency, and integration.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div dir =“ auto”&gt;&#xA; &lt;div dir =“ auto”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div dir =“ auto”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div dir =“ auto”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;此博客探讨了低编码/无代码工具的演变，其挑战，（不）使用视觉编码以及如何使用Apache Kafka和Flink进行生成的AI和数据流如何重塑软件和数据工程环境。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;低代码/无代码工具已被称赞为软件开发和数据工程的变革性，提供了可视化非技术用户技术访问的视觉接口。但是，低代码 /无代码空间（充满了数百个供应商和工具）面临可扩展性，一致性和集成的挑战。&lt; / p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Microservices: The Emerging Post-Monolith Architecture for 2025】超越微服务：2025年新兴的货币后建筑</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/post-monolith-architecture-2025</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Rise and Slowdown of Microservices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Microservices gained popularity by solving issues in monolithic systems. In the 2010s, teams embraced splitting applications into small, single-purpose services for independent development, scalable deployment, and varied tech stacks. This approach, supported by cloud and containers, promised quicker releases and resilience. Micro frontends brought these ideas to the UI, allowing multiple teams to build features in parallel using different web frameworks. Early on, the benefits were obvious: squads gained autonomy, they could “deploy independently” using the right tools for each task, and they could scale parts of an app on demand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Over time, though, problems arose in the microservice-first model. Engineering leaders noticed that keeping track of dozens or hundreds of services didn’t always pay off. In reality, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-microservices-an-introduction-to-microserv&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;microservices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; can be just as tricky as a monolith — services often end up tightly coupled, changes to one can break another, and running thousands of tiny services requires huge tooling and operational effort. Once the initial excitement wore off, companies ran into these integration struggles (some engineers even mention “microservice fatigue” from years of dealing with tangled issues).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;微服务的上升和放缓&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;微服务通过解决整体系统中的问题而获得了流行。在2010年代，团队将应用程序分为小型单用途服务，用于独立开发，可扩展的部署和多样化的技术堆栈。在云和容器支持的支持下，这种方法提供了更快的释放和弹性。 Micro前端将这些想法带到UI，允许多个团队使用不同的Web框架并行构建功能。早期，好处很明显：班级获得了自治权，他们可以使用适合每个任务的正确工具“独立部署”，并且可以按需扩展应用程序的一部分。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;随着时间的流逝，在微服务优先模型中出现了问题。工程领导者注意到，跟踪数十个或数百个服务并不总是会得到回报。实际上，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-microservices-microservices-an-san-introduction-to-microserv”&gt; &lt;span&gt; microservices &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt;通常与单声道一样棘手 - 通常需要紧密地进行操作，并且可以努力地进行操作，并在一个努力上进行操作。一旦最初的兴奋消失了，公司就会遇到这些整合斗争（一些工程师甚至在处理纠结问题的多年中提到了“微服务疲劳”）。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Neuron AI: Create Full-Featured AI Agents in PHP】引入神经元AI：在PHP中创建全功能的AI代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/neuron-ai-create-ai-agents-php</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the last few months, I have worked hard to push the integration of AI agents into my SaaS product to a higher level. It was a very long journey, starting more than a year ago with the first experiments. I have to say that understanding all the moving parts of an AI-driven system was far from easy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a PHP developer, I struggled a lot, mainly because the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-php-is-back-for-real&#34;&gt;PHP ecosystem&lt;/a&gt; for developing this kind of “Agentic” features into existing applications is not as advanced and rich as it is in other technologies.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在过去的几个月中，我一直在努力将AI代理集成到SaaS产品中。这是一段漫长的旅程，从一年多以前就进行了第一个实验。我不得不说，了解AI驱动系统的所有活动部分都不容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为PHP开发人员，我挣扎了很多，主要是因为&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/why-php-is-back-for-real”&gt; php ecosystem&gt; php ecosystem &lt;/a&gt;用于将这种“代理”功能开发到现有的应用中不像其他技术一样，是其他技术中的高级应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimus Alpha Analyzes Team Data】Optimus Alpha分析团队数据</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimus-alpha-analyzes-team-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Optimus Alpha Creates Useful Retrospective Format&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this experiment, OpenAI’s new stealthy LLM Optimus Alpha demonstrated exceptional performance in team data analysis, quickly identifying key patterns in complex agile metrics and synthesizing insights about technical debt, value creation, and team dynamics. The model provided a tailored retrospective format based on real team data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Its ability to analyze performance metrics and translate them into solid, actionable retrospective designs represents a significant advancement for agile practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; TL; DR：Optimus Alpha创建有用的回顾格式&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在该实验中，OpenAI的新型隐形LLM Optimus Alpha在团队数据分析中表现出了出色的性能，快速识别复杂的敏捷指标中的关键模式，并综合了有关技术债务，价值创造和团队动态的见解。该模型根据真实团队数据提供了量身定制的回顾格式。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其分析性能指标并将其转化为可行的可行的回顾性设计的能力代表了敏捷从业者的重大进步。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>