<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Infrastructure as Code (IaC) for Data Center Management】将基础架构作为数据中心管理的代码（IAC）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-iac-for-data-center-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Infrastructure as code (IaC) automates antiquated manual configurations in the most critical digital landscapes within communities. As the urgency and role of data centers continue to evolve, IaC could become an expectation for building managers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What can software developers learn about the advantages and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-infrastructure-as-code&#34;&gt;best practices for using IaC&lt;/a&gt; in delicate data center environments? We’re sharing more below.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;基础架构作为代码（IAC）自动化社区内最关键的数字景观中的过时的手动配置。随着数据中心的紧迫性和作用继续发展，IAC可能会成为建筑经理的期望。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;软件开发人员可以了解什么优势，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/hath what what-is-is-infrastructure-as-as-ascode”&gt;用于在精致的数据中心环境中使用IAC &lt;/a&gt;的最佳实践？我们在下面分享更多。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How I Taught OpenAI a New Programming Language With Fine-Tuning】我如何用微调来教开一种新的编程语言</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fine-tuning-openai-new-language</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you go to ChatGPT and ask it about Hyperlambda, at best, it will hallucinate wildly and generate something that resembles a bastardized mutation between Bash and Python. For the record, Claude is not any better here. The reason is that there&#39;s simply not enough Hyperlambda out there for the website scrapers from OpenAI and Anthropic to pick up its syntax. This was a sore thumb for me for a long time, so I realised I just had to do something about it. So, I started fine-tuning OpenAI on Hyperlambda.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If I had known what a job this would be, I&#39;d probably never have started. To teach &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.ainiro.io/hyperlambda/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hyperlambda&lt;/a&gt; to the point where it does &lt;em&gt;&#34;most simple things correct&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;,&#34;&lt;/em&gt; it took me 3,500 training snippets and about 550 validation snippets. Each snippet is, on average, about 20 lines of code;&lt;/span&gt; multiplied by 4,000, we&#39;re up to 80 KLOC of code.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您去Chatgpt并询问有关Hyperlambda的问题，它充其量会幻觉，并产生类似于Bash和Python之间的混蛋突变的东西。作为记录，克劳德在这里没有什么更好的。原因是那里根本没有足够的Hyperlambda来吸引Openai和Anthropic的网站刮刀来拾取其语法。这对我来说是一个很长一段时间的拇指，所以我意识到我只需要对此做些事情。因此，我开始在Hyperlambda上进行微调Openai。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果我知道这是什么工作，我可能永远不会开始。教授&lt;a href =“ https://docs.ainiro.io.io/hyperlambda/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; hyperlambda &lt;/a&gt;到达它所做的点&lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;“最简单的事物”正确&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;填充：0px;“&gt; &lt;em&gt;”，&lt;/em&gt;，我花了3,500个培训片段和大约550个验证片段。每个片段平均是约20行代码； &lt;/span&gt;乘以4,000，我们的代码最高为80 kloc。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing a Lightweight Apache JMeter Docker Image】引入轻巧的Apache Jmeter Docker图像</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/lightweight-apache-jmeter-docker</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for a lean, secure, and versatile Docker image for Apache JMeter to streamline your load testing of workflows? Look no further! Today, I’m excited to share a new Dockerfile I’ve crafted that delivers a lightweight Apache JMeter image without compromising on functionality. Whether you’re a developer, DevOps engineer, or QA professional, this image is designed to make your performance testing faster, easier, and more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34;&gt;Why This JMeter Docker Image Stands Out&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This isn’t your average JMeter setup. Here’s what makes this Docker image special:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否正在寻找Apache Jmeter的精益，安全和多功能的Docker映像来简化工作流程的负载测试？别再看！今天，我很高兴分享一个我精心制作的新的Dockerfile，它可以提供轻巧的Apache Jmeter图像，而不会损害功能。无论您是开发人员，DevOps工程师还是QA专业人员，此图像都旨在使您的性能测试更快，更容易且更有效。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block头”&gt;为什么这个jmeter docker映像&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这不是您的普通Jmeter设置。这是使此Docker图像特别的原因：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Quantum Cloud Computing: The Future of Cloud Computing Technology】量子云计算：云计算技术的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-cloud-computing-future</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Quantum cloud computing is a merge of quantum and cloud technology and a new computational model in capabilities. It can potentially tackle complex issues well beyond conventional computers&#39; capabilities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With quantum mechanical processes, including quantum interference, quantum entanglement, and quantum superposition, quantum cloud computing brings unparalleled computational capabilities over the cloud and allows companies and researchers to execute quantum algorithms with no in-house quantum infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;量子云计算是量子和云技术的合并，也是功能中的新计算模型。它可能会远远超出传统计算机的功能，可以解决复杂问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用量子机械过程，包括量子干扰，量子纠缠和量子叠加，量子云计算在云上带来了无与伦比的计算能力，并允许公司和研究人员执行无内部量子基础结构的量子算法。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Three AI Superpowers: Classification AI vs Predictive AI vs Generative AI】三个AI超级大国：分类AI与预测性AI与生成AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/classification-vs-predictive-vs-generative-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;308&#34; data-start=&#34;0&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence (AI) is a vast, evolving domain at the heart of countless modern technologies. To navigate its complexity, it’s helpful to divide AI into three core “families,” each with its own unique purpose and “personality”: classification AI, predictive AI, and generative AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul data-end=&#34;941&#34; data-start=&#34;310&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;514&#34; data-start=&#34;310&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;333&#34; data-start=&#34;312&#34;&gt;Classification AI&lt;/strong&gt; is your data organizer, skilled at labeling inputs into defined categories — think of how email services sort spam from genuine messages or how photo apps recognize familiar faces.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;728&#34; data-start=&#34;515&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;534&#34; data-start=&#34;517&#34;&gt;Predictive AI&lt;/strong&gt; acts like a crystal ball, analyzing patterns in past data to make informed guesses about the future—whether it’s forecasting tomorrow’s weather or predicting a sudden spike in product demand.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;941&#34; data-start=&#34;729&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;748&#34; data-start=&#34;731&#34;&gt;Generative AI&lt;/strong&gt;, by contrast, is the creative mastermind capable of producing entirely new outputs, such as realistic images, expressive music, or natural-sounding text, based on the patterns it has learned.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1177&#34; data-is-last-node=&#34;&#34; data-is-only-node=&#34;&#34; data-start=&#34;943&#34;&gt;Together, these three “families” of AI provide a comprehensive toolkit for organizing data, anticipating trends, and inventing novel ideas, ensuring that artificial intelligence continues to transform and reshape industries worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 308” data-start =“ 0”&gt;人工智能（AI）是无数现代技术的核心，是一个庞大的，不断发展的领域。为了探讨其复杂性，将AI分为三个核心“家庭”很有帮助，每个核心都具有其独特的目的和“个性”：分类AI，预测性AI和生成性AI。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul data-end =“ 941” data-start =“ 310”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 514” data-start =“ 310”&gt; &lt;strong data-end =“ 333” data-start =“ 312”&gt;分类ai &lt;/strong&gt;是您的数据组织者，擅长将输入输入到定义的类别中 - 想想如何从真实的消息或如何识别熟悉的照片的熟悉的熟悉的熟悉的照片。&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 728” data-start =“ 515”&gt; &lt;strong data-end =“ 534” data-start =“ 517”&gt;预测性ai &lt;/strong&gt;的作用像水晶球，分析过去数据中的模式，以对未来做出明智的猜测，以预测明天的天气或预测刺激性的刺激性或预测突然的产品。&#xA; 相比之下，&lt;li data-end =“ 941” data-start =“ 729”&gt; &lt;strong data-end =“ 748” data-start =“ 731”&gt;生成的ai &lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt;相反，具有创造性的策划者，能够产生全新的输出，例如逼真的图像，表达的音乐，表达性音乐，或基于自然单位的文本，基于知识的模式。&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1177” data-is-last-node =“” data-is-is-inly-node =“” data-start =“ 943”&gt;一起，AI的这三个“家庭”为组织数据提供了一个全面的工具包，以组织数据，预测趋势并发明新颖的想法，以确保人工智能继续转化和重新塑造世界的工业界，&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shift-Right Testing: Smart Automation Through AI and Observability】右翼测试：通过AI智能自动化和可观察性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/shift-right-testing-ai-observability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Conventional testing practices have mainly focused on discovering problems before the software is released to the market, also referred to as shift-left testing. Nevertheless, due to the heightened pace of software development owing to DevOps and CI/CD, many real-world conditions that do not mimic the live environment can go undetected in pre-production environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This is where shift-right testing comes in. Therefore, it is possible to improve the effectiveness of the strategies implemented by QA automation engineers through testing in production-like environments and with the help of AI-driven observability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;传统的测试实践主要集中于在软件释放到市场之前发现问题，也称为左翼测试。然而，由于由于DevOps和CI/CD的速度提高了软件开发的速度，因此许多不模仿实时环境的现实世界中可能会在预生产环境中发现。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这是转移权测试进入的地方。因此，有可能通过在类似生产的环境中进行测试并借助AI-driens的可观察力来提高QA自动化工程师实施的策略的有效性。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Agile Outsourcing Accelerates Software Project Delivery】敏捷外包如何加速软件项目交付</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agile-outsourcing-project-acceleration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The software development world is growing at a rapid pace, meaning that the quality of work should never be compromised while delivering projects on time. Agile outsourcing merges the iterative and flexible approaches of Agile development with the scope and breadth of outsourcing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This allows companies to change in response to market shifts, equate to the different skill sets available in the market, and ensure that work is being done continuously, which results in expedited delivery of software projects.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;软件开发世界正在快速增长，这意味着在按时交付项目时，不应妥协工作质量。敏捷外包将敏捷开发的迭代和灵活方法与外包的范围和广度融合在一起。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这使公司可以响应市场变化，等同于市场上可用的不同技能，并确保连续完成工作，这导致了加快软件项目的交付。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implement PHP Zmanim in WordPress Using Zmanim-WP】使用zmanim-WP在WordPress中实现PHP ZNOM</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implement-php-zmanim-in-wordpress-using-zmanim-wp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been following this blog, you know I’ve had a running series on implementing PHP Zmanim, the library based on Kosher Java that simplifies the work needed to calculate times related to Jewish religious observance. (If you need a full explanation of what that is, check out the first blog in the series.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the work of understanding and implementing &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/zachweix/PhpZmanim&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PHP Zmanim&lt;/a&gt; has been fun for it’s own sake, I was working on a larger goal behind the scenes: A WordPress plugin that implemented the library in a way that non-programmers could use on their (WordPress-based) websites.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您一直在关注此博客，您知道我已经有一个关于实施PHP Zmanim的跑步系列，该图书馆基于Kosher Java，简化了计算与犹太宗教遵守有关的时间所需的工作。 （如果您需要对那是什么的完整说明，请查看该系列的第一个博客。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然理解和实施&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/zachweix/phpzmanim” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; php zmanim &lt;/a&gt;很有趣（基于WordPress）网站。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Natural Language Queries for Multi-Service Information Retrieval】优化自然语言查询以获取多服务信息</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/natural-language-queries-multi-service-retrieval</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the age of rapid evolution of AI-related technologies, channel applications, e.g., web, kiosk, IVR, etc., are becoming increasingly intelligent where industries are developing strategies to scale the initial experimentations to scaled implementation resolving data quality, governance, and responsible AI challenges. Nonetheless, there is continuous effort put into moving past these inhibitors and scaling the implementations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s take an example of a channel application that supports foundation customer services. In the traditional architectural approach, the application would consume several APIs exposed by the enterprise with different types, e.g., experience and process APIs, to render the services. More often, in an orchestrated information fetch, this approach has resulted in significant chattiness, network overheads, and performance (e.g., response time) issues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在AI相关技术，渠道应用程序（例如Web，Kiosk，IVR等）快速发展的时代，在行业正在制定策略以扩展最初的实验以缩放数据质量，治理和负责AI挑战的策略，以扩展最初的实施策略，以扩展最初的实验，以扩展最初的实验，以扩展最初的实验。尽管如此，超越这些抑制剂并扩展实现的努力仍在不断努力。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们以支持基础客户服务的渠道应用程序的示例。在传统的架构方法中，该应用程序将消费企业与不同类型（例如经验和过程API）呈现服务的几种API，以提供服务。更常见的是，在精心策划的信息获取中，这种方法导致了巨大的融合，网络开销和性能（例如响应时间）问题。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimize Slow Data Queries With Doris JOIN Strategies】使用多丽丝加入策略来优化缓慢的数据查询</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/slow-data-queries-doris-join-strategies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In the world of data analysis, &#34;slow queries&#34; are like workplace headaches that just won&#39;t go away.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; Recently, I&#39;ve met quite a few data analysts who complain about queries running for hours without results, leaving them staring helplessly at the spinning progress bar. Last week, I ran into an old friend who was struggling with the performance of a large table JOIN.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#34;The query speed is slower than a snail, and my boss is driving me crazy...&#34; he said with a frustrated look.&lt;br&gt;&#xA; As a seasoned database optimization expert with years of experience on the front lines, I couldn&#39;t help but smile: &#34;JOIN performance is slow because you don&#39;t understand its nature. Just like in martial arts, understanding how to use force effectively can make all the difference.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;在数据分析的世界中，“慢查询”就像工作场所的头痛一样。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA; 最近，我遇到了很多数据分析师，他们抱怨查询几个小时没有结果，使他们无助地盯着旋转进度栏。上周，我遇到了一个老朋友，他正在挣扎着一张大桌子的表演。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“查询速度比蜗牛慢，我的老板让我发疯……”他沮丧地说道。&lt;br&gt;&#xA; 作为一名经验丰富的数据库优化专家，在前线有多年的经验，我忍不住微笑：“加入性能很慢，因为您不了解其本质。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>