<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Gracefully Deal With Contention】如何优雅地处理争用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gracefully-deal-with-contention</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Problem Statement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;When multiple clients, processes, or threads compete for a limited number of resources simultaneously, causing degraded turnaround time and performance, the system enters a state called contention. This is the most common problem in systems that handle high traffic volumes. Without graceful dealing, contention leads to race conditions and an inconsistent state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Example Scenario&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Consider buying flight tickets online. There is only one seat available on the flight. Alice and Bob both want this seat and click &#34;Book Now&#34; at exactly the same time.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;问题陈述&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;当多个客户端、进程或线程同时竞争有限数量的资源时，导致周转时间和性能下降，系统进入称为争用的状态。这是处理高流量的系统中最常见的问题。如果没有优雅的处理，争用会导致竞争条件和不一致的状态。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;示例场景&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;考虑在线购买机票。航班上只有一个座位。 Alice 和 Bob 都想要这个座位，并同时点击“立即预订”。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Illusion of Deep Learning: Why &#34;Stacking Layers&#34; Is No Longer Enough】深度学习的错觉：为什么“堆叠层”已经不够了</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/illusion-deep-learning-stacking-layers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Have we reached the limit of what we can achieve with our current AI models? At the very heart of the race for parameters and power conducted by Big Tech players, a fundamental question emerges: Do our AIs truly understand the changing world, or are they simply reciting a frozen past?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the study shared by the &lt;strong&gt;Google Research&lt;/strong&gt; team in their paper &lt;em&gt;&#34;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nested Learning: The Illusion of Deep Learning Architectures&#34;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;(1), the finding is unequivocal. According to them, our large language models (LLMs) suffer from &#34;anterograde amnesia syndrome.&#34; Like patient Henry Molaison, a famous clinical case (2), who was incapable of forming new memories after his operation, our models, once their training is complete, are frozen.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我们是否已达到当前人工智能模型所能实现的极限？在大型科技公司进行的参数和权力竞赛的核心，出现了一个基本问题：我们的人工智能是否真正理解不断变化的世界，或者它们只是在复述冰冷的过去？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google 研究&lt;/strong&gt;团队在其论文“嵌套学习：深度学习架构的幻觉”(1) 中分享的研究中，这一发现是明确的。根据他们的说法，我们的大型语言模型（LLM）患有“顺行性遗忘综合症”。就像著名的临床病例亨利·莫莱森 (Henry Molaison) 患者 (2) 一样，他在手术后无法形成新的记忆，我们的模型一旦训练完成，就会被冻结。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【RAG Applications with Vertex AI】具有 Vertex AI 的 RAG 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rag-applications-with-vertex-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Most organizations experimenting with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;generative AI&lt;/a&gt; face a common bottleneck: their LLMs can chat nicely, but they do not consistently know the company’s own data. A customer wants to know a policy clause, or an engineer asks a question about a system diagram, and the model makes something up or simply provides an ambiguous, incomplete response.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This won’t work in industries such as healthcare, financial services, or insurance where accuracy is critical. What we want is the creative power of LLMs, but also the ability to reliably know our organization’s stuff. &amp;nbsp;Here, we will explore how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) gives us those solutions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大多数尝试&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;生成式人工智能&lt;/a&gt;的组织都面临着一个共同的瓶颈：他们的法学硕士可以很好地聊天，但他们并不总是了解公司自己的数据。客户想了解保单条款，或者工程师询问有关系统图的问题，模型会编造一些内容或只是提供模糊、不完整的响应。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这在医疗保健、金融服务或保险等准确性至关重要的行业中不起作用。我们想要的是法学硕士的创造力，但也需要可靠地了解我们组织的东西的能力。  在这里，我们将探讨&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented- Generation-rag&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;检索增强生成&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) 如何为我们提供这些解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is TOON the Next Lightweight Hero in Event Stream Processing With Apache Kafka?】TOON 是 Apache Kafka 事件流处理领域的下一个轻量级英雄吗？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/toon-lightweight-event-streaming-kafka</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The data serialization format is a key factor when dealing with stream processing, as it decides how efficiently the data is forwarded on the wire and optimized internally in order to be stored, understood, and processed by a distributed system. The data serialization format is core to stream processing in that it directly influences the speed, reliability, scalability, and maintainability of the entire pipeline. Choosing the right one can eliminate expensive lock-ins and ensure that our streaming infrastructure remains stable as data volume and intricacy evolve.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In a stream-processing platform where millions of events per second must be handled with low latency by ingestion systems such as Apache Kafka and processing engines like Flink or Spark, reducing CPU usage is important, as it depends on efficient data formats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;数据序列化格式是处理流处理时的关键因素，因为它决定了数据在网络上转发和内部优化的效率，以便由分布式系统存储、理解和处理。数据序列化格式是流处理的核心，它直接影响整个管道的速度、可靠性、可扩展性和可维护性。选择正确的解决方案可以消除昂贵的锁定，并确保我们的流媒体基础设施随着数据量和复杂性的发展而保持稳定。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;在流处理平台中，每秒数百万个事件必须通过 Apache Kafka 等摄取系统和 Flink 或 Spark 等处理引擎以低延迟处理，减少 CPU 使用率非常重要，因为它取决于高效的数据格式。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Next-Gen AI-Based QA: Why Data Integrity Matters More Than Ever】下一代基于人工智能的质量保证：为什么数据完整性比以往任何时候都更加重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-qa-data-integrity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence has changed the way we work across different industries. From chatbots that quickly resolve customer issues to systems that detect equipment failures before they occur, automation is now a standard practice. As these smart systems become more independent, one question keeps emerging: how much can we trust the data behind them?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data integrity may not make the news often, but it supports every AI-driven process. When data is inconsistent, incomplete, or biased, even the best algorithms can fail. In an automated setup, those failures don’t just stay small; they grow, causing flawed predictions, distorted insights, or even unethical results. Bias, safety, disinformation, copyright, and alignment are big problems with AI thus robust data quality matters ever than before.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能改变了我们在不同行业的工作方式。从快速解决客户问题的聊天机器人到在设备故障发生之前检测到的系统，自动化现已成为一种标准做法。随着这些智能系统变得更加独立，一个问题不断出现：我们在多大程度上可以信任它们背后的数据？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据完整性可能不会经常成为新闻，但它支持每个人工智能驱动的流程。当数据不一致、不完整或有偏差时，即使是最好的算法也可能会失败。在自动化设置中，这些故障不仅很小，而且还很严重。它们不断增长，导致错误的预测、扭曲的见解，甚至不道德的结果。偏见、安全、虚假信息、版权和一致性是人工智能的大问题，因此强大的数据质量比以往任何时候都重要。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Repetition to Reusability: How Maven Archetypes Save Time】从重复到可重用：Maven 原型如何节省时间</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-maven-archetypes-save-time</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Within the discipline of software engineering, practitioners are frequently encumbered by the monotonous ritual of initializing identical project scaffolds — configuring dependencies, establishing directory hierarchies, and reproducing boilerplate code prior to engaging in substantive problem‑solving. Although indispensable, such preliminary tasks are inherently repetitive, susceptible to human error, and inimical to efficiency.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-maven-story&#34;&gt;Maven&lt;/a&gt;, a cornerstone of the Java build ecosystem, furnishes an elegant mechanism to mitigate this redundancy through the construct of &lt;strong&gt;archetypes&lt;/strong&gt;. An archetype functions as a canonical blueprint, enabling the instantaneous generation of standardized project structures aligned with organizational conventions. By engineering bespoke archetypes, development teams can institutionalize consistency, accelerate delivery, and reallocate intellectual effort toward innovation rather than procedural repetition.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在软件工程学科中，从业者经常被初始化相同项目支架的单调仪式所困扰 - 配置依赖项、建立目录层次结构以及在解决实质性问题之前复制样板代码。尽管必不可少，但此类初步任务本质上是重复性的，容易出现人为错误，并且不利于效率。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-maven-story&#34;&gt;Maven&lt;/a&gt; 是 Java 构建生态系统的基石，它提供了一种优雅的机制，通过构建&lt;strong&gt;原型&lt;/strong&gt;来减轻这种冗余。原型充当规范蓝图，能够即时生成符合组织惯例的标准化项目结构。通过设计定制原型，开发团队可以将一致性制度化，加速交付，并将智力工作重新分配给创新而不是程序重复。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Level Up Your API Design: 8 Principles for World-Class REST APIs】提升您的 API 设计：世界级 REST API 的 8 条原则</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/level-up-api-design-rest-principles</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;b787&#34;&gt;You’ve probably built a “REST API” before. But what does “RESTful” truly mean? It’s not just about using JSON and HTTP. It’s a spectrum, best described by the &lt;strong&gt;Richardson Maturity Model (RMM)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;2958&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Level 0 (The Swamp)&lt;/strong&gt;: Using HTTP as a transport system for remote procedure calls (RPC). Think of a single /api endpoint where all operations are POST requests.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;29c7&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Level 1 (Resources)&lt;/strong&gt;: Introducing the concept of &lt;em&gt;resources&lt;/em&gt;. Instead of one endpoint, you have multiple URIs like /users and /orders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;3138&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Level 2 (HTTP Verbs)&lt;/strong&gt;: Using HTTP methods (GET, POST, PUT, DELETE) and status codes (2xx, 4xx) to operate on those resources. This is where most “REST” APIs live.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;1e7b&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Level 3 (Hypermedia  —  HATEOAS)&lt;/strong&gt;: The “holy grail” of REST. The API’s responses include links (hypermedia) that tell the client what they can do next. The client navigates your API by &lt;em&gt;discovering&lt;/em&gt; these links, not by hard-coding URLs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;7d34&#34;&gt;The eight principles I’m sharing today are a blend of my own production experience and the pragmatic wisdom from industry-leading guides like Zalando’s. These should help you move your APIs up this maturity ladder, creating designs that are more robust, scalable, and easier to use.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;b787&#34;&gt;您之前可能构建过“REST API”。但“RESTful”的真正含义是什么？这不仅仅是使用 JSON 和 HTTP。这是一个范围，最好用&lt;strong&gt;理查森成熟度模型 (RMM)&lt;/strong&gt; 来描述。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;2958&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;0 级（沼泽）&lt;/strong&gt;：使用 HTTP 作为远程过程调用 (RPC) 的传输系统。想象一个 /api 端点，其中所有操作都是 POST 请求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;29c7&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 1 级（资源）&lt;/strong&gt;：介绍资源的概念。&lt;em&gt;资源&lt;/em&gt;。您拥有多个 URI，例如 /users 和 /orders，而不是一个端点。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;3138&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2 级（HTTP 动词）&lt;/strong&gt;：使用 HTTP 方法（GET、POST、PUT、DELETE）和状态代码（2xx、4xx）对这些资源进行操作。这是大多数“REST”API 所在的位置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;1e7b&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3 级（超媒体  —  HATEOAS）&lt;/strong&gt;：REST 的“圣杯”。 API 的响应包括告诉客户端下一步可以做什么的链接（超媒体）。客户端通过&lt;em&gt;发现&lt;/em&gt;这些链接来导航您的 API，而不是通过硬编码 URL。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;7d34&#34;&gt;我今天分享的八项原则融合了我自己的制作经验和 Zalando 等行业领先指南的务实智慧。这些应该可以帮助您提升 API 的成熟度，创建更强大、可扩展且更易于使用的设计。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Five Nonprofit &amp;amp; Charity APIs That Make Due Diligence Way Less Painful for Developers】五个非营利组织和慈善机构 API 可以减轻开发人员的尽职调查痛苦</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/five-nonprofit-amp-charity-apis-that-make-due-dili</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;534&#34; data-start=&#34;347&#34;&gt;I learned this lesson the hard way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;534&#34; data-start=&#34;347&#34;&gt;A few years back, I built a donation platform I thought was bulletproof. The design? Slick. Payments? Smooth. I figured, “Alright, I’ve nailed it.”&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;534&#34; data-start=&#34;347&#34;&gt;我通过惨痛的教训学到了这一课。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;534&#34; data-start=&#34;347&#34;&gt;几年前，我建立了一个我认为万无一失的捐赠平台。设计？光滑。付款？光滑的。我想，“好吧，我成功了。”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Running Istio in Production: Five Hard-Won Lessons From Cloud-Native Teams】在生产环境中运行 Istio：来自云原生团队的五个来之不易的经验教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/running-istio-in-production-lessons</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Istio has established itself as a popular, trusted, and powerful service mesh platform. It complements Kubernetes with powerful features such as security, observability, and traffic management with no code changes. Istio’s several key features strengthen cloud-native and distributed systems, ensuring consistency, security, and resilience across diverse environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio has also recently graduated under the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-is-cloud-native-are-you-ready&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Computing Foundation&lt;/a&gt; (CNCF), along with other projects like Kubernetes. In this article, we will cover Istio&#39;s best practices for building a production-grade service mesh layer that offers secure, resilient, and durable performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Istio 已成为一个流行、值得信赖且功能强大的服务网格平台。它以安全性、可观察性和流量管理等强大功能补充了 Kubernetes，且无需更改代码。 Istio 的几个关键功能增强了云原生和分布式系统，确保跨不同环境的一致性、安全性和弹性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio 最近还与 Kubernetes 等其他项目一起在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-is-cloud-native-are-you-ready&#34;&gt;云原生计算基金会&lt;/a&gt; (CNCF) 下毕业。在本文中，我们将介绍 Istio 构建生产级服务网格层的最佳实践，该层可提供安全、弹性和持久的性能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Simple MCP Server and Client: An In-Memory Database】构建简单的 MCP 服务器和客户端：内存数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/simple-mcp-server-client-database</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If you&#39;ve been diving into the world of AI-assisted programming or tool-calling protocols, you might have come across Model Context Protocol (MCP). MCP is an open-source standard for connecting AI applications to external systems. It is a lightweight framework that lets you expose functions as &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://modelcontextprotocol.io/docs/learn/server-concepts#tools&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;tools&lt;/a&gt;&#34; to language models, enabling seamless interaction between AI agents and your code. Think of it as a bridge that turns your functions into callable endpoints for models.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this post, we’ll build a basic in-memory database server using MCP, with code samples to extend and learn from. We&#39;ll dissect the code step by step, and by the end, you&#39;ll have a working prototype. Plus, I&#39;ll ask you to extend it with update, delete, and drop functionalities. Let&#39;s turn your terminal into a mini SQL playground!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果您一直在深入研究人工智能辅助编程或工具调用协议的世界，您可能已经遇到过模型上下文协议 (MCP)。 MCP 是一种用于将 AI 应用程序连接到外部系统的开源标准。它是一个轻量级框架，可让您将函数作为“&lt;a href=&#34;https://modelcontextprotocol.io/docs/learn/server-concepts#tools&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;工具&lt;/a&gt;”公开给语言模型，从而实现 AI 代理与代码之间的无缝交互。将其视为将您的函数转变为模型的可调用端点的桥梁。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将使用 MCP 构建一个基本的内存数据库服务器，并提供可供扩展和学习的代码示例。我们将逐步剖析代码，最后，您将拥有一个工作原型。另外，我会要求您通过更新、删除和删除功能来扩展它。让我们将您的终端变成一个迷你 SQL 游乐场！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>