<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Measuring DevOps Success in the Enterprise With DORA Metrics】通过Dora指标来衡量企业中的Devops成功</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devops-success-enterprise-dora-metrics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DevOps Research and Assessment (DORA) metrics came into play when businesses needed a clear way to measure the performance of DevOps teams. Before this, software developers and operational managers were working independently, which resulted in slower deployments and increased risk rates. With the help of DORA metrics, businesses can have a look at detailed insights about which software team needs attention and what the key points of excellence are. Tracking the software development teams regularly helps businesses improve their weak areas, resulting in higher efficiency and subsequently increased productivity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This blog will introduce five &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/dora-metrics-in-devops&#34;&gt;DORA metrics&lt;/a&gt;, their benefits, and how to utilize them to enhance software performance and quality.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; DevOPS研究与评估（DORA）指标开始起作用，当时企业需要一种清晰的方法来衡量DevOps团队的性能。在此之前，软件开发人员和运营经理正在独立工作，这导致部署较慢和风险率提高。在Dora指标的帮助下，企业可以查看有关哪些软件团队需要关注以及卓越的关键点的详细见解。跟踪软件开发团队会定期帮助企业改善其弱领域，从而提高效率，并随后提高生产率。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;此博客将介绍五个&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/dora-metrics-in-devops”&gt; dora Meterrics &lt;/a&gt;，它们的好处以及如何利用它们来增强软件性能和质量。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Secure Multi-Tenancy in SaaS Applications: A Developer&#39;s Checklist】在SaaS应用程序中实施安全的多租户：开发人员的清单</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-multi-tenancy-saas-developer-checklist</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Secure Multi-Tenancy Implementation Guide&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a developer who has worked extensively with SaaS applications, I&#39;ve learned that implementing secure multi-tenancy is one of the most critical aspects of building scalable software-as-a-service platforms. Through my experience, I&#39;ve compiled this comprehensive checklist to help fellow developers navigate the complexities of multi-tenant architecture while maintaining the highest security standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multi-tenancy allows a single instance of my application to serve multiple customers (tenants) while keeping their data completely isolated and secure. Let me walk you through everything I&#39;ve learned about implementing this architecture effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt;安全的多租户实施指南&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为与SaaS应用程序广泛合作的开发人员，我了解到实施安全的多租户是构建可扩展软件即服务平台的最关键方面之一。通过我的经验，我已经编辑了这份全面的清单，以帮助开发人员在维护最高安全标准的同时浏览多租户建筑的复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多租户允许我的应用程序的一个实例为多个客户（租户）提供服务，同时保持数据完全隔离和安全。让我带您了解我学到的有关有效实施此体系结构的所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker Model Runner Makes Running Models Simpler】Docker Model Runner使运行模型更简单</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-model-runner-makes-running-models-simpler</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Docker is a cornerstone for the cloud industry, well-known for running container-based workloads. And the newest addition to their armoury is Docker Model Runner, which takes running models on your desktop to a whole new level. So,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;let&#39;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;dive in and explore what a model runner is and how it simplifies local development with LLMs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;The first thing I love about the Docker model runner is that you can package models as Open Container (OCI) artefacts and distribute them using the same registries we already use for container images.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Just look at the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hub.docker.com/catalogs/gen-ai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Docker GenAI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;registry;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;it already supports a&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;bunch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;of popular models&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;like&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;DeepSeek, Gemma, Mistral, LLAMA, and PHI.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt; docker是云行业的基石，以运行基于容器的工作负载而闻名。而且，他们的军械库的最新成员是Docker Model Runner，它将桌面上的跑步型号提升到一个全新的水平。因此，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-pleserver spaces =“ true”&gt;让我们&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;潜入并探索模型跑步者是什么以及它如何用LLMS简化本地开发。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/ps&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;我喜欢Docker Model Runner的第一件事是，您可以将模型作为开放容器（OCI）人工制品包装，并使用已经用于容器图像的相同注册表进行分配。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver-spaces =“ true”&gt;只需查看&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://hub.docker.com/catalogs/catalogs/gen-ai” target =“ _ black”&gt; &lt;span data data data-proserver-paces =“ true” data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;it already supports a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;bunch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; of popular models &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;like&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; DeepSeek, Gemma，Mistral，Llama和Phi。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Debugging Bias: How to Audit Machine Learning Models for Fairness at Scale】调试偏见：如何大规模审核机器学习模型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/debugging-bias-auditing-ml-models</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As machine learning (ML) systems increasingly shape decisions in finance, healthcare, hiring, and justice, questions of fairness are no longer philosophical or peripheral; they&#39;re foundational. While model accuracy and performance still dominate technical discussions, they alone don’t guarantee ethical or responsible AI. In fact, a highly accurate model can still be deeply unfair if it&#39;s built on biased data or deployed without regard to disparate impacts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1157&#34; data-start=&#34;759&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-fairness-360-a-comprehensive-guide-for-develope&#34;&gt;Fairness in ML&lt;/a&gt; is a multifaceted and often misunderstood problem. It’s not just about intent, it’s about outcomes. A seemingly neutral model can encode historical bias or reflect systemic inequalities, producing skewed decisions that affect real lives. That’s why fairness audits are essential, not as one-time checks, but as continuous, technical practices baked into the machine learning lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着机器学习（ML）系统越来越多地塑造财务，医疗保健，招聘和正义的决策，公平性问题不再是哲学或外围的。它们是基础。尽管模型的准确性和性能仍然主导着技术讨论，但它们并不能保证道德或负责人的AI。实际上，如果它是建立在有偏见的数据上或部署而不考虑不同影响的情况下，高度准确的模型仍然可能是不公平的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1157” data-start =“ 759”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-fairness-360-a-comprehens-guide-guide-for-develope”&gt; ML中的公平性&lt;/a&gt;是一个多面化和常见的问题。这不仅是意图，还与结果有关。看似中立的模型可以编码历史偏见或反映系统性不平等，从而产生影响现实生活的偏斜决定。这就是为什么公平审核是必不可少的，不是一次性检查，而是作为连续的技术实践在机器学习生命周期中烘烤的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【5 Ways Microsoft’s MCP Protocol Will Transform Software Testing Forever】微软的MCP协议将永远转换软件测试的5种方式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/microsoft-mcp-protocol-software-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;The AI Testing Revolution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft’s Model Context Protocol (MCP) signifies a paradigm shift in how AI agents engage with applications and services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently announced as a foundational component of Windows 11’s “agentic OS” at Microsoft Build 2025, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/natural-language-sql-queries-with-mcp&#34;&gt;MCP&lt;/a&gt; offers a standardized framework for AI agents to connect with native applications, enabling seamless orchestration across local and remote services (Microsoft, 2025a). Much like how HTTP revolutionized web communication, MCP is set to become the universal standard for AI agent interactions, fundamentally transforming software testing methodologies and practices.&lt;img class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;80.8 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1751001895069&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;06/27/2025 05:24 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18493350-mcp-architechture.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;80838&#34; data-name=&#34;mcp-architechture.png&#34; data-id=&#34;18493350&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18493350-mcp-architechture.png&#34; style=&#34;width: 683px;&#34; alt=&#34;MCP Architecture Hierarchy&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; &lt;span&gt; AI测试革命&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Microsoft的模型上下文协议（MCP）表示AI代理如何与应用程序和服务互动的范式转变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近宣布是Microsoft Build 2025上的Windows 11的“代理OS”的基础组成部分2025a）。 Much like how HTTP revolutionized web communication, MCP is set to become the universal standard for AI agent interactions, fundamentally transforming software testing methodologies and practices.&lt;img class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;80.8 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1751001895069&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;06/27/2025 05:24 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18493350-mcp-architechture.png&#34; data-modificationdate =“ null” data-size =“ 80838” data-name =“ mcp-architechture.png” data-id =“ 18493350” data-src =“ https://dz2cdn1.dzon1.dzone.com/storage/storage/storage/temp/temp/temp/1849333330-mcp-cpp-cracp-cractitechitechitechitechit.6hy fiere field field field field fierts fiere = alt =“ MCP架构层次结构”&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Intelligent Applications Using Generative AI and Azure Database for PostgreSQL】使用生成AI和Azure数据库构建智能应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-azure-postgresql-intelligent-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Generative AI is transforming how modern applications are built, deployed, and scaled. Developers can now run text summarization within the database using a simple SQL command.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/database-migration-to-azure-for-postgresql&#34;&gt;Azure Database for PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt; provides an ability to integrate directly with Azure AI services so that the developers have the power to directly use GenAI capabilities into their own data layer, streamlining workflow, automating the insights, and providing next-level user experiences.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;生成型AI正在改变现代应用程序的构建，部署和缩放的方式。开发人员现在可以使用简单的SQL命令在数据库中运行文本摘要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https：//dzone.com/articles/database-migration-migration-migration-migration-to-azure-for-postgresql“洞察力，并提供下一级用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting Started With DuckDB in Python: A Fast and Lightweight Analytics Database】Python中的DuckDB入门：快速且轻量级的分析数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/duckdb-python-sql-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Data professionals today are looking for tools that combine speed, ease of use, and flexibility. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-to-duckdb-optimization&#34;&gt;DuckDB&lt;/a&gt; is one such tool that is gaining popularity quickly. It is an embedded SQL OLAP database that lets you run fast analytical queries right inside your Python environment. Whether you are working in a Jupyter notebook or building a local pipeline, DuckDB helps you explore and analyze data efficiently without needing a full-scale database setup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Think of DuckDB as SQLite&#39;s analytical cousin. While &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/build-simple-api-with-python-flask-and-sql&#34;&gt;SQLite&lt;/a&gt; is designed for transactional workloads, DuckDB is optimized for analytical tasks. It reads Parquet and CSV files directly, integrates easily with pandas, and runs SQL with minimal overhead. This tutorial will walk you through everything you need to start using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-handling-sensitive-data-with-duckdb&#34;&gt;DuckDB with Python&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;当今的数据专业人员正在寻找结合速度，易用性和灵活性的工具。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-to-duckdb-optimization”&gt; duckdb &lt;/a&gt;就是这样一种工具，它正在迅速获得流行。这是一个嵌入式SQL OLAP数据库，可让您在Python环境中运行快速的分析查询。无论您是在Jupyter笔记本电脑中工作还是构建本地管道，DuckDB都可以帮助您有效地探索和分析数据，而无需全尺寸的数据库设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;将duckdb视为sqlite的分析表弟。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/build-simple-api-with-with-python-flask-and-sql”&gt; sqlite &lt;/a&gt;是为交易工作载荷而设计的，但DuckDB已优化用于分析任务。它直接读取Parquet和CSV文件，与Pandas轻松集成，并以最小的开销运行SQL。本教程将带您完成使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-guide-guide-sensive-data-with-duckdb”&gt; with python &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt; duckdB</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Ethically Integrate AI Into Your Software】如何将AI道德集成到您的软件中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-ethically-integrate-ai-into-your-software</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence has very quickly become a standard part of the software we use every day. In fact, research shows that&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wpforms.com/ai-statistics-and-trends-you-need-to-know/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;73% of companies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;in the U.S. are already using AI in some capacity, and this trend isn&#39;t showing any signs of slowing down.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;As AI&#39;s capabilities grow, so does the importance of thinking about how to use it ethically. The main challenge for developers and companies is to find the right balance between pushing forward with AI innovation and making sure&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;it&#39;s done&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;responsibly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span数据范围=“ true”&gt;人工智能已很快成为我们每天使用的软件的标准部分。实际上，研究表明，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://wpforms.com/ai-statistics-and-you-trends-you-need-to-know/-” AI以某种身份，这种趋势没有显示出放慢的任何迹象。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;随着AI的功能的增长，考虑如何在道德上使用它的重要性也是如此。开发人员和公司的主要挑战是在推动AI创新前进和确保&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-data-perserver spaces =“ true”&gt;之间找到适当的平衡。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS vs. Azure vs. GCP: A Comprehensive Guide to Choosing the Right Cloud Provider】AWS与Azure vs. GCP：选择合适的云提供商的综合指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-vs-azure-vs-gcp-a-comprehensive-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Cloud computing has completely transformed the way businesses treat their IT infrastructure. With features like scalability, flexibility, and cost savings, cloud computing has become indispensable for organizations of all spheres. However, choosing a cloud provider from the great three players—&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-vs-azure-which-is-better-for-cloud-computing&#34;&gt;Microsoft Azure&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-resources-to-help-you-get-started-in-the-cloud&#34;&gt;Amazon Web Services&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/google-cloud-vs-aws-right-cloud-platform&#34;&gt;Google Cloud Platform&lt;/a&gt; - against the background of the vast range of services and pricing models is not easy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud computing allows organizations to rent computing resources instead of having to manage their own physical hardware. This is a flexible, scalable, and cost-effective solution. Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services, and Google Cloud each represent one of the three major players in the space, each offering a different mix of business appeal and some unique benefits. When considering their core strengths, Azure, AWS, and GCP cater to varied business needs. You may find a cloud service more suitable for your company based on some of the following factors: hybrid cloud integration, enterprise support, scale, AI capabilities, and cost optimization.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;云计算完全改变了业务对待其IT基础架构的方式。凭借可扩展性，灵活性和节省成本的功能，对于所有领域的组织来说，云计算变得必不可少。但是，从伟大的三个球员中选择一个云提供者 -  &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/aws-vs-vs-azure-which-is-better-better-for-cloud-computing”&gt; Microsoft Azure &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-resources-to-help-you-get-started-in-the-cloud&#34;&gt;Amazon Web Services&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/google-cloud-vs-aws-right-cloud-platform&#34;&gt;Google Cloud Platform&lt;/a&gt; - against the background of the vast range of services and定价模型并不容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云计算使组织可以租用计算资源，而不必管理自己的物理硬件。这是一种灵活，可扩展且具有成本效益的解决方案。 Microsoft Azure，Amazon Web Services和Google Cloud每个代表了该领域的三个主要参与者之一，每个人都提供了不同的业务吸引力和一些独特的好处。考虑到它们的核心优势，Azure，AWS和GCP满足各种业务需求。您可能会根据以下一些因素找到更适合您公司的云服务：混合云集成，企业支持，规模，AI功能和成本优化。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling Systems for Travel Tuesday: Surviving Billion-Event Spikes】周二旅行的缩放系统：幸存的十亿个事件尖峰</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scale-for-travel-tuesday-black-friday-traffic-spikes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Travel Tuesday – the tourism industry&#39;s answer to Black Friday – can hammer online systems with a tidal wave of transactions in a matter of hours. One minute your platform is humming along at millions of requests; the next, it’s spiking towards billions. Handling this surge is like facing a self-induced DDoS attack, and the question is: can your infrastructure handle the stampede or will it buckle under pressure? As a seasoned engineer might say, these mega-sale events are the ultimate scalability test. In this article, we’ll explore how logistics and e-commerce providers architect, fortify, and operate their systems to thrive during events like Travel Tuesday (and similarly intense spikes on Black Friday, Prime Day, etc.), scaling from millions to billions of events without crumbling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Architectural Strategies for Massive Scale&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Architectural choices lay the groundwork for scaling. Smart design can ensure your system handles sudden load gracefully:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;旅行周二 - 旅游业对黑色星期五的回答 - 可以在几个小时内以潮汐交易浪潮来锤击在线系统。一分钟，您的平台按照数百万要求的要求嗡嗡作响。接下来，它朝着数十亿美元尖叫。处理这种激增就像面对自我引起的DDOS攻击，问题是：您的基础设施可以处理踩踏还是在压力下扣紧？正如经验丰富的工程师可能会说的那样，这些大型销售事件是最终的可伸缩性测试。在本文中，我们将探讨物流和电子商务提供商建筑师，加强和运营其系统如何在旅行周二等活动中蓬勃发展（在黑色星期五，黄金日等类似地激烈的峰值），从数百万到数十亿美元的活动不崩溃。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;大规模规模的建筑策略&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;建筑选择为缩放奠定了基础。智能设计可以确保您的系统优雅地处理突然的负载：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>