<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Container Runtimes】集装箱运行时间指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-guide-to-container-runtimes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes, also known as K8S, is an open-source container orchestration system that is used for automating the deployment, scaling, and management of containerized workloads.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Containers are at the heart of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/kubernetes&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kubernetes ecosystem&lt;/a&gt; and are the building blocks of the services built and managed by K8S. Understanding how containers are run is key to optimizing your Kubernetes environment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; kubernetes，也称为K8S，是一个开源容器编排系统，用于自动化容器化工作负载的部署，缩放和管理。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;容器是&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kubernetes/kubernetes” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; kubernetes ecosystem &lt;/a&gt;，并且是由k8s内置和管理的服务块。了解容器的运行方式是优化Kubernetes环境的关键。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fixing Common Oracle Database Problems】解决常见的Oracle数据库问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fixing-common-oracle-database-problems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Lots of businesses use Oracle databases to keep their important stuff. These databases mostly work fine, but yeah, sometimes they run into issues. Anyone who&#39;s worked with Oracle knows the feeling when things go wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Don&#39;t worry, though — these problems happen to everyone. Most fixes are actually pretty easy once you know what you are doing. I&#39;ll show you the usual Oracle headaches and how to fix them.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;很多企业都使用Oracle数据库来保留其重要内容。这些数据库主要工作正常，但是，有时它们会遇到问题。与Oracle一起工作的任何人都知道发生了问题时的感觉。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不用担心 - 这些问题发生在每个人身上。一旦知道自己在做什么，大多数修复程序实际上就很容易。我将向您展示通常的Oracle头痛以及如何修复它们。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Develop a Reverse Proxy With Caching in Go】在GO中使用缓存而开发反向代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/reverse-proxy-with-caching-in-go</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Reverse proxies act as a crucial intermediary layer in modern web infrastructure, sitting between clients and servers and offering additional functionality such as load balancing, SSL termination, and caching. In this article, we are going to construct a reverse proxy with HTTP response caching using Go’s standard library.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Basic Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a first step, we will declare our core data structures. We need:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;反向代理在现代网络基础架构中充当至关重要的中间层，坐在客户和服务器之间，并提供其他功能，例如负载平衡，SSL终止和缓存。在本文中，我们将使用GO的标准库来构建使用HTTP响应缓存的反向代理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;基本结构&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为第一步，我们将声明我们的核心数据结构。我们需要：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Create Your Own AI-Powered Virtual Tutor: An Easy Tutorial】创建自己的AI驱动的虚拟导师：简单的教程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/create-an-ai-powered-virtual-tutor</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;It is a very powerful world with AI being a thing. Now, you can have a tutor who never gets tired, who doesn’t roll their eyes at your dumb questions (we all have them, I do, admit it), and who is available 24/7 — no scheduling problems, no coffee breaks, just straight knowledge on demand. That’s the magic of AI-based tutors. But before we start dreaming about how AI could replace your least favorite professors, let’s discuss how to build one in fact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As someone who has tinkered with AI models for countless hours (and broken them here and there), I have been somewhat obsessed with the notion of an AI tutor. In this guide, I’m going to take you through the main components needed to build one for yourself, from &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/natural-language-processing-nlp-in-software-testin&#34;&gt;Natural Language Processing&lt;/a&gt; (NLP) to knowledge graphs and adaptive learning models. No, this is not a plug-and-play recipe, though it will provide you with a strong road map for your path.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这是一个非常强大的世界，AI是事物。现在，您可以有一位永远不会累的导师，他们不会对您的愚蠢问题（我们都有，我愿意，承认），并且24/7全天候有空 - 没有时间安排问题，没有咖啡休息，只需按需直接的知识。那就是基于AI的导师的魔力。但是，在我们开始梦想AI如何取代您最不喜欢的教授之前，让我们讨论如何建立一个。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;作为一个用无数小时修补AI模型的人（在这里和那里打破了它们），我对AI导师的概念有些痴迷。在本指南中，我将带您完成为自己构建一个的主要组件，从&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/natural-language-processing-nlp-inlp-inlp-in-software-testin”&gt;自然语言处理&lt;/a&gt;（NLP）到知识图和自适应学习模型。不，这不是插件食谱，尽管它将为您提供强大的路线图。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Google Cloud Document AI Basics】Google云文档AI基础知识</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/google-cloud-document-ai-basics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Google Cloud’s Document AI (Doc AI) helps organizations automate the processing, extraction, and classification of massive amounts of documents.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Doc AI has a lot of capabilities and use cases, and here are a few ways it can help organizations. They’re tailored towards the public sector since that’s the customers I help; however, these use cases also apply to private companies.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p数​​据选择 - 段落=“”&gt; Google Cloud的文档AI（DOC AI）可帮助组织自动化大量文档的处理，提取和分类。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据可选 - 段落=“”&gt; DOC AI具有很多功能和用例，并且以下几种方法可以帮助组织。他们是针对公共部门量身定制的，因为那是我帮助的客户；但是，这些用例也适用于私人公司。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Scalable and Resilient Data Pipelines With Apache Airflow】用Apache气流构建可扩展和弹性的数据管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scalable-resilient-data-pipelines-apache-airflow</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I have seen articles discussing Apache Airflow and its many capabilities. It&#39;s crucial to understand production-quality data pipelines meant to &#34;handle&#34; terabytes of daily data generated by the enterprise&#39;s software-as-a-service (SaaS) applications. The article takes you beyond the basic introductory stuff and on to more advanced techniques and best practices for developing scalable, fault-tolerant, and observable Airflow workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Administration for an enterprise in a modern &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-saas-integration&#34;&gt;SaaS context&lt;/a&gt; is very challenging. It comes with a myriad of challenges in terms of monitoring, administration, and understanding the usage of applications across the organization. It involves the management of increasing amounts of unstructured data with a high tendency for real-time visibility under user activity, resource utilization, and compliance requirements. From this data, organizations need clear insights into usage within their applications to enable them to manage their human resources efficiently and optimally while being effective and compliant. Therefore, they need a powerful Admin Insights pipeline capable of:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我已经看到文章讨论了Apache气流及其许多功能。重要的是要了解旨在“处理”企业软件即服务（SAAS）应用程序生成的每日数据的生产质量数据管道。这篇文章将带您超越基本的介绍性内容，并获得更高级的技术和最佳实践，以开发可扩展，容忍和可观察的气流工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在现代&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-is-saas-integration”&gt; saaS上下文&lt;/a&gt;的企业中的企业&lt;/a&gt;非常具有挑战性。在监视，管理和理解整个组织应用程序的使用方面，它面临着无数的挑战。它涉及管理越来越多的非结构化数据的管理，在用户活动，资源利用和合规要求下，具有很高的实时可见性趋势。从这些数据中，组织需要清楚地了解其应用程序中的用法，以使他们能够在有效和合规的同时有效，最佳地管理人力资源。因此，他们需要一个强大的管理员见解管道，能够：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker Model Runner: Streamlining AI Deployment for Developers】Docker Model Runner：简化开发人员的AI部署</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-model-runner-ai-deployment</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Development teams working in the fast-evolving AI development environment must tackle efficient model deployment as their primary operational challenge. Docker Model Runner represents a transformative containerization solution that drives changes in how developers create, deploy, and expand their applications that use AI technology.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article will cover how this technology bridges the gap between data science testing phases and the deployment of ready-to-use AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在快速发展的AI开发环境中工作的开发团队必须将有效的模型部署作为其主要运营挑战。 Docker Model Runner代表了一种变换的容器化解决方案，该解决方案可以推动开发人员创建，部署和扩展使用AI技术的应用程序的变化。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文将涵盖该技术如何弥合数据科学测试阶段与现成AI系统的部署之间的差距。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling Mobile App Performance: How We Cut Screen Load Time From 8s to 2s】缩放移动应用程序性能：我们如何将屏幕加载时间从8s缩短到2s</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cutting-screen-load-time</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;User experience is king in the crowd-sourced world of mobile app development, especially in the case of speed. If your app takes too long to load, those same users will bypass your app in favour of a speedy, seamless offering.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When we realized that our app was taking a frustrating 8 seconds to load some screens, this was a hard reality for us to accept. With the competition being fierce and users becoming more and more impatient, we knew something had to change. Read this article as we detail our path from an 8-second screen load time to under 2 seconds, all with a combined multi-sided attack on mobile optimization.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;用户体验是在移动应用程序开发的众包世界中，尤其是在速度的情况下。如果您的应用程序花费太长的加载，那么相同的用户将绕过您的应用程序，而有利于快速，无缝的产品。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;当我们意识到我们的应用程序正在花8秒钟来加载一些屏幕时，这对我们来说是一个很难接受的现实。随着竞争激烈，用户变得越来越不耐烦，我们知道必须改变一些事情。在我们详细介绍从8秒的屏幕加载时间到不到2秒的路径时，请阅读本文，所有这些都对移动优化进行了组合多边攻击。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java’s Next Act: Native Speed for a Cloud-Native World】Java的下一个行为：云原始世界的本地速度</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-native-speed-cloud-native-future</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Once the unshakable king of enterprise development, Java is now facing its most important existential moment since its creation. &lt;strong&gt;It’s not that Java has failed&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;strong&gt; it’s that the world around it has changed&lt;/strong&gt;. And Java, with its traditional runtime model and heavyweight architecture, hasn’t always kept up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In a cloud-native world where agility, speed, and efficiency matter more than ever, traditional Java stacks often struggle. They’re too slow to start, too heavy on memory, and too rigid for the ephemeral, elastic environments of today’s infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;曾经是企业发展的不可动摇的国王，Java现在正面临其创造以来最重要的生存时刻。 &lt;strong&gt;并不是说Java失败了&lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;周围的世界已经改变了&lt;/strong&gt;。 Java凭借其传统的运行时模型和重量级体系结构一直保持不变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在一个云端的世界中，敏捷性，速度和效率比以往任何时候都重要，传统的Java堆栈经常挣扎。它们太慢了，无法开始，在记忆上太重，对于当今基础设施的短暂，弹性环境来说太僵硬了。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Setting Up Data Pipelines With Snowflake Dynamic Tables】使用雪花动态表设置数据管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-dynamic-tables-data-pipelines</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This guide walks through the steps to set up a data pipeline specifically for near-real-time or event-driven data architectures and continuously evolving needs. This guide covers each step, from setup to data ingestion, to the different layers of the data platform, and deployment and monitoring, to help manage large-scale applications effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;1&#34; type=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Expertise in basic and complex SQL for scripting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Experience with maintaining data pipelines and orchestration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Access to a Snowflake for deployment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Knowledge of ETL frameworks for efficient design&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data pipeline workloads are an integral part of today’s world, and maintaining these workloads needs massive effort, and it&#39;s cumbersome. A solution is provided within Snowflake, which is called dynamic tables. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本指南将详细介绍针对近实时或事件驱动的数据架构以及不断发展的需求的专门设置数据管道的步骤。本指南涵盖了从设置到数据摄入到数据平台的不同层的每个步骤，以及部署和监视，以帮助有效地管理大规模应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;先决条件&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start =“ 1” type =“ 1”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;基本和复杂SQL的专业知识用于脚本&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;维护数据管道和编排的经验&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;进入部署的雪花&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;有效设计的ETL框架的知识&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据管道工作负载是当今世界不可或缺的一部分，维持这些工作量需要巨大的努力，而且很麻烦。在雪花中提供了一个解决方案，这称为动态表。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>