<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Decoding DORA: EU&#39;s Unified Approach to ICT Risk Governance】解读 DORA：欧盟 ICT 风险治理统一方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-dora</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;As financial services become increasingly digitized, the need for robust operational resilience has grown more critical. The Digital Operational Resilience Act (DORA), set to take effect on January 17, 2025, aims to establish a unified framework for Information and Communication Technology (ICT) risk management across the European Union&#39;s financial sector. This new regulation will significantly impact how banks, insurers, and other financial entities approach their digital risks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DORA represents an important step in regulatory evolution, designed to address the growing complexities of the digital financial landscape. But what does this mean for financial institutions? And how can organizations prepare for this shift in regulatory expectations?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;随着金融服务日益数字化，对强大的运营弹性的需求变得更加重要。 《数字运营弹性法案》(DORA) 将于 2025 年 1 月 17 日生效，旨在为整个欧盟金融部门的信息和通信技术 (ICT) 风险管理建立统一框架。这项新法规将极大地影响银行、保险公司和其他金融实体应对数字风险的方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DORA 代表了监管演变的重要一步，旨在解决数字金融领域日益复杂的问题。但这对金融机构意味着什么呢？组织如何为监管期望的这种转变做好准备？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【CI/CD Pipelines in the Cloud: How Cloud Hosting Is Accelerating Software Delivery】云中的 CI/CD 管道：云托管如何加速软件交付</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cicd-pipelines-in-the-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the fast-evolving world of software engineering, one of the most transformative innovations is the combination of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-ci-cd&#34;&gt;Continuous Integration (CI) and Continuous Deployment (CD)&lt;/a&gt; pipelines with cloud hosting. This powerful integration has revolutionized the way developers deploy, test, and update software, allowing for faster delivery, improved scalability, and enhanced collaboration. By utilizing cloud hosting platforms, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-a-site-reliability-engineer-is-important-to-yo&#34;&gt;software engineering teams&lt;/a&gt; can now automate processes that once took weeks, turning them into streamlined workflows. Let’s explore how CI/CD pipelines in the cloud are accelerating software delivery, with insights backed by research and industry trends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Power of CI/CD in Software Engineering&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment (CI/CD) are critical for modern software development, driving automation from code integration to deployment. In traditional settings, deployment often required manual effort, introducing the risk of human error, delays, and inconsistencies. CI/CD pipelines automate these processes, enabling developers to integrate code changes more frequently and deploy updates to production environments seamlessly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在快速发展的软件工程世界中，最具变革性的创新之一是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-ci-cd &#34;&gt;使用云托管进行持续集成 (CI) 和持续部署 (CD)&lt;/a&gt; 管道。这种强大的集成彻底改变了开发人员部署、测试和更新软件的方式，从而实现更快的交付、提高可扩展性并增强协作。通过利用云托管平台，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-a-site-reliability-engineer-is-important-to-yo&#34;&gt;软件工程团队&lt;/a&gt;现在可以实现自动化曾经需要数周时间的流程，现在变成了简化的工作流程。让我们利用研究和行业趋势支持的见解，探讨云中的 CI/CD 管道如何加速软件交付。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;软件工程中 CI/CD 的力量&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;持续集成和持续部署 (CI/CD) 对于现代软件开发至关重要，可推动从代码集成到部署的自动化。在传统环境中，部署通常需要手动操作，从而带来人为错误、延迟和不一致的风险。 CI/CD 管道使这些流程自动化，使开发人员能够更频繁地集成代码更改并将更新无缝部署到生产环境。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What We Learned About Secrets Security at AppSec Village at DEF CON 32】我们在 DEF CON 32 上的 AppSec Village 学到了什么关于秘密安全的知识</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secrets-security-at-appsec-village-at-def-con-32</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you grew up in the US, chances are you have a memory of going to summer camp. Even if you didn&#39;t attend one yourself, the camp experience of going away from home, learning all sorts of arts and crafts, meeting new best friends, and going on memorable adventures is baked into &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Salute_Your_Shorts&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;pop culture&lt;/a&gt; and media. Every August, the largest hacker summer camp on earth takes place in the heat of Las Vegas. This year marked the thirty-second iteration of &lt;a href=&#34;https://defcon.org/html/defcon-32/dc-32-index.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;DEF CON&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DEF CON can be hard to explain without experiencing it. Yes, there are speaking tracks, official workshops, and multiple capture-the-flags (CTFs), but there is so much more. No other conference contains so many sub-conferences and community-led events. Even attendees who have been going for years say they still don&#39;t think they have experienced everything on offer. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您在美国长大，您很可能有参加夏令营的记忆。即使您自己没有参加，远离家乡、学习各种艺术和手工艺、结识新的好朋友以及进行难忘的冒险的营地体验也会融入&lt;a href=&#34;https://en .wikipedia.org/wiki/Salut_Your_Shorts&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;流行文化&lt;/a&gt;和媒体。每年八月，地球上最大的黑客夏令营都会在炎热的拉斯维加斯举行。今年是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://defcon.org/html/defcon-32/dc-32-index.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;DEF CON 的第三十二次迭代&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果没有亲身经历，DEF CON 很难解释。是的，有演讲、官方研讨会和多个夺旗活动 (CTF)，但还有更多。没有其他会议包含如此多的分会议和社区主导的活动。即使已经参加多年的与会者也表示，他们仍然认为自己没有体验到所提供的一切。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hello, K.AI: How I Trained a Chatbot of Myself Without Coding】你好，K.AI：我如何在不编码的情况下训练自己的聊天机器人</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-i-trained-a-chatbot-of-myself-without-coding</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Generative AI (GenAI) enables many new use cases for enterprises and private citizens. While I work on real-time enterprise-scale AI/ML deployments with data streaming, big data analytics, and cloud-native software applications in my daily business life, I also wanted to train a conversational chatbot for myself. This blog post introduces my journey without coding to train K.AI, a personal chatbot that can be used to learn in a conversational pace format about data streaming and the most successful use cases in this area. Yes, this is also based on my expertise, domain knowledge, and opinion, which is available as public internet data, like my hundreds of blog articles, LinkedIn shares, and YouTube videos.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Hi, K.AI: Let&#39;s Chat&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The evolution of Generative AI (GenAI) around OpenAI&#39;s chatbot ChatGPT and many similar large language models (LLM), open source tools like LangChain and SaaS solutions for building a conversational AI led me to the idea of building a chatbot trained with all the content I created over the past years.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;生成式人工智能 (GenAI) 为企业和个人提供了许多新的用例。当我在日常业务生活中使用数据流、大数据分析和云原生软件应用程序进行实时企业级 AI/ML 部署时，我还想为自己训练一个对话聊天机器人。这篇博文介绍了我无需编码即可训练 K.AI 的旅程，K.AI 是一个个人聊天机器人，可用于以对话方式学习数据流以及该领域最成功的用例。是的，这也是基于我的专业知识、领域知识和观点，这些可以作为公共互联网数据获取，例如我的数百篇博客文章、LinkedIn 分享和 YouTube 视频。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;嗨，K.AI：我们来聊聊&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;围绕 OpenAI 聊天机器人 ChatGPT 和许多类似的大型语言模型 (LLM)、LangChain 等开源工具以及用于构建对话式 AI 的 SaaS 解决方案的生成式 AI (GenAI) 的发展，让我产生了构建一个接受所有训练的聊天机器人的想法。我在过去几年中创建的内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Set up OAuth JWT Flow and mTLS in the Salesforce Connector for a MuleSoft App】如何在 MuleSoft 应用程序的 Salesforce 连接器中设置 OAuth JWT 流和 mTLS</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/set-up-oauth-jwt-flow-and-mtls-in-salesforce</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-original-attrs=&#34;{&amp;quot;style&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;}&#34;&gt;In the &lt;a data-original-attrs=&#34;{&amp;quot;data-original-href&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://mulegon.blogspot.com/2024/07/how-to-setup-oauth-jwt-in-salesforce.html&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;style&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;target&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;}&#34; href=&#34;https://www.blogger.com/blog/post/edit/2363231060218855319/793948230180576969?hl=en-GB#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-setup-oauth-jwt-in-the-salesforce-connector&#34;&gt;first part of this series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;u&gt;,&lt;/u&gt; we set up a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-mule&#34;&gt;Mule&lt;/a&gt; app and a Salesforce Connected app for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identify-the-relevant-salesforce-authentication-fl&#34;&gt;OAuth JWT bearer token flow&lt;/a&gt;. In this second part, we’ll go through the required steps to set up mutual TLS between the Mule app and the Salesforce Connected App we created in that first post.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-original-attrs=&#34;{&amp;quot;style&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Create a New Profile in Salesforce for mTLS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul data-original-attrs=&#34;{&amp;quot;style&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;}&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-original-attrs=&#34;{&amp;quot;aria-level&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;style&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If the Profile you used in Part 1 of this guide (linked earlier) is the definitive one that you’ll use for this Mule app, skip this step.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-original-attrs=&#34;{&amp;quot;aria-level&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;style&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Go to &lt;strong&gt;Setup&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Profiles&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-original-attrs=&#34;{&amp;quot;aria-level&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;style&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Click on &lt;strong&gt;New Profile&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-original-attrs=&#34;{&amp;quot;role&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;presentation&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;style&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;img width=&#34;624&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;144.6 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1723456140455&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;08/12/2024 09:49 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17850028-1723456139480.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;144626&#34; data-name=&#34;1723456139480.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17850028&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17850028-1723456139480.png&#34; style=&#34;width: 808px; height: 477.808px;&#34; alt=&#34;Click on New Profile&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-original-attrs=&#34;{&#34;style&#34;:&#34;&#34;}&#34;&gt;在&lt;a data-original-attrs=&#34;{&#34;data-original-href&#34;:&#34;https://mulegon.blogspot.com/ 2024/07/how-to-setup-oauth-jwt-in-salesforce.html&#34;,&#34;style&#34;:&#34;&#34;,&#34;target&#34;:&#34;_blank&#34;}&#34; href=&#34;https://www.blogger.com/ blog/post/edit/2363231060218855319/793948230180576969?hl=en-GB#&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-setup-oauth-jwt-in-the -salesforce-connector&#34;&gt;本系列的第一部分&lt;/a&gt;&lt;u&gt;，&lt;/u&gt;我们设置了一个&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-mule&#34;&gt;Mule&lt;/ a&gt; 应用程序和用于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identify-the-relevant-salesforce-authentication-fl&#34;&gt;OAuth JWT 不记名令牌流&lt;/a&gt;的 Salesforce Connected 应用程序。在第二部分中，我们将完成在 Mule 应用程序和我们在第一篇文章中创建的 Salesforce Connected 应用程序之间设置相互 TLS 所需的步骤。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-original-attrs=&#34;{&#34;style&#34;:&#34;&#34;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在 Salesforce 中为 mTLS 创建新配置文件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul data-original-attrs=&#34;{&#34;style&#34;:&#34;&#34;}&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-original-attrs=&#34;{&#34;aria-level&#34;:&#34;1&#34;,&#34;style&#34;:&#34;&#34;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果您在本指南第 1 部分（之前链接）中使用的配置文件是如果您将用于此 Mule 应用程序，请跳过此步骤。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-original-attrs=&#34;{&#34;aria-level&#34;:&#34;1&#34;,&#34;style&#34;:&#34;&#34;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;转至&lt;strong&gt;设置&lt;/strong&gt; &gt; &lt;strong&gt;配置文件&lt; /strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-original-attrs=&#34;{&#34;aria-level&#34;:&#34;1&#34;,&#34;style&#34;:&#34;&#34;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;点击&lt;strong&gt;新建个人资料&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-original-attrs=&#34;{&#34;role&#34;:&#34;presentation&#34;,&#34;style&#34;:&#34;&#34;}&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;img width=&#34;624&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib 延迟加载&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;144.6 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1723456140455&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;08/12/2024 09:上午 49 点&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17850028-1723456139480.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;144626&#34; 数据-name=&#34;1723456139480.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17850028&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17850028-1723456139480.png&#34; style=&#34;宽度：808px；高度：477.808像素；” alt=&#34;点击新个人资料&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Serverless Computing and GraphQL: Modern App Development】无服务器计算和 GraphQL：现代应用程序开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-computing-and-graphql</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will guide you through the process of creating a serverless GraphQL API using TypeScript, AWS Lambda, and Apollo Server.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serverless Computing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Serverless computing is a cloud-computing execution model where cloud providers automatically manage the infrastructure for running applications. In this model, developers write code, and the cloud provider takes care of running, scaling, and maintaining the servers, meaning developers don&#39;t need to worry about server management, infrastructure provisioning, or scaling. The term &#34;serverless&#34; doesn&#39;t mean that there are no servers involved, but rather that the server management tasks are abstracted away from developers. &lt;strong&gt;AWS Lambda&lt;/strong&gt; is a serverless compute service provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS) that allows you to run code without provisioning or managing servers&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将指导您完成使用 TypeScript、AWS Lambda 和 Apollo Server 创建无服务器 GraphQL API 的过程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;无服务器计算&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无服务器计算是一种云计算执行模型，云提供商自动管理运行应用程序的基础设施。在此模型中，开发人员编写代码，云提供商负责运行、扩展和维护服务器，这意味着开发人员无需担心服务器管理、基础设施配置或扩展。术语“无服务器”并不意味着不涉及服务器，而是将服务器管理任务从开发人员中抽象出来。 &lt;strong&gt;AWS Lambda&lt;/strong&gt; 是 Amazon Web Services (AWS) 提供的无服务器计算服务，允许您在不预置或管理服务器的情况下运行代码&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Amazon Redshift Workload Management (WLM): A Step-by-Step Guide】Amazon Redshift 工作负载管理 (WLM)：分步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/amazon-redshift-workload-management-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-article-id=&#34;2001957&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;As a database administrator or data engineer working with Amazon Redshift, it&#39;s crucial to manage resources effectively to handle different workloads. Amazon Redshift&#39;s Workload Management (WLM) feature lets you define how queries are prioritized and how resources like CPU and memory are allocated. This guide will walk you through setting up WLM step by step, making it easy for newbies to get started.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;what-is-workload-management-wlm&#34; href=&#34;https://dev.to/arvind_toorpu/amazon-redshift-workload-management-wlm-a-step-by-step-guide-145o#what-is-workload-management-wlm&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;What Is Workload Management (WLM)?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;WLM allows Amazon Redshift to handle multiple concurrent queries by allocating resources to query queues. You can create custom queues, allocate memory, and set concurrency limits for specific workloads, ensuring that critical queries run efficiently even under heavy loads.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-article-id=&#34;2001957&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;作为使用 Amazon Redshift 的数据库管理员或数据工程师，有效管理资源以处理不同的工作负载至关重要。 Amazon Redshift 的工作负载管理 (WLM) 功能可让您定义如何确定查询的优先级以及如何分配 CPU 和内存等资源。本指南将引导您逐步设置 WLM，使新手能够轻松上手。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;what-is-workload-management-wlm&#34; href=&#34;https://dev.to/arvind_toorpu/amazon-redshift-workload-management-wlm-a-step-by-step-guide -145o#what-is-workload-management-wlm&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;什么是工作负载管理 (WLM)？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;WLM 允许 Amazon Redshift 通过向查询队列分配资源来处理多个并发查询。您可以创建自定义队列、分配内存并为特定工作负载设置并发限制，确保关键查询即使在重负载下也能高效运行。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 19:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Writing Great Code: The Five Principles of Clean Code】编写出色的代码：干净代码的五个原则</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/five-principles-of-clean-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;One of the finest ways to make the code easy to read, maintain, and improve can be done by &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/clean-code-tips&#34;&gt;writing clean code&lt;/a&gt;. Clean code helps to reduce errors, improves the code quality of the project, and makes other developers and future teams understand and work with the code. The well-organized code reduces mistakes and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-engineers-complete-guide-to-technical-debt&#34;&gt;maintenance a lot easier&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Use Meaningful Names&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Clean code should have meaningful names that describe the purpose of variables, functions, and classes. The name itself should convey what the code does. So, anyone who is reading it can understand its purpose without referring to any additional documentation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;使代码易于阅读、维护和改进的最佳方法之一可以通过 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/clean 来完成-code-tips&#34;&gt;编写干净的代码&lt;/a&gt;。干净的代码有助于减少错误，提高项目的代码质量，并使其他开发人员和未来的团队理解并使用代码。组织良好的代码减少了错误，并且&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-engineers-complete-guide-to-technical-debt&#34;&gt;维护更加容易&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p &gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.使用有意义的名称&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;干净的代码应该有有意义的名称来描述变量、函数和类的用途。名称本身应该传达代码的作用。因此，任何阅读它的人都可以理解其目的，而无需参考任何其他文档。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Battle of Data: Statistics vs Machine Learning】数据之战：统计与机器学习</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-battle-of-data-statistics-vs-machine-learning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The goal of the paper is to investigate the fields of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-guide-to-math-and-statistics-for-data-s&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;statistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;m&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;achine learning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and look at the differences, similarities, usage, and ways of analyzing data in these two branches. Both branches of science allow interpreting data, however, they are based on different pillars: statistics on mathematics and the other on computer science – the focus of machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence together with machine learning is presently the technologically advanced means of extracting useful information from the raw data that is changing every day around us. On the contrary, statistics — a very old field of research of over 3 centuries — has always been regarded as a core discipline for the interpretation of the collected data and decision-making. Even though both of them share one goal of studying data, how the goal is achieved and where the focus is varies in statistics and machine learning.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本文的目标是研究&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-guide-to-math-and-statistics-for-data-s&#34;&gt;领域&lt;strong&gt;统计数据&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;m&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;机器学习&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;并研究这两个分支的差异、相似之处、用法和分析数据的方法。这两个科学分支都允许解释数据，但是它们基于不同的支柱：数学统计和计算机科学（机器学习的重点）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能与机器学习相结合是目前技术先进的手段，可以从我们周围每天都在变化的原始数据中提取有用的信息。相反，统计学——一个拥有三个多世纪历史的非常古老的研究领域——一直被视为解释收集的数据和决策的核心学科。尽管两者都有一个研究数据的目标，但统计学和机器学习如何实现这一目标以及侧重点各不相同。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 20:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unleashing the Power of Gemini With LlamaIndex】通过 LlamaIndex 释放 Gemini 的力量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unleashing-the-power-of-gemini-with-llamaindex</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large language models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ditl-of-a-developer-with-google-gemini-code-assist-pt1&#34;&gt;Google&#39;s Gemini&lt;/a&gt; are revolutionizing how we interact with information, but harnessing their power for your own applications can seem daunting. That&#39;s where LlamaIndex comes in, providing a simple yet powerful framework to leverage LLMs like Gemini.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This tutorial will guide you through a practical example, using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-python&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; code snippet as a starting point, to demonstrate how to seamlessly integrate Gemini&#39;s LLM and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-guide-to-vector-embeddings-for-product-and-softw&#34;&gt;embedding capabilities&lt;/a&gt; into your projects using LlamaIndex.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/a&gt; 例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https:// /dzone.com/articles/ditl-of-a-developer-with-google-gemini-code-assist-pt1&#34;&gt;Google 的 Gemini&lt;/a&gt; 正在彻底改变我们与信息交互的方式，同时将其力量用于您自己的应用程序看起来令人畏惧。这就是 LlamaIndex 的用武之地，它提供了一个简单而强大的框架来利用 Gemini 等法学硕士。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本教程将指导您通过一个实际示例，使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-python&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; 代码片段作为起点，演示如何使用 Gemini 的 LLM 和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-guide-to-vector-embeddings-for-product-and-softw&#34;&gt;嵌入功能&lt;/a&gt;将其无缝集成到您的项目中骆驼指数。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 12:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>