<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Stop Writing Excel Specs: A Markdown-First Approach to Enterprise Java】停止编写 Excel 规范：Markdown 优先的 Enterprise Java 方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/stop-writing-excel-specs-markdown-first-approach</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Design documents in Enterprise Java often end up trapped in binary silos like Excel or Word, causing them to drift away from the actual code. This pattern shows how to treat Design Docs as source code by using structured &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/writing-in-markdown-an-introduction&#34;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-generative-text-ai&#34;&gt;generative AI&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve all been there: the architecture team delivers a &lt;strong&gt;Detailed Design Document (DDD)&lt;/strong&gt; to the development team. It’s a 50-page Word file, even worse, a massive Excel spreadsheet with multiple tabs defining Java classes, fields, and validation rules.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Enterprise Java 中的设计文档通常最终会陷入 Excel 或 Word 等二进制孤岛中，导致它们偏离实际代码。此模式展示了如何使用结构化 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/writing-in-markdown-an-introduction&#34;&gt;Markdown&lt;/a&gt; 和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-generative-text-ai&#34;&gt;生成式 AI&lt;/a&gt; 将设计文档视为源代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们都经历过这样的情况：架构团队向开发团队交付&lt;strong&gt;详细设计文档 (DDD)&lt;/strong&gt;。这是一个 50 页的 Word 文件，更糟糕的是，这是一个巨大的 Excel 电子表格，其中包含多个定义 Java 类、字段和验证规则的选项卡。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reproducible SadTalker Pipeline in Google Colab for Single-Image, Single-Audio Talking-Head Generation】Google Colab 中可重现的 SadTalker 管道，用于生成单图像、单音频头部说话</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/reproducible-sadtalker-pipeline-google-colab</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever wanted to bring a still photo to life using nothing more than an audio clip, &lt;a href=&#34;https://sadtalkerai.com/sadtalker-google-colab/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SadTalker&lt;/a&gt; makes it surprisingly easy once it&#39;s set up correctly. Running it locally can be tricky because of GPU drivers, missing dependencies, and environment mismatches, so this guide walks you through a clean, reliable setup in Google Colab instead.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The goal is simple&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;a fully reproducible, copy-and-paste workflow that lets you upload a single image and a single audio file, then generate a talking-head video without spending hours troubleshooting your system.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您想仅使用音频剪辑就可以让静态照片栩栩如生，&lt;a href=&#34;https://sadtalkerai.com/sadtalker-google-colab/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SadTalker&lt;/a&gt; 一旦设置正确，它就会变得异常简单。由于 GPU 驱动程序、缺少依赖项和环境不匹配，在本地运行它可能会很棘手，因此本指南将引导您在 Google Colab 中完成干净、可靠的设置。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;目标很简单&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;完全可复制的复制粘贴工作流程，让您可以上传单个图像和单个音频文件，然后生成头部说话视频，而无需花费数小时对系统进行故障排除。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Engineering Evidence‑Grounded Review Pipelines With Hybrid RAG and LLMs】混合 RAG 和法学硕士的工程证据审查流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/engineering-evidence-review-pipelines-with-hybrid</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Unchecked language generation is not a harmless bug — it is a costly liability in regulated domains.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;A single invented citation in a visa evaluation can derail an application and triggering months of appeal.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;A hallucinated clause in a compliance report can result in penalties.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;A fabricated reference in a clinical review can jeopardize patient safety.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-large-language-models-and-how-they-work&#34;&gt;Large language models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; are not “broken”; they are simply &lt;strong&gt;unaccountable&lt;/strong&gt;. Retrieval‑augmented generation (RAG) helps, but standard RAG remains brittle:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;未经检查的语言生成并不是一个无害的错误 - 它是受监管领域中代价高昂的责任。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;签证评估中的一次虚构引文可能会导致申请失败并引发数月的上诉。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;合规报告中的幻想条款可能会导致处罚。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;临床审查中伪造的参考资料可能会危及患者安全。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-large-language-models-and-how-they-work&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/a&gt; 并未“损坏”；他们简直&lt;strong&gt;不负责任&lt;/strong&gt;。检索增强生成 (RAG) 有所帮助，但标准 RAG 仍然很脆弱：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MCP Elicitation: Human-in-the-Loop for MCP Servers】MCP 启发：MCP 服务器的人机交互</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mcp-elicitation-human-in-the-loop-for-mcp-servers</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;What Is MCP&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-to-do-app-with-mcp&#34;&gt;Model Context Protocol&lt;/a&gt; (MCP) is an open standard developed by Anthropic that enables large language models (LLMs) to receive data from any backend or application in a single, standardized format. Prior to the introduction of MCP, developers working on agent-based AI systems had to rely on custom tools and logic to connect with the APIs of various third-party applications. This process was often tedious and didn&#39;t scale effectively, as every integration had to be manually built and maintained by the developers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With MCP, this responsibility has shifted: application developers can now expose their APIs in a unified format that most models and agent frameworks can easily understand right from the outset.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;什么是MCP&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-to-do-app-with-mcp&#34;&gt;模型上下文协议&lt;/a&gt; (MCP) 是 Anthropic 开发的开放标准，使大型语言模型 (LLM) 能够以单一标准化格式从任何后端或应用程序接收数据。在引入 MCP 之前，开发基于代理的 AI 系统的开发人员必须依赖自定义工具和逻辑来连接各种第三方应用程序的 API。这个过程通常很乏味，并且无法有效扩展，因为每个集成都必须由开发人员手动构建和维护。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过 MCP，这种责任发生了转变：应用程序开发人员现在可以以统一的格式公开其 API，大多数模型和代理框架从一开始就可以轻松理解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Privacy-Preserving ML for CRM Systems With Federated Learning】通过联邦学习为 CRM 系统构建隐私保护的机器学习</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/privacy-preserving-ml-crm-federated-learning</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Problem: Training Models on Distributed Data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When creating ML models for lead scoring, customer data is often stored in CRM systems across the EU, the US, and APAC. Because the GDPR prohibits moving EU data to central servers and violations are costly, traditional approaches are ineffective.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul type=&#34;disc&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Centralized training&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Violates data residency laws&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Separate regional models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Poor performance, no cross-regional learning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Data replication&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;: Compliance nightmare&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/federated-learning-training-models-without-sharing&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Federated learning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; addresses this by training models in each region and sharing only updates to the model, not the raw data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;问题：分布式数据训练模型&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;创建用于潜在客户评分的机器学习模型时，客户数据通常存储在欧盟、美国和亚太地区的 CRM 系统中。由于 GDPR 禁止将欧盟数据转移到中央服务器，而且违规成本高昂，因此传统方法无效。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul类型=“光盘”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;集中培训&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;：违反数据驻留法&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;单独的区域模型&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;：性能较差，没有跨区域学习&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;数据复制&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;：合规噩梦&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/federated-learning-training-models-without-sharing&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;联邦学习&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;通过在每个区域训练模型并仅共享模型更新而不共享原始数据来解决此问题。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Zero Trust on Google Cloud】在 Google Cloud 上实施零信任</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-zero-trust-google-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Cybersecurity now requires more than just perimeter defences. As you adopt microservices, hybrid workloads, and AI pipelines on Google Cloud, identity becomes your new perimeter. Zero Trust means never trust and always verify. It is no longer optional but essential.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article guides you on implementing zero trust with Google Cloud Platform. You will learn how to use strong &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identity-and-access-management-best-practices-for&#34;&gt;identity and access management strategies&lt;/a&gt;. The focus is on practical advice for modern DevSecOps teams using the latest GCP tools.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;网络安全现在需要的不仅仅是外围防御。当您在 Google Cloud 上采用微服务、混合工作负载和 AI 管道时，身份将成为您的新边界。零信任意味着从不信任并始终验证。它不再是可选的而是必需的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文将指导您如何使用 Google Cloud Platform 实现零信任。您将学习如何使用强大的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identity-and-access-management-best-practices-for&#34;&gt;身份和访问管理策略&lt;/a&gt;。重点是为使用最新 GCP 工具的现代 DevSecOps 团队提供实用建议。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Green AI: Lessons in GPU Efficiency From the Trenches】构建绿色人工智能：GPU 效率的实践经验教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/green-ai-gpu-efficiency-lessons</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;1177&#34; data-start=&#34;1127&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1177&#34; data-start=&#34;1131&#34;&gt;The Real Problem With Modern Deep Learning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1350&#34; data-start=&#34;1179&#34;&gt;Let’s be honest — we all love scaling. Bigger models, more GPUs, larger clusters. But here’s what we found in production: most GPU time isn’t spent doing useful work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1516&#34; data-start=&#34;1352&#34;&gt;Even when the utilization graph says “busy,” your &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/nvidia-gpu-operator-explained-simplifying-gpu-work&#34;&gt;GPUs&lt;/a&gt; might be sitting idle waiting for data. The issue isn’t the hardware — it’s inefficiency across three fronts:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;1177&#34; data-start=&#34;1127&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1177&#34; data-start=&#34;1131&#34;&gt;现代深度学习的真正问题&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1350&#34; data-start=&#34;1179&#34;&gt;说实话，我们都喜欢扩展。更大的模型、更多的 GPU、更大的集群。但我们在生产中发现：大多数 GPU 时间都没有花在做有用的工作上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1516&#34; data-start=&#34;1352&#34;&gt;即使利用率图表显示“忙”，您的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/nvidia-gpu-operator-explained-simplifying-gpu-work&#34;&gt;GPU&lt;/a&gt; 也可能处于空闲状态等待数据。问题不在于硬件，而在于三个方面的低效率：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【WebAssembly Is Eating the Cloud: Why Devs Should Care】WebAssembly 正在吞噬云：为什么开发人员应该关心</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/webassembly-is-eating-the-cloud-why-devs-should-ca</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Remember when WebAssembly (Wasm) was just that thing you&#39;d use to squeeze extra performance out of web apps? Those days are over. WebAssembly&#39;s jumped the fence and is now quietly reshaping the entire cloud infrastructure landscape. Most developers I talk to are still treating it like a nice-to-have browser feature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Big mistake.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;还记得 WebAssembly (Wasm) 只是用来从 Web 应用程序中榨取额外性能的东西吗？那些日子已经结束了。 WebAssembly 已经跨越了界限，现在正在悄然重塑整个云基础设施格局。与我交谈过的大多数开发人员仍然将其视为一项可有可无的浏览器功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大错误。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Web App Load Testing Using Maven Plugins for Apache JMeter, and Analyzing the Results】使用 Apache JMeter 的 Maven 插件进行 Web 应用程序负载测试并分析结果</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/running-load-test-web-app-using-maven-plugins</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will walk you through how to conduct a &lt;strong&gt;load test&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;analyze&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;the results using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-create-a-java-library-from-scratch-to-maven&#34;&gt;Java Maven&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;technology. We&#39;ll covering everything from launching the test to generating informative graphs and tables.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For this demonstration, we&#39;ll utilize various files, including Project Object Model (POM) files, JMeters scripts, and CSV data, from the &lt;strong&gt;jpetstore_loadtesting_dzone&lt;/strong&gt; project available on GitHub. This will help illustrate the steps involved and the functionality of the necessary plugins and tools. You can find the project here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vdaburon/jpetstore_loadtesting_dzone&#34;&gt;https://github.com/vdaburon/jpetstore_loadtesting_dzone&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将引导您了解如何使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-create-a-java-library-from-scratch-to-maven&#34;&gt;Java Maven&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;技术进行&lt;strong&gt;负载测试&lt;/strong&gt;并&lt;strong&gt;分析结果&lt;/strong&gt;。我们将涵盖从启动测试到生成信息图表和表格的所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本演示中，我们将使用来自 GitHub 上的 &lt;strong&gt;jpetstore_loadtesting_dzone&lt;/strong&gt; 项目的各种文件，包括项目对象模型 (POM) 文件、JMeters 脚本和 CSV 数据。这将有助于说明所涉及的步骤以及必要插件和工具的功能。您可以在这里找到该项目：&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vdaburon/jpetstore_loadtesting_dzone&#34;&gt;https://github.com/vdaburon/jpetstore_loadtesting_dzone&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Apache Phoenix With Variable-Length Encoded Data】具有可变长度编码数据的 Apache Phoenix</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/apache-phoenix-variable-length-encoded-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;602&#34; data-start=&#34;266&#34;&gt;Apache Phoenix is an open-source, SQL skin over &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/hbase&#34;&gt;Apache HBase&lt;/a&gt; that enables lightning-fast OLTP (Online Transactional Processing) operations on petabytes of data using standard SQL queries. Phoenix helps combine the scalability of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/embracing-nosql-the-future-of-data-storage&#34;&gt;NoSQL&lt;/a&gt; with the familiarity and power of SQL. By supporting large-scale aggregate and non-aggregate functionality, Phoenix has evolved into an OLTP and OLAP (Online Analytical Processing) database. This makes it a compelling choice for organizations looking to combine real-time data processing with complex analytical querying in a single, unified system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Phoenix supports several variable-length data types:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;602&#34; data-start=&#34;266&#34;&gt;Apache Phoenix 是一个基于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/hbase&#34;&gt;Apache HBase&lt;/a&gt; 的开源 SQL 皮肤，可使用标准 SQL 查询对 PB 级数据进行闪电般快速的 OLTP（在线事务处理）操作。 Phoenix 有助于将 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/embracing-nosql-the-future-of-data-storage&#34;&gt;NoSQL&lt;/a&gt; 的可扩展性与 SQL 的熟悉性和强大功能结合起来。通过支持大规模聚合和非聚合功能，Phoenix 已发展成为 OLTP 和 OLAP（在线分析处理）数据库。对于希望在单个统一系统中将实时数据处理与复杂分析查询相结合的组织来说，这使其成为一个令人信服的选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Phoenix 支持多种可变长度数据类型：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>