<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【From Prompt to Running Microservice: ServiceBricks Step-By-Step】从提示到运行微服务：ServiceBricks 一步一步</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/from-prompt-to-running-microservice-servicebricks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservice-architecture-2&#34;&gt;Microservices have become a popular architectural style&lt;/a&gt; for building scalable and modular applications. However, setting up a microservice from scratch can still feel complicated, especially when juggling frameworks, templates, and version support. ServiceBricks aims to simplify this by allowing you to quickly generate fully functional, open-source microservices based on a simple prompt using artificial intelligence and source code generation. In this tutorial, we’ll walk through the entire process — from signing up to running your newly created microservice locally.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;A web browser&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Visual Studio 2022&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1: Register for an Account&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Begin by registering for an account on the ServiceBricks.com website. Once you’ve signed up and logged in, you’ll have access to the platform’s microservice generation features and receive 10 free credits to evaluate the product.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservice-architecture-2&#34;&gt;微服务已成为构建可扩展和模块化应用程序的流行架构风格&lt;/a&gt;。然而，从头开始设置微服务仍然感觉很复杂，尤其是在兼顾框架、模板和版本支持时。 ServiceBricks 旨在简化这一过程，允许您使用人工智能和源代码生成，根据简单的提示快速生成功能齐全的开源微服务。在本教程中，我们将逐步完成从注册到在本地运行新创建的微服务的整个过程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;开始使用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;先决条件&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;网络浏览器&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Visual Studio 2022&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 1 步：注册帐户&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先在 ServiceBricks.com 网站上注册一个帐户。注册并登录后，您将可以使用该平台的微服务生成功能，并获得 10 个免费积分来评估产品。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring Binary Quantization in Vector Databases】探索矢量数据库中的二进制量化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-binary-quantization-in-vector-databases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Vector databases are specialized systems designed to handle the storage and retrieval of high-dimensional vector representations of unstructured, complex data — like images, text, or audio. By representing complex data as numerical vectors, these systems understand context and conceptual similarity, providing noticeably similar results to queries rather than exact matches, which enables advanced data analysis and retrieval.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the volume of data in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/vector-database-for-llms-generative-ai-and-deep-le&#34;&gt;vector databases&lt;/a&gt; increases, storing and retrieving information becomes increasingly challenging. Binary quantization simplifies high-dimensional vectors into compact binary codes, reducing data size and enhancing retrieval speed. This approach improves storage efficiency and enables faster searches, allowing databases to manage larger datasets more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;矢量数据库是专门的系统，旨在处理非结构化、复杂数据（例如图像、文本或音频）的高维矢量表示的存储和检索。通过将复杂数据表示为数值向量，这些系统可以理解上下文和概念相似性，为查询提供明显相似的结果，而不是完全匹配，从而实现高级数据分析和检索。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/vector-database-for-llms-generative-ai-and-deep-le&#34;&gt;矢量数据库&lt;/a&gt;中数据量的增加，存储和检索信息变得越来越具有挑战性。二进制量化将高维向量简化为紧凑的二进制代码，减少了数据大小并提高了检索速度。这种方法提高了存储效率并实现了更快的搜索，从而使数据库能够更有效地管理更大的数据集。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Ethical AI: Practical Techniques for Aligning AI Agents With Human Values】实施道德人工智能：使人工智能代理与人类价值观保持一致的实用技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-ethical-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI is now common in all software development lifecycles, particularly in application design, testing, and deployment. However, the growing presence of such systems necessitates ensuring that they serve instead of acting against human values. Misalignment of Artificial Intelligence Agents could lead to unintended consequences such as ethical breaches, discrimination in decision-making, or abuse of certain capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding AI Alignment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI Alignment, or value alignment, refers to the process or philosophy where the aims of the AI systems are made to be compatible or at least possible to coexist with other human aims and actions. As AI technology continues to develop, AI may turn out to be self-destructive or act against human beings, which makes the need to invest in AI ethics even more pressing.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能现在在所有软件开发生命周期中都很常见，特别是在应用程序设计、测试和部署中。然而，随着此类系统的不断出现，有必要确保它们服务于人类价值观，而不是违背人类价值观。人工智能代理的失调可能会导致意想不到的后果，例如违反道德、决策中的歧视或滥用某些能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;了解 AI 对齐&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能对齐，或价值对齐，是指人工智能系统的目标与其他人类目标和行为兼容或至少可能共存的过程或理念。随着人工智能技术的不断发展，人工智能可能会自我毁灭或反人类，这使得对人工智能伦理的投资变得更加迫切。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transitioning From Postman to Insomnia】从邮递员到失眠症的转变</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/transitioning-from-postman-to-insomnia</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As we move away from using Postman, many of us are transitioning to Insomnia for API testing. In this article, I will share how I’ve set up Insomnia to streamline my own workflow. While Insomnia offers a wide range of capabilities beyond HTTP requests, I focus on using it solely for exercising HTTP requests. I hope this provides a useful reference as you configure your own setups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just to clarify upfront, this isn&#39;t an installation guide. Getting Insomnia installed correctly can be a bit tricky, and I, too, have encountered some challenges during the installation and setup process.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着我们不再使用 Postman，我们中的许多人正在过渡到 Insomnia 进行 API 测试。在本文中，我将分享我如何设置 Insomnia 来简化我自己的工作流程。虽然 Insomnia 提供了 HTTP 请求之外的广泛功能，但我只专注于使用它来执行 HTTP 请求。我希望这可以在您配置自己的设置时提供有用的参考。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;预先澄清一下，这不是安装指南。正确安装 Insomnia 可能有点棘手，我在安装和设置过程中也遇到了一些挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【10+ Essential Visualization Libraries for Svelte Apps in 2024】2024 年 Svelte 应用程序的 10 多个基本可视化库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/10-essential-visualization-libraries-for-svelte-apps-in-2024</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://survey.stackoverflow.co/2024/technology/#1-web-frameworks-and-technologies&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;online survey&lt;/a&gt; conducted in July 2024 by Stack Overflow, Svelte is currently on the list of most popular web frameworks and technologies with the usage score of 6.5%. In 2023, Svelte was rated highly by the respondents, thus winning the title of the second-most admired web framework, and it has been maintaining its leading position ever since.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With Svelte&#39;s ever-growing popularity and the recent major release of Svelte 5, the ecosystem of tools and libraries for solving a wide range of tasks within Svelte applications continues to grow.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;根据 &lt;a href=&#34;https://survey.stackoverflow.co/2024/technology/#1-web-frameworks-and-technologies&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34; _blank&#34;&gt;Stack Overflow 于 2024 年 7 月进行的在线调查&lt;/a&gt;显示，Svelte 目前位列最流行的 Web 框架和技术榜单，使用得分为 6.5%。 2023 年，Svelte 获得了受访者的高度评价，从而赢得了第二大最受赞赏的 Web 框架的称号，并一直保持领先地位。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着 Svelte 的日益普及以及 Svelte 5 最近的主要发布，用于解决 Svelte 应用程序中各种任务的工具和库生态系统不断发展。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Challenges and Solutions in Developing Real-Time Messaging Systems】开发实时消息系统的挑战和解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/developing-real-time-messaging-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Social media networks, service marketplaces, and online shops all rely heavily on real-time messaging. Instant communication is essential for platforms like TaskRabbit, Thumbtack, and a multitude of others. Real-time interactions accelerate growth and foster user engagement, making messaging features pivotal for any business to succeed online.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Yet, building a real-time messaging system is anything but simple. The intricate complexities of creating and successfully integrating said feature imply plenty of underwater rocks, and modern developers are forced to look for effective and highly scalable solutions to this conundrum.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;社交媒体网络、服务市场和在线商店都严重依赖实时消息传递。即时通信对于 TaskRabbit、Thumbtack 和许多其他平台来说至关重要。实时交互可加速增长并促进用户参与，使消息传递功能成为任何企业在线成功的关键。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;然而，构建实时消息传递系统绝非简单。创建和成功集成上述功能的复杂性意味着大量的水下岩石，现代开发人员被迫寻找有效且高度可扩展的解决方案来解决这一难题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating Scalable, Compliant Cloud Data Pipelines in SaaS through AI Integration】通过 AI 集成在 SaaS 中创建可扩展、合规的云数据管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-scalable-compliant-ai-cloud-pipelines-for-saas</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-message-author-role=&#34;assistant&#34; data-message-id=&#34;fd5b840d-0d3d-4ecc-bbc8-3a004c19912f&#34; data-message-model-slug=&#34;gpt-4o-mini&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;Data management is undergoing a rapid transformation and is emerging as a critical factor in distinguishing success within the Software as a Service (SaaS) industry. With the rise of AI, SaaS leaders are increasingly turning to AI-driven solutions to optimize data pipelines, improve operational efficiency, and maintain a competitive edge. However, effectively integrating AI into data systems goes beyond simply adopting the latest technologies. It requires a comprehensive strategy that tackles technical challenges, manages complex real-time data flows, and ensures compliance with regulatory standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article will explore the journey of building a successful AI-powered &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-data-pipeline&#34;&gt;data pipeline&lt;/a&gt; for a SaaS product. We will cover everything from initial conception to full-scale adoption, highlighting the key challenges, best practices, and real-world use cases that can guide SaaS leaders through this critical process.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-message-author-role=&#34;assistant&#34; data-message-id=&#34;fd5b840d-0d3d-4ecc-bbc8-3a004c19912f&#34; data-message-model-slug=&#34;gpt-4o-mini&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34; &gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;数据管理正在经历快速转型，并正在成为软件即服务 (SaaS) 行业取得成功的关键因素。随着人工智能的兴起，SaaS 领导者越来越多地转向人工智能驱动的解决方案来优化数据管道、提高运营效率并保持竞争优势。然而，将人工智能有效地集成到数据系统中不仅仅是采用最新技术。它需要一个全面的策略来应对技术挑战、管理复杂的实时数据流并确保符合监管标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文将探讨构建成功的人工智能驱动的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-data-pipeline&#34;&gt;数据管道&lt; /a&gt; 对于 SaaS 产品。我们将涵盖从最初构想到全面采用的所有内容，重点介绍可指导 SaaS 领导者完成这一关键过程的关键挑战、最佳实践和实际用例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Stress Testing for Resilience in Modern Infrastructure】现代基础设施弹性压力测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/stress-testing-for-resilience-in-modern-infrastructure</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-element_type=&#34;widget&#34; data-id=&#34;7e6d65a&#34; data-widget_type=&#34;heading.default&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;Today, users&#39; expectations of seamless performance mean the system cannot afford downtime or disruption that might turn into losses in revenue and reputation. Therefore, no one can underestimate the role of stress testing in ensuring that the systems are resilient against unfortunate events and failures. Indeed, chaos engineering is an innovation concerning testing infrastructure resilience these days.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;This article discusses chaos engineering and defines what deliberate failures are so that one understands how they are introduced into the test to understand the robustness and adaptability of systems, which is especially useful for companies in building more resilient infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-element_type=&#34;widget&#34; data-id=&#34;7e6d65a&#34; data-widget_type=&#34;heading.default&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;如今，用户对无缝性能的期望意味着系统无法承受可能导致收入和声誉损失的停机或中断。因此，任何人都不能低估压力测试在确保系统能够抵御不幸事件和故障方面的作用。事实上，混沌工程是当今测试基础设施弹性的一项创新。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;本文讨论了混沌工程并定义了什么是故意故障，以便人们了解如何将它们引入测试中以了解系统的稳健性和适应性，这对于构建更具弹性的基础设施的公司特别有用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top 18 Test Automation Trends to Look Out for in 2024 and Beyond】2024 年及以后值得关注的 18 个测试自动化趋势</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/18-test-automation-trends-to-look-out-for-in-2024</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;There are two misconceptions when it comes to testing. One of them is that developers alone can test products to reduce costs. The second is that nothing much has changed since automated testing came into play.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The truth is? The testing industry is evolving by leaps and bounds, and if you don’t invest in testing, the cost of glitches can be extremely high. &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;You may have heard about &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2016/03/17/software-printer-problems-delayed-discovery-of-bangladesh-heist/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Bangladesh Bank,&lt;/a&gt; which was hacked, and $81 million was stolen.&lt;/span&gt; However, they could have easily prevented this if not for a system glitch that interrupted the printing process and made it impossible to detect suspicious transactions in time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在测试方面存在两个误解。其中之一是开发人员可以单独测试产品以降低成本。其次，自从自动化测试开始发挥作用以来，一切都没有发生太大变化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;事实是这样吗？测试行业正在突飞猛进地发展，如果你不投资于测试，出现故障的成本可能会非常高。 &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;您可能听说过&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thestar.com.my/tech/tech-news/2016/03/17/software -printer-problems-delayed-discovery-of-bangladesh-heist/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;孟加拉国银行&lt;/a&gt;遭到黑客攻击，损失 8100 万美元&lt;/span&gt;然而，如果不是系统故障中断了打印过程并导致无法及时检测可疑交易，他们本可以轻松阻止这种情况。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Managing Software Engineering Teams of Artificial Intelligence Developers】管理人工智能开发人员的软件工程团队</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/managing-software-engineering-teams-of-ai-devs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Regardless of its industry, every organization has an AI solution, is working on AI integration, or has a plan for it in its roadmap. While developers are being trained in the various technological skills needed for development, senior leadership must focus on strategies to integrate and align these efforts with the broader organization. In this article, let&#39;s take a step back to examine the entire AI product landscape. We will identify the areas where the organization can add significant customer value, develop the necessary skills among developers, utilize modern AI development tools, and structure teams for greater efficiency.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Generative AI Product Landscape&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The diagram illustrates how the landscape of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;Generative AI&lt;/a&gt; development can be broadly divided into three layers at a high level.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;无论哪个行业，每个组织都有人工智能解决方案，正在致力于人工智能集成，或者在其路线图中有相关计划。虽然开发人员正在接受开发所需的各种技术技能的培训，但高层领导必须关注将这些工作与更广泛的组织整合和协调的策略。在本文中，让我们退后一步来审视整个人工智能产品格局。我们将确定组织可以在哪些领域增加显着的客户价值、培养开发人员必要的技能、利用现代人工智能开发工具以及构建团队以提高效率。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;生成式 AI 产品格局&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;该图展示了&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;生成式 AI&lt;/a&gt; 开发的前景在较高的层次上大致分为三层。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>