<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Using ChartMuseum as a Helm Repository】使用ChartMuseum作为舵库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/using-chartmuseum-as-a-helm-repository</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-deploy-helidon-application-to-kubernetes-wi&#34;&gt;ChartMuseum&lt;/a&gt; is an open-source, self-hosted Helm Chart repository server that enables users to store and manage &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-package-management-with-helm&#34;&gt;Helm charts&lt;/a&gt; efficiently. Helm is the standard package manager for Kubernetes, allowing developers to deploy applications seamlessly. While Helm provides public repositories like Artifact Hub, organizations often require private and secure repositories for managing their Helm charts internally. ChartMuseum fills this gap by offering a lightweight and flexible solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;ChartMuseum provides a robust API that allows users to interact with it programmatically, making it an essential tool for automated &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-need-to-know-about-cicd-pipeline-pa&#34;&gt;CI/CD pipelines&lt;/a&gt;. It is written in Go and can be deployed as a standalone binary, within a container, or as a Kubernetes deployment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;P Data-Selectable-paragraph =“”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-deploy-helidon-helidon-application-to-kubernetes-wi&gt; chartermuseum&gt; ChartMuseum &lt;/a&gt;是一家开放式，开放式的，自宿主的头盔repository Server href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-package-management-with-helm”&gt; helm图表&lt;/a&gt;有效。 Helm是Kubernetes的标准软件包经理，使开发人员可以无缝部署应用程序。赫尔姆（Helm）提供公共存储库，例如Artifact Hub，但组织通常需要私人且安全的存储库来内部管理其Helm图表。 ChartMuseum通过提供轻巧且灵活的解决方案来填补这一空白。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;ChartMuseum provides a robust API that allows users to interact with it programmatically, making it an essential tool for automated &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-need-to-know-about-cicd-pipeline-pa&#34;&gt;CI/CD pipelines&lt;/a&gt;.它是用GO编写的，可以部署为独立二进制，在容器中或Kubernetes部署中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tutorial: RAG at Scale With Vector Databases vs. Lakehouse Architectures】教程：与矢量数据库与Lakehouse Architectures进行大规模抹布</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/tutorial-rag-at-scale-with-vector-databases-vs-lakehouse</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rag-architectures-evolution-simple-to-agentic&#34;&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) is quickly becoming the standard enterprise pattern for deploying &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;large language models&lt;/a&gt; (LLMs). Instead of relying solely on pretraining, RAG enriches prompts with fresh, domain-specific information. The result? More accurate answers, fewer hallucinations, and outputs that enterprises can trust.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But building RAG at enterprise scale is tricky. You’re not embedding a few PDFs anymore—you’re embedding billions of rows from databases, log streams, or knowledge repositories. That leads to a critical architectural question:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/rag-Architectures-evolution-evolution-simple-to-to-gentic”&gt; reterieval-augmented Generatiged &lt;/a&gt;（rag）正在迅速成为用于部署的标准企业模式，用于部署&lt;a href =“语言模型&lt;/a&gt;（LLMS）。 Rag不仅依靠训练训练，而是用新鲜的领域特定信息富含提示。结果？更准确的答案，较少的幻觉和企业可以信任的输出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是在企业量表上建造抹布很棘手。您不再嵌入几个PDF，而是从数据库，日志流或知识存储库中嵌入数十亿行。这导致了一个关键的建筑问题：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Table Statistics in SQL Server: Importance, Performance Impact, and Practical Examples】了解SQL Server中的表统计信息：重要性，性能影响和实际示例</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sql-server-table-statistics-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/indexed-views-in-sql-server&#34;&gt;SQL Server&lt;/a&gt;, table statistics are metadata objects that store information about the data distribution within one or more columns of a table. These statistics are crucial for the query optimizer, which uses them to estimate the number of rows that a query&#39;s predicates will return. This estimation, known as cardinality estimation, is the foundation of a good execution plan. For example, if a query filters on a column with a skewed data distribution (i.e., some values appear much more frequently than others), the optimizer can use statistics to choose a more efficient access method, such as a clustered index scan over a non-clustered index seek, avoiding a costly lookup operation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-sql-server-query-store&#34;&gt;DBA&lt;/a&gt;, I believe keeping statistics up to date is paramount for maintaining optimal query performance. Stale statistics, which don&#39;t accurately reflect changes in the underlying data (e.g., due to frequent &lt;code&gt;INSERT&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;UPDATE&lt;/code&gt;, or &lt;code&gt;DELETE&lt;/code&gt; operations), can lead the optimizer to make poor cardinality estimates. This results in inefficient execution plans that could use more system resources and run longer than necessary. Regularly updating statistics either manually with &lt;code&gt;UPDATE STATISTICS&lt;/code&gt; or by allowing the database engine&#39;s automatic update feature (&lt;code&gt;AUTO_UPDATE_STATISTICS&lt;/code&gt;) to do so ensures the query optimizer has the most accurate information available. This proactive maintenance helps prevent performance degradation and ensures that queries continue to run efficiently as the data in the database evolves.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; in &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/indexed-views-in-sql-server”&gt; sql server &lt;/a&gt;，表统计信息是元数据，它们在表的一个或多个列中存储有关数据分布的信息。这些统计信息对于查询优化器至关重要，该统计数据使用它们来估计查询谓词将返回的行数。该估计称为基数估计，是一个良好的执行计划的基础。例如，如果在具有偏斜的数据分布的列上查询过滤器（即某些值比其他值更频繁），则优化器可以使用统计信息来选择更有效的访问方法，例如在非簇的索引上进行群集索引扫描，避免了昂贵的查找操作。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-sql-server-query-store”&gt; dba &lt;/a&gt;，我相信，保持统计信息保持最新是维持最佳查询性能的至关重要。不准确反映基础数据的变化的过时统计信息（例如，由于频繁&lt;code&gt;插入&lt;/code&gt;，&lt;code&gt;更新&lt;/code&gt;或&lt;code&gt; delete &lt;/code&gt;操作）可以导致优化器来对差的心脏估计进行差。这会导致效率低下的执行计划，这些计划可以使用更多的系统资源并运行的时间比必要的时间更长。定期使用&lt;code&gt;更新统计量统计信息&lt;/code&gt;或允许数据库引擎的自动更新功能（&lt;code&gt; auto_update_statistics &lt;/code&gt;）手动更新统计信息，以确保查询优化器具有最准确的信息。这种主动的维护有助于防止性能下降，并确保随着数据库中的数据的发展，查询继续有效地运行。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Blockchain-Based Authentication: The Future of Secure Identity Verification】基于区块链的身份验证：安全身份验证的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/blockchain-authentication-secure-identity-verification</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Traditional authentication methods — passwords, centralized databases, and third-party identity providers — are plagued by security breaches, identity theft, and data privacy concerns. Blockchain-based authentication offers a decentralized, tamper-proof, and more secure alternative. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this deep dive, we’ll explore: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;传统身份验证方法 - 密码，集中数据库和第三方身份提供者 - 受到安全漏洞，身份盗窃和数据隐私问题的困扰。基于区块链的身份验证提供了分散，防篡改和更安全的替代方案。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这次深度潜水中，我们将探索：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Use Jenkins Effectively With ECS/EKS Cluster】如何通过ECS/EKS群集有效地使用Jenkins</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/use-jenkins-effectively-with-ecseks-cluster</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In modern DevOps workflows, Jenkins is the cornerstone for continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) pipelines. Because of its flexibility and wide-ranging plugins available, it&#39;s indispensable in the automation of build, test, and deployment processes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;On the other hand, AWS provides Elastic Container Service and Elastic &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/services-networking/service/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Service&lt;/a&gt; as powerful managed services for deploying and managing containerized applications. This article explores how Jenkins can be effectively integrated with both ECS and EKS clusters to optimize the CI/CD process.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在现代DevOps工作流程中，Jenkins是连续集成和连续部署（CI/CD）管道的基石。由于其灵活性和广泛的插件可用，因此在构建，测试和部署过程的自动化中是必不可少的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;另一方面，AWS提供弹性容器服务和弹性&lt;a href =“ https://kubernetes.io/docs/docs/conepts/conepts/services-networking/service/service/”申请。本文探讨了如何将Jenkins与EC和EKS簇有效地集成以优化CI/CD过程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Probably Secure: A Look at the Security Concerns of Deterministic vs Probabilistic Systems】可能安全：查看确定性与概率系统的安全问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/security-concerns-deterministic-vs-probabilistic-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Would you rather have determined that you are in fact secure, or are you willing to accept that you are &#34;probably&#34; doing things securely? This might seem like a silly question on the surface, after all, audits don&#39;t work on probability; they work on documented facts. We are in an era of rapidly advancing artificial intelligence-driven applications across our organizations, covering a wide variety of use cases. We all love LLMs. There are numerous benefits to applying AI effectively, but like any technology, if we misapply it, we risk opening the door to new dangers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we further adopt these tools and apply AI in novel ways to our workflows across all departments, it is likely a good idea to take a step back and think through how these systems work, which boils down to most likely getting a correct answer versus repeatedly getting the same expected results based on the same specific inputs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否宁愿确定自己实际上是安全的，还是愿意接受自己“可能”安全地做事？毕竟，这似乎是一个愚蠢的问题，毕竟审计对概率无效。他们从事记录的事实。我们正处于整个组织中迅速推进人工智能驱动的应用程序的时代，涵盖了各种用例。我们都喜欢LLM。有效地应用AI有很多好处，但是像任何技术一样，如果我们误用了，我们可能会打开新危险的大门。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们进一步采用这些工具并以新颖的方式将AI应用于各个部门的工作流程时，最好退后一步，考虑一下这些系统的工作方式，这归结为最有可能获得正确的答案，而不是基于相同的特定投入的反复获得相同的预期结果。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Secure Your Spring Boot Apps Using Keycloak and OIDC】使用KeyCloak和OIDC保护您的Spring Boot应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-spring-boot-apps-keycloak-oidc</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this blog, we will take a closer look at Spring Security, specifically in combination with Keycloak using OpenID Connect, all supported with examples and unit tests. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many applications are supported by means of authentication and authorization. However, it is also something software developers find difficult to grasp. In this blog, Spring Security is introduced, which is Spring&#39;s solution for adding security to your Spring applications. By means of examples and unit tests, you will learn the annotations and Spring classes. The end goal is to set up an application using OpenID Connect in combination with Keycloak. An introduction to OpenID Connect and Keycloak can be found in a &lt;a href=&#34;https://mydeveloperplanet.com/2025/05/28/setup-openid-connect-with-keycloak-a-step-by-step-guide/&#34;&gt;previous blog&lt;/a&gt;. It is advised to read this blog if you are not yet familiar with the concepts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在此博客中，我们将仔细研究Spring Security，特别是使用OpenID Connect结合KeyCloak结合使用，所有这些都由示例和单位测试支持。享受！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过身份验证和授权支持许多应用程序。但是，这也是软件开发人员很难掌握的东西。在此博客中，引入了Spring Security，这是春季解决方案，可为您的春季应用程序添加安全性。通过示例和单位测试，您将学习注释和春季课程。最终目标是与KeyCloak结合使用OpenID Connect设置应用程序。可以在a &lt;a href =“ https://mydeveloperplanet.com/2025/05/05/28/setup-openid-connect-connect-with-keycloak-akeycloak-a-step-byby-step-by-step-guide/”&gt;中找到OpenID Connect和KeyCloak的简介。如果您还不熟悉这些概念，建议阅读此博客。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is Your AI a Psychopath?】您的AI是精神病患者吗？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/is-your-ai-a-psychopath</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The &#34;Whack-A-Mole&#34; Problem: Why We&#39;re Losing the AI Bug War&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You just added the newest LLM to your main product. The demos were excellent, but now the support tickets are coming in fast. The customer service chatbot&#39;s AI is giving strangely passive-aggressive answers. You spend a whole day coming up with a clever meta-prompt to make it more &#34;friendly.&#34; Yes! But a week later, you find out that it&#39;s now &#34;helpfully&#34; making up product features that don&#39;t exist, which confuses many users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You just started the &#34;whack-a-mole&#34; game for fixing AI bugs. Given the structure of the game, the outcome is inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;“ whack-a-mole”问题：为什么我们输掉AI Bug War &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您刚刚将最新的LLM添加到了主要产品中。演示很棒，但是现在支持门票快到了。客户服务聊天机器人的AI给出了奇怪的被动攻击答案。您花了一整天的时间来提出一个聪明的元信息，以使其更加“友好”。是的！但是一周后，您发现它现在“有用”构成了不存在的产品功能，这使许多用户感到困惑。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您刚刚启动了用于修复AI错误的“ whack-a-mole”游戏。鉴于游戏的结构，结果是不可避免的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud Automation Excellence: Terraform, Ansible, and Nomad for Enterprise Architecture】卓越云自动化：Terraform，Ansible和Nomad for Enterprise Architecture</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-automation-excellence-terraform-ansible-amp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Enterprise cloud architecture demands sophisticated orchestration of infrastructure, configuration, and workload management across diverse computing platforms. The traditional approach of manual provisioning and siloed tool adoption has become a bottleneck for organizations seeking cloud-native agility while maintaining operational excellence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores the strategic integration of three complementary automation technologies: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/must-have-terraform-tools&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Terraform&lt;/a&gt; for infrastructure provisioning, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/automation-ansible-ai&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ansible&lt;/a&gt; for configuration management, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.hashicorp.com/nomad&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;HashiCorp Nomad&lt;/a&gt;, which serves as a lightweight workload orchestrator, managing application deployment, scaling, and scheduling across diverse infrastructure environments with minimal operational overhead. Unlike monolithic solutions, this ecosystem approach leverages specialized tools that excel in their respective domains while maintaining platform-agnostic capabilities across AWS, Azure, Google Cloud, IBM Cloud, and hybrid environments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;企业云体系结构需要各种计算平台上基础架构，配置和工作负载管理的复杂编排。对于寻求云本地敏捷性的组织而在保持卓越运营的同时，手动配置和孤立的工具采用的传统方法已成为一种瓶颈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了三种互补自动化技术的战略整合：&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/must-have-terraform-tools” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; terraform &lt;/a&gt;用于基金&lt;/a&gt;用于基金&lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/automation-ansible-ai” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; ansible &lt;/a&gt;用于配置管理，&lt;a href =“ target =“ _ blank”&gt; Hashicorp nomad &lt;/a&gt;，它是轻量化的工作负载编排，在不同的基础架构环境中管理应用程序部署，缩放和调度，而操作最小的高架开销。与整体解决方案不同，这种生态系统方法利用专门的工具，可以在其各自的域中表现出色，同时在AWS，Azure，Google Cloud，IBM Cloud和Hybrid Environments跨保持平台 - 不可能的功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Toward Explainable AI (Part 8): Bridging Theory and Practice—SHAP: Powerful, But Can We Trust It?】迈向可解释的AI（第8部分）：桥接理论和实践 - 划分：强大，但是我们可以相信吗？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/series-toward-explainable-ai-bridging-theory-and-p-7</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Series reminder: This series explores how explainability in AI helps build trust, ensure accountability, and align with real-world needs, from foundational principles to practical use cases.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Previously, in Part VII:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-shap-financial-decision-making&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;SHAP:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bringing Clarity to Financial Decision-Making&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;em&gt;系列提醒：该系列探讨了AI中的解释性如何帮助建立信任，确保问责制并与现实需求保持一致，从基本原理到实际用例。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;em&gt;以前，在第七部分：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-aap-financial-decisial-decisial-decisial-decisial-decisial-making”&gt; &lt;em&gt; shap：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;使财务决策&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>