<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes v1.34: Enabling Smarter Traffic Routing With PreferSameNode and PreferSameZone】Kubernetes v1.34：使用 PreferSameNode 和 PreferSameZone 实现更智能的流量路由</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-traffic-routing-prefersamenode-prefersamezone</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Kubernetes has steadily evolved into an industry standard for container orchestration, powering platforms from small developer clusters to hyperscale AI and data infrastructures. Every new release introduces features that not only make workloads easier to manage but also improve performance, cost efficiency, and resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the v1.34 release, one of the standout enhancements is the introduction of traffic distribution preferences for Kubernetes Services. Specifically:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 已稳步发展成为容器编排的行业标准，为从小型开发人员集群到超大规模人工智能和数据基础设施的平台提供支持。每个新版本都引入了一些功能，这些功能不仅使工作负载更易于管理，而且还提高了性能、成本效率和弹性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在 v1.34 版本中，一项突出的增强功能是引入了 Kubernetes 服务的流量分配首选项。具体来说：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Dashboards: How Autonomous AI Agents Are Redefining Enterprise Analytics】超越仪表板：自主人工智能代理如何重新定义企业分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-autonomous-ai-agents-are-redefining-enterprise-analytics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The field of data analytics is going through the biggest change since business intelligence platforms were first introduced. Agentic AI — &#34;intelligent systems that perceive, reason, plan, and act on their own&#34; — is changing the way businesses get information and make choices. Generative AI only responds to prompts, but agentic systems work on their own, going after complex goals with little human oversight. They also have persistent memory and can adapt to new situations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This change marks a shift from reactive analytics to proactive intelligence. Companies are moving away from static dashboards and manual analysis cycles in favor of self-driving systems that monitor data, find insights, and make decisions. The market is expected to be &lt;a href=&#34;https://market.us/report/agentic-ai-market/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;worth $196.6 billion by 2034&lt;/a&gt;, and 62% of executives &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pagerduty.com/resources/ai/learn/companies-expecting-agentic-ai-roi-2025/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;expect a return on investment&lt;/a&gt; of more than 100%. This change is transitioning from small-scale tests to large-scale deployments, which significantly impact how businesses operate.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;数据分析领域正在经历自商业智能平台首次推出以来最大的变化。代理人工智能——“能够自行感知、推理、计划和行动的智能系统”——正在改变企业获取信息和做出选择的方式。生成式人工智能只对提示做出反应，但代理系统会自行工作，在几乎没有人类监督的情况下追求复杂的目标。他们还具有持久记忆，可以适应新情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这一变化标志着从被动分析到主动情报的转变。公司正在放弃静态仪表板和手动分析周期，转而采用监控数据、发现见解和做出决策的自动驾驶系统。预计&lt;a href=&#34;https://market.us/report/agentic-ai-market/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;到 2034 年价值将达到 1966 亿美元&lt;/a&gt;，62% 的高管&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pagerduty.com/resources/ai/learn/companies-expecting-agentic-ai-roi-2025/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;预计投资回报率&lt;/a&gt;超过 100%。这一变化正在从小规模测试过渡到大规模部署，这对企业的运营方式产生了重大影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Prompt Engineering vs Context Engineering】即时工程与情境工程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/prompt-engineering-vs-context-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As AI integration becomes standard in modern applications, developers face a very critical decision: How do we effectively communicate with large language models (LLMs) to get reliable and accurate results? The answer lies in understanding two distinct &amp;nbsp;but often confused approaches: prompt engineering and context engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;While these terms are frequently used interchangeably, they represent fundamentally different strategies for working with AI systems. Understanding their differences is important for building robust and production-ready applications that leverage LLMs effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着人工智能集成成为现代应用程序的标准，开发人员面临着一个非常关键的决策：我们如何与大型语言模型 (LLM) 有效地沟通以获得可靠且准确的结果？答案在于理解两种不同但经常混淆的方法：即时工程和情境工程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;虽然这些术语经常互换使用，但它们代表了使用人工智能系统的根本不同的策略。了解它们的差异对于构建有效利用法学硕士的强大且可用于生产的应用程序非常重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Does a Scrum Master Improve the Productivity of the Development Team?】Scrum Master 如何提高开发团队的生产力？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-scrum-masters-boost-team-productivity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The role of a Scrum Master is to establish Scrum, and the Scrum Master is accountable for the Scrum Team’s effectiveness. Thus, it is quite tempting to ask how a Scrum Master can help improve the productivity of the development team. But, in a complex working environment like software development, productivity is often not the right measure to showcase all the complexities of software developers’ knowledge work. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In simple working environments, productivity means a ratio of output to input. The traditional idea is to know how much is achieved (output) with a given amount of resources (inputs), largely in numbers, and the focus is on maximizing the output. That’s why, in traditional project management of software development projects, stakeholders evaluate the development team’s productivity based on the lines of code. Or, even today in Agile project management, stakeholders with a traditional mindset ask for the number of story points per iteration, known as &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sprint-velocity-the-ultimate-guide&#34;&gt;Sprint Velocity&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Scrum Master 的角色是建立 Scrum，Scrum Master 对 Scrum 团队的有效性负责。因此，人们很容易会问 Scrum Master 如何帮助提高开发团队的生产力。但是，在软件开发等复杂的工作环境中，生产力通常不是展示软件开发人员知识工作的所有复杂性的正确衡量标准。       &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在简单的工作环境中，生产力意味着产出与投入的比率。传统的想法是知道在给定数量的资源（投入）（主要是数量）下实现了多少（产出），重点是最大化产出。这就是为什么在软件开发项目的传统项目管理中，利益相关者根据代码行数来评估开发团队的生产力。或者，即使在今天的敏捷项目管理中，具有传统心态的利益相关者也会要求每次迭代的故事点数量，称为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sprint-velocity-the-ultimate-guide&#34;&gt;冲刺速度&lt;/a&gt;。   &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Proxies and the Importance of Japanese Proxies in Modern Networking】了解代理以及日本代理在现代网络中的重要性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-proxies-and-japanese-proxies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the current digital age, which largely revolves around the use of the internet, privacy and security, as well as access to the whole world, are some of the main concerns for individuals and businesses. One of the most effective methods to achieve these objectives is the use of proxy servers. Proxy servers essentially change your IP address and reroute your online traffic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Many types of proxies are available, but Japanese proxies are considered to be the best because they are not only stable but also have very low latency and offer you excellent regional access.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在当前的数字时代，主要围绕互联网的使用、隐私和安全以及对整个世界的访问，是个人和企业的一些主要关注点。实现这些目标的最有效方法之一是使用代理服务器。代理服务器本质上会更改您的 IP 地址并重新路由您的在线流量。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;有许多类型的代理可用，但日本代理被认为是最好的，因为它们不仅稳定，而且延迟非常低，并为您提供出色的区域访问。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Production-Grade React Project Structure: From Setup to Scale】生产级 React 项目结构：从设置到规模</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/production-grade-react-project-structure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Do you struggle to organize your React project folder &lt;span&gt;structures&lt;/span&gt;? The right folder organization does more than &lt;span&gt;just&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;keep things tidy. &lt;span&gt;The&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;development efficiency and team collaboration of your project&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;depend on it. A solid folder structure makes &lt;span&gt;the&lt;/span&gt; project look clean and speeds up scalability, collaboration, and debugging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The way developers organize files and components is vital &lt;span&gt;to the long-term success of any React project&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-react-a-complete-guide&#34;&gt;React applications&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;are&lt;/span&gt; easier to scale, debug, and onboard new team members through a clean folder structure and clear system design. The best folder structure practices help developers find files and components quickly, which &lt;span&gt;reduces the&lt;/span&gt; time spent searching through &lt;span&gt;the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;code. &lt;span&gt;The&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;consistent folder structure of your application&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;prevents chaos and confusion as it grows. Team members work together more smoothly&lt;span&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; with fewer merge conflicts and improved productivity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否很难组织 React 项目文件夹&lt;span&gt;结构&lt;/span&gt;？正确的文件夹组织不仅仅是&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;保持一切整洁。 &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;项目的开发效率和团队协作&lt;/span&gt;取决于它。可靠的文件夹结构使&lt;span&gt;项目&lt;/span&gt;看起来干净，并加速可扩展性、协作和调试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开发人员组织文件和组件的方式对于任何 React 项目的长期成功都至关重要&lt;/span&gt;。通过干净的文件夹结构和清晰的系统设计，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-react-a-complete-guide&#34;&gt;React 应用程序&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;更容易扩展、调试和加入新团队成员。最佳文件夹结构实践可帮助开发人员快速查找文件和组件，从而&lt;span&gt;减少&lt;/span&gt;搜索代码所花费的时间。 &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;应用程序的一致文件夹结构&lt;/span&gt;可以防止随着应用程序的增长而出现混乱和困惑。团队成员的合作更加顺畅&lt;span&gt;，&lt;/span&gt;减少了合并冲突并提高了工作效率。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Laravel + Next.js Integration Guide (Real-World Setup, 2025)】Laravel + Next.js 集成指南（实际设置，2025 年）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/laravel-nextjs-integration-guide-real-world-setup</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The goal is simple: build a secure app that uses SSR or SSG for SEO, CSRF-safe session cookies, clear CORS rules, and a smooth deploy to Vercel plus Forge or Vapour.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By the end, readers will know how to wire &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/laravel-for-beginners-an-overview-of-the-php-frame&#34;&gt;Laravel&lt;/a&gt; routes and controllers, fetch from Next.js with credentials, handle CSRF and sessions, and deploy with confidence. A short troubleshooting list covers common 401, 419, and CORS issues so teams do not get stuck.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;目标很简单：构建一个安全的应用程序，使用 SSR 或 SSG 进行 SEO、CSRF 安全会话 cookie、明确的 CORS 规则以及顺利部署到 Vercel 加 Forge 或 Vapour。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;到最后，读者将了解如何连接 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/laravel-for-beginners-an-overview-of-the-php-frame&#34;&gt;Laravel&lt;/a&gt; 路由和控制器，使用凭证从 Next.js 获取，处理 CSRF 和会话，并自信地进行部署。简短的故障排除列表涵盖常见的 401、419 和 CORS 问题，因此团队不会陷入困境。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding the Idle-Timer】了解空闲计时器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-the-idle-timer</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;What is an Idle Timer?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An idle timer is a software component that tracks user inactivity or idleness within an application or website. It measures the duration of time a user remains inactive—no mouse movements, keyboard inputs, or touch events—and triggers specific actions after a predefined idle period, such as logging out the user, showing a warning, or saving work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Problems Does an Idle Timer Solve?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Idle timers are essential in many scenarios, including:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;什么是空闲计时器？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;空闲计时器是一个软件组件，用于跟踪应用程序或网站内用户的不活动或空闲状态。它测量用户保持不活动状态的持续时间（无鼠标移动、键盘输入或触摸事件），并在预定义的空闲时间段后触发特定操作，例如注销用户、显示警告或保存工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;空闲定时器可以解决什么问题？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;空闲计时器在许多场景中都是必不可少的，包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Workload Identities: Bridging Infrastructure and Application Security】工作负载身份：桥接基础设施和应用程序安全</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/workload-identities-bridging-infrastructure-and-ap</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Infrastructure security has long been about protecting networks, hosts, and cloud platforms. Application security focuses on securing APIs, data flows, and business logic to protect critical assets. Both approaches are critical, but they can’t provide complete protection on their own. When isolated from each other, there is a higher risk that attackers can exploit the security gaps in either layer, which is why workload identities should be employed to serve as a bridge that unifies both layers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Two Security Worlds: Infrastructure vs. Application&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Infrastructure security is about protecting the foundation, including measures such as network segmentation, least-privilege identity and access management (IAM) roles, container isolation, and applying zero-trust principles at the infrastructure level. Application security works higher up in the stack, closer to data and user interactions. It deals with authentication, authorization, token management, session handling, and API protection.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;基础设施安全长期以来一直致力于保护网络、主机和云平台。应用程序安全侧重于保护 API、数据流和业务逻辑，以保护关键资产。这两种方法都很重要，但它们本身无法提供完整的保护。当彼此隔离时，攻击者利用任一层中的安全漏洞的风险更高，这就是为什么应采用工作负载身份作为统一两层的桥梁的原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;两个安全世界：基础设施与应用程序&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;基础设施安全是为了保护基础，包括网络分段、最低权限身份和访问管理 (IAM) 角色、容器隔离以及在基础设施级别应用零信任原则等措施。应用程序安全性在堆栈中的较高位置工作，更接近数据和用户交互。它处理身份验证、授权、令牌管理、会话处理和 API 保护。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Docker Compose】Docker Compose 初学者指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/beginners-guide-to-docker-compose</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;The constant need to run &lt;code&gt;docker run&lt;/code&gt; in multiple terminals for managing multi-container setups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If you’re new to Docker, you’ve likely already discovered the &lt;code&gt;docker run&lt;/code&gt; command that makes it easy to run a single container. However, what happens if your app requires a database? A cache? Before you know it, you’re dealing with a terminal tab nightmare:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;经常需要在多个终端中运行 &lt;code&gt;docker run&lt;/code&gt; 来管理多容器设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果您是 Docker 新手，您可能已经发现了 &lt;code&gt;docker run&lt;/code&gt; 命令，它可以轻松运行单个容器。但是，如果您的应用程序需要数据库，会发生什么情况？缓存？在您意识到之前，您正在处理终端选项卡的噩梦：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>