<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Advance Traffic Management in Canary Using Istio, Argo Rollouts, and HPA】使用 Istio、Argo 部署和 HPA 推进 Canary 流量管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advance-traffic-management-in-canary</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As enterprises mature in their CI/CD journey, they tend to ship code faster, safely, and securely. One essential strategy the DevOps team applies is releasing code progressively to production, also known as canary deployment. Canary deployment is a bulletproof mechanism that safely releases application changes and provides flexibility for business experiments. It can be implemented using open-source software like &lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/argo-rollouts/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.flagger.app/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Flagger&lt;/a&gt;. However, advanced DevOps teams want to gain granular control over their traffic and pod scaling while performing canary deployment to reduce overall costs. Many enterprises achieve advanced traffic management of canary deployment at scale using open-source Istio service mesh. We want to share our knowledge with the DevOps community through this blog.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Before we get started, let us discuss the canary architecture implemented by Argo Rollouts and Istio.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着企业在 CI/CD 之旅中日趋成熟，他们倾向于更快、更安全地交付代码。 DevOps 团队应用的一项基本策略是将代码逐步发布到生产环境，也称为金丝雀部署。金丝雀部署是一种防弹机制，可以安全地发布应用程序变更，并为业务实验提供灵活性。它可以使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/argo-rollouts/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt; a href=&#34;https://docs.flaagger.app/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Flagger&lt;/a&gt;。然而，高级 DevOps 团队希望在执行金丝雀部署时获得对其流量和 Pod 扩展的精细控制，以降低总体成本。许多企业使用开源 Istio 服务网格实现大规模金丝雀部署的高级流量管理。我们希望通过此博客与 DevOps 社区分享我们的知识。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在开始之前，我们先讨论一下 Argo Rollouts 和 Istio 实现的金丝雀架构。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Essential Guidelines for Building Optimized ETL Data Pipelines in the Cloud With Azure Data Factory】使用 Azure 数据工厂在云中构建优化的 ETL 数据管道的基本指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-optimized-etl-pipelines-in-the-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When building &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolution-of-data-pipelines&#34;&gt;ETL data pipelines&lt;/a&gt; using Azure Data Factory (ADF) to process huge amounts of data from different sources, you may often run into performance and design-related challenges. This article will serve as a guide in building high-performance ETL pipelines that are both efficient and scalable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below are the major guidelines to consider when building optimized ETL data pipelines in ADF:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用 Azure 数据工厂 (ADF) 构建 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolution-of-data-pipelines&#34;&gt;ETL 数据管道&lt;/a&gt;以处理大量数据时由于数据来源不同，您可能经常会遇到性能和设计相关的挑战。本文将作为构建高效且可扩展的高性能 ETL 管道的指南。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是在 ADF 中构建优化的 ETL 数据管道时要考虑的主要准则：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Safeguarding Democracy in the Digital Age: Insights from Day 1 at Black Hat 2024 and Las Vegas Officials】维护数字时代的民主：Black Hat 2024 和拉斯维加斯官员第一天的见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/safeguarding-democracy-in-the-digital-age-insights</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In an era where technology and geopolitics intersect more than ever before, the importance of cybersecurity in maintaining democratic processes cannot be overstated. At Black Hat 2024, global leaders and local officials converged to discuss the challenges and strategies for protecting elections, critical infrastructure, and the very foundations of democracy. This article delves into the insights shared at the conference, offering developers, engineers, and architects a comprehensive view of the cybersecurity landscape and its implications for democratic societies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Changing Landscape of Global Threats&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Jeff Moss, founder of Black Hat, set the stage by highlighting the rapid evolution of the threat landscape. &#34;Things are different now,&#34; Moss observed. &#34;Things have sped up. You have all the routine problems and a giant bucket of other problems, you have all these risks you didn&#39;t think about.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在一个技术和地缘政治比以往任何时候都更加交叉的时代，网络安全在维持民主进程方面的重要性怎么强调也不为过。在 Black Hat 2024 上，全球领导人和地方官员齐聚一堂，讨论保护选举、关键基础设施和民主基础的挑战和战略。本文深入探讨了会议上分享的见解，为开发人员、工程师和架构师提供了网络安全格局及其对民主社会影响的全面看法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;全球威胁的变化&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Black Hat 创始人 Jeff Moss 通过强调威胁形势的快速演变奠定了基础。 “现在情况不同了，”莫斯观察到。 “事情已经加速了。你遇到了所有常规问题和一大堆其他问题，你遇到了所有这些你没有想到的风险。”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Revolutionizing Billing Processes With AI: Enhancing Efficiency and Accuracy】利用人工智能彻底改变计费流程：提高效率和准确性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/revolutionizing-billing-processes-with-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The market for software as a service (SaaS) has expanded at an extraordinary pace and given businesses access to scalable solutions. However, one major difficulty still stands in its way: generating and collecting revenue efficiently and accurately. Traditional billing systems often prove inadequate leading to inefficiencies and inaccuracies. This blog post examines the integration of AI into SaaS pricing methods, with a focus on improving efficiency and effectiveness by highlighting data analysts, data scientists, data product managers, and data-driven software professionals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Role of AI in Modern Billing Systems&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is changing the face of Saas business by addressing many challenges related to traditional billing systems. Fundamental technologies like machine learning (ML), predictive analytics, or automation simplify billing processes and make them more accurate.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;软件即服务 (SaaS) 市场以惊人的速度扩张，并为企业提供了可扩展的解决方案。然而，仍然存在一个主要困难：高效、准确地产生和收取收入。传统的计费系统往往存在不足，导致效率低下和不准确。这篇博文探讨了人工智能与 SaaS 定价方法的集成，重点是通过强调数据分析师、数据科学家、数据产品经理和数据驱动软件专业人员来提高效率和有效性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能在现代计费系统中的作用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能 (AI) 通过解决与传统计费系统相关的许多挑战，正在改变 SaaS 业务的面貌。机器学习 (ML)、预测分析或自动化等基础技术简化了计费流程并使其更加准确。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unboxing the Black Box】拆箱黑匣子</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unboxing-the-black-box</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today, several significant and safety-critical decisions are being made by deep &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/neural-network-essentials&#34;&gt;neural networks&lt;/a&gt;. These include driving decisions in autonomous vehicles, diagnosing diseases, and operating robots in manufacturing and construction. In all such cases, scientists and engineers claim that these models help make better decisions than humans and hence, help save lives. However, how these networks reach their decisions is often a mystery, for not just their users, but also for their developers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;These changing times, thus, necessitate that as engineers we spend more time &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-making-the-black-box-transparent&#34;&gt;unboxing these black boxes&lt;/a&gt; so that we can identify the biases and weaknesses of the models that we build. This may also allow us to identify which part of the input is most critical for the model and hence, ensure its correctness. Finally, explaining how models make their decisions will not only build trust between AI products and their consumers but also help meet the diverse and evolving regulatory requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;今天，深度&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/neural-network-essentials&#34;&gt;神经网络&lt;/a&gt;正在做出一些重大且安全关键的决策。其中包括自动驾驶汽车的驾驶决策、诊断疾病以及在制造和建筑业中操作机器人。在所有这些情况下，科学家和工程师声称这些模型有助于做出比人类更好的决策，从而有助于拯救生命。然而，这些网络如何做出决策往往是一个谜，不仅对于它们的用户来说，而且对于它们的开发人员来说也是如此。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;因此，时代的变化要求我们作为工程师花更多的时间&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-making-the-black-box-transparent ”拆箱这些黑匣子&lt;/a&gt;，以便我们能够识别我们构建的模型的偏见和弱点。这也可以让我们识别输入的哪一部分对模型最关键，从而确保其正确性。最后，解释模型如何做出决策不仅可以在人工智能产品与其消费者之间建立信任，还有助于满足多样化且不断变化的监管要求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why AI-Assisted Code Generation Is Transforming Software Development】为什么人工智能辅助代码生成正在改变软件开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-assisted-code-generation-transforming-software</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Software development and architecture is continuously evolving with artificial intelligence (AI). AI-assisted code generation stands out as a particularly revolutionary advancement, offering developers the ability to create high-quality code more efficiently and accurately than ever before. This innovation not only enhances productivity, but also opens the door to new possibilities in software creation, particularly in the realm of microservices development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Evolution of Code Generation: Traditional Coding vs. AI-Assisted Coding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional coding requires developers to write and test extensive lines of code manually. This process is time consuming and prone to errors. Conversely, AI-assisted code generation leverages machine learning algorithms to analyze patterns in existing codebases, understands programming logic, and generates code snippets or entire programs based on specific requirements. This technology can drastically reduce the time spent on repetitive coding tasks and minimize human errors. It is not a substitute for developers, but rather a productivity tool that eliminates tedious and monotonous infrastructure and plumbing code.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;软件开发和架构随着人工智能 (AI) 的发展而不断发展。人工智能辅助代码生成是一项特别革命性的进步，使开发人员能够比以往更高效、更准确地创建高质量代码。这项创新不仅提高了生产力，而且为软件创建的新可能性打开了大门，特别是在微服务开发领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;代码生成的演变：传统编码与人工智能辅助编码&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统编码需要开发人员手动编写和测试大量代码。这个过程非常耗时并且容易出错。相反，人工智能辅助代码生成利用机器学习算法来分析现有代码库中的模式，理解编程逻辑，并根据特定要求生成代码片段或整个程序。该技术可以大大减少重复编码任务所花费的时间，并最大限度地减少人为错误。它不是开发人员的替代品，而是一种生产力工具，可以消除繁琐单调的基础设施和管道代码。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tour of Snowflake Ingestion Using CockroachDB and Redpanda Connect】使用 CockroachDB 和 Redpanda Connect 进行雪花摄取之旅</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-ingestion-using-cockroachdb-and-redpanda</link>
      <description>【&lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Previous Articles on Snowflake&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-snowflake-with-trino&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;Integrating Snowflake with Trino&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Previous Articles on CockroachDB CDC&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-apache-pulsar&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;Using CockroachDB CDC with Apache Pulsar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-azure-event-hubs&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;Using CockroachDB CDC with Azure Event Hubs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/saas-galore-integrating-cockroachdb-with-confluent&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;SaaS Galore: Integrating CockroachDB with Confluent Kafka, FiveTran, and Snowflake&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-confluent-cloud-kafka-a&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;Using CockroachDB CDC with Confluent Cloud Kafka and Schema Registry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cockroachdb-cdc-using-minio-as-cloud-storage-sink&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;CockroachDB CDC using Minio as cloud storage sink&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cockroachdb-cdc-with-hadoop-ozone-s3-gateway-and-d&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;CockroachDB CDC using Hadoop Ozone S3 Gateway as cloud storage sink&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;I work with financial services clients, and it&#39;s common to encounter a need for streaming changes in the operational data store into a data warehouse or a data lake. A former colleague recently reached out for advice on the fastest and most efficient way to load trade data into Snowflake. I&#39;ve come up with at least three methods, which I will explore in a follow-up series of articles. However, I&#39;ve decided to first explore &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redpanda.com/connect&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Redpanda Connect&lt;/a&gt;, a solution that has recently caught my attention. This is by no means a conclusive guide on how changefeed data must be loaded into Snowflake; we&#39;re merely exploring the possibilities and discussing the pros and cons in later articles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;CockroachDB changefeeds are an enterprise feature and require a license. In this tutorial, I&#39;m using a free-to-start version of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cockroachlabs.com/lp/serverless/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CockroachDB Serverless&lt;/a&gt;, which has enterprise changefeeds enabled.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;之前关于雪花的文章&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-snowflake-with-trino&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;将 Snowflake 与 Trino 集成&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;之前关于 CockroachDB CDC 的文章&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-apache-pulsar&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;将 CockroachDB CDC 与 Apache Pulsar 结合使用&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-azure-event-hubs&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;将 CockroachDB CDC 与 Azure 事件中心结合使用&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /里&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/saas-galore-integrating-cockroachdb-with-confluence&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;SaaS Galore：将 CockroachDB 与 Confluence Kafka、FiveTran 和 Snowflake 集成&lt; /a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-confluence-cloud-kafka-a&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;将 CockroachDB CDC 与 Confluence Cloud Kafka 和架构注册表结合使用&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cockroachdb-cdc-using-minio-as-cloud-storage-sink&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;CockroachDB CDC 使用 Minio 作为云存储接收器&lt;/一个&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cockroachdb-cdc-with-hadoop-ozone-s3-gateway-and-d&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;CockroachDB CDC 使用 Hadoop Ozone S3 网关作为云存储接收器&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;div 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;动机&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;我与金融服务客户合作，经常需要将操作数据存储中的更改流式传输到数据仓库或数据湖中。一位前同事最近寻求有关将贸易数据加载到 Snowflake 的最快、最有效方法的建议。我已经提出了至少三种方法，我将在后续系列文章中对其进行探讨。不过，我决定首先探索 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redpanda.com/connect&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Redpanda Connect&lt;/a&gt;，这是一个最近推出的解决方案引起了我的注意。这绝不是关于如何将变更源数据加载到 Snowflake 中的决定性指南；我们只是探索可能性并在后面的文章中讨论其优缺点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;CockroachDB 变更源是一项企业功能，需要许可证。在本教程中，我使用免费启动版本的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cockroachlabs.com/lp/serverless/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CockroachDB Serverless &lt;/a&gt;，它启用了企业变更源。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Pipeline vs. ETL Pipeline】数据管道与 ETL 管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-pipeline-vs-etl-pipeline</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s world, data is a key success factor for many information systems. To exploit data, it needs to be moved and collected from many different locations, using many different technologies and tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is important to understand the difference between a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-data-pipeline&#34;&gt;data pipeline&lt;/a&gt; and an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-integration-and-etl-for-dummies-like-me&#34;&gt;ETL pipeline&lt;/a&gt;. While both are designed to move data from one place to another, they serve different purposes and are optimized for different tasks. The comparison table below highlights the key differences:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当今世界，数据是许多信息系统成功的关键因素。为了利用数据，需要使用许多不同的技术和工具从许多不同的位置移动和收集数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-data-pipeline&#34;&gt;数据管道&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href= “https://dzone.com/articles/data-integration-and-etl-for-dummies-like-me&#34;&gt;ETL 管道&lt;/a&gt;。虽然两者都旨在将数据从一个地方移动到另一个地方，但它们具有不同的目的并针对不同的任务进行了优化。下面的比较表突出显示了主要差异：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Large Language Models: Changing the Game in Software Development With Code Generation, Debugging, and CI/CD Integration】大型语言模型：通过代码生成、调试和 CI/CD 集成改变软件开发的游戏规则</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llms-changing-software-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With AI, the domain of software development is experiencing a &lt;a data-cke-saved-href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2406.00515&#34; href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2406.00515&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;breakthrough phase&lt;/a&gt; with the continuous &lt;a data-cke-saved-href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2311.10372&#34; href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2311.10372&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;integration of state-of-the-art Large Language Models&lt;/a&gt; like GPT-4 and Claude Opus. These models extend beyond the role of traditional developer tools to directly assist developers in translating &lt;a data-cke-saved-href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2308.10620&#34; href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2308.10620&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;verbal instructions into executable code&lt;/a&gt; across a variety of programming languages, which speeds up the process of coding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Code Generation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://code.visualstudio.com/docs/copilot/overview&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 808px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;813.6 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1723229715783&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;08/09/2024 06:55 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17847875-1723229713584.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;813554&#34; data-name=&#34;1723229713584.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17847875&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17847875-1723229713584.png&#34; alt=&#34;Code generation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhancing Developer Productivity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLMs&lt;/a&gt; understand context and generate best-practice pieces of code, making them very good at enhancing the productivity of developers and their &lt;a data-cke-saved-href=&#34;https://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2310.03533&#34; href=&#34;https://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2310.03533&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;future research&lt;/a&gt;. They work as a developer on-call assistant, offering insight and alternatives that may even elude more experienced programmers. Such a role gains a lot of importance in large and complex projects where the integration of different software modules might introduce subtle, sometimes undetectable bugs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;借助人工智能，软件开发领域正在经历&lt;a data-cke-saved-href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2406.00515&#34; href=&#34;http://ar5iv. labs.arxiv.org/html/2406.00515&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;突破阶段&lt;/a&gt;与连续的&lt;a data-cke-saved-href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs。 arxiv.org/html/2311.10372&#34; href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2311.10372&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;集成最先进的大语言模型&lt;/a&gt;，例如 GPT-4 和 Claude Opus。这些模型超越了传统开发人员工具的作用，可以直接帮助开发人员翻译 &lt;a data-cke-saved-href=&#34;http://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2308.10620&#34; href=&#34;http:// ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2308.10620&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;跨多种编程语言将口头指令转换为可执行代码&lt;/a&gt;，从而加快编码过程。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;代码生成&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://code.visualstudio.com/docs/copilot/overview&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 808px;&#34; class =“fr-fic fr-dib lazyload”data-image =“true”data-new =“false”data-sizeformatted =“813.6 kB”data-mimetype =“image / png”data-creationdate =“1723229715783”数据-creationdateformatted=&#34;08/09/2024 06:55 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17847875-1723229713584.png&#34; data-modificationdate= “null”data-size =“813554”data-name =“1723229713584.png”data-id =“17847875”data-src =“https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17847875-1723229713584.png” &#34; alt=&#34;代码生成&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;提高开发人员生产力&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;法学硕士&lt;/a&gt;了解上下文并生成最佳实践代码片段，使它们非常适合擅长提高开发人员及其&lt;a data-cke-saved-href=&#34;https://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org/html/2310.03533&#34; href=&#34;https://ar5iv.labs.arxiv.org /html/2310.03533&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;未来研究&lt;/a&gt;。他们作为开发人员随叫随到的助理，提供甚至可能让更有经验的程序员无法理解的见解和替代方案。这样的角色在大型复杂的项目中变得非常重要，在这些项目中，不同软件模块的集成可能会引入微妙的、有时无法检测到的错误。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Hands-On Guide to OpenTelemetry: Visualizing Instrumentation for Developers Using Jaeger】OpenTelemetry 实践指南：使用 Jaeger 为开发人员提供可视化仪器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/otel-guide-visualizing-instrumentation-in-jaeger</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to start your journey on the road to collecting telemetry data from your applications? Great observability begins with great instrumentation!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this series, you&#39;ll explore how to adopt &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; and how to instrument an application to collect tracing telemetry. You&#39;ll learn how to leverage out-of-the-box automatic instrumentation tools and understand when it&#39;s necessary to explore more advanced manual instrumentation for your applications. By the end of this series, you&#39;ll have an understanding of how telemetry travels from your applications to the OpenTelemetry Collector, and be ready to bring OpenTelemetry to your future projects. Everything discussed here is supported by &lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a hands-on, self-paced workshop&lt;/a&gt; authored &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;by Paige Cruz&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您准备好开始从应用程序收集遥测数据的旅程了吗？出色的可观测性始于出色的仪器！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本系列中，您将探索如何采用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; 以及如何检测一个应用程序来收集跟踪遥测数据。您将学习如何利用开箱即用的自动仪表工具，并了解何时需要为您的应用探索更高级的手动仪表。在本系列结束时，您将了解遥测如何从应用程序传输到 OpenTelemetry Collector，并准备好将 OpenTelemetry 引入您未来的项目。这里讨论的所有内容均由&lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;动手、自定进度的研讨会&lt;/ a&gt; 作者：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;由 Paige Cruz&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>