<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Agents Demystified: From Language Models to Autonomous Intelligence】揭秘人工智能代理：从语言模型到自主智能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agents-language-models-autonomous-action</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Exactly Is an AI Agent?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence has entered a new phase, one where systems no longer just respond, but reason, plan, and act.&lt;br&gt;&#xA; &amp;nbsp;Language models like GPT, Gemini, or Claude are incredibly powerful, but they live inside a box. They can generate, summarize, and explain, but they can’t take real-world action unless connected to something beyond themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agents-future-of-automation-or-overhyped-buzzword&#34;&gt;AI agents&lt;/a&gt; come in.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI 代理到底是什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能已进入一个新阶段，系统不再只是做出响应，而是推理、计划和行动。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  像 GPT、Gemini 或 Claude 这样的语言模型非常强大，但它们存在于一个盒子里。他们可以生成、总结和解释，但除非与自身之外的事物联系起来，否则他们无法采取现实世界的行动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agents-future-of-automation-or-overhyped-buzzword&#34;&gt;人工智能代理&lt;/a&gt;发挥作用的地方。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Parallax and Scroll-Based Animations】视差和滚动动画指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/awesome-parallax-effect-with-css-only</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Parallax animation can transform static web pages into immersive, interactive experiences. While traditional parallax relies on simple background image movement and tons of JavaScript code, scroll-based CSS animation opens up a world of creative possibilities with no JavaScript at all. In this guide, we’ll explore two distinct approaches:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SVG block animation&lt;/strong&gt;: Creating movement using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/keeping-your-fonts-in-embedded-svg&#34;&gt;SVG graphics&lt;/a&gt; for unique, customizable effects.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-image parallax background&lt;/strong&gt;: Stacking and animating multiple image layers for a classic parallax illusion.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ll walk through each technique step by step, compare their strengths and limitations, and offer practical tips for responsive design.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;视差动画可以将静态网页转变为身临其境的交互式体验。传统的视差依赖于简单的背景图像移动和大量的 JavaScript 代码，而基于滚动的 CSS 动画则在根本不需要 JavaScript 的情况下开辟了一个充满创意可能性的世界。在本指南中，我们将探索两种不同的方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SVG 块动画&lt;/strong&gt;：使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/keeping-your-fonts-in-embedded-svg&#34;&gt;SVG 图形&lt;/a&gt;创建运动，以获得独特的可自定义效果。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;多图像视差背景&lt;/strong&gt;：堆叠多个图像层并为其设置动画，以实现经典的视差错觉。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将逐步介绍每种技术，比较它们的优点和局限性，并提供响应式设计的实用技巧。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Quantum-Safe Trading Systems: Preparing Risk Engines for the Post-Quantum Threat】量子安全交易系统：为后量子威胁准备风险引擎</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-safe-trading-systems-post-quantum-risk</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Coming Break in Trust&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1070&#34; data-start=&#34;238&#34;&gt;Picture this: a structured BRL-USD note is booked and hedged in 2025, stitched across FX triggers, callable steps, and a sovereign curve that looks stable enough to lull even the cautious. Trade capture is clean, risk logs balance, settlement acknowledges signatures, and the desk moves on. Years pass. The note remains live, coupons roll, collateral terms are amended twice, and the position is referenced by downstream analytics and audit trails that assume the original cryptographic guarantees still hold. Then the ground shifts. Adversaries who quietly harvested network traffic in 2025 now possess hardware that can break the RSA and ECC protections that guarded those artifacts. The trade’s lineage—what was agreed, authorized, and attested — no longer rests on unforgeable proofs. It rests on assumptions that no longer apply.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;2291&#34; data-is-last-node=&#34;&#34; data-is-only-node=&#34;&#34; data-start=&#34;1072&#34;&gt;This is not a scare line for a compliance deck. It is a systems problem with direct pricing consequences. If a payoff confirmation, margin call message, or risk model artifact can be replayed, altered, or repudiated because yesterday’s signatures are breakable tomorrow, the integrity of the entire lifecycle is at risk. You can mark a curve correctly and still be wrong if the attestation that links a payout to a specific state of the world becomes suspect.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;信任即将破裂&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1070&#34; data-start=&#34;238&#34;&gt;想象一下：结构性巴西雷亚尔兑美元票据在 2025 年进行登记和对冲，涵盖了外汇触发因素、可赎回步骤以及看起来足够稳定甚至足以让谨慎人士平静下来的主权曲线。交易捕获干净，风险记录平衡，结算确认签名，交易台继续前进。岁月流逝。该票据仍然有效，优惠券滚动，抵押品条款修改两次，并且假设原始加密保证仍然有效的下游分析和审计跟踪会引用该位置。然后地面发生了变化。在 2025 年悄悄收集网络流量的对手现在拥有可以破坏保护这些工件的 RSA 和 ECC 保护的硬件。交易的血统——即商定、授权和证明的——不再依赖于不可伪造的证据。它所基于的假设不再适用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;2291&#34; data-is-last-node=&#34;&#34; data-is-only-node=&#34;&#34; data-start=&#34;1072&#34;&gt;这不是合规平台的恐吓线。这是一个直接影响定价的系统问题。如果因为昨天的签名明天就可以破解而导致收益确认、追加保证金消息或风险模型工件可以重放、更改或否认，则整个生命周期的完整性将面临风险。你可以正确地标记一条曲线，但如果将支出与世界的特定状态联系起来的证明变得可疑，那么仍然是错误的。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build an MCP Server】如何构建 MCP 服务器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-build-mcp-server</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Model Context Protocol has been playing a crucial role in integrating various tools with agents in a very streamlined manner. You can expose your tools via APIs and connect to the MCP clients. At the same time, there has been lots of confusion about MCP. &amp;nbsp;Below clarifies the doubt:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What MCP Server Is Not&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;MCP is not a framework for building agents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;MCP is not a Python library.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;MCP is not a container.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;MCP is not a way to code agents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;How Model Context Protocol (MCP) Works&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;模型上下文协议在以非常简化的方式将各种工具与代理集成方面发挥着至关重要的作用。您可以通过 API 公开您的工具并连接到 MCP 客户端。与此同时，人们对 MCP 也存在很多困惑。  下面澄清了这个疑问：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;MCP 服务器不是什么&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;MCP 不是构建代理的框架。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;MCP 不是 Python 库。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;MCP 不是容器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;MCP 不是一种对代理进行编码的方法。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;模型上下文协议 (MCP) 的工作原理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终，&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling Enterprise RPA With Secure Automation and Robust Governance】通过安全自动化和稳健的治理扩展企业 RPA</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enterprise-rpa-secure-automation-governance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Enterprise RPA has matured from “task bots” into a core capability for automating business processes at scale across several domains, including finance operations, customer onboarding, supply chain workflows, HR shared services, and regulated back-office functions. The challenge is no longer whether automation works, but whether it can be scaled predictably without creating new operational risk: credential sprawl, uncontrolled bot changes, fragile UI dependencies, audit gaps, and inconsistent exception handling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;This article lays out a blueprint for enterprise RPA that supports scaling robotic process automation across teams, business units, and geographies while delivering secure and compliant RPA solutions under a strong governance model.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;企业 RPA 已从“任务机器人”发展成为跨多个领域大规模自动化业务流程的核心功能，包括财务运营、客户入职、供应链工作流程、人力资源共享服务和受监管的后台功能。挑战不再是自动化是否有效，而是自动化是否可以在不产生新的运营风险的情况下进行可预测的扩展：凭证蔓延、不受控制的机器人更改、脆弱的 UI 依赖性、审计差距和不一致的异常处理。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;335551550&#34;:6,&#34;335551620&#34;:6}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;本文描绘了企业 RPA 的蓝图，支持跨团队、业务部门和地域扩展机器人流程自动化，同时在强大的治理模型下提供安全且合规的 RPA 解决方案。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Green AI in Practice: How I Track GPU Hours, Energy, CO₂, and Cost for Every ML Experiment】绿色 AI 实践：我如何跟踪每个 ML 实验的 GPU 时间、能源、二氧化碳和成本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/green-ai-how-to-track-gpu-carbon-and-cost</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;216&#34; data-start=&#34;76&#34;&gt;Most data teams track &lt;strong data-end=&#34;110&#34; data-start=&#34;98&#34;&gt;Accuracy&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong data-end=&#34;123&#34; data-start=&#34;112&#34;&gt;Latency&lt;/strong&gt;, and maybe &lt;strong data-end=&#34;154&#34; data-start=&#34;135&#34;&gt;GPU Utilization&lt;/strong&gt; if someone is watching the dashboard. Almost no one tracks:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;265&#34; data-start=&#34;220&#34;&gt;How many &lt;strong data-end=&#34;242&#34; data-start=&#34;229&#34;&gt;GPU-hours&lt;/strong&gt; a model run consumed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;314&#34; data-start=&#34;268&#34;&gt;How many &lt;strong data-end=&#34;284&#34; data-start=&#34;277&#34;&gt;kWh&lt;/strong&gt; of electricity that implies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;391&#34; data-start=&#34;317&#34;&gt;How much &lt;strong data-end=&#34;333&#34; data-start=&#34;326&#34;&gt;CO₂&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong data-end=&#34;353&#34; data-start=&#34;338&#34;&gt;cloud spend&lt;/strong&gt; are associated with each experiment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;500&#34; data-start=&#34;393&#34;&gt;Once I started paying attention to these metrics, it completely changed how I design and run experiments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;216&#34; data-start=&#34;76&#34;&gt;大多数数据团队都会跟踪&lt;strong data-end=&#34;110&#34; data-start=&#34;98&#34;&gt;准确度&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong data-end=&#34;123&#34; data-start=&#34;112&#34;&gt;延迟&lt;/strong&gt;，如果有人查看仪表板，可能还会跟踪&lt;strong data-end=&#34;154&#34; data-start=&#34;135&#34;&gt;GPU利用率&lt;/strong&gt;。几乎没有人跟踪：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;265&#34; data-start=&#34;220&#34;&gt;模型运行消耗了多少 &lt;strong data-end=&#34;242&#34; data-start=&#34;229&#34;&gt;GPU 小时&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;314&#34; data-start=&#34;268&#34;&gt;这意味着多少 &lt;strong data-end=&#34;284&#34; data-start=&#34;277&#34;&gt;kWh&lt;/strong&gt; 电量&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;391&#34; data-start=&#34;317&#34;&gt;每个实验关联的&lt;strong data-end=&#34;333&#34; data-start=&#34;326&#34;&gt;CO2&lt;/strong&gt; 和&lt;strong data-end=&#34;353&#34; data-start=&#34;338&#34;&gt;云支出&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;500&#34; data-start=&#34;393&#34;&gt;一旦我开始关注这些指标，它就彻底改变了我设计和运行实验的方式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Sierra Charts】介绍塞拉利昂图表</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/all-about-sierra-charts</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/HTTP-RPC/Sierra&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Sierra&lt;/a&gt; is an open-source framework for simplifying the development of Java Swing applications. It is based on the open-source &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/HTTP-RPC/Kilo&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kilo framework&lt;/a&gt;, which has been discussed in previous articles:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cleaner-code-with-collections-and-optionals&#34;&gt;Writing (Slightly) Cleaner Code With Collections and Optionals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/efficiently-transforming-jdbc-query-results-to-json-1&#34;&gt;Efficiently Transforming JDBC Query Results to JSON&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-schema-annotations-to-create-and-execute-sql&#34;&gt;Using Schema Annotations to Create and Execute SQL Queries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, Sierra&#39;s &lt;code&gt;UILoader&lt;/code&gt; class can be used to easily construct a hierarchy of user interface elements:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/HTTP-RPC/Sierra&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Sierra&lt;/a&gt; 是一个开源框架，用于简化 Java Swing 应用程序的开发。它基于开源 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/HTTP-RPC/Kilo&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kilo 框架&lt;/a&gt;，该框架已在之前的文章中讨论过：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cleaner-code-with-collections-and-options&#34;&gt;使用集合和可选值编写（稍微）更简洁的代码&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/efficiently-transforming-jdbc-query-results-to-json-1&#34;&gt;高效地将 JDBC 查询结果转换为 JSON&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-schema-annotations-to-create-and-execute-sql&#34;&gt;使用架构注释创建和执行 SQL 查询&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，Sierra 的 &lt;code&gt;UILoader&lt;/code&gt; 类可用于轻松构建用户界面元素的层次结构：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Human Bottleneck in DevOps: Automating Knowledge with AIOps and SECI】DevOps 中的人力瓶颈：利用 AIOps 和 SECI 实现知识自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-human-bottleneck-in-devops-automating-knowledg</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;428&#34; data-start=&#34;223&#34;&gt;In modern IT operations (ITOps), we face a paradox: our infrastructure is dynamic, scalable, and cloud-native, but our operational processes are often static, manual, and dependent on a few hero engineers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;649&#34; data-start=&#34;430&#34;&gt;When an incident occurs, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/banish-anxiety-lower-mttr-budget-incident-response&#34;&gt;mean time to recovery (MTTR)&lt;/a&gt; often depends less on the technology stack and more on who is on call. If the expert is unavailable, the system stays down. This is the &lt;strong data-end=&#34;648&#34; data-start=&#34;624&#34;&gt;knowledge bottleneck&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;428&#34; data-start=&#34;223&#34;&gt;在现代 IT 运营 (ITOps) 中，我们面临一个悖论：我们的基础设施是动态的、可扩展的、云原生的，但我们的运营流程通常是静态的、手动的，并且依赖于少数英雄工程师。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;649&#34; data-start=&#34;430&#34;&gt;发生事件时，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/banish-anxiety-lower-mttr-budget-incident-response&#34;&gt;平均恢复时间 (MTTR)&lt;/a&gt; 通常较少取决于技术堆栈，而更多取决于待命人员。如果专家不在，系统就会停止运行。这是&lt;strong data-end=&#34;648&#34; data-start=&#34;624&#34;&gt;知识瓶颈&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Serverless Is Not Cheaper by Default】默认情况下，无服务器并不便宜</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-is-not-cheaper-by-default</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-test-render-count=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div data-is-streaming=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p data-end=&#34;543&#34; data-start=&#34;253&#34;&gt;The pitch is clean: you pay only for what you use. No servers idling at 3 a.m., burning cash. No capacity planning. Just functions that appear when needed and disappear when done. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-computing-the-future-of-scalable-cloud-applications&#34;&gt;Serverless&lt;/a&gt; feels like the ideal everyone was waiting for — and sometimes it actually is. Then the bill shows up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p data-end=&#34;1016&#34; data-start=&#34;545&#34;&gt;A developer I know — an experienced guy, not some junior making rookie mistakes — built what looked like a simple proof of concept. AWS Bedrock knowledge base, OpenSearch Serverless backend. Nothing fancy. A few LLM queries, maybe 2 GB of PDFs uploaded for testing. He was expecting maybe twenty or thirty bucks. The invoice came back at over $200. He spent an hour just staring at the line items, trying to figure out what happened. No error, no hack. Just the way it works.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-test-render-count=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div data-is-streaming=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p data-end=&#34;543&#34; data-start=&#34;253&#34;&gt;推销很干净：您只需为您使用的内容付费。凌晨 3 点没有服务器闲置，烧钱。没有容量规划。只是在需要时出现并在完成时消失的功能。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-computing-the-future-of-scalable-cloud-applications&#34;&gt;无服务器&lt;/a&gt;感觉像是每个人都在等待的理想选择 - 有时确实如此。然后账单就会出现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p data-end=&#34;1016&#34; data-start=&#34;545&#34;&gt;我认识的一位开发人员 - 一个经验丰富的人，而不是一些犯新手错误的新手 - 构建了一个看起来像简单的概念验证的东西。 AWS Bedrock 知识库、OpenSearch 无服务器后端。没什么花哨的。一些 LLM 查询，可能上传了 2 GB 的 PDF 进行测试。他预计大概是二十或三十美元。发票退回200多美元。他花了一个小时盯着这些订单项，试图弄清楚发生了什么。没有错误，没有黑客。就是这样工作的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Developer-Centric Cloud Architecture Framework (DCAF) for Enterprise Platforms】适用于企业平台的以开发人员为中心的云架构框架 (DCAF)</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/developer-centric-cloud-architecture-framework-dcaf</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;441&#34; data-start=&#34;262&#34;&gt;Enterprise-class &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-systems-drift-exceptions-turn-normal&#34;&gt;cloud systems&lt;/a&gt; seldom fail because of infrastructure constraints; rather, problems arise when architectural vision cannot scale to match the scale of the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;575&#34; data-start=&#34;443&#34;&gt;With the increasing use of the cloud by various teams, geographic locations, and business units, certain recurring scenarios emerge:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;441&#34; data-start=&#34;262&#34;&gt;企业级&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-systems-drift-exceptions-turn-normal&#34;&gt;云系统&lt;/a&gt;很少会因为基础设施限制而出现故障；相反，当架构愿景无法扩展以匹配业务规模时，就会出现问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;575&#34; data-start=&#34;443&#34;&gt;随着各个团队、地理位置和业务部门越来越多地使用云，会出现某些反复出现的场景：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>