<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Playwright for Real-Time Applications: Testing WebSockets and Live Data Streams】实时应用程序的剧作家：测试 WebSocket 和实时数据流</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/playwright-for-real-time-applications-testing-webs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;462&#34; data-start=&#34;308&#34;&gt;Real-time applications are everywhere these days. From chat apps to stock dashboards and collaborative tools, users expect instant feedback.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;692&#34; data-start=&#34;464&#34;&gt;If you’ve ever tried to test these apps, you know the challenge: traditional automation just doesn’t cut it. The page doesn’t reload, elements appear and disappear unpredictably, and multiple users can interact simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 462” data-start =“ 308”&gt;实时应用程序如今无处不在。从聊天应用到库存仪表板和协作工具，用户期望即时反馈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 692” data-start =“ 464”&gt;如果您曾经尝试过测试这些应用程序，则会知道挑战：传统自动化不会削减它。该页面没有重新加载，元素出现并消失了不可预测，并且多个用户可以同时进行交互。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hyperparameter Tuning and Feature Engineering: A Guide to Optimizing Machine Learning Models】高参数调整和功能工程：优化机器学习模型的指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/hyperparameter-tuning-feature-engineering-ml</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Unlocking maximum performance from machine learning (ML) models rarely comes down to modeling choices alone. Far more often, excellence rests on how well one tunes hyperparameters and how deftly one engineers features. These processes-the quiet backbone of practical machine learning-are where the gap between acceptable and outstanding results is made or lost. This guide explores actionable strategies and decision frameworks for both, showing experienced developers and ML leads how targeted optimization can drive tangible business outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why Model Optimization Matters: Impact on Outcomes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Building a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/creating-and-serving-your-first-machine-learning-m&#34;&gt;machine learning model&lt;/a&gt; is relatively straightforward. Ensuring that the model is reliable, performant, and cost-effective in real-world environments is not. Under-optimized models carry hidden costs: wasted compute, poor user experience, biased or unstable predictions, and missed commercial opportunities. In production, these issues can translate to direct business losses or negative user impact.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;从机器学习（ML）模型中解锁最大性能很少归结为仅建模选择。卓越的频率更高，这取决于一个人对超参数的调音以及一位工程师的特征。这些过程 - 实用机器学习的安静骨干 - 是可接受和杰出结果之间的差距。本指南探讨了两者的可行策略和决策框架，显示有经验的开发人员和ML领导目标优化如何推动切实的业务成果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么模型优化很重要：对结果的影响&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;构建a &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/creating-and-serving-your-first-machine-learning-m”&gt;机器学习模型&lt;/a&gt;相对简单。在现实环境中确保模型可靠，性能和成本效益不是。不足优化的模型带有隐藏的成本：浪费的计算，差的用户体验，偏见或不稳定的预测以及错过的商业机会。在生产中，这些问题可以转化为直接业务损失或用户负面影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why GPT-OSS:20B Feels Painfully Slow (And How Quantization Can Save Your Sanity)】为什么 GPT-OSS:20B 感觉慢得令人痛苦（以及量化如何拯救你的理智）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimize-gpt-oss20b-quantization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you are into AI and specifically generative AI, you definitely did not miss the buzz about OpenAI releasing open-source models for the first time since February 2019, and this was with GPT-2.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s like OpenAI has finally brought back the open into play.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您进入了AI，特别是Generative AI，那么自2019年2月以来，您绝对不会错过Openai发布开源型号的嗡嗡声，这是GPT-2。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;就像Openai终于将公开赛恢复了。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【LangGraph Beginner to Advanced: Part 1 — Introduction to LangGraph and Some Basic Concepts】langgraph的高级初学者：第1部分 - 朗格拉夫和一些基本概念简介</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/langgraph-beginner-to-advanced-introduction</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;f394&#34;&gt;Welcome to this &lt;strong&gt;LangGraph Beginner to Advanced series&lt;/strong&gt;. LangGraph is one of the most popular frameworks for building agentic AI applications. With agentic AI, the application has a lot more scope and tasks to accomplish by navigating various flows and autonomously invoking various agents to fulfill a task completely. LangGraph is built within the LangChain system to act as an orchestration framework to build a multi-step flow for each task execution. Unlike a linear chain of events that you build with LangChain, with a multi-step flow, the orchestration can have logical conditions that decide which agent to invoke, it can make decisions, use various tools, and maintain the state of the conversation throughout the flow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;b678&#34;&gt;If you’ve ever wanted to build AI agents and design graph-based conversational workflows, this course-style blog series is for you.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name =“ f394”&gt;欢迎来到高级系列&lt;/strong&gt;的&lt;strong&gt; langgraph初学者。 Langgraph是建筑代理AI应用程序最受欢迎的框架之一。借助Agesic AI，该应用程序具有更多的范围和任务，可以通过导航各种流程并自主调用各种代理以完全完成任务。 Langgraph构建在Langchain系统中，以充当编排框架，为每个任务执行构建多步流。与您使用Langchain建立的线性事件链不同，编排可以具有决定要调用哪种代理的逻辑条件，它可以做出决策，使用各种工具，并在整个流程中保持对话状态。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name =“ b678”&gt;如果您曾经想构建AI代理和设计基于图形的对话工作流，则此课程风格的博客系列适合您。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Predictable Low Latencies for Apache HBase】Apache HBase可预测的低潜伏期</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/predictable-low-latencies-apache-hbase</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apache HBase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apache HBase is an open-source, strongly consistent distributed database designed to store record-oriented data across a scalable cluster of machines. HBase stores rows of data in &lt;strong&gt;tables&lt;/strong&gt; that can be grouped into &lt;strong&gt;namespaces&lt;/strong&gt;, and a table can belong to only one namespace at a time. Tables are split into groups of lexicographically adjacent rows called regions. By &#34;lexicographically adjacent,&#34; we mean that all rows in the table that sort between the region’s start row key and end row key are stored in the same region.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regions&lt;/strong&gt; are distributed across the cluster, hosted, and made available to clients by RegionServer processes. Regions are the physical mechanism used to shard and distribute the write and query load across the fleet of RegionServers. Regions are also non-overlapping: A single row key belongs to exactly one region at any point in time. Together with the special META table, a table’s regions effectively form a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/B-tree&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;B-tree&lt;/a&gt; for the purposes of locating a row within a table.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Apache HBase &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Apache HBase是一种开源，非常一致的分布式数据库，旨在在可扩展的机器群中存储以记录为导向的数据。 HBASE将数据行存储在&lt;strong&gt;表中&lt;/strong&gt;可以分组到&lt;strong&gt;命名空间&lt;/strong&gt;中，并且表一次只能属于一个名称空间。表被分为词典相邻行的组，称为区域。通过“词典相邻的词典”，我们的意思是表格在该区域的起始行键和结束行键之间排序的所有行都存储在同一区域中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;区域&lt;/strong&gt;分布在整个群集上，托管并由RegionServer流程提供给客户。区域是用于在整个地区舰队中分解和分配写入和查询负载的物理机制。区域也是不重叠的：一个行键在任何时间点都属于一个区域。与特殊的元表一起，一个表的区域有效地形成了a &lt;a href =“ https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/wiki/b-tree” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; b-tree &lt;/a&gt;是为了在桌子列表中找到一排。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering AOSP Bluetooth Debugging】掌握AOSP蓝牙调试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-aosp-bluetooth-debugging</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’re a Bluetooth system engineer working with AOSP, you already know debugging can get messy. Connections drop, profiles misbehave, and sometimes nothing seems to add up. In those moments, the dumpsys tool should be the first thing you reach for. And when it comes to Bluetooth, no command is more useful than adb shell dumpsys bluetooth_manager.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This single command can reveal a wealth of information about the state of the Bluetooth stack on your device. It tells you if Bluetooth is enabled, what profiles are running, whether devices are bonded, and even the state machines inside each profile. In short, it gives you a peek behind the curtain so you can figure out what’s really going on.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您是与AOSP一起工作的蓝牙系统工程师，您已经知道调试会变得凌乱。连接下降，表现不佳，有时似乎没有加起来。在那一刻，垃圾箱工具应该是您所追求的第一件事。当谈到蓝牙时，没有命令比adb shell dumpsys bluetooth_manager更有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此单个命令可以揭示有关设备上蓝牙堆栈状态的大量信息。它告诉您是否启用了蓝牙，运行了哪些配置文件，是否键入设备，甚至每个配置文件中的状态机。简而言之，它可以让您在窗帘后面窥视，以便您可以弄清楚到底发生了什么。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Developing Low-Cost AI-Based Similarity Search】开发基于低成本AI的相似性搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/developing-low-cost-ai-based-similarity-search</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The world of artificial intelligence (AI) and large language models (LLMs) often conjures images of immense computing power, proprietary platforms, and colossal GPU clusters. This perception can create a high barrier to entry, discouraging curious developers from exploring the fundamentals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently embarked on a project — a sophisticated yet simple &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tacticaxyz/tactica.faq.similaritysearch&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AI-powered chatbot&lt;/a&gt; I call the Wiki Navigator — that proves this complexity is often unnecessary for learning the essentials. By focusing on core concepts like &lt;strong&gt;tokenization, vector embeddings, and cosine similarity&lt;/strong&gt;, I built a functional RAG (retrieval-augmented generation) search solution that operates across 9,000 documents in the Chromium open-source codebase. It took me a few hours to run, and the next day, I was able to reuse the same codebase to train a chatbot on open-source books about the Rust programming language to have useful help during my Rust learning journey.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能（AI）和大语言模型（LLM）的世界通常会想到巨大的计算能力，专有平台和巨大的GPU群集。这种看法可以创造出很高的入境障碍，使好奇的开发人员无法探索基本面。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently embarked on a project — a sophisticated yet simple &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tacticaxyz/tactica.faq.similaritysearch&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AI-powered chatbot&lt;/a&gt; I call the Wiki Navigator — that proves this complexity is often unnecessary for learning the要点。通过关注&lt;strong&gt;令牌化，矢量嵌入和余弦相似性等核心概念&lt;/strong&gt;，我构建了一个功能性的抹布（检索型生成生成）搜索解决方案，该搜索解决方案在铬开源代码库中的9,000个文档中运行。我花了几个小时才能跑步，第二天，我能够重复使用相同的代码库来培训有关Rust编程语言的开源书籍的聊天机器人，以在我的Rust学习旅程中获得有用的帮助。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【7 AWS Services Every Data Engineer Should Master】7 AWS服务每个数据工程师都应掌握</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-services-for-data-engineers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you work in data engineering, you know the job is a constant balance between speed, reliability, and maintainability. It is not enough to just move data from one system to another. You must make sure the process will still work next month, that it can handle more volume next year, and that someone else can understand it without asking you a hundred questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been through years of building &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/etl-architecture-multi-source-data-integration&#34;&gt;ETL jobs&lt;/a&gt;, chasing down broken pipelines, rewriting transformations after schema changes, and tuning performance when reports were too slow to be useful. The biggest lesson is that the tools you choose matter more than you think. The wrong choice can lead to constant firefighting. The right one can make the system almost invisible because it just works.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您从事数据工程工作，则知道该作业是速度，可靠性和可维护性之间的持续平衡。仅将数据从一个系统移至另一个系统是不够的。您必须确保该过程下个月仍然可以正常工作，明年它可以处理更多的音量，并且其他人可以理解它而无需问您一百个问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我已经经历了多年的建设&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/etl-architecture-multi-source-data-integration”&gt; etl jobs &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;/a&gt;，追逐损坏的管道，架构后的重写转换以及在报告后更慢的情况下的调整性能太慢而无法使用。最大的教训是，您选择的工具比您想象的要重要。错误的选择会导致不断的消防。正确的一个可以使系统几乎看不见。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guardrails for AI: Protecting Privacy in Both Prompts and Responses】AI的护栏：在提示和响应中保护隐私</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guardrails-for-ai-privacy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Large language models (LLMs) like OpenAI’s ChatGPT, Anthropic’s Claude, Google’s Gemini, or Meta’s Llama have taken the world by storm, offering powerful text-generation capabilities for everything from coding help to customer service. But as their use grows, so do concerns about privacy and data protection.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the past year alone, an internal data leak at Samsung prompted the company to ban employees from using ChatGPT &lt;a href=&#34;https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/02/samsung-bans-use-of-generative-ai-tools-like-chatgpt-after-april-internal-data-leak/#:~:text=A%20month%20after%20internal%2C%20sensitive,services%20like%20Bard%20from%20Google&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;, and Italy’s data protection authority temporarily blocked ChatGPT nationwide over alleged privacy violations &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reuters.com/technology/italy-data-protection-agency-opens-chatgpt-probe-privacy-concerns-2023-03-31/#:~:text=Sign%20up%20here&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;[2]&lt;/a&gt;. These incidents underscore a critical point: both what we put into these LLMs and AI systems, and what they output, can pose serious privacy risks.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大型语言模型（LLMS），例如Openai的Chatgpt，人类的Claude，Google的Gemini或Meta的Llama席卷了世界，为所有事物提供了强大的文本生成能力，包括对客户服务的编码帮助。但是随着它们使用的增长，因此对隐私和数据保护的关注。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仅在过去的一年中，三星的内部数据泄漏促使该公司禁止员工使用Chatgpt &lt;a href =“ https://techcrunch.com/2023/05/02/samsung-bans-use-of-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-like-like-chatgpt--chatgpt-fer-april-april-internal-internal-data-leak/#: text = ext = xtt = xt = axt = axt = axt = a%20month; rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; [1] &lt;/a&gt;，意大利的数据保护局因涉嫌侵犯隐私权而暂时阻止了全国范围内的Chatgpt &lt;a href =“ https://www.reuters.com/technology/itey-data-protection-protection-agency-agency-opens-chatgpt-probe-probe-probe-privacy-concerns-concern--2023-03-03-03-31/#: text = fast = xt = xign = sign;这些事件强调了一个关键点：我们投入这些LLM和AI系统及其输出的内容都可能构成严重的隐私风险。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Brief Overview of Designing and Testing Effective Chatbots】设计和测试有效聊天机器人的简要概述</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/designing-testing-effective-chatbots</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As startups, enterprises&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; and individuals all around are looking to understand how they can incorporate chatbots into their systems for customer service&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; internal workflows&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; and compliance&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; it is incredibly important to understand how you should design and test these for them to be truly effective.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With bigger large language models and tools such as retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/model-context-protocol-mcp-guide-architecture-uses-implementation&#34;&gt;Model Context Protocol&lt;/a&gt; (MCP) all the craze&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; it is important to understand that if a clear understanding of use case&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; design&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; and testing isn&#39;t done&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; these will likely become &#34;black boxes.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为初创企业，企业&lt;em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;和周围的个人都在寻求了解他们如何将聊天机器人纳入其系统中的客户服务&lt;em&gt;，&lt;em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;内部Workfrows &lt;em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;，您应该如何设计和测试它们，这是非常重要的。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;具有更大的大型语言模型和工具，例如重试的生成（RAG）和&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/model-context-protocol-mcp-guide-mcp-guide-architecture-usecture-uss-imimplementation-imimplementation-&#39;&gt; posent上下文协议&lt;/a&gt;（mcp）（MCP）所有狂热的使用&lt;/a&gt;案例&lt;em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;设计&lt;em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;和测试未完成&lt;em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt;，这些可能会变成“黑匣子”。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>