<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【The Modern Era of Data Orchestration: From Data Fragmentation to Collaboration】数据编排的现代时代：从数据碎片到协作</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-modern-era-of-data-orchestration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-data-engineering-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Data Engineering: Enriching Data Pipelines, Expanding AI, and Expediting Analytics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Data engineering and software engineering have long been at odds, each with their own unique tools and best practices. A key differentiator has been the need for dedicated orchestration when building data products. In this article, we&#39;ll explore the role data orchestrators play and how recent trends in the industry may be bringing these two disciplines closer together than ever before.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-data-engineering-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;数据工程：丰富数据管道、扩展人工智能和加速分析&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a &gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;数据工程和软件工程长期以来一直存在分歧，各自都有自己独特的工具和最佳实践。一个关键的区别是在构建数据产品时需要专门的编排。在本文中，我们将探讨数据协调器所扮演的角色，以及行业的最新趋势如何使这两个学科比以往任何时候都更加紧密地结合在一起。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Digitalization of Airport and Airlines With IoT and Data Streaming Using Kafka and Flink】使用 Kafka 和 Flink 通过物联网和数据流实现机场和航空公司的数字化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/digitalization-of-airport-and-airlines</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The digitalization of airports faces challenges such as integrating diverse legacy systems, ensuring cybersecurity, and managing the vast amounts of data generated in real time. The vision for a digitalized airport includes seamless passenger experiences, optimized operations, consistent integration with airlines and retail stores, and enhanced security through the use of advanced technologies like IoT, AI, and real-time data analytics. This blog post shows the relevance of data streaming with Apache Kafka and Flink in the aviation industry to enable data-driven business process automation and innovation while modernizing the IT infrastructure with cloud-native hybrid cloud architecture. Schiphol Group operating Amsterdam Airport shows a few real-world deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Digitalization of Airports and the Aviation Industry&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Digitalization transforms airport operations and improves the experience of employees and passengers. It affects various aspects of airport operations, passenger experiences, and overall efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;机场的数字化面临着集成各种遗留系统、确保网络安全以及管理实时生成的大量数据等挑战。数字化机场的愿景包括无缝的乘客体验、优化的运营、与航空公司和零售商店的一致集成，以及通过使用物联网、人工智能和实时数据分析等先进技术来增强安全性。这篇博文展示了在航空业中使用 Apache Kafka 和 Flink 进行数据流处理的相关性，以实现数据驱动的业务流程自动化和创新，同时利用云原生混合云架构实现 IT 基础设施的现代化。运营阿姆斯特丹机场的史基浦集团展示了一些实际部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;机场和航空业的数字化&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数字化改变了机场运营并改善了员工和乘客的体验。它影响机场运营、乘客体验和整体效率的各个方面。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Vector Search Performance With Elasticsearch】使用 Elasticsearch 优化矢量搜索性能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-vector-search-performance-with-elasticsearch</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In an era characterized by an exponential increase in data generation, organizations must effectively leverage this wealth of information to maintain their competitive edge. Efficiently searching and analyzing customer data — such as identifying user preferences for movie recommendations or &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/simple-sentiment-analysis-with-nlp&#34;&gt;sentiment analysis&lt;/a&gt; — plays a crucial role in driving informed decision-making and enhancing user experiences. For instance, a streaming service can employ &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/vector-search-hottest-topic-in-information-retrieval&#34;&gt;vector search&lt;/a&gt; to recommend films tailored to individual viewing histories and ratings, while a retail brand can analyze customer sentiments to fine-tune marketing strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As data engineers, we are tasked with implementing these sophisticated solutions, ensuring organizations can derive actionable insights from vast datasets. This article explores the intricacies of vector search using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-elasticsearch-1&#34;&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/a&gt;, focusing on effective techniques and best practices to optimize performance. By examining case studies on image retrieval for personalized marketing and text analysis for customer sentiment clustering, we demonstrate how optimizing vector search can lead to improved customer interactions and significant business growth.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在数据生成呈指数级增长的时代，组织必须有效利用这些丰富的信息来保持竞争优势。有效搜索和分析客户数据 - 例如确定用户对电影推荐的偏好或&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/simple-sentiment-analysis-with-nlp&#34;&gt;情绪分析&lt;/a&gt; - 发挥作用在推动明智决策和增强用户体验方面发挥着至关重要的作用。例如，流媒体服务可以使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/vector-search-hottest-topic-in-information-retrieval&#34;&gt;矢量搜索&lt;/a&gt;来推荐适合个人的电影查看历史记录和评分，而零售品牌可以分析客户情绪以调整营销策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为数据工程师，我们的任务是实施这些复杂的解决方案，确保组织能够从庞大的数据集中获得可行的见解。本文探讨了使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-elasticsearch-1&#34;&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/a&gt; 进行矢量搜索的复杂性，重点介绍优化性能的有效技术和最佳实践。通过研究用于个性化营销的图像检索和用于客户情绪聚类的文本分析的案例研究，我们演示了优化矢量搜索如何改善客户互动并实现显着的业务增长。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Distributed System Performance… From the Grocery Store】从杂货店了解分布式系统性能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/distributed-system-performance-grocery-store</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I visited a small local grocery store which happens to be in a touristy part of my neighborhood. If you’ve ever traveled abroad, then you’ve probably visited a store like that to stock up on bottled water without purchasing the overpriced hotel equivalent. This was one of these stores.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To my misfortune, my visit happened to coincide with a group of tourists arriving all at once to buy beverages and warm up (it’s winter!).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我参观了当地的一家小杂货店，它恰好位于我附近的旅游胜地。如果您曾经出国旅行过，那么您可能会去过这样的商店购买瓶装水，而无需购买价格过高的酒店同等产品。这是其中一间商店。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不幸的是，我的访问恰逢一群游客同时到来购买饮料和取暖（现在是冬天！）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 22:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Supporting Multiple Redis Databases With Infinispan Cache Aliases Enhancement】通过 Infinispan 缓存别名增强支持多个 Redis 数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/supporting-multiple-redis-databases-with-infinispan</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In Infinispan 15, we provided a large set of commands to make it possible to replace your Redis Server with Infinispan without changing your code. In this tutorial, you will learn how Infinispan cache aliases will help you replace your Redis Server with Infinispan for multiple Redis databases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key takeaways&lt;/strong&gt;:&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;What are cache aliases and how to create caches with aliases or update existing ones&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;Learn how Infinispan and Redis differ in data organization&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;Support multiple databases in Infinispan with cache aliases when using the &lt;strong&gt;RESP protocol&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Supporting multiple Redis databases has been available since Infinispan 15.0 (the latest stable release at the time of this writing). However, Hot Rod, CLI, and Infinispan Console support is Tech Preview in Infinispan 15.1 (in development right now).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在 Infinispan 15 中，我们提供了大量命令，使您可以在不更改代码的情况下用 Infinispan 替换 Redis 服务器。在本教程中，您将了解 Infinispan 缓存别名如何帮助您使用 Infinispan 替换多个 Redis 数据库的 Redis 服务器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;要点&lt;/strong&gt;：&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;什么是缓存别名以及如何使用别名创建缓存或更新现有缓存&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;了解 Infinispan 和 Redis 在数据组织方面有何不同&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;使用 &lt;strong&gt;RESP 协议&lt;/strong&gt;时，通过缓存别名支持 Infinispan 中的多个数据库&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自 Infinispan 15.0（撰写本文时的最新稳定版本）以来，就可以支持多个 Redis 数据库。不过，Hot Rod、CLI 和 Infinispan Console 支持是 Infinispan 15.1 中的技术预览（目前正在开发中）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Flashcard Application With Next.js, Clerk, Firebase, Material UI, and LLaMA 3.1】具有 Next.js、Clerk、Firebase、Material UI 和 LLaMA 3.1 的 AI 支持的抽认卡应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-flashcard-application</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Flashcards have long been used as an effective tool for learning by providing quick, repeatable questions that help users memorize facts or concepts. Traditionally, flashcards contain a question on one side and the answer on the other. The concept is simple, yet powerful for retention, whether you&#39;re learning languages, mathematics, or any subject.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An AI-powered flashcard game takes this learning method to the next level. Rather than relying on static content, AI dynamically generates new questions and answers based on user input, learning patterns, and performance over time. This personalization makes the learning process more interactive and adaptive, providing questions that target specific areas where the user needs improvement.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;抽认卡长期以来一直被用作一种有效的学习工具，通过提供快速、可重复的问题来帮助用户记住事实或概念。传统上，抽认卡的一侧包含问题，另一侧包含答案。这个概念很简单，但无论您是在学习语言、数学还是任何学科，都可以有效地记住。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能驱动的抽认卡游戏将这种学习方法提升到了一个新的水平。人工智能不依赖静态内容，而是根据用户输入、学习模式和一段时间内的表现动态生成新的问题和答案。这种个性化使学习过程更具互动性和适应性，并针对用户需要改进的特定领域提供问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Showing Long Animation Frames in Your DevTools】在开发工具中显示长动画帧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/showing-long-animation-frames-in-your-devtools</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’re a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-of-web-development-predictions-and-poss&#34;&gt;web developer&lt;/a&gt;, you probably spend a fair amount of time working with Chrome DevTools. It’s one of the best tools out there for diagnosing and improving the performance of your web applications. You can use it to track loading times, optimize &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/corecss-part1&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/object-oriented-javascript&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt;, and inspect network activity. But there’s an important piece of performance data that DevTools doesn’t yet expose by default: Long Animation Frames (LoAFs).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, I’ll show you how to use the Performance API and Chrome’s extensibility features to expose LoAF data in DevTools. Along the way, I’ll explain what LoAFs are, why they’re crucial for web performance, and provide code snippets to help you track and debug them in your own projects.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-of-web-development-predictions-and-poss&#34;&gt;网络开发人员&lt;/a&gt;，您可能会花费相当多的时间使用 Chrome DevTools。它是诊断和提高 Web 应用程序性能的最佳工具之一。您可以使用它来跟踪加载时间、优化 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/corecss-part1&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz /object-oriented-javascript&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt;，并检查网络活动。但 DevTools 默认情况下尚未公开一项重要的性能数据：长动画帧 (LoAF)。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我将向您展示如何使用 Performance API 和 Chrome 的可扩展性功能在 DevTools 中公开 LoAF 数据。在此过程中，我将解释 LoAF 是什么、为什么它们对 Web 性能至关重要，并提供代码片段来帮助您在自己的项目中跟踪和调试它们。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Protect Yourself From the Inevitable GenAI Crash】如何保护自己免受不可避免的 GenAI 崩溃的影响</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/protect-yourself-from-the-inevitable-genai-crash</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I had the dubious pleasure of living through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dot-com_bubble&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;dot.com bubble&lt;/a&gt;, from the nascent early web in 1995 through the crash in 2000. It’s no wonder, therefore, that today’s generative AI (GenAI) bubble is giving me a serious case of déjà vu. Been there, done that, got the t-shirts to prove it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now I’m older and wiser. So listen up, young ‘uns, and let me pass along some hard-won wisdom from the last millennium.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我有幸度过了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dot-com_bubble&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;dot.com 泡沫&lt; /a&gt;，从 1995 年刚刚兴起的早期网络到 2000 年的崩溃。因此，毫不奇怪，今天的生成式人工智能 (GenAI) 泡沫让我有一种严重的似曾相识的感觉。去过那里，做到了这一点，并用 T 恤来证明这一点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在我长大了，也更聪明了。所以，听着，年轻人，让我传递一些上个千年来之不易的智慧。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 21:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ditch Your Local Setup: Develop Apps in the Cloud With Project IDX】放弃本地设置：使用 Project IDX 在云中开发应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/develop-apps-in-the-cloud-with-project-idx</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Recent years have seen a rise in cloud-based IDEs and several options have emerged such as CodeSandBox, Replit, StackBlitz, and more. Cloud-based IDEs allow programming without the need to have a dedicated developer specification machine as they run in the browser directly. They provide complete freedom of writing software from anywhere and anytime. These IDEs have traditionally been great at creating showcase demos and POCs, and have their limitations. In August 2023, Google launched its own cloud-based IDE known as Project IDX. Project IDX provides a complete development environment for developing multi-platform applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of Project IDX&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Project IDX has several key benefits over other major cloud-based IDEs:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;近年来，基于云的 IDE 不断兴起，并出现了多种选择，例如 CodeSandBox、Replit、StackBlitz 等。基于云的 IDE 允许编程，无需专用的开发人员规范机器，因为它们直接在浏览器中运行。它们提供随时随地编写软件的完全自由。这些 IDE 传统上非常擅长创建展示演示和 POC，但也有其局限性。 2023 年 8 月，Google 推出了自己的基于云的 IDE，称为 Project IDX。 Project IDX 为开发多平台应用程序提供了完整的开发环境。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;IDX 项目的优势&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与其他主要的基于云的 IDE 相比，Project IDX 有几个关键优势：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Oracle Database 23AI for Generative AI RAG Implementation: Part 1】使用 Oracle Database 23AI 实施生成式 AI RAG：第 1 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/oracle-database-23ai-for-genai-rag-part-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;At the recent &lt;a data-text-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://social.ora.cl/60035eVvJ&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CloudWorld&lt;/a&gt; event, Oracle introduced &lt;a data-text-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://www.oracle.com/database/free/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Oracle Database 23c&lt;/a&gt;, its next-generation database, which incorporates AI capabilities through the addition of AI vector search to its converged database. This vector search feature allows businesses to run multimodal queries that integrate various data types, enhancing the usefulness of GenAI in business applications. With Oracle Database 23c, there’s no need for a separate database to store and query AI-driven data. By supporting vector storage alongside relational tables, graphs, and other data types, Oracle 23c becomes a powerful tool for developers building business applications, especially for semantic search needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this two-part blog series, we’ll explore the basics of vectors and embeddings, explain how the Oracle vector database works, and develop a Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) application to enhance a local LLM.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在最近的&lt;a data-text-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://social.ora.cl/60035eVvJ&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CloudWorld&lt;/a&gt;活动中， Oracle 推出了 &lt;a data-text-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://www.oracle.com/database/free/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Oracle Database 23c&lt;/a&gt;，其下一代数据库，通过在其融合数据库中添加人工智能矢量搜索来整合人工智能功能。这种矢量搜索功能允许企业运行集成各种数据类型的多模式查询，从而增强 GenAI 在业务应用程序中的实用性。使用 Oracle Database 23c，无需单独的数据库来存储和查询 AI 驱动的数据。通过支持向量存储以及关系表、图形和其他数据类型，Oracle 23c 成为开发人员构建业务应用程序的强大工具，特别是满足语义搜索需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这个由两部分组成的博客系列中，我们将探讨向量和嵌入的基础知识，解释 Oracle 向量数据库的工作原理，并开发检索增强生成 (RAG) 应用程序来增强本地 LLM。&lt;/p &gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>