<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Self-Supervised Learning Techniques】自我监督的学习技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/self-supervised-learning-techniques-visual-tracking</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Visual tracking systems are essential for applications ranging from surveillance to autonomous navigation. However, these systems have a significant Achilles&#39; heel: they rely heavily on large, labeled datasets for training. This reliance makes it challenging to deploy them in real-world situations where labeled data is scarce or expensive to obtain. In this article, we will learn about self-supervised learning (SSL) and how it leverages unlabeled data to train models.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is the Problem?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Visual tracking involves identifying and following an object across frames in a video. Traditional methods depend on vast amounts of labeled data to learn how to recognize and track objects accurately. This dependence poses several problems:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;视觉跟踪系统对于从监视到自动导航的应用至关重要。但是，这些系统具有重要的致命弱点：它们严重依赖大型，标有培训的数据集。这种依赖使得将它们部署在现实世界中的情况很少或昂贵的情况下。在本文中，我们将了解自我监督的学习（SSL）以及它如何利用未标记的数据来培训模型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;有什么问题？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;视觉跟踪涉及在视频中识别和跟随对象。传统方法取决于大量标记的数据，以学习如何准确识别和跟踪对象。此依赖性提出了几个问题：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Traditional CI/CD Falls Short for Cloud Infrastructure】为什么传统的CI/CD在云基础架构上缩短</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cicd-falls-short-cloud-infrastructure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;For years, CI/CD pipelines have been the gold standard for software delivery—fast, repeatable, and reliable. But when it comes to cloud infrastructure, the model breaks down. It’s not that CI/CD is broken. It’s that infrastructure isn’t software. It has different constraints, different risks, and very different failure modes. And treating it like software introduces risk, drift, friction, and operational overhead—right when teams need speed and stability most.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The more your cloud estate grows, the more these problems compound—until visibility, control, and velocity start to erode.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;多年来，CI/CD管道一直是软件交付的黄金标准 - 快速，可重复且可靠。但是，当涉及云基础架构时，该模型会崩溃。并不是说CI/CD被打破了。基础架构不是软件。它具有不同的限制，不同的风险和非常不同的故障模式。像对待软件一样对待它会引入风险，漂移，摩擦和操作开销 - 当团队最需要速度和稳定性时，&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您的云庄园的增长越多，这些问题就越复杂 - 直到可见性，控制和速度开始侵蚀。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 11:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building V1 Gen-AI Products at Scale: Technical Product Patterns That Work】按大规模建造V1 Gen-AI产品：有效的技术产品模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gen-ai-v1-product-launch-enterprise</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Shipping the first version of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/top-generative-ai-services&#34;&gt;Gen-AI product&lt;/a&gt; is not only a technical problem but a systems-level event. Coordinating the product, infra, security, design, and executive layers when doing it in the enterprise or a consumer-grade setting is necessary. This is especially true when the product interacts with real users and serves in a business-critical environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This is not a testbed prompt with an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ive-built-an-automatic-proposal-generation-large-l&#34;&gt;open-source LLM&lt;/a&gt;. This is a real-world deployment; at this scale, every minute of latency and every hallucination incurred ceases to be some model parameter and becomes a business liability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;运送&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/top-generative-ai-services”&gt; gen-ai product &lt;/a&gt;不仅是一个技术问题，而且是系统级事件。在企业或消费级设置中进行产品时，必须协调产品，下文，安全性，设计和行政层。当产品与真实用户互动并在关键业务环境中服务时尤其如此。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这不是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ive-built-an-automatic-proposal-generation-large-large-l”&gt;开放式Source llm &lt;/a&gt;的测试床提示。这是现实世界的部署；在这个规模上，每分钟的延迟和每一个幻觉都停止成为某种模型参数并成为业务责任。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing Microservices Architecture With a Custom Spring Boot Starter and Auto-Configuration Framework】使用自定义弹簧启动器和自动配置框架设计微服务体系结构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/designing-microservices-architecture-with-a-custom-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Spring Boot has &amp;nbsp;Java development with its embedded servers, auto-configuration, and convention-over-configuration philosophy. Among its many features, one of the most powerful — but often underused — is the ability to create &lt;strong&gt;custom Spring Boot starters&lt;/strong&gt;. These components enable development teams to package and reuse common configuration and boilerplate logic, making microservices more modular, maintainable, and consistent across a large-scale enterprise platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores how to build and use custom &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-spring-boot-starters-integrate-with-your-project&#34;&gt;Spring Boot starters&lt;/a&gt; with auto-configuration to centralize concerns such as database access, authentication, and WebSocket communication, especially valuable in environments like loan servicing and trading platforms that operate with numerous microservices.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Spring Boot具有Java开发，其嵌入式服务器，自动配置和与会议的哲学哲学。在其许多功能中，最强大但通常没有使用的功能之一就是能够创建&lt;strong&gt;自定义春季启动器&lt;/strong&gt;。这些组件使开发团队能够包装和重复使用通用配置和样板逻辑，从而使微服务在大型企业平台上更加模块化，可维护和一致。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores how to build and use custom &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-spring-boot-starters-integrate-with-your-project&#34;&gt;Spring Boot starters&lt;/a&gt; with auto-configuration to centralize concerns such as database access, authentication, and WebSocket communication, especially valuable in environments like loan servicing and trading platforms that operate with numerous微服务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Use AI to Understand Gaps in Your Resume and Job Descriptions】如何使用AI了解简历和职位描述中的空白</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-ai-resumes-job-descriptiption-ats</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;At the beginning of my career, when I applied for jobs,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;I felt&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;there was always a gap between what my &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/smarter-hiring-building-an-ai-powered-full-stack-r&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;resume&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;had and what the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-fundamental-components-of-securing-a-job-as-a&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;job description &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;I used to spend many hours staring at my resume, second-guessing whether it reflected my skills correctly or aligned with the Job Description and what recruiters were looking for. Not knowing if my resume would surpass the Applicant Tracking Systems (ATS) drove me to understand what might work in today&#39;s job search game.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;That&#39;s when I realized that&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;there might be many of those who are&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;struggling with such issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;However, people who are constantly up-leveling their skills in software engineering and have gained might find it easier to at least get through the ATS filtering with their experience, specific job requirements, or domain knowledge needed to crack the job. But for someone who&#39;s new to software engineering or who knows how to use AI but needs a head start with building an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ai-ml&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;AI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; (LLM-based) tool for themselves, this solution might help.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;在我职业生涯的初期，当我申请工作时，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data data data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;我感到&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data data data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;我的&lt;/span&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/smarter-hiring-building-building-an-ai-power-power-stack-r”&gt; &lt;span data data data-proserver-spaces =“ true”&gt;简历&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span data data data data data-proserver space = href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-fundamental-components-of-securing-securing-a-job-as-a-”&gt; &lt;span data data-proserver-spaces =“ true”&gt;“ true”&gt;职位描述&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data data data data-proserver-spaces =“ true”&gt;第二猜测是正确地反映了我的技能还是与职位描述以及招聘人员想要的内容相符。不知道我的履历是否会超过申请人跟踪系统（ATS）促使我了解当今求职游戏中可能有效的内容。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-data-proserver空间=“ true”&gt;那是我意识到&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-parserver spaces =“ true”&gt;可能有许多是&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;在此类问题上挣扎。至少要通过其经验，特定的工作要求或破解工作所需的领域知识来通过ATS过滤。 But for someone who&#39;s new to software engineering or who knows how to use AI but needs a head start with building an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ai-ml&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;AI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; (LLM-based) tool for themselves, this solution might help. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Time Market Data Processing: Designing Systems for Low Latency and High Throughput】实时市场数据处理：为低潜伏期和高吞吐量设计系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-market-data-processing-designing-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In financial markets, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/batch-vs-real-time-processing-understanding-the-differences&#34;&gt;real-time data processing&lt;/a&gt; is critical for trading, risk management, and decision-making. Market data systems must ingest and process millions of updates per second while ensuring ultra-low latency. During my time at Bloomberg and Two Sigma, I worked on optimizing such systems for speed and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By the means of this article, I’d like to explore key challenges in real-time market data processing, design strategies, and optimizations—with code snippets where applicable. I’ll try my best to keep things succinct without going into too much details!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在金融市场中，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/batch-vs-vs-real time-processing-undercessing-undercanding-the-differences”&gt;实时数据处理&lt;/a&gt;对于交易，风险管理和决策至关重要。市场数据系统必须每秒摄入并处理数百万个更新，同时确保超低潜伏期。在彭博社和两个Sigma期间，我致力于优化此类系统以提高速度和可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过本文，我想探讨实时市场数据处理，设计策略和优化方面的关键挑战，并在适用的情况下进行代码段。我会尽力使事情保持简洁，而无需介绍太多细节！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The OWASP Top 10 for LLM Applications: An Overview of AI Security Risks】LLM应用程序的OWASP前10名：AI安全风险的概述</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/owasp-top-10-llm-security-risks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The world of AI, especially with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-comprehensive-guide&#34;&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs) and Generative AI&lt;/a&gt;, is changing the game. It&#39;s like we&#39;ve unlocked a superpower for creating content, automating tasks, and solving tricky problems. But, as with any new superpower, there are new ways things can go wrong. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/deploying-llms-securely-with-owasp-top-10&#34;&gt;Open Worldwide Application Security Project&lt;/a&gt; (OWASP) experts have put together a list of the top 10 security risks specifically for these new AI applications in 2025. Think of it as a field guide to help everyone from developers to CISO’s, spot and fix these new kinds of digital vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s break down these top 10 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-security-challenges-best-practices&#34;&gt;AI security risks&lt;/a&gt;, with simple explanations and everyday examples:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; AI的世界，尤其是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-comprehend-guide”&gt;大语言模型（LLMS）和Generative AI &lt;/a&gt;正在改变游戏。就像我们解锁了创建内容，自动化任务和解决棘手问题的超级大国一样。但是，与任何新的超级大国一样，事情可能会出错。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/deploying-llms-securely-with-owasp-top-10”&gt;全球范围内的应用程序安全项目&lt;/a&gt;（OWASP）专家汇总了这些新的AI应用程序的专门列表，这些新AI在2025年中的新ai指南都可以帮助所有领域，以帮助这些新的AI范围，以帮助这些新的AI范围，以帮助这些新的Fielders the Unight It the Enfication。漏洞。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们分解这些前10个&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-security-challenges-best--------------------&gt; ai安全风险&lt;/a&gt;，带有简单的解释和日常示例：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Seata the Deal: No More Distributed Transaction Nightmares Across (Spring Boot) Microservices】SEATA交易：不再有分布式交易的噩梦（春季靴）微服务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/seata-distributed-transactions-spring-boot-microservices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In a time when nostalgia may have gone a little too far, the software development world has been swept by a heated debate: has the massive adoption of the microservices pattern truly delivered the expected benefits, or is its balance sheet more uncertain? Many teams are starting to wonder whether it’s time for a “homecoming” to the good old, reliable monolith — or if the answer lies somewhere in between, in the form of the modular monolith.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;fr-inner&#34; contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;A distracted architect&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;strong&gt;distributed transactions&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在怀旧之时可能走得太远了，软件开发界已经被激烈的辩论所席卷：是否大量采用微服务模式确实带来了预期的收益，还是它的资产负债表更加不确定？许多团队开始怀疑是时候该对旧的，可靠的巨石进行“归乡”，或者答案是否位于模块化巨石的形式中。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class =“ fr-inner” contenteaditable =“ true”&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption contentedible =“ true”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;分心的建筑师&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;strong&gt;分布式交易&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advanced gRPC in Microservices: Hard-Won Insights and Best Practices】微服务的高级GRPC：硬赢的见解和最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-grpc-in-microservices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Building microservices at scale often means pushing beyond the basics of gRPC. Many teams adopt gRPC for its high performance and cross-language support, only to discover subtle complexities when running it in production. In this article, we delve into advanced gRPC concepts — streaming, deadlines, interceptors, load balancing — and share practical “dos and don’ts” learned from real-world systems. We’ll also examine how industry leaders like Netflix have leveraged gRPC to boost productivity and solve tough issues in their microservice architectures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The goal is a leadership-level view of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-grpc-concepts-use-cases-amp-best-pra&#34;&gt;gRPC&lt;/a&gt;: not just how to write a service, but how to build and scale a gRPC-based microservice ecosystem effectively. Let’s explore the key concepts and hard-won lessons for making the most of gRPC in production.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;规模构建微服务通常意味着推动超越GRPC的基础。许多团队的高性能和跨语言支持采用GRPC，只是在生产中运行它时发现了微妙的复杂性。在本文中，我们深入研究了先进的GRPC概念 - 流媒体，截止日期，拦截器，负载平衡 - 并共享从现实世界系统中学到的实用“ DOS和DOSS”。我们还将研究Netflix等行业领导者如何利用GRPC来提高生产力并解决其微服务体系结构中的艰难问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;目标是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-grpc-concepts-use-cases-use-cases-cases-amp-best-pra”&gt; grpc &lt;/a&gt;的领导力级别的观点：不仅是如何构建和规模缩放基于GRPC的Microservice EcosSems。让我们探讨以充分利用生产中GRPC的关键概念和硬季节。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How We Broke the Monolith (and Kept Our Sanity): Lessons From Moving to Microservices】我们如何打破整体（并保持理智）：从移向微服务的教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-we-broke-the-monolith-and-kept-our-sanity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;514&#34; data-start=&#34;184&#34;&gt;If you’ve ever been nervous about deploying code on a Friday, trust me — you’re not alone. A few years ago, I was leading a team at a major e-commerce company, wrangling a monolithic beast that could break in a hundred creative ways. The idea of microservices was everywhere, but nobody really tells you about the messy parts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;614&#34; data-start=&#34;516&#34;&gt;Here’s what we learned the hard way — warts and all — while moving from &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-you-should-move-from-monolith-to-microservices&#34;&gt;monolith to microservices&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 514” data-start =“ 184”&gt;如果您曾经对周五部署代码感到紧张，请相信我 - 您并不孤单。几年前，我在一家大型电子商务公司领导了一支团队，他扭转了一只可以以一百个创造性方式破坏的整体野兽。微服务的想法无处不在，但没有人真正告诉您有关杂乱的部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 614” data-start =“ 516”&gt;这是我们从&lt;a href =“ https：//dzone.com/articles/why-youou shy-youould-move-from-monolith-monolith-monolith-monolith-to-microserces”&gt; Monolith of Microservices&#39;&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>