<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Apache Spark Framework for Clustering Algorithms in Distributed Mode】用于在分布式模式下聚类算法的Apache Spark框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/apache-spark-clustering-algorithms-distributed-mode</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Apache Spark is a distributed computing engine that has libraries for building data pipelines using programming APIs, SQL API, and APIs for carrying out tasks that are part of the machine learning life cycle, such as feature engineering, model training, inference, and evaluation. The advantage of SparkML is that it can leverage computing power across the nodes, VMs, or containers to execute computationally and memory-intensive model training.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;However, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/apache-spark-all-you-need-to-know&#34;&gt;SparkML&lt;/a&gt; does not support every machine learning algorithm out of the box. Several advanced or specialized algorithms, particularly in the area of unsupervised learning, are not currently implemented in SparkML, and DBSCAN is one such unsupervised clustering algorithm. These algorithms are highly valuable for tasks where cluster boundaries are non-linear or when the number of clusters is not known in advance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Apache Spark是一种分布式计算引擎，它具有用于使用编程API，SQL API和API来构建数据管道的库，用于执行是机器学习生命周期的一部分，例如功能工程，模型培训，推断和评估。 SparkML的优点是它可以利用节点，VM或容器的计算能力来执行计算和内存密集型模型培训。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;但是，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/apache-park-spark-all-you-need-to-need-know”&gt; sparkml &lt;/a&gt;不支持每个机器学习算法。 SparkML目前尚未实施几种高级或专业算法，特别是在无监督学习领域，而DBSCAN是一种无监督的聚类算法。这些算法对于集群边界非线性或群集数不提前知道的任务非常有价值。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for iPaaS: A Shift Towards Intelligent Automation】2025年Gartner魔术象限用于IPAAS：向智能自动化的转变</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gartner-ipaas-2025-ai-low-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The latest 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/integration-platform-as-a-service-ipaas&#34;&gt;Integration Platform as a Service&lt;/a&gt; (iPaaS) highlights a transformational shift that&#39;s beginning to redefine the future of integration. Once a sector dominated by traditional vendors and service bus-based architectures, the iPaaS space is now undergoing a dramatic evolution — driven by low-code platforms, artificial intelligence (AI), and agentic automation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What was once a relatively stable market focused on cloud-to-cloud and hybrid integration has now expanded into a converged space that touches workflow automation, robotic process automation (RPA), and AI orchestration. This year&#39;s Gartner report is especially important for IT leaders, architects, and developers looking to align their integration strategies with the next decade of business transformation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/integration-platform-as-a-a-service-ipaas”&gt;集成平台作为服务&lt;/a&gt;（ipaas）强调了一个未来整合的变革转变。曾经是一个由传统供应商和基于服务总线的架构主导的部门，IPAAS空间现在正在经历戏剧性的发展 - 由低代码平台，人工智能（AI）和代理自动化驱动。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;曾经是一个相对稳定的市场，专注于云到云和混合集成，现已扩展为融合的空间，该空间触及了工作流动自动化，机器人过程自动化（RPA）和AI编排。今年的Gartner报告对于IT领导者，建筑师和开发人员尤其重要</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Driven Threat Hunting: Catching Zero-Day Exploits Before They Strike】AI驱动的威胁狩猎：捕获零日的利用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-driven-threat-hunting-zero-day-exploit-detection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Picture this: you&#39;re a cybersecurity pro up against an invisible enemy. Hidden in your network are zero-day exploits, which represent unknown vulnerabilities that await their moment to strike. The time you spend examining logs becomes pointless because the attack might already be causing harm. AI-driven threat hunting emerges as your most valuable new ally. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Your network receives a real-time protection system through AI, which functions like a super-intelligent guard dog that detects threats. The following article explains how AI detects hard-to-find threats while demonstrating its real-world impact and providing Python-based instructions to create your own threat-hunting tool. Buckle up, let’s go!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;图片：您是一个网络安全专业人士，反对一个看不见的敌人。隐藏在您的网络中的是零日的利用，这代表了未知的漏洞，等待其罢工的时刻。您花费检查日志的时间变得毫无意义，因为攻击可能已经造成伤害。 AI驱动的威胁狩猎是您最有价值的新盟友。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您的网络通过AI接收一个实时保护系统，该系统的功能像检测威胁的超级智能护卫狗。以下文章解释了AI在展示其现实世界影响的同时如何检测到难以找到的威胁，并提供基于Python的指示来创建自己的威胁狩猎工具。系好，让我们走！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Federated Identity: The Modern Approach to Cloud Security and Automation】联合身份：现代的云安全和自动化方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/federated-identity-cloud-security-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;582&#34; data-start=&#34;150&#34;&gt;In the rapidly evolving landscape of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-need&#34;&gt;cloud automation&lt;/a&gt; and multi-cloud strategies, the secure handling of sensitive data, particularly credentials, has emerged as a paramount concern. Traditional methods of storing long-lived credentials, whether in configuration files, CI/CD pipelines, or dedicated secret managers, introduce significant operational overhead and, more critically, expose organizations to heightened security risks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;875&#34; data-start=&#34;584&#34;&gt;Enter &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identity-federation-simplifying-authentication-and&#34;&gt;federated identity credentials&lt;/a&gt; — a modern, robust alternative that allows workloads to authenticate using ephemeral tokens issued by trusted identity providers. This approach eliminates the need for persistent secret storage, fundamentally transforming how cloud automation is secured.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 582” data-start =“ 150”&gt;在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/everythicty-you-need”&gt; cloud you-need的迅速发展的景观中，&lt;/a&gt;和多人cloud-cloud策略，敏感数据的安全处理，尤其是符合条件，尤其是符合条件，尤其是comparact。无论是在配置文件，CI/CD管道还是专门的秘密经理中，都会引入大量的运营开销，更重要的是将组织暴露于增强的安全风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;875&#34; data-start=&#34;584&#34;&gt;Enter &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identity-federation-simplifying-authentication-and&#34;&gt;federated identity credentials&lt;/a&gt; — a modern, robust alternative that allows workloads to authenticate using ephemeral tokens issued by trusted identity providers.这种方法消除了对持续秘密存储的需求，从根本上改变了云自动化的确保。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Secure Transaction APIs for Modern Fintech Systems Using GitHub Copilot】使用GitHub Copilot为现代金融科技系统建立安全的交易API</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-transaction-api-fintech-github-copilot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;GitHub Copilot is not just a new tool anymore. It&#39;s becoming a code productivity accelerator tool. In regulated industries like fintech, where speed must match uncompromising security standards. AI-assisted coding can shift the developer workflow from reactive to proactive.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In fintech, where delays can mean failed transactions or regulatory breaches, building performant and secure APIs quickly is mission-critical. This is where&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/github-copilot-secure-code-writing&#34;&gt; GitHub Copilot&lt;/a&gt; comes in with speed and structure to help developers build secure components without breaking the flow. This is a key advantage when time-to-market is critical in financial applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; github副驾驶不再只是一个新工具。它已成为代码生产力加速器工具。在像金融科技这样的受监管行业中，速度必须符合毫不妥协的安全标准。 AI辅助编码可以将开发人员的工作流程从反应性转移到主动。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在金融科技中，延误可能意味着失败的交易或监管漏洞，迅速建立表演和安全的API至关重要。这就是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/github-copilot-secure-code-writing”&gt; github copilot &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;有速度和结构来帮助开发人员在不破坏流程的情况下构建安全的组件。当上市时间在财务应用中至关重要时，这是一个关键优势。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Demystifying Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) in the Deep Learning】在深度学习中揭开卷积神经网络（CNN）的神秘面纱</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cnn-convolutional-neural-networks-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Thinking through my experience in working with Deep learning models has been rewarding. From reading raw pixels to powering self-driving cars, CNNs remain the cornerstone of modern visual perception. This article walks through how they work, why they matter, and where they&#39;re headed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why Convolution?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;393&#34; data-start=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/basic-convolutional-neural-network-architectures&#34;&gt;Convolution&lt;/a&gt;, in a nutshell, is a way of “mixing” two functions (or two arrays of numbers) so that one acts as a &lt;em data-end=&#34;122&#34; data-start=&#34;114&#34;&gt;filter&lt;/em&gt; over the other. It measures how much the two overlap as one slides (shifts) across the other. Because of that sliding‑and‑multiplying behavior, convolution extracts local patterns and produces a new signal or image in which those patterns are emphasized or suppressed.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;通过我与深度学习模型合作的经验进行思考是很有意义的。从阅读原始像素到为自动驾驶汽车提供动力，CNN仍然是现代视觉感知的基石。本文介绍了他们的工作方式，为什么重要以及他们前进的位置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么要卷积？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 393” data-start =“ 0”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/basic-convolutional-neural-neural-network-architectures”&gt;卷积&lt;/a&gt;，简而data-start =“ 114”&gt; filter &lt;/em&gt;在另一个上方。它衡量了两个幻灯片（移动）越过另一个幻灯片的重叠程度。由于这种滑动和长期行为，卷积提取了局部模式，并产生一个新的信号或图像，其中这些模式被强调或抑制。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting Started With DuckDB in Python: A Fast and Lightweight Analytics Database】Python中的DuckDB入门：快速且轻量级的分析数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/duckdb-python-sql-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Data professionals today are looking for tools that combine speed, ease of use, and flexibility. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-to-duckdb-optimization&#34;&gt;DuckDB&lt;/a&gt; is one such tool that is gaining popularity quickly. It is an embedded SQL OLAP database that lets you run fast analytical queries right inside your Python environment. Whether you are working in a Jupyter notebook or building a local pipeline, DuckDB helps you explore and analyze data efficiently without needing a full-scale database setup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Think of DuckDB as SQLite&#39;s analytical cousin. While &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/build-simple-api-with-python-flask-and-sql&#34;&gt;SQLite&lt;/a&gt; is designed for transactional workloads, DuckDB is optimized for analytical tasks. It reads Parquet and CSV files directly, integrates easily with pandas, and runs SQL with minimal overhead. This tutorial will walk you through everything you need to start using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-handling-sensitive-data-with-duckdb&#34;&gt;DuckDB with Python&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;当今的数据专业人员正在寻找结合速度，易用性和灵活性的工具。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-to-duckdb-optimization”&gt; duckdb &lt;/a&gt;就是这样一种工具，它正在迅速获得流行。这是一个嵌入式SQL OLAP数据库，可让您在Python环境中运行快速的分析查询。无论您是在Jupyter笔记本电脑中工作还是构建本地管道，DuckDB都可以帮助您有效地探索和分析数据，而无需全尺寸的数据库设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;将duckdb视为sqlite的分析表亲。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/build-simple-api-with-with-python-flask-and-sql”&gt; sqlite &lt;/a&gt;是为交易工作载荷而设计的，但DuckDB已优化用于分析任务。它直接读取Parquet和CSV文件，与Pandas轻松集成，并以最小的开销运行SQL。本教程将带您完成使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-guide-guide-sensive-data-with-duckdb”&gt; with python &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt; duckdB</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Most IaC Strategies Still Fail (And How to Fix Them)】为什么大多数IAC策略仍然失败（以及如何修复）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-most-iac-strategies-still-fail</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Infrastructure as Code (IaC) was supposed to solve the chaos of cloud operations. It promised visibility, governance, and the ability to scale infrastructure with confidence. But for many teams, the reality is far from ideal.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead of clarity and control, they’re dealing with conflicting tools, unmanaged assets, drifting configs, and unpredictable processes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;基础架构作为代码（IAC）应该解决云操作的混乱。它承诺可见性，治理和自信地扩展基础设施的能力。但是对于许多团队来说，现实远非理想。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;而不是清晰和控制，而是处理冲突的工具，不受管理的资产，漂移配置和不可预测的过程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【TypeScript in Cloud Applications: Why It’s a Powerful Choice】云应用程序中的打字稿：为什么它是一个有力的选择</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/typescript-in-cloud-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;648&#34; data-start=&#34;339&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-cloud&#34;&gt;Cloud computing&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;is no longer just a technological advantage—it&#39;s the foundation of modern software ecosystems. Companies ranging from startups to Fortune 500 giants rely on cloud-native applications to deliver fast, scalable, and resilient services to users across the globe. These applications are typically:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;691&#34; data-start=&#34;652&#34;&gt;Distributed across regions and services&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;755&#34; data-start=&#34;694&#34;&gt;Composed of independent &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/microservices&#34;&gt;microservices&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-vs-containers-choosing-right-architecture&#34;&gt;serverless&lt;/a&gt; functions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;784&#34; data-start=&#34;758&#34;&gt;Built to scale dynamically&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;827&#34; data-start=&#34;787&#34;&gt;Maintained by globally distributed teams&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1007&#34; data-start=&#34;829&#34;&gt;In this complex, interconnected world, reliability, maintainability, and developer productivity are paramount. Choosing the right language and tools becomes critical.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 648” data-start =“ 339”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/getting-started-cloud”&gt;云计算&lt;/a&gt;不再只是技术优势，它是现代软件生态系统的基础。从初创企业到《财富》 500强巨头的公司都依靠云代表应用程序为全球用户提供快速，可扩展和弹性的服务。这些应用程序通常是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 691” data-start =“ 652”&gt;分布在区域和服务上&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 755” data-start =“ 694”&gt;由独立&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/microservices”&gt; microservices &lt;/a&gt;或&lt;A href =“&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 784” data-start =“ 758”&gt;动态扩展&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 827” data-start =“ 787”&gt;由全球分布式团队维护&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1007” data-start =“ 829”&gt;在这个复杂的，相互联系的世界，可靠性，可维护性和开发人员生产率至关重要。选择正确的语言和工具变得至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Development to Deployment: Automating Machine Learning】从开发到部署：自动化机器学习</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-machine-learning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Building a machine learning (ML) model is both fascinating and complex, requiring careful navigation through a series of steps. The journey from machine learning model development to deployment is the most critical phase in bringing AI to life. A well-trained model, on the right algorithm and relevant data, covers the development stage, then the focus shifts toward deployment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deploying a machine learning model can be a tedious process: building APIs, containerizing, managing dependencies, configuring cloud environments, and setting up servers and clusters often require significant effort, but imagine if the entire workflow could be automated. In this article, we’ll talk about how ML deployment automation can unify and simplify all these processes. The deployment process can be simplified by using general tools, preconfigured modules, and easy-to-integrate automated scripts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;构建机器学习（ML）模型既有趣又复杂，需要仔细通过一系列步骤进行导航。从机器学习模型开发到部署的旅程是使AI栩栩如生的最关键阶段。训练有素的模型，在右侧算法和相关数据上涵盖了开发阶段，然后重点转向部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;部署机器学习模型可能是一个繁琐的过程：构建API，容器化，管理依赖关系，配置云环境以及设置服务器和群集通常需要大量的努力，但想象一下是否可以自动化整个工作流程。在本文中，我们将讨论ML部署自动化如何统一和简化所有这些过程。可以通过使用一般工具，预配置的模块和易于整合的自动化脚本来简化部署过程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>