<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing AI Privacy: Federated Learning and Differential Privacy in Machine Learning】增强AI隐私：联合学习和机器学习中的差异隐私</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/privacy-preserving-machine-learning-models-federat</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Privacy-preserving techniques are keeping your data safe in the age of AI. In particular, federated learning (FL) keeps data local, while differential privacy (DP) strengthens individual privacy. In this article, we will discuss challenges associated with this, practical tools, and emerging trends like secure aggregation and personalized FL for stronger privacy in AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;隐私保护技术在AI时代确保您的数据安全。特别是，联邦学习（FL）可以保留数据本地，而差异隐私（DP）则加强了个人隐私。在本文中，我们将讨论与此，实用工具以及新兴趋势相关的挑战，例如安全汇总和个性化的FL，以在AI中获得更强的隐私。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shifting Left in Software Testing: Integrating AI-Driven Early Defect Detection into Agile Development Workflows】在软件测试中剩下的转移：将AI驱动的早期缺陷检测集成到敏捷开发工作流程中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/shifting-left-ai-defect-detection-agile</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Nobody likes bugs. Not the developers who accidentally write them, not the testers who hunt them down, and certainly not the users who stumble into them. But here’s the kicker — according to IBM, &lt;a href=&#34;https://public.dhe.ibm.com/software/rational/info/do-more/RAW14109USEN.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;5 to 30% of software defects&lt;/a&gt; still slip into production, costing companies up to 30 times more to fix post-release than if caught early.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The statistic highlights the essential nature of discovering software defects at the earliest point in development. Testing processes must shift left in development lifecycles according to the shifting left concept.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;没有人喜欢错误。不是不小心写下它们的开发人员，而不是测试人员追捕他们，当然不是偶然发现它们的用户。 But here’s the kicker — according to IBM, &lt;a href=&#34;https://public.dhe.ibm.com/software/rational/info/do-more/RAW14109USEN.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;5 to 30% of software defects&lt;/a&gt; still slip into production, costing companies up to 30 times more to fix释放比提早捕获。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;统计量强调了在开发中最早发现软件缺陷的基本性质。测试过程必须根据变化的左概念在开发生命周中向左移动。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI for Ensuring Data Integrity and Simplifying Migration in Microservices Ecosystems】AI用于确保数据完整性并简化微服务生态系统中的迁移</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-data-integrity-microservices-migration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Organizations implement microservices architectures to create adaptable, scalable applications that function efficiently, but must overcome significant challenges to maintain data accuracy during migration. The data sharing mechanism of microservices architecture enables beneficial advantages but produces complex data accuracy and reliability challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence functions as a powerful instrument that enables users to manage data integrity and optimize the data migration process. AI delivers efficient solutions for microservices ecosystems to handle data integrity issues and execute data migration operations effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;组织实施微服务体系结构，以创建有效运行的可自适应，可扩展的应用程序，但必须克服重大挑战以保持迁移过程中的数据准确性。微服务体系结构的数据共享机制可实现有益的优势，但会产生复杂的数据准确性和可靠性挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能是一种强大的工具，使用户能够管理数据完整性并优化数据迁移过程。 AI为微服务生态系统提供有效的解决方案来处理数据完整性问题并有效执行数据迁移操作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Deploying AI Models in Air-Gapped Environments: A Practical Guide From the Data Center Trenches】在气动环境中部署AI模型：数据中心战es的实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deploying-ai-models-in-air-gapped-environments</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Organizations are eager to harness machine learning and deep learning — but not everyone is racing to the cloud. For highly regulated industries, government entities, and security-first organizations, air-gapped environments remain essential. The question many are now asking is: How do we bring AI into air-gapped or isolated systems, and do it securely, reliably, and scalably?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;After nearly two decades managing on-prem data centers and private cloud environments, I’ve seen the evolution — from physical servers and VLANs to containerized workloads and AI clusters. In this article, I’ll share practical strategies for deploying AI models in air-gapped environments, with a focus on lessons learned, key technical considerations, and actionable guidance for both engineers and decision-makers.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;组织渴望利用机器学习和深度学习 - 但并不是每个人都在云上竞赛。对于高度受监管的行业，政府实体和安全优先组织，气开环境仍然至关重要。许多人现在问的问题是：我们如何将AI带入空白或孤立的系统，并安全，可靠，可靠地？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在管理本地数据中心和私有云环境的近二十年后，我已经看到了从物理服务器和VLAN到容器的工作负载和AI群集的演变。在本文中，我将分享用于在气动环境中部署AI模型的实用策略，重点是对工程师和决策者的经验教训，关键的技术考虑以及可行的指导。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Security Concerns in Open GPTs: Emerging Threats, Vulnerabilities, and Mitigation Strategies】开放式GPT中的安全问题：新兴威胁，脆弱性和缓解策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/security-concerns-in-open-gpts</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;With the increasing use of Open GPTs in industries such as finance, healthcare, and software development, security concerns are growing. Unlike proprietary models, open-source GPTs allow greater customization but also expose organizations to various security vulnerabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This analysis explores real-world breaches, case studies, and advanced security techniques to safeguard Open GPT deployments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;随着在金融，医疗保健和软件开发等行业中越来越多地使用开放式GPT，安全问题正在增长。与专有模型不同，开源GPT允许更大的自定义，但也使组织暴露于各种安全漏洞。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;此分析探讨了现实世界中的漏洞，案例研究和高级安全技术以保护开放GPT的部署。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI for Data Cleaning: How AI Can Clean Your Data and Save You Hours and Money】用于数据清洁的AI：AI如何清洁您的数据并节省您的数小时和金钱</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-for-data-cleaning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Dirty data is the bane of the analytics industry. Almost every organization that deals with data has had to deal with some degree of unreliability in its numbers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pragmaticinstitute.com/resources/articles/data/overcoming-the-80-20-rule-in-data-science/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Pragmatic Institute&lt;/a&gt;, data practitioners spend 80% of their time identifying, cleansing, and arranging data and 20% analyzing it. This 80/20 rule is referred to as the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/paretoprinciple.asp&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Pareto Principle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;肮脏的数据是分析行业的祸根。几乎每个处理数据的组织都必须处理一定程度的不可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据&lt;a href =“ https://www.pragmaticinstitute.com/resources/resources/articles/data/data/data/overcoming-the-the-the-the-the-the-the-the-the-the-data-science/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” targ 20％分析它。该80/20规则称为&lt;a href =“ https://www.investopedia.com/terms/p/paretoprinciple.asp” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” noopener noreferrer“ target =” _ blank&gt; pareto printiple &lt;/a&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Quantum Machine Learning (QML) for Developers: A Beginner&#39;s Guide】开发人员的量子机学习（QML）：初学者指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-machine-learning-for-beginners</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Quantum computing is transforming artificial intelligence. Traditional AI faces challenges in optimization, large-scale data processing, and security. Quantum machine learning (QML) integrates quantum mechanics with AI, offering advantages such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Faster AI model training and inference&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Better pattern recognition and optimization&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Improved security using quantum cryptography&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide covers practical implementations using:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;量子计算正在改变人工智能。传统的AI在优化，大规模数据处理和安全性方面面临挑战。量子机学习（QML）将量子力学与AI整合，提供了以下优势：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;更快的AI模型培训和推理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;更好的模式识别和优化&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;使用量子密码学提高了安全性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南涵盖了使用：&lt;/p&gt;的实际实现。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Demystifying Kubernetes on AWS: A Comparative Analysis of Deployment Options】在AWS上揭开Kubernetes的神秘面纱：部署选项的比较分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-aws-deployment-options</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes has become the industry-standard platform for container orchestration, offering automated deployment, scaling, and management of containerized applications. Its ability to efficiently utilize resources, abstract infrastructure complexities, and provide robust enterprise features makes it essential for modern application infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; can run on-premises, deploying on AWS provides significant advantages, including on-demand scaling, cost optimization, and integration with AWS services for security, monitoring, and operations. With multi-AZ high availability and a global presence in 32 regions, AWS delivers the reliability needed for mission-critical applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; kubernetes已成为集装箱编排的行业标准标准平台，提供自动部署，扩展和管理集装箱应用程序。它有效利用资源，抽象基础架构复杂性并提供强大的企业功能的能力使其对于现代应用程序基础架构至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes”&gt; kubernetes &lt;/a&gt;可以运行本地式，在AWS上部署在AWS上可提供重要的优势，包括与AWS的按需缩放，成本优化，以及为AWS服务提供的安全性，并为安全性提供了安全性，并提供了安全性，和操作，并提供了安全性，和行动。 AWS具有多AZ高可用性和在32个地区的全球存在，可提供关键任务应用所需的可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Real-time Data Transfer Magic of Doris Kafka Connector&#39;s &#34;Data Package&#34;: Part 1】Doris Kafka连接器的“数据包”的实时数据传输魔法：第1部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-data-doris-kafka-connector</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Apache Doris provides multi-dimensional data ingestion capabilities. In addition to the built-in Routine Load and Flink&#39;s support for reading from Kafka and writing to Doris, the Doris Kafka Connector [1], as an extended component of the Kafka Connect ecosystem, not only supports importing Kafka data into Doris but also relies on the vast Kafka Connect ecosystem to achieve the following features [2]:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Rich Format Support&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Natively parses complex formats such as Avro/Protobuf.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Automatically registers and converts schemas.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Optimizes the efficient processing of binary data streams.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Heterogeneous Integration of Multiple Data Sources&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relational databases&lt;/strong&gt;: MySQL, Oracle, SQL Server, DB2, Informix, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NoSQL databases&lt;/strong&gt;: MongoDB, Cassandra, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Message queue systems&lt;/strong&gt;: ActiveMQ, IBM MQ, RabbitMQ, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud data warehouses&lt;/strong&gt;: Snowflake, Google BigQuery, Amazon Redshift, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 792px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;823.1 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1741340128837&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;03/07/2025 09:35 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18265162-ac.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;823091&#34; data-name=&#34;ac.png&#34; data-id=&#34;18265162&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18265162-ac.png&#34; alt=&#34;Heterogeneous integration of multiple data sources&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Apache Doris提供了多维数据摄入功能。除了内置的常规负载和Flink对从Kafka阅读并写信给Doris的支持，Doris Kafka Connector [1]，作为Kafka Connection Ecosystem的扩展组成部分，不仅支持将Kafka数据导入Doris，而且还依赖于Kafka Connect kafka Connect Connect Ecosystem以实现以下功能[2]&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;丰富的格式支持&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;本性解析复合格式，例如avro/protobuf。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;自动注册并转换架构。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;优化二进制数据流的有效处理。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;多个数据源的异质整合&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;关系数据库&lt;/strong&gt;：MySQL，Oracle，SQL Server，DB2，Informix等&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; nosql数据库&lt;/strong&gt;：mongodb，cassandra等&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;消息队列系统&lt;/strong&gt;：ActiveMQ，IBM MQ，RabbitMQ等&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云数据仓库&lt;/strong&gt;：雪花，Google Bigquery，Amazon Redshift等&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;img style =“ width：792px;” class =“ fr-fic fr-dib懒惰” data-image =“ true” data-new =“ false” data-sizeFormatted =“ 823.1 kb” data-mimetype =“ image/png” data-creationdate =“ 1741340128837” data-creationdate formanted =“ data-CreationdateFormatted =” 03/07/07/202507/20250.3550.35 AM&#39;FES data-url =“ https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18265162-ac.png” data-modificationdate =“ nul null” data-size =“ 823091” data-name =“ ac.png” data-src =“ https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18265162-ac.png” alt =“多个数据源的异构集成”&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tuples and Records (Part 4): Optimize React and Prevent Re-Renders】元组和记录（第4部分）：优化反应并防止重新租赁</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/tuples-and-records-part-4</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Part 4 dives into React, showing how Tuples and Records can cut down unnecessary re-renders. By using immutable, value-based data structures, React can efficiently detect state changes, keeping your components lean and fast. We’ll explore why re-renders happen and how adopting Tuples and Records simplifies state management while boosting performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also read:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;第4部分潜入React，展示了元素和记录如何减少不必要的重新租赁。通过使用不变的，基于价值的数据结构，React可以有效地检测状态变化，使您的组件保持精益和快速。我们将探讨为什么重新租赁会发生以及采用元组和记录如何简化州管理，同时提高绩效。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;也阅读：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>