<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Redefining Developer Productivity: Balancing Data and Human Experience in Developer Success Measurements】重新定义开发人员生产率：平衡数据和人类在开发人员成功测量中的经验</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/redefining-developer-productivity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-devex-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Experience: The Coalescence of Developer Productivity, Process Satisfaction, and Platform Engineering&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Delivering production-ready software tools requires focusing on developer productivity measured by qualitative and quantitative metrics. To understand developer productivity, this article focuses on three elements:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;编辑注：以下是为Dzone的2025趋势报告编写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/link.com/link/2025-tr-tr-devex-contributor -article“ rel =” noopener noreferrer“ target =“ _ blank”&gt; &lt;em&gt;开发人员体验：开发人员生产率，过程满意度的合并，和平台工程&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;提供可用生产的软件工具需要专注于通过定性和定量指标衡量的开发人员生产率。为了了解开发人员的生产力，本文重点介绍了三个要素：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Simplifying Multi-LLM Integration With KubeMQ】简化与Kubemq的多LLM集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/simplifying-multi-llm-integration-with-kubemq</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Integrating multiple large language models (LLMs) like OpenAI and Anthropic&#39;s Claude into applications can be a daunting task. The complexities of handling different APIs and communication protocols and ensuring efficient routing of requests can introduce significant challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But using a message broker and router can be an elegant solution to this problem, addressing these pain points and providing several key advantages.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;集成了多个大型语言模型（LLM），例如Openai和Anthropic的Claude将其纳入应用程序可能是一项艰巨的任务。处理不同的API和通信协议并确保有效的请求路由的复杂性可能引入重大挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;，但是使用消息经纪和路由器可以是解决此问题的优雅解决方案，解决这些痛点并提供了几个关键优势。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Non-Human Identity Security in the Age of AI】AI时代的非人类身份安全</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/non-human-identity-security-in-the-age-of-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It is not a coincidence that non-human identities (NHIs) have come into focus recently while AI-powered tools and autonomous agents are rapidly being adopted. In fact, this is partially what is driving the explosion of NHIs in the enterprise. This has sparked a lot of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cyberark.com/resources/blog/why-machine-identities-are-essential-strands-in-your-zero-trust-strategy?ref=blog.gitguardian.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;research and conversations&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; about &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.gitguardian.com/identities-do-not-exist-in-a-vacuum/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;u&gt;machine identity and governance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like human users of systems, NHIs, such as AI agents, bots, scripts, and cloud workloads, &lt;strong&gt;operate using secrets&lt;/strong&gt;. These credentials grant access to sensitive systems and data. They can take many forms and must always be accounted for, from creation to offboarding. Unlike humans, machines can&#39;t use multifactor authentication or passkeys, and developers can generate hundreds of these credentials through their work deploying applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;非人类身份（NHIS）最近开始焦点并不是一个巧合，而AI驱动的工具和自主代理正在迅速采用。实际上，这部分是驱动NHI在企业中爆炸的原因。这引发了很多&lt;a href =“ https://www.cyberark.com/resources/blog/why-machine-indistities-indistities-ectenties-are-estential-sential-strands-in-your-zero-zero-trust-trategy？ref=blog .gitguardian.com“ target =“ _ blank”&gt; &lt;u&gt;研究与对话href =“ https://blog.gitguardian.com/indentities-do-not-exist-in-a-vacuum/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; &lt;u&gt;机器身份和治理&lt;/u &gt; &lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;就像系统的使用者一样，NHIS，例如AI代理，机器人，脚本和云工作负载，&lt;strong&gt;使用Secrets &lt;/strong&gt;进行操作。这些凭证授予对敏感系统和数据的访问。他们可以采取多种形式，必须始终考虑从创建到卸货。与人类不同，机器不能使用多因素身份验证或Passkeys，并且开发人员可以通过部署应用程序来生成数百个凭据。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Spring Framework or Hibernate, Which One Is Better?】春季框架或冬眠，哪一个更好？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spring-framework-or-hibernate-which-one-is-better</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In modern software or website development processes, Java frameworks are widely used as they make it easy to build dynamic apps and websites. Moreover, in 2023, the value of the Java frameworks software market was USD 3,982.40 million.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Furthermore, it is forecasted to reach USD 9,049.22 million by 2030. This proves the significance of using Java frameworks such as Grails, Google Web Toolkit (GWT), Quarkus, and not to mention the Hibernate and Spring frameworks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在现代软件或网站开发过程中，Java Frameworks被广泛使用，因为它们可以轻松构建动态应用程序和网站。此外，在2023年，Java Frameworks软件市场的价值为39.824亿美元。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;此外，预计到2030年，它预计将达到9,0.492亿美元。这证明了使用Java框架（例如Grails，Google Web Toolkit（GWT），Quarkus，Quarkus）的重要性框架。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Protecting Critical Infrastructure From Ransomware】保护关键基础设施免受勒索软件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/protecting-critical-infrastructure-from-ransomware</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Safeguarding critical infrastructure from ransomware has become a critical issue in today&#39;s interconnected world. Regions, for instance, power clinical benefits and government face extending perils that could disturb supplies, impact fragile data, and cause essential financial and reputational hurt.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ransomware attacks planned to pressure portions by encoding significant information highlight the sincere necessity for solid organization insurance strategies. This plan examines necessary techniques to defend against ransomware in critical infrastructure, focusing on proactive specific gatekeepers and a solid procedure framework. By grasping the attack and completing comprehensive protections, associations can lessen the chance and ensure the adaptability of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/critical-infrastructure-protection-in-the-age-of-c&#34;&gt;critical infrastructure against advanced risks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;保护关键基础设施免受勒索软件已成为当今相互联系的关键问题。例如，区域的权力临床福利和政府面临的危险可能会干扰供应，影响脆弱的数据并造成基本的财务和声誉伤害。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;勒索软件攻击计划通过编码大量信息来强调稳固的组织保险策略的真诚必要性，从而向部分施加压力。该计划研究了必要的技术，以防御关键基础设施中的勒索软件，重点关注主动的特定守门人和坚实的程序框架。通过抓住攻击并完成全面的保护，关联可以减轻机会并确保&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/critical-incritation-infradectionure-protectionure-prototection-in-the-the-the-age-of-c”的适应性。 &gt;针对高级风险的关键基础设施&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating AI Agent Workflows in the SOC】将AI代理工作流程在SOC中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-ai-agent-workflows-soc</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Defending against zero- to low-cost attacks generated by threat actors (TA) is becoming increasingly complex as they leverage sophisticated generative AI-enabled infrastructure. TAs try to use AI tools in their attack planning to make social engineering schemes, convincing phishing emails, deepfake videos, different types of malware, and many other types of attack vectors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A potential solution to defend against these challenges is to enable the use of GenAI and AI agents in the Security Operations Center (SOC). An orchestrated workflow with a team of AI agents presents an opportunity for better response. In traditional detection and response, detections are not easily achieved, and manual responses cannot match the required machine-level speed. To avoid burnout and alert fatigue of SOC analysts, a shift in the SOC strategy is required by automating routine tasks using AI agents.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;捍卫威胁参与者（TA）产生的零至低成本攻击，因为他们利用了复杂的生成AI-ai-ai-ai-ai-aigable基础架构，因此变得越来越复杂。 TA试图在攻击计划中使用AI工具来制定社会工程计划，令人信服的网络钓鱼电子邮件，Deepfake视频，不同类型的恶意软件以及许多其他类型的攻击向量。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;防止这些挑战的潜在解决方案是使在安全操作中心（SOC）中使用Genai和AI代理。与AI代理团队一起精心策划的工作流程为更好的回应提供了机会。在传统的检测和响应中，检测不容易实现，手动响应不能匹配所需的机器级速度。为了避免SOC分析师的倦怠和警报疲劳，通过使用AI代理自动执行常规任务需要SOC策略的转变。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Generative AI Is Revolutionizing Cloud Operations】生成的AI如何彻底改变云操作</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-revolutionizes-cloud-operations</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;LLMs have made it possible to operate cloud services more effectively and cheaply than ever before. They can assimilate natural language and code, enabling new preventative and remediatory tools. Language models are improving at a breakneck velocity. As the models get better, services that have integrated them into their operations will reap the benefits for free.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;We explore the most compelling applications in this article, many of which are already being deployed at top tech companies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; llms使比以往任何时候都更有效，便宜地运营云服务。它们可以吸收自然语言和代码，从而实现新的预防和补救工具。语言模型以惊人的速度有所改善。随着模型变得更好，将它们整合到运营中的服务将免费获得收益。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我们探讨了本文中最引人注目的应用程序，其中许多应用程序已经在顶级科技公司部署。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Future of Data Lakehouses: Apache Iceberg Explained】数据湖区的未来：Apache Iceberg解释了</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-of-data-lakehouses-apache-iceberg</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;We know that data management today is changing completely. For decades, businesses relied on data warehouses, which stored information in an appropriate manner. They are structured, governed, and quick to extract information from, although expensive and rigid in nature. In contrast, data lakes are more efficient and allow for the storage of enormous amounts of data regardless of structure. However, the emergence of the data lakehouse architecture combines the benefits of the data lakes and data warehouses. Lakehouse models allow the retention of the flexibility provided by data lakes while integrating the reliability, governance, and performance of a data warehouse.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The most notable open-source table format created for large-scale data analytics is &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-short-introduction-to-apache-iceberg&#34;&gt;Apache Iceberg&lt;/a&gt;. Iceberg is at the forefront of this transformation and enhances the value of data in the lakehouse architecture. Additionally, Iceberg provides solutions for many of the problems that data lakes face, including schema evolution, ACID transactions, data consistency, and query performance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;我们知道今天的数据管理正在完全改变。几十年来，企业一直依赖数据仓库，该仓库以适当的方式存储信息。它们是结构化，管理和迅速从本质上昂贵且僵硬的信息中提取信息的。相比之下，数据湖效率更高，允许存储大量数据，而不管结构如何。但是，Data Lakehouse体系结构的出现结合了数据湖和数据仓库的好处。 Lakehouse模型允许保留数据湖泊提供的灵活性，同时整合了数据仓库的可靠性，治理和性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;为大规模数据分析创建的最著名的开源表格式是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a -short-Intoduction-to-apache-setberg“&gt; Apache Iceberg &lt;/a&gt;。冰山是这种转变的最前沿，并增强了湖泊建筑中数据的价值。此外，冰山还为数据湖面临的许多问题提供解决方案，包括模式进化，酸性交易，数据一致性和查询性能。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Spark Job Optimization】火花作业优化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spark-job-optimization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We are living in an age where data is of utmost importance, be it analysis or reporting, training data for LLM models, etc. The amount of data we capture in any field is increasing exponentially, which requires a technology that can process large amounts of data in a short duration. One such technology would be Apache Spark.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/apache-spark-all-you-need-to-know&#34;&gt;Apache Spark&lt;/a&gt; is a cluster-based architecture that can be accessed in different flavors like Python, Scala, Java, and Spark SQL, which would make it versatile and easy to fit into most applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们生活在一个最重要的时代，无论是分析或报告，LLM模型的培训数据等。我们在任何领域中捕获的数据量呈指数增长，这需要一项可以处理的技术大量数据在短时间内。这样的技术将是Apache Spark。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在Python，Scala，Java和Spark SQL等不同的口味将使它具有多功能且易于适合大多数应用程序。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Hidden Cost of Dirty Data in AI Development】AI开发中肮脏数据的隐藏成本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-hidden-cost-of-dirty-data-in-ai-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence operates as a transformative force that transforms various industries, including healthcare, together with finance and all other sectors. AI systems achieve their highest performance through data that has been properly prepared for training purposes. AI success depends on high-quality data because inaccurate all-inclusive or duplicated data or conflicting records lead to both diminished performance and higher operational costs, biased decisions, and flawed insights. AI developers understate the true impact of dirty data-related expenses because these factors directly affect business performance levels together with user trust and project achievement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Financial Burden of Poor Data Quality&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The financial costs represent one direct expense related to using dirty data during &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-governance-challenges-in-generative-ai&#34;&gt;AI development processes&lt;/a&gt;. Organizations that depend on AI systems for decision automation need to budget sizable expenses toward cleaning data, preparing it for processing, and validating existing datasets. Studies show poor data quality annually creates millions of dollars of financial losses through several efficiency issues, prediction mistakes, and resource ineffectiveness. Faulty data that train AI models sometimes leads businesses to make mistakes involving resource wastage and incorrect targeting of customers, followed by incorrect healthcare diagnoses of patients.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;人工智能是一种变革性的力量，可以改变包括医疗保健在内的各种行业，以及金融和所有其他部门。 AI系统通过已适当准备培训目的的数据实现了最高的性能。 AI成功取决于高质量数据，因为不准确的全包或重复的数据或相互矛盾的记录导致绩效下降和更高的运营成本，偏见的决策和有缺陷的见解。 AI开发人员低估了肮脏的数据相关费用的真正影响，因为这些因素直接影响业务绩效水平以及用户信任和项目成就。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;数据质量差的财务负担&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;财务成本代表与在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/data-governance-challenges-challenges-ingerative---ingenerative-ai”期间使用肮脏数据有关的一个直接费用开发过程&lt;/a&gt;。依靠AI系统进行决策自动化的组织需要预算可观的费用来清洁数据，准备处理以及验证现有数据集。研究表明，每年的数据质量差会通过几个效率问题，预测错误和资源无效造成数百万美元的财务损失。训练AI模型的错误数据有时会导致企业犯涉及资源浪费和不正确针对客户的错误，然后是患者的医疗保健诊断不正确。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>