<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Elevate Your Career: Three-Step Strategy to Advance Career in the IT Industry】提升您的职业生涯：在 IT 行业提升职业生涯的三步策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/elevate-your-it-career-three-step-strategy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Sometimes in our careers, we feel like we&#39;re not progressing from our current level. Well, who doesn&#39;t? The least said about it, it is an annoying place to be: working hard, putting in long hours, and feeling like our career is going nowhere. I was there too. So, after having navigated my way through it, here&#39;s advice I wish I could give my past self.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Reality Check: Why Hard Work Alone Isn’t Enough&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ve noticed a common myth at workplaces that working long hours will get you a promotion. The reality is that putting in extra hours is not a differentiator. While dedication and a strong work ethic are important, it may not take you to the next level. Any leadership looks for people who can tackle higher-level challenges and lead through influence rather than effort. You have more chances to move forward if you are a strategic thinker rather than a hard worker.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我们的职业生涯中，有时我们会觉得自己没有从目前的水平上取得进步。嗯，谁不呢？至少要说的是，这是一个令人讨厌的地方：努力工作，投入很长时间，却感觉我们的职业生涯毫无进展。我也在场。因此，在经历了这一切之后，我希望我能给过去的自己提供以下建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;现实检验：为什么单靠努力工作还不够&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我注意到工作场所存在一个常见的误区：长时间工作会让你升职。现实情况是，加班并不能带来差异化。虽然奉献精神和强烈的职业道德很重要，但它可能无法让您更上一层楼。任何领导层都在寻找能够应对更高级别挑战并通过影响力而不是努力来领导的人。如果您是一个战略思考者而不是一个努力工作的人，您就有更多的机会前进。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 18:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Best Practices for Salesforce Data Management and Security】Salesforce 数据管理和安全的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-for-salesforce-data-management-and-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Effective Salesforce data management and security are crucial for organizations aiming to maximize their CRM potential while safeguarding sensitive information. As &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/salesforce-application-design&#34;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/a&gt; continues to be a cornerstone for customer relationship management, ensuring data integrity, accessibility, and security becomes increasingly vital. This article explores best practices for Salesforce data management and security, covering essential strategies such as data governance, access controls, encryption, regular audits, and compliance with industry regulations. By adhering to these best practices, businesses can protect their data assets, enhance operational efficiency, and maintain the trust of their customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, we will discuss the top five Salesforce data management and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-privacy-and-security&#34;&gt;security&lt;/a&gt; best practices you should consider implementing, if you have not done so already.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;有效的 Salesforce 数据管理和安全对于希望在保护敏感信息的同时最大限度地发挥 CRM 潜力的组织至关重要。随着 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/salesforce-application-design&#34;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/a&gt; 继续成为客户关系管理的基石，确保数据完整性、可访问性和安全性变得越来越重要。本文探讨 Salesforce 数据管理和安全性的最佳实践，涵盖数据治理、访问控制、加密、定期审计和遵守行业法规等基本策略。通过遵循这些最佳实践，企业可以保护其数据资产、提高运营效率并维持客户的信任。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将讨论前五个 Salesforce 数据管理和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-privacy-and-security&#34;&gt;安全性&lt;/a &gt; 如果您还没有这样做，您应该考虑实施最佳实践。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Going on a Threat Hunt: Advanced Strategies for Defending the Digital Frontier】进行威胁搜寻：捍卫数字前沿的高级策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-strategies-threat-hunting</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-security-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Enterprise Security: Reinforcing Enterprise Application Defense&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Threat hunting is a proactive cybersecurity strategy that actively searches for hidden threats throughout an organization&#39;s entire digital environment. Unlike traditional security measures that primarily react to incidents, threat hunting assumes a breach has already occurred and aims to identify malicious activity before it escalates. By analyzing vast amounts of data from networks, endpoints, and cloud environments, organizations can uncover suspicious patterns, neutralize threats, and significantly reduce their risk of a successful cyberattack.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-security-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;企业安全：加强企业应用程序防御&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;威胁搜寻是一种主动的网络安全策略，可在组织的整个数字环境中主动搜索隐藏的威胁。与主要对事件做出反应的传统安全措施不同，威胁搜寻假设漏洞已经发生，旨在在恶意活动升级之前识别出恶意活动。通过分析来自网络、端点和云环境的大量数据，组织可以发现可疑模式、消除威胁并显着降低网络攻击成功的风险。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Transparency to the Perils of Oversharing】从透明度到过度分享的危险</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/from-transparency-to-the-perils-of-oversharing</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Why Too Much Transparency Can Have a Detrimental Effect&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While transparency is often touted as essential in Agile, too much can have negative consequences. Oversharing can lead to micromanagement, misinterpretation, and loss of trust within the team. Examples include excessive scrutiny during Daily Scrums, misreading progress metrics, and creating a blame culture that erodes psychological safety.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Strategic opacity may sometimes be necessary to protect the team’s autonomy and maintain a healthy dynamic. Be transparent, but not at the expense of the team’s independence and well-being.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR：为什么太多的透明度会产生有害影响&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然透明度经常被认为是敏捷中的必要条件，但太多可能会产生负面后果。过度分享可能会导致微观管理、误解和团队内部失去信任。例子包括每日 Scrums 期间的过度审查、误读进度指标以及创造侵​​蚀心理安全的指责文化。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;战略不透明有时可能是保护团队自主权和保持健康活力所必需的。保持透明，但不能以牺牲团队的独立性和福祉为代价。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Monolithic vs Microservices Architecture: Key Differences】单体架构与微服务架构：主要区别</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/monolithic-vs-microservices-architecture-key-differences</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Architecture design is imperative to modern software development. It impacts application performance, development time, quality, and overall user experience. Monolithic and microservices are two popular architectural designs powering most software applications today.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Monolithic design is a more traditional approach that treats the entire application as a single entity. On the other hand, microservices are a more modern approach that divides the application into smaller components, giving developers granular control. For most developers, currently, microservices stand out as the best approach since they are a novel concept and provide finer control. However, this is not necessarily true in all cases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;架构设计对于现代软件开发至关重要。它会影响应用程序性能、开发时间、质量和整体用户体验。单体和微服务是当今大多数软件应用程序的两种流行的架构设计。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;单体设计是一种更传统的方法，它将整个应用程序视为单个实体。另一方面，微服务是一种更现代的方法，它将应用程序划分为更小的组件，为开发人员提供精细的控制。目前，对于大多数开发人员来说，微服务是最好的方法，因为它们是一个新颖的概念并提供更精细的控制。然而，这并不一定在所有情况下都是如此。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Revolutionize Your MuleSoft Deployments With GitOps】使用 GitOps 彻底改变您的 MuleSoft 部署</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mulesoft-deployments-with-gitops</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-heading=&#34;Revolutionize Your MuleSoft Deployments with GitOps&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;In the dynamic world of integration, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mulesoft-video-tutorials-basic-to-complex&#34;&gt;MuleSoft&lt;/a&gt; stands out as a powerful platform that enables not only to unlock data across legacy systems, cloud apps, and devices but also to make smarter and faster decisions, and offer highly connected experiences for end-users. As organizations strive for faster and more reliable deployments, the adoption of GitOps is transforming how we manage and automate MuleSoft deployments. In this blog post, we&#39;ll explore how we can apply the principles of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/the-essentials-of-gitops&#34;&gt;GitOps&lt;/a&gt; to our MuleSoft deployment process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-heading=&#34;What is GitOps?&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;What Is GitOps?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitOps is a new method of controlling infrastructure and application deployments by relying on a Git repository as the primary source of information. Teams can have more oversight, transparency, and tracking of their deployment processes by storing configuration files in a Git repository. GitOps principles prioritize declarative configurations and automated workflows to achieve consistent and reliable deployments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-heading=&#34;使用 GitOps 彻底改变您的 MuleSoft 部署&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;在动态的集成世界中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mulesoft-video-tutorials-basic- to-complex&#34;&gt;MuleSoft&lt;/a&gt; 是一个功能强大的平台，不仅能够跨遗留系统、云应用程序和设备解锁数据，还能做出更明智、更快速的决策，并为最终用户提供高度互联的体验。随着组织努力实现更快、更可靠的部署，GitOps 的采用正在改变我们管理和自动化 MuleSoft 部署的方式。在这篇博文中，我们将探讨如何将 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/the-essentials-of-gitops&#34;&gt;GitOps&lt;/a&gt; 的原则应用到我们的 MuleSoft 部署过程中.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-heading=&#34;什么是 GitOps？&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;什么是 GitOps？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitOps 是一种依靠 Git 存储库作为主要信息源来控制基础架构和应用程序部署的新方法。通过将配置文件存储在 Git 存储库中，团队可以对其部署过程进行更多的监督、透明度和跟踪。 GitOps 原则优先考虑声明性配置和自动化工作流程，以实现一致且可靠的部署。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 20:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero Trust and Its Impact on Cybersecurity】零信任及其对网络安全的影响</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/future-of-cybersecurity-with-remote-work</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;According to Forbes, 1 out of 5 people are working remotely. With a more distributed workforce,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;enterprises have significantly changed their operation style&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;, encompassing shifts in company culture, meeting structures, and a surge in Virtual and Augmented Reality.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Along with them, the approach to c&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;ybersecurity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;also evolved.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;To better understand, let&#39;s rewind to the early 2000s when employees were onsite, connected to the company&#39;s corporate network acting as a security perimeter. All the egress and ingress traffic went through the perimeter protected by firewalls. With the advancement in Internet infrastructure, employees started working from home but continued connecting to corporate networks using VPNs. As years passed, devices became smarter, and how we access work spread from company-issued devices to personal mobiles and tablets. Subsequent &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/from-zero-trust-to-secure-access-the-evolution-of&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;growth in Cloud&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; and IoT moved the workloads from running on-prem to operating globally, effectively dissolving the concept of a security p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;erimeter,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;demanding a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/whitepapers/the-security-of-applications-supporting-the-new-re&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;new approach to secure enterprises&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;据《福布斯》报道，五分之一的人正在远程工作。随着员工队伍更加分散，&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;企业已显着改变其运营方式&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;，包括公司内部的转变文化、会议结构以及虚拟和增强现实的激增。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;与它们一起，实现网络安全的方法&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;网络安全&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver -spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; 也进化了。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;为了更好地理解，让我们回到 2000 年代初期，当时员工在现场，连接到公司的企业网络作为安全边界。所有出口和入口流量都经过防火墙保护的边界。随着互联网基础设施的进步，员工开始在家工作，但继续使用 VPN 连接到公司网络。随着时间的推移，设备变得更加智能，我们访问工作的方式也从公司发行的设备扩展到个人手机和平板电脑。后续 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/from-zero-trust-to-secure-access-the-evolution-of&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34; &gt;云计算的增长&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;和物联网将工作负载从本地运行转移到全球运行，有效地消除了安全性的概念&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;erimeter，&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; 和 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;要求 &lt; /span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/whitepapers/the-security-of-applications-supporting-the-new-re&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;新方法确保企业安全&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Telemetry Pipelines Workshop: Integrating Fluent Bit With OpenTelemetry, Part 2】遥测管道研讨会：将 Fluent Bit 与 OpenTelemetry 集成，第 2 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-fluent-bit-with-opentelemetry-part-two</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to get started with cloud-native observability and telemetry pipelines?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article is part of a series exploring a workshop guiding you through the open source project Fluent Bit, what it is, a basic installation, and setting up the first telemetry pipeline project. Learn how to manage your cloud-native data from source to destination using the telemetry pipeline phases covering collection, aggregation, transformation, and forwarding from any source to any destination.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您准备好开始使用云原生可观测性和遥测管道了吗？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文是一系列研讨会的一部分，该研讨会将指导您了解开源项目 Fluent Bit、它是什么、基本安装以及设置第一个遥测管道项目。了解如何使用遥测管道阶段（涵盖从任何源到任何目标的收集、聚合、转换和转发）来管理从源到目标的云原生数据。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 19:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Part 3: Taste Testing and Fine-Tuning, Evaluating Your Meal Planning Bot】第 3 部分：口味测试和微调，评估您的膳食计划机器人</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/meal-planning-bot-part-3-taste-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-product-to-learn-ai-pt-2&#34;&gt;Part 2,&lt;/a&gt; you poured your heart and soul into creating a cutting-edge AI meal planner. You&#39;ve meticulously chosen the right ingredients (data!), carefully blended them through training, and now your LLM creation is poised to serve up culinary delights. But before you unleash it upon the world, there&#39;s one crucial step: a thorough taste test! This is where a robust evaluation framework becomes your most valuable tool.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;img width=&#34;512&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; style=&#34;width: 355px; height: 355px;&#34; alt=&#34;Filling in circles on a test&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;422.2 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1725291587648&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/02/2024 03:39 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17893995-1725291587874.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;422183&#34; data-name=&#34;1725291587874.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17893995&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17893995-1725291587874.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Is an Eval?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;An &#34;eval&#34; refers to the process of evaluating or assessing (sometimes referred to as &#34;challenging&#34;) the performance of an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLM&lt;/a&gt;, to make sure it behaves the way you expect it to. This involves systematically testing the model&#39;s ability to generate accurate, relevant, and coherent responses across a variety of tasks and scenarios. Evals often employ diverse datasets and metrics, capturing aspects like factual accuracy, contextual understanding, fluency, and even the potential for bias or harmful outputs. The insights gleaned from these evaluations guide ongoing development and refinement, ultimately shaping the LLM&#39;s ability to serve users effectively and responsibly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-product-to-learn-ai-pt-2&#34;&gt;第 2 部分&lt;/a&gt;中，您倾注了心血并全身心投入创建尖端的人工智能膳食计划。您精心选择了正确的食材（数据！），通过培训仔细混合它们，现在您的法学硕士创作已准备好为您带来美食。但在将其推向世界之前，还有一个关键步骤：彻底的口味测试！这就是强大的评估框架成为您最有价值的工具的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;img width=&#34;512&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-diblazyload&#34; style=&#34;width: 355px; height: 355px;&#34; alt=&#34;在测试中填写圆圈&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;422.2 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1725291587648&#34; data-创建日期格式 =“09/02/2024 03:39 PM” data-type =“temp” data-url =“https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17893995-1725291587874.png”data-modificationdate =“ null&#34; data-size=&#34;422183&#34; data-name=&#34;1725291587874.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17893995&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17893995-1725291587874.png&#34; &gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;什么是评估？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;“评估”是指评价或评估（有时称为“挑战”）&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting- start-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLM&lt;/a&gt;，以确保它的行为符合您的预期。这涉及系统地测试模型在各种任务和场景中生成准确、相关和连贯响应的能力。评估通常采用不同的数据集和指标，捕获事实准确性、上下文理解、流畅性，甚至​​潜在的偏见或有害输出等方面。从这些评估中收集的见解指导持续的开发和完善，最终塑造法学硕士有效和负责任地服务用户的能力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【API-Led Example: MuleSoft】API 主导的示例：MuleSoft</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/api-led-example-salesforce</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This article gives an impression of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-pros-and-cons-of-api-led-connectivity&#34;&gt;API-led&lt;/a&gt; architecture using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mulesoft-for-beginners-mule-4-development-complete&#34;&gt;Mule4&lt;/a&gt; APIs in order to give a clear understanding of the development process of an API-led approach. It covers all 3 of the API layers (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mule-api-experience-process-system-layer-example&#34;&gt;System, Process, and Experience&lt;/a&gt;) using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/salesforce-application-design&#34;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://api.first.org/data/v1/countries&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;FIRST.org&lt;/a&gt; as the source. Additionally, we cover applying best practices in each layer of development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAML&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;code&gt;Common library&lt;/code&gt;, &amp;nbsp;&lt;code&gt;traits&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;data definition&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;reusable resources&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;health endpoint&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;code&gt;Externalize property files&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;encryption of properties&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;externalize dwl code&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;reusable http requester&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;common error handling&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;applying policies&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;applying loggings&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Create and get account details from Salesforce CRM&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Input has country code in the request for shipping and billing details tags, which needs to be looked up against FIRST.org open source REST API to get the country name&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Implement &lt;code&gt;clientID&lt;/code&gt; enforcement policy with SLA-based rate limiting; limit 100 requests in a minute&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Follow the best practices:&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;Reusable traits, library, and response code in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/raml-tutorial-for-beginners-and-experienced-basic&#34;&gt;RAML&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;Define respective APIs with proper error handling,&lt;code&gt;&amp;nbsp;global connectors&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;logging&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;munit testcases&lt;/code&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 768px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;52.0 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/jpeg&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1724415835082&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;08/23/2024 12:23 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17871419-salesforce-poc.jpg&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;52000&#34; data-name=&#34;salesforce-poc.jpg&#34; data-id=&#34;17871419&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17871419-salesforce-poc.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;MuleSoft API-led example&#34;&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Common Library&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Common Traits&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client credentials headers&lt;/strong&gt;: To re-use for APIs where the developer wants to secure the resources using the Client ID enforcement &amp;nbsp;policy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-wrapper&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeHeader&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;i class=&#34;icon-cancel-circled-1 cm-remove&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-code--wrapper&#34; data-code=&#34;#%RAML 1.0 Trait&#xA;    headers:&#xA;      client_id:&#xA;        type: string&#xA;        description: Client Id for the respective consumer application&#xA;      client_secret:&#xA;        type: string&#xA;        description: Client Secret for the respective consumer application&#34; data-lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;#%RAML 1.0 Trait&#xA;    headers:&#xA;      client_id:&#xA;        type: string&#xA;        description: Client Id for the respective consumer application&#xA;      client_secret:&#xA;        type: string&#xA;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; description: Client Secret for the respective consumer application&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本文给出了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-pros-and-cons-of-api-led-connectivity&#34;&gt;API 主导的&lt;/a&gt;架构的印象&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mulesoft-for-beginners-mule-4-development-complete&#34;&gt;Mule4&lt;/a&gt; API，以便清楚地了解 API 的开发过程主导的方法。它涵盖了所有 3 个 API 层（&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mule-api-experience-process-system-layer-example&#34;&gt;系统、流程和体验&lt;/a&gt;）使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/salesforce-application-design&#34;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://api.first.org/data/v1/countries&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;FIRST.org&lt;/a&gt; 作为来源。此外，我们还介绍了在每个开发层中应用最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAML&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;code&gt;通用库&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;特征&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;数据定义&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;可重用资源&lt;/code&gt; , &lt;code&gt;健康端点&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;code&gt;外部化属性文件&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;属性加密&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;外部化 dwl 代码&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;可重用 http请求者&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;常见错误处理&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;应用策略&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;应用日志记录&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;要求&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;从 Salesforce CRM 创建并获取帐户详细信息&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;输入在运输和帐单详细信息标签请求中包含国家/地区代码，需要根据 FIRST.org 开源 REST API 进行查找以获取国家/地区名称&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;通过基于 SLA 的速率限制实施 &lt;code&gt;clientID&lt;/code&gt; 强制策略；一分钟限制 100 个请求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;遵循最佳实践：&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/raml-tutorial-for-beginners-and-experienced-basic&#34;&gt;RAML&lt;/a&gt; 中的可重用特征、库和响应代码&lt;/li &gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;通过适当的错误处理、&lt;code&gt;全局连接器&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;日志记录&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;munit 测试用例&lt;/code&gt;定义相应的 API&lt;img style=&#34;width: 768px;&#34; class =“fr-fic fr-dib lazyload”data-image =“true”data-new =“false”data-sizeformatted =“52.0 kB”data-mimetype =“image/jpeg”data-creationdate =“1724415835082”数据-creationdateformatted=&#34;08/23/2024 12:23 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17871419-salesforce-poc.jpg&#34; data-修改日期=“空”数据大小=“52000”数据名称=“salesforce-poc.jpg”数据id=“17871419”数据src=“https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17871419 -salesforce-poc.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;MuleSoft API 主导的示例&#34;&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;通用库&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;共同特征&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;客户端凭据标头&lt;/strong&gt;：重复用于开发者希望使用客户端 ID 强制策略保护资源的 API&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-wrapper&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div 类=“codeHeader”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;i class=&#34;icon-cancel-circled-1 cm-remove&#34;&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-code--wrapper&#34; data-code=&#34;#%RAML 1.0 特征&#xA;    标题：&#xA;      客户 ID：&#xA;        类型：字符串&#xA;        描述：相应消费者应用程序的客户端 ID&#xA;      客户端秘密：&#xA;        类型：字符串&#xA;        描述：相应消费者应用程序的客户端密钥” data-lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;#%RAML 1.0 特征&#xA;    标题：&#xA;      客户 ID：&#xA;        类型：字符串&#xA;        描述：相应消费者应用程序的客户端 ID&#xA;      客户端秘密：&#xA;        类型：字符串&#xA;        描述：相应消费者应用程序的客户端密钥&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>