<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Calm Down, Cloud&#39;s Not THAT Different!】冷静点，云并没有那么不同！</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/calm-down-clouds-not-that-different</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I was at a tech conference recently – &lt;a href=&#34;https://nanog.org/events/nanog-91/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;one built by (and for) networking professionals&lt;/a&gt; – chatting with another attendee about the usual mix of news, tech challenges, and hobbies when the conversation took a sudden and sobering turn:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I guess I have a lot more time for side quests these days. I got laid off a couple of months back and can’t seem to land even a solid conversation, let alone a job offer. I thought it would be easier than this.”&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我最近参加了一个技术会议 - &lt;a href=&#34;https://nanog.org/events/nanog-91/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;由网络构建（并用于）的会议专业人士&lt;/a&gt; – 与另一位与会者谈论新闻、技术挑战和爱好的常见组合，但谈话突然发生了发人深省的转变：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我想这些天我有更多的时间来做支线任务。几个月前，我被解雇了，似乎连一次正式的谈话都无法进行，更不用说找到工作机会了。我认为这会比这更容易。”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AIGenOps: Generative AI and Platform Engineering】AIGenOps：生成式人工智能和平台工程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aigenops-generative-ai-and-platform-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;A While Ago...&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have been collaborating with a client in finance for some time now, and in a moment of relaxation, we started discussing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;generative artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt;. And so, caught up in the excitement, as in a positive retroactive system, we began to sketch out the idea of how to integrate it and implement it in the real-world scenario in which we found ourselves.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Merging the LLM/AI skills and knowledge of a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-devops-principles&#34;&gt;DevOps&lt;/a&gt; engineer with the vision of a platform engineer, we began to define the requirements, constraints, and loads of a real scenario in the area of regulated software and then define possible processes and solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;不久前...&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们与一位金融客户合作已经有一段时间了，在放松的时刻，我们开始讨论&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-企业“生成人工智能”&lt;/a&gt;。因此，我们沉浸在兴奋之中，就像在积极的追溯系统中一样，我们开始勾勒出如何将其集成并在我们所处的现实世界场景中实施的想法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-devops-principles&#34;&gt;DevOps&lt;/a&gt; 工程师的 LLM/AI 技能和知识与平台工程师，我们开始定义受监管软件领域真实场景的要求、约束和负载，然后定义可能的流程和解决方案。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Don’t Get Hacked! Essential Cybersecurity Tips You Need To Know】不要被黑客攻击！您需要了解的基本网络安全技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dont-get-hacked-essential-cybersecurity-tips</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Technology in the digital age has revolutionized our lives. However, this convenience comes with a growing threat: cybercrime. Malicious actors, ranging from petty thieves to sophisticated cybercriminals, operate online, seeking to exploit vulnerabilities and steal sensitive information, financial data, and even identities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;From online banking and shopping to social media and remote work, the internet has become an essential part of our daily routines. What does it mean when your online identity is turned against you? Or when you need to prove your own identity to regain control of tools you previously assumed were solely there to make your life easier?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;数字时代的技术彻底改变了我们的生活。然而，这种便利也伴随着日益严重的威胁：网络犯罪。从小偷到老练的网络犯罪分子等恶意行为者都在网上进行活动，试图利用漏洞窃取敏感信息、财务数据甚至身份。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;从网上银行和购物到社交媒体和远程工作，互联网已成为我们日常生活的重要组成部分。当您的在线身份对您不利时，这意味着什么？或者当您需要证明自己的身份以重新控制您以前认为只是为了让您的生活更轻松的工具时？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【K3s vs. Talos Linux】K3s 与 Talos Linux</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/k3s-vs-talos-linux</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the world of Kubernetes choosing the right technology can make a big difference in how smoothly and efficiently our applications run. This is where focused Kubernetes distributions like K3s and Talos Linux stand out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;From large data centers to smaller devices on the edge, Kubernetes plays an important role in managing applications across various environments. As multiple businesses are using Kubernetes at the edge to run AI nowadays, specialized versions like K3s and Talos have come to tackle various operational challenges.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在 Kubernetes 世界中，选择正确的技术可以对我们的应用程序运行的流畅性和高效性产生重大影响。这就是 K3s 和 Talos Linux 等专注的 Kubernetes 发行版脱颖而出的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;从大型数据中心到边缘的小型设备，Kubernetes 在跨各种环境管理应用程序方面发挥着重要作用。如今，随着多个企业在边缘使用 Kubernetes 来运行人工智能，K3s 和 Talos 等专用版本已经开始解决各种运营挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using SingleStore for Iceberg Catalog Storage】使用 SingleStore 进行 Iceberg 目录存储</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/using-singlestore-for-iceberg-catalog-storage</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;SingleStore recently announced bi-directional support for Apache Iceberg. Iceberg uses catalogs that are an integral part of the Iceberg table format, designed to manage large-scale tabular data in a more efficient and reliable way. Catalogs store metadata and track the location of tables, enabling data discovery, access, and management. Iceberg supports multiple catalog backends, including Hive Metastore, AWS Glue, and Hadoop, and through a database system using JDBC. This allows users to choose the most suitable backend for their specific data infrastructure. In this short article, we&#39;ll implement an Iceberg catalog using SingleStore and JDBC.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The notebook file used in this article is available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/iceberg-catalog&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;SingleStore 最近宣布对 Apache Iceberg 提供双向支持。 Iceberg 使用的目录是 Iceberg 表格式的组成部分，旨在以更高效、更可靠的方式管理大规模表格数据。目录存储元数据并跟踪表的位置，从而实现数据发现、访问和管理。 Iceberg 支持多个目录后端，包括 Hive Metastore、AWS Glue 和 Hadoop，并通过使用 JDBC 的数据库系统支持。这允许用户为他们的特定数据基础设施选择最合适的后端。在这篇短文中，我们将使用 SingleStore 和 JDBC 实现 Iceberg 目录。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文中使用的笔记本文件可在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/iceberg-catalog&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; 上找到。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Application-Level Tracing: The Good, the Bad, and the Alternative】应用程序级跟踪：好的、坏的和替代方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/application-level-tracing-the-good-the-bad-and-the</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Sailormen&#39;s Legacy: A &#34;Trace&#34; of the Past&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By the late 16th century, sailors were measuring speed with a chip log — &amp;nbsp;a method crucial for navigation. Knots were tied at regular intervals in a rope, with one end attached to a pie-slice-shaped piece of wood (&#34;chip&#34;) and flung behind the vessel. The rope played freely as the ship traveled for a fixed amount of time, which was measured using an hourglass. The number of knots that passed over the stern was counted to determine the ship&#39;s speed, with one knot equaling one nautical mile an hour. Thus, a ship going at 15 knots could traverse 15 nautical miles in an hour. Records of these measurements were kept in a logbook, which was used to calculate the ship&#39;s speed over a given period. This logbook was also used to record the ship&#39;s course, weather conditions, and other relevant information. The term &#34;log&#34; was derived from this practice, and it has since been used in various contexts to refer to a record of events or activities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In software engineering, the principle of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/log-management&#34;&gt;logging&lt;/a&gt; has been refined and expanded to include “&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-deep-dive-into-distributed-tracing&#34;&gt;traces&lt;/a&gt;.&#34; In software development, tracing represents a dynamic method of observing, debugging, and recording activities within an application, providing a more detailed, sometimes interactive, insight than traditional logging.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;水手的遗产：过去的“痕迹”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;到了 16 世纪末，水手们开始使用计程仪测量速度——这是一种对导航至关重要的方法。绳子上每隔一段距离打一个结，绳子的一端连接到一块饼状的木片（“碎片”）上，然后扔到容器后面。当船行驶一段固定的时间（用沙漏测量）时，绳子可以自由发挥。通过计算船尾的节数来确定船的速度，一节等于每小时一海里。因此，一艘以 15 节速度行驶的船每小时可行驶 15 海里。这些测量的记录保存在航海日志中，用于计算给定时间内船舶的速度。该航海日志还用于记录船舶的航向、天气状况和其他相关信息。 “日志”一词源自这种做法，此后它被用于各种上下文中，指事件或活动的记录。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在软件工程中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/log-management&#34;&gt;日志记录&lt;/a&gt;的原则已得到完善和扩展，包括“&lt;a href=&#34;https: //dzone.com/articles/a-deep-dive-into-distributed-tracing&#34;&gt;跟踪&lt;/a&gt;。”在软件开发中，跟踪代表了一种观察、调试和记录应用程序内活动的动态方法，提供了比传统日志记录更详细、有时甚至是交互式的洞察力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Achieve High GC Throughput】如何实现高 GC 吞吐量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-achieve-high-gc-throughput</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this post, let’s explore a key performance metric studied during garbage collection analysis: &#34;GC throughput.&#34; We’ll understand what it means, its significance in Java applications, and how it impacts overall performance. Additionally, we’ll delve into actionable strategies to improve GC throughput, unlocking its benefits for modern software development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Garbage Collection Throughput?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whenever an automatic garbage collection event runs, it pauses the application to identify unreferenced objects from memory and evict them. During that pause period, no customer transactions will be processed. Garbage collection throughput indicates what percentage of the application’s time is spent in processing customer transactions and what percentage of time is spent in the garbage collection activities. For example, if someone says his application’s GC throughput is 98%, it means his application spends 98% of its time processing customer transactions and the remaining 2% of the time processing Garbage Collection activities. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将探讨垃圾收集分析过程中研究的一个关键性能指标：“GC 吞吐量”。我们将了解它的含义、它在 Java 应用程序中的重要性以及它如何影响整体性能。此外，我们将深入研究提高 GC 吞吐量的可行策略，释放其对现代软件开发的好处。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是垃圾收集吞吐量？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每当自动垃圾收集事件运行时，它都会暂停应用程序以识别内存中未引用的对象并将其逐出。在此暂停期间，不会处理任何客户交易。垃圾收集吞吐量表示应用程序花在处理客户事务上的时间百分比以及花在垃圾收集活动上的时间百分比。例如，如果某人说他的应用程序的 GC 吞吐量为 98%，则意味着他的应用程序花费了 98% 的时间处理客户事务，其余 2% 的时间处理垃圾收集活动。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing and Deploying a Real-Time AI-Powered Chatbot With Serverless Architecture】使用无服务器架构实施和部署由人工智能驱动的实时聊天机器人</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-ai-powered-chatbot-with-serverless-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll walk through the process of creating and deploying a real-time AI-powered chatbot using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-serverless-architecture&#34;&gt;serverless architecture&lt;/a&gt;. We&#39;ll cover the entire workflow from setting up the backend with serverless functions to building a responsive frontend chat interface. This approach not only streamlines development but also ensures scalability and cost-efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of the Project&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ll be building a simple chatbot that interacts with users in real time. Our chatbot will leverage a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transfer-learning-in-nlp-leveraging-pre-trained-mo&#34;&gt;pre-trained AI model&lt;/a&gt; to generate responses and will be deployed using serverless computing to handle the backend logic. For this tutorial, we&#39;ll use &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-lambda-basics-writing-serverless-code&#34;&gt;AWS Lambda&lt;/a&gt; for the serverless backend and a basic &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-html&#34;&gt;HTML&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/corecss-part1&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/object-oriented-javascript&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt; interface for the front end.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将逐步介绍使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-serverless- 创建和部署实时 AI 支持的聊天机器人的过程。架构“&gt;无服务器架构&lt;/a&gt;。我们将介绍从设置具有无服务器功能的后端到构建响应式前端聊天界面的整个工作流程。这种方法不仅简化了开发，还确保了可扩展性和成本效益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;项目概述&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将构建一个与用户实时交互的简单聊天机器人。我们的聊天机器人将利用&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transfer-learning-in-nlp-leveraging-pre-trained-mo&#34;&gt;预训练的人工智能模型&lt;/a&gt;来生成响应并将使用无服务器计算来部署来处理后端逻辑。在本教程中，我们将使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-lambda-basics-writing-serverless-code&#34;&gt;AWS Lambda&lt;/a&gt; 作为无服务器后端和基本的 &lt; a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-html&#34;&gt;HTML&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/corecss-part1&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt; /&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/object-oriented-javascript&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt; 前端接口。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Databases for Modern DevOps Practices: A Guide to Common Patterns and Anti-Patterns for Database Automation Techniques】现代 DevOps 实践的数据库自动化：数据库自动化技术常见模式和反模式指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-databases-for-modern-devops-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-database-systems-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Database Systems: Modernization for Data-Driven Architectures&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As companies increasingly depend on data for decision making, operational improvements, and enhanced customer experiences, the manual management of large and complex databases becomes a daunting task, as shown in Figure 1. Database automation offers a solution by simplifying operations, reducing errors, and enhancing efficiency. Automation can handle tasks such as provisioning, scaling, and backups, allowing IT teams to focus on other initiatives. Some common techniques include scripting and scheduling, configuration management tools, Infrastructure as Code (IaC), automated testing, and more.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-database-systems-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;数据库系统：数据驱动架构的现代化&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。 p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着公司越来越依赖数据来制定决策、改进运营和增强客户体验，手动管理大型复杂数据库成为一项艰巨的任务，如图 1 所示。数据库自动化提供了一种解决方案通过简化操作、减少错误并提高效率。自动化可以处理配置、扩展和备份等任务，使 IT 团队能够专注于其他计划。一些常见技术包括脚本和调度、配置管理工具、基础设施即代码 (IaC)、自动化测试等等。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 14:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guarding Privacy: Cutting-Edge Technologies for Data Protection】保护隐私：数据保护的尖端技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guarding-privacy-cutting-edge-technologies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;a04a&#34;&gt;Data has become a valuable commodity in today’s digital era. It innovatively drives businesses to make informed decisions and personalized experiences for their customers, optimize operational efficiency, and accurately predict market trends. However, data’s immense value comes with an equally significant risk: the possibility of data breaches and malicious attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;555d&#34;&gt;As we live in an era where large amounts of sensitive information are stored and transferred via digital means, their protection becomes extremely important. The &lt;a data-href=&#34;https://www.metacompliance.com/blog/data-breaches/5-damaging-consequences-of-a-data-breach&#34; href=&#34;https://www.metacompliance.com/blog/data-breaches/5-damaging-consequences-of-a-data-breach&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;stakes&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;considering data breaches are high, as a single data breach can lead to:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;a04a&#34;&gt;数据已成为当今数字时代的宝贵商品。它以创新方式推动企业为客户做出明智的决策和个性化体验、优化运营效率并准确预测市场趋势。然而，数据的巨大价值也伴随着同样重大的风险：数据泄露和恶意攻击的可能性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;555d&#34;&gt;由于我们生活在一个通过数字方式存储和传输大量敏感信息的时代，它们的保护变得极其重要。 &lt;a data-href=&#34;https://www.metacompliance.com/blog/data-breaches/5-damaging-consequences-of-a-data-breach&#34; href=&#34;https://www.metacompliance.com /blog/data-breaches/5-damaging-consequences-of-a-data-breach&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;考虑到数据泄露风险很高，因为单个数据泄露可能会导致至：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>