<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking AI Coding Assistants Part 2: Generating Code】解锁AI编码助手第2部分：生成代码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-ai-coding-assistants-generate-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI coding assistants can help you build working code faster, eliminate manual repetition, and even propose solutions you might not have considered. In this blog, we&#39;ll explore how AI tools can become a powerful coding ally, saving you time, boosting creativity, and making your work smoother and more efficient. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article is the second in the series, with emphasis on generating code. The first part can be read here: &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-coding-assistant-use-case&#34;&gt;Unlocking AI Coding Assistants Part 1: Real-World Use Cases&lt;/a&gt;.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; AI编码助手可以帮助您更快地构建工作代码，消除手动重复，甚至提出可能未考虑的解决方案。在此博客中，我们将探讨AI工具如何成为强大的编码盟友，为您节省时间，增强创造力，并使您的工作更加顺畅，更有效。享受！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文是该系列的第二本，重点是生成代码。可以在此处阅读第一部分：“ &lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/ai-coding-assistant-use-case&#39;&gt;解锁AI编码助手第1部分：现实世界中用例。” &lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Replicate Oracle Data to BigQuery With Google Cloud Datastream】如何使用Google Cloud DataStream将Oracle数据复制到BigQuery</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/oracle-to-bigquery-replication-google-cloud-datastream</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;5:1-5:710&#34;&gt;This technical guide outlines the steps to set up data replication using Google Cloud Datastream. Specifically, it details the process of setting up data replication from an Oracle 19c database hosted on a Google Compute Engine virtual machine into Google BigQuery. The tutorial covers all necessary steps, including prerequisites—enabling APIs and configuring firewalls, setting up the Oracle source environment, establishing secure networking, creating connection profiles for both Oracle and BigQuery in Datastream, preparing the Oracle database for Change Data Capture (CDC), and finally, creating and validating the Datastream replication job.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before proceeding, ensure the following &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-built-translate-solutions-with-google-cloud&#34;&gt;Google Cloud&lt;/a&gt; APIs are enabled within your project. This is done through the Google Cloud Console under APIs &amp;amp; Services&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;P Data-Sourcepos =“ 5：1-5：710”&gt;本技术指南概述了使用Google Cloud DataStream设置数据复制的步骤。具体而言，它详细介绍了从Google Compure Engine虚拟机上托管的Oracle 19C数据库中设置数据复制的过程。该教程涵盖了所有必要的步骤，包括先决条件 - 增强API和配置防火墙，设置Oracle Source环境，建立安全的网络，为DataStream中的Oracle和BigQuery创建连接配置文件，为Oracle Database准备更改数据捕获（CDC）以及最终创建和验证DataStream Replication Replication Replication abor。&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;先决条件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在继续操作之前，请确保以下&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-built-translate-solutions-with-google-cloud”&gt; Google Cloud &lt;/a&gt;在您的项目中启用了API。这是通过API＆Services下的Google Cloud Console完成的&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Role of Artificial Intelligence in Climate Change Mitigation】人工智能在缓解气候变化中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-climate-change</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;Climate change is among the most demanding global challenges we have. Governments and organizations worldwide are trying to figure out ways to tackle it. Amidst all this, several branches of technology, especially artificial intelligence, are emerging as major contributors to climate change mitigation and adaptation. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: justify;&#34;&gt;Understanding the role of AI in climate change mitigation has opened doors to impactful projects. It has also highlighted a number of opportunities for developers to leverage the wonders of technology for a sustainable future. As we approach a new year, the contribution of AI towards mitigating climate change is expected to grow significantly. We owe this growth to huge improvements in computational power, data availability, and algorithmic efficiency. Let me guide you through all the ways developers can use AI effectively to tackle the challenges climate change brings. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p Style =“ Text-Align：Jusify;”&gt;气候变化是我们面临的最苛刻的全球挑战之一。全世界的政府和组织正在努力弄清楚解决方案的方法。在这一切之中，技术的几个分支，尤其是人工智能，正在成为缓解气候变化和适应的主要贡献者。   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：Jusify;”&gt;了解AI在缓解气候变化中的作用为有影响力的项目打开了大门。它还强调了开发人员将技术奇迹带来可持续未来的许多机会。随着新的一年，预计AI对缓解气候变化的贡献将显着增长。我们将这种增长归功于计算能力，数据可用性和算法效率的巨大改善。让我指导您了解开发人员可以有效使用AI来应对气候变化带来的挑战的所有方式。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Transformative Power of Artificial Intelligence in Cloud Security】人工智能在云安全中的变革力量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-transformative-power-of-artificial-intelligence-in-cloud-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Cloud computing has reshaped how businesses operate, offering unmatched scalability, flexibility, and cost-efficiency. However, as organizations continue to shift critical operations to the cloud, they face escalating cybersecurity challenges. Traditional security systems often struggle to protect complex, interconnected cloud environments from increasingly sophisticated cyberattacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) has emerged as the ultimate game-changer in cloud security. By enabling &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/threat-detection-1&#34;&gt;real-time threat detection&lt;/a&gt;, predictive analytics, and automated responses, AI is addressing challenges that older systems cannot handle. A report from Cybersecurity Ventures highlights that by 2028, spending on AI in cybersecurity is expected to exceed $60 billion, underscoring its growing importance. This article explores the evolving role of AI in cloud security, the benefits it brings, and the challenges it helps organizations overcome. This article explores how AI is reshaping cloud security, supported by &lt;strong&gt;graphs that provide insights into data trends and AI’s impact&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;云计算已经重塑了企业的运作方式，提供了无与伦比的可伸缩性，灵活性和成本效率。但是，随着组织继续将关键操作转移到云中，他们面临着不断升级的网络安全挑战。传统的安全系统通常难以保护复杂的，相互联系的云环境免受越来越复杂的网络攻击。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能（AI）已成为云安全性的终极游戏规则改变者。通过启用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/threat-detection-1”&gt;实时威胁检测&lt;/a&gt;，预测分析和自动响应，AI正在解决较旧的系统无法应付的挑战。网络安全企业的一份报告强调，到2028年，网络安全上的AI支出预计将超过600亿美元，强调其越来越重要。本文探讨了人工智能在云安全性，其带来的好处以及它有助于组织克服的挑战中的不断发展的作用。本文探讨了AI如何重塑云安全性，并得到&lt;strong&gt;图的支持，这些图形提供了洞察数据趋势和AI影响的见解&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Debugging Core Dump Files on Linux - A Detailed Guide】在Linux上调试核心转储文件 - 详细指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/debugging-core-dump-files-on-linux-a-detailed-guid</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Core dumps play a key roll role in debugging programs that exit abnormally. They preserve a state of a program at failure, and with them, programmers can view and identify causes of failures. In this article, a walkthrough is taken through a step-by-step exercise of enabling, creating, and checking out core dumps in Linux and touches on high-end tools and techniques for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-linux-troubleshooting-techniques-for-sres&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;debugging sophisticated failures,&lt;/a&gt; and enables quick diagnoses and resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Enabling Core Dumps in Linux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check and Set ulimit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol data-spread=&#34;true&#34; start=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Check for current value for core dumps:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;核心转储在调试异常退出的程序中起关键作用。他们保留了失败的程序状态，并且程序员可以查看和确定失败的原因。 In this article, a walkthrough is taken through a step-by-step exercise of enabling, creating, and checking out core dumps in Linux and touches on high-end tools and techniques for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-linux-troubleshooting-techniques-for-sres&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;debugging复杂的失败，&lt;/a&gt;并可以快速诊断和解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。在Linux中启用核心转储&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3&gt; &lt;strong&gt;检查并设置Ulimit &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol data-spread =“ true” start =“ 1”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;检查核心转储的当前值：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【On-Call That Doesn’t Suck: A Guide for Data Engineers】呼叫不会吸吮的呼叫：数据工程师指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/on-call-that-doesnt-suck</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In large-scale data platforms, reliability doesn’t end with the pipeline&#39;s DAG finishing successfully. It ends when the data consumers, whether dashboards, ML models, or downstream pipelines, can trust the data. But ensuring this is harder than it sounds. Poorly designed alerts can turn on-call into a reactive firefight, masking the signal with noise and reducing operator effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article presents five engineering principles for scalable, actionable, and low-fatigue data quality monitoring systems, derived from real-world learnings.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在大规模数据平台中，可靠性并不能以管道的DAG完成成功结束。当数据消费者（无论是仪表板，ML模型还是下游管道）都可以信任数据时，它结束了。但是，确保这比听起来要难。设计不佳的警报可以将通话转换为反应性的消防，从而用噪音掩盖了信号并降低操作员的有效性。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;本文介绍了五个工程原理，用于可扩展，可行和低效果数据质量监控系统，源自现实世界的学习。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build an MCP Server Using Go to Connect AI Agents With Databases】使用GO构建MCP服务器将AI代理与数据库连接</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mcp-server-go-ai-agents-database-connection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Like many of you, I have been playing around with Model Context Protocol (MCP).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To dive in, I built a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/abhirockzz/mcp_cosmosdb_go&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;sample MCP server implementation&lt;/a&gt; for Azure Cosmos DB with Go. It uses the &lt;a href=&#34;https://pkg.go.dev/github.com/Azure/azure-sdk-for-go/sdk/data/azcosmos&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Go SDK&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mark3labs/mcp-go&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;mcp-go&lt;/a&gt; as the MCP Go implementation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;像你们中的许多人一样，我一直在使用模型上下文协议（MCP）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;深入研究，我构建了a &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/abhirockzz/mcp_cosmosdb_go” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;示例mcp服务器实现&lt;/a&gt; azure cosmos db with go with go。它使用&lt;a href =“ https://pkg.go.dev/github.com/azure/azure-sdk-for-go/sdk/sdk/data/azcosmos” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; href =“ https://github.com/mark3labs/mcp-go” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; mcp-go &lt;/a&gt;作为MCP GO实施。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Modern Data Stack Is Overrated — Here’s What Works】现代数据堆栈被高估了 - 这是有效的</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/modern-data-stack-is-overrated</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Once upon a time, getting insights from your data meant running a cron job, dumping a CSV, and tossing it into a dashboard. It was rough, but it worked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Then came the wave — the “Modern Data Stack.” Suddenly, you weren’t doing data unless you had:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;曾经，从数据中获得见解意味着运行cron作业，倾倒CSV并将其扔进仪表板。这很粗糙，但是奏效了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;然后又出现了“现代数据堆”。突然，除非有：&lt;/p&gt;，否则您不会执行数据</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Java Signals】了解Java信号</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-java-signals</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;To tee off this presentation, consider a &lt;code&gt;TodosList&lt;/code&gt; that contains &lt;code&gt;Todo&lt;/code&gt; items. You wish to be able to react to the following events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;In any &lt;code&gt;Todo&lt;/code&gt;item, when:&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;The title is changed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;The completion status is toggled&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;In the &lt;code&gt;TodosList&lt;/code&gt;, when:&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;A new item is added&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;An existing item is removed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Diving In&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is a basic representation of the respective domain classes:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;要开发本演示文稿，请考虑包含&lt;code&gt; todo &lt;/code&gt;项目的&lt;code&gt; Todoslist &lt;/code&gt;。您希望能够对以下事件做出反应。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;在任何&lt;code&gt; todo &lt;/code&gt;项目中，&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;标题已更改&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;完成的完成状态已切换&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;在&lt;code&gt; todoslist &lt;/code&gt;中，何时：&#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;添加了一个新项目&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;   &lt;li&gt;删除现有项目&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;潜水&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是相应域类的基本表示：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling InfluxDB for High-Volume Reporting With Continuous Queries (CQs)】与连续查询（CQS）进行大量报告的缩放量表</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-influxdb-high-volume-cqs</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;The Bottleneck&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our systems are constantly generating high-volume transactional events. In our case, these events are funneled through Kafka and ingested into InfluxDB. Each event includes details such as timestamps, categories, and other metadata. Initially, this architecture supported our analytical needs well. We used InfluxDB to store these metrics and performed queries to generate category-wise transaction reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our typical reporting queries looked like this:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;瓶颈&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的系统正在不断生成大量的交易事件。在我们的情况下，这些事件是通过Kafka进行的，并摄入了ImpruxDB。每个事件都包括时间戳，类别和其他元数据等详细信息。最初，该体系结构很好地支持了我们的分析需求。我们使用InfluxDB存储这些指标并进行了查询以生成类别事务报告。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的典型报告查询看起来像：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>