<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker Bake: A Modern Approach to Container Building】Docker Bake：一种现代化的容器建造方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-bake-modern-container-building</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The traditional way of building Docker images using the docker build command is simple and straightforward, but when working with complex applications consisting of multiple components, this process can become tedious and error-prone. This is where Docker Bake comes in — a powerful and flexible tool for organizing multi-stage and parallel image building.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll look at the capabilities of Docker Bake, its advantages over the standard approach, and practical examples of its use for various development scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用Docker build命令构建Docker图像的传统方式简单明了，但是当使用由多个组件组成的复杂应用程序工作时，此过程可能会变得乏味且容易出错。这是Docker Bake进来的地方 - 一种强大而灵活的工具，用于组织多阶段和平行图像构建。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将研究Docker Bake的功能，其优势在标准方法中，以及其用于各种开发方案的实际示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Materialized Views in Data Stream Processing With RisingWave】使用RisingWave的数据流处理中的物质视图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/materialized-views-data-stream-processing-risingwave</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Incremental computation in data streaming means updating results as fresh data comes in, without redoing all calculations from the beginning. This method is essential for handling ever-changing information, like real-time sensor readings, social media streams, or stock market figures.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In a traditional, non-entrepreneurial calculation model, we need to process the entire dataset every time we get a new piece of data. It can be incompetent and slow. In incremental calculations, only the part of the result affected by new data is updated.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;数据流中的增量计算意味着随着新数据的进来，更新结果，而无需从一开始就重做所有计算。此方法对于处理不断变化的信息至关重要，例如实时传感器读数，社交媒体流或股票市场数字。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;在传统的非企业家计算模型中，我们需要每次获得新数据时处理整个数据集。它可能是无能和缓慢的。在增量计算中，仅更新了受新数据影响的结果的部分。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How I Made My Liberty Microservices Load-Resilient】我如何使我的自由微服务负载弹性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/liberty-microservices-load-resilient</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;It started with an all-too-familiar problem: As the traffic spiked, our microservices started slowing down, some even crashing under the pressure. Users experienced frustrating delays and outright bulk API request failures, and reliability took a hit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/docs/en/was-liberty/base?topic=liberty-overview&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IBM Liberty&lt;/a&gt; gave us a solid, lightweight foundation, but we needed to do more. To keep things running smoothly, we had to fine-tune our architecture and make our services truly resilient to heavy loads.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;它从一个非常熟悉的问题开始：当流量飙升时，我们的微服务开始放慢，有些甚至在压力下坠毁。用户经历了令人沮丧的延迟和彻底的批量API请求失败，可靠性受到了打击。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/docs/en/was-liberty/base?topic=liberty-overview&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IBM Liberty&lt;/a&gt; gave us a solid, lightweight foundation, but we needed to do more.为了使事情顺利进行，我们必须微调建筑并使我们的服务真正韧性。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero-Trust Infinite Security: Masking&#39;s Powerful New Ally】零信任无限安全：掩盖了强大的新盟友</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-infinite-security-maskings-new-ally</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Escalating data breach risks and intensifying regulatory guidelines have put organizations&#39; readiness for privacy protection into the spotlight. Until now, obscuring data sets via different methods of masking has been the anchor, but rising uncertainty around the nature of attacks requires a more proactive approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When applied with masking, zero-trust architectures have enabled organizations to shield sensitive information through various methods, such as role-based access, identity verification, and continuous encryption. The outcome? A robust and sophisticated defense against breaches.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;不断提高数据泄露风险和加强监管指南，使组织对隐私保护的准备就绪。到目前为止，通过不同的掩盖方法掩盖数据集一直是锚点，但是围绕攻击性质的不确定性提高需要一种更加主动的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;使用屏蔽应用时，零值体系结构使组织能够通过各种方法（例如基于角色的访问，身份验证和连续加密）来屏蔽敏感信息。结果？对违规行为的强大而精致的防御。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Handling Dynamic Data Using Schema Evolution in Delta】使用Delta中的架构进化来处理动态数据</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/handling-dynamic-data-schema-evolution-delta</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest challenges of managing data nowadays is its constantly changing nature. We recently came across a requirement to ingest survey data and send it for sentimental analysis. The survey data is very dynamic, and even for existing surveys, new questions will be added, modified, or deleted.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the data source evolves and adapts to new changes, the challenge is how to deal with the dynamically changing data to be represented in a table format. We implemented this by leveraging the schema evolution feature in Delta tables.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当今管理数据的最大挑战之一就是它不断变化的性质。最近，我们遇到了摄入调查数据并将其发送以进行感性分析的要求。调查数据非常动态，即使对于现有的调查，也将添加，修改或删除新问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着数据源的发展并适应了新的变化，挑战是如何处理以表格格式表示要表示的动态变化的数据。我们通过利用Delta表中的架构演变功能来实现此功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【API Management as Code: A Declarative Approach to Scaling API Operations】API管理作为代码：缩放API操作的声明性方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/api-management-as-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the rapidly evolving landscape of software development, Application Programming Interfaces (APIs) have emerged as the fundamental building blocks of modern applications, facilitating seamless communication and data exchange between diverse software systems. However, as organizations experience growth and their digital ecosystems expand, the manual management of hundreds or even thousands of APIs becomes increasingly arduous and unsustainable. This is where the paradigm of API Management as Code emerges as a transformative solution, offering a declarative approach to the efficient and scalable management of API artifacts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article explores the key concepts behind API management as code, the benefits of automation, and how technologies like GitOps and the operator pattern streamline API lifecycle management.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在软件开发的快速发展的景观中，应用程序编程界面（API）已成为现代应用程序的基本构件，从而促进了各种软件系统之间的无缝通信和数据交换。但是，随着组织经历增长及其数字生态系统的扩展，数百甚至数千个API的手册管理变得越来越艰巨和不可持续。这是API管理范式作为代码作为一种变革性解决方案出现的地方，为API工件的高效和可扩展管理提供了一种声明性的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;本文探讨了API管理背后的关键概念作为代码，自动化的好处以及Gitops和Operators Pattern Streams api API Lifecycle Management之类的技术。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Modern Data Processing Libraries: Beyond Pandas】现代数据处理库：超越熊猫</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/modern-data-processing-libraries-beyond-pandas</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;As discussed in my previous article about &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-architectures-emphasis-on-emerging-trends&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;data architectures emphasizing emerging trends&lt;/a&gt;, data processing is one of the key components in the modern data architecture. This article discusses various alternatives to Pandas library for better performance in your data architecture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Data processing and data analysis are crucial tasks in the field of data science and data engineering. As datasets grow larger and more complex, traditional tools like pandas can struggle with performance and scalability. This has led to the development of several alternative libraries, each designed to address specific challenges in data manipulation and analysis.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ auto”&gt;如我上一篇关于&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/data-architectures-emphasis-emphasis-on-emerging-trends” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black“ _ black”&gt; data Archite at emerge emerge emering emerge &lt;/aighopedation earthersone earmemems &lt;/aighope &lt;/ai operage partody atermone，本文讨论了熊猫库的各种替代方案，以提高您的数据架构性能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“自动”&gt;数据处理和数据分析是数据科学和数据工程领域的关键任务。随着数据集变得更大，越来越复杂的情况，像大熊猫这样的传统工具可能会在性能和可扩展性上挣扎。这导致了几个替代库的发展，每个库旨在应对数据操作和分析中的特定挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding the Data Culture】了解数据文化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-data-culture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A data culture is the collective behaviors and beliefs of people who value, practice, and encourage the use of data and AI to propel organizational transformation. It equips everyone in an organization with intuitive, productive insights for tackling complex business challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction: Data Culture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Creating a data culture helps you accelerate the value of analytics and AI. It transforms the quality and speed of decision-making across an organization and forms a foundation of data trust and transparency.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据文化是重视，实践和鼓励使用数据和AI来推动组织转型的人们的集体行为和信念。它使组织中的每个人都具有直观，富有成效的见解，以应对复杂的业务挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介：数据文化&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建数据文化可帮助您加速分析和AI的价值。它改变了整个组织的决策质量和速度，并构成了数据信任和透明度的基础。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Time Data Series: The Rest of the Story】时间数据系列：故事的其余部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/time-data-series-the-rest-of-the-story</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since I wrote about PHP Zmanim &lt;em&gt;—&lt;/em&gt; the work I’ve done with it and the things I’ve learned while implementing it. But despite the delay, I always intended to continue the conversation. That’s what we’re doing today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/time-data-series-getting-started-with-php-zmanim&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;first post&lt;/a&gt;, I explained how to install and get started with the PHP Zmanim library. &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Then, in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/time-data-series-working-with-php-zmanim&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;next post,&lt;/a&gt; I dug into calculating more complex times and the real power of the tool &lt;em&gt;—&lt;/em&gt; applying the most common Rabbinic opinions for various zmanim.&lt;/span&gt; I’m picking up where I left off with minimal overlap, so if you need to take a minute to get back up to speed, &amp;nbsp;I’ve linked to those previous posts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;自从我写了有关PHP Zanim &lt;em&gt;  -  &lt;/em&gt;我所做的工作以及我在实施它时学到的东西已经有一段时间了。但是尽管延迟，我总是打算继续对话。这就是我们今天正在做的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/time-data-series-getting-started-with-php-zmanim” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;第一个帖子&lt;/a&gt;我解释了如何安装和使用PHP ZMANIM库。 &lt;span style =“边距：0px;填充：0px;”&gt;然后，在&lt;a href =“ https：//dzone.com/articles/time-data-series-working-working-with-php-zmanim” target =“ _ _ black”&gt;下一篇文章，&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;我&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/&gt; &lt;/&gt; &lt;/&gt; &lt;/embir &lt;/emb &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em &lt;/em&gt;》对于各种Zanim。&lt;/span&gt;我要接下来的重叠的地方，因此，如果您需要花一分钟的时间才能恢复快速，我已经链接到了以前的帖子。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI in Agile Product Teams】敏捷产品团队的AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-in-agile-product-teams</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I have been interested in how artificial intelligence as an emerging technology may shape our work since the advent of ChatGPT; see my various articles on the topic. As you may imagine, when OpenAI’s Deep Research became available to me last week, I had to test-drive it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I asked it to investigate how AI-driven approaches enable agile product teams to gain deeper customer insights and deliver more innovative solutions. The results were enlightening, and I’m excited to share both my experience with this research approach and the key insights that emerged.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我一直对人工智能作为一种新兴技术的发展可能会如何塑造我们的作品以来自从Chatgpt出现以来；请参阅我有关该主题的各种文章。您可能想象的，当Openai的深入研究上周对我进行深入研究时，我不得不测试它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我要求它调查AI驱动的方法如何使敏捷产品团队获得更深入的客户见解并提供更多创新的解决方案。结果令人启发，我很高兴与这种研究方法和出现的关键见解分享我的经验。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>