<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Your Own IoT Project: A Step-By-Step Guide】构建您自己的物联网项目：分步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-your-own-iot-project-a-step-by-step-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/iot-security-strategies-challenges-and-essential-t&#34;&gt;IoT&lt;/a&gt;) is revolutionizing the way we interact with technology, enabling everyday objects to connect, collect data, and communicate with each other. Whether you’re a tech enthusiast or a beginner, diving into your own IoT project can be both exciting and rewarding.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide will walk you through the essential steps to build your first IoT project, ensuring you have a solid foundation to explore this fascinating field.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;物联网 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/iot-security-strategies-challenges-and-essential-t&#34;&gt;IoT&lt;/a&gt;) 正在彻底改变我们的互动方式通过技术，使日常物体能够连接、收集数据并相互通信。无论您是技术爱好者还是初学者，深入研究自己的物联网项目都既令人兴奋又有益。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南将引导您完成构建第一个物联网项目的基本步骤，确保您拥有探索这个迷人领域的坚实基础。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI vs. Human: Who Detects Bugs Better?】人工智能与人类：谁能更好地检测错误？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-vs-human-who-detects-bugs-better</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Software testing processes are evolving with the interaction of AI technologies. The advancement in AI tech has helped organizations witness improvements in their testing capabilities. Robust testing enables the release of high-quality and reliable products and services, and bug detection assists.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Earlier bug detection and reporting processes required intensive manual labor, which was time-consuming and prone to human errors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;软件测试流程随着人工智能技术的交互而不断发展。人工智能技术的进步帮助组织见证了测试能力的提高。强大的测试能够发布高质量和可靠的产品和服务，并协助错误检测。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;早期的错误检测和报告流程需要大量的体力劳动，既耗时又容易出现人为错误。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Emerging Trends in Data Warehousing: What’s Next?】数据仓库的新兴趋势：下一步是什么？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/emerging-trends-in-data-warehousing-whats-next</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-lakes-warehouses-and-lakehouses-which-is-best&#34;&gt;Data warehousing&lt;/a&gt; has been a cornerstone of business intelligence and analytics for decades, providing organizations with a structured way to store, manage, and analyze large volumes of data. However, as technology continues to evolve, so do the capabilities and expectations of data warehousing systems. This article explores the latest advances and future trends in data warehousing technologies, highlighting the innovations that are shaping the next generation of data warehouses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the era of big data, the traditional data warehouse is undergoing significant changes. The need for real-time analytics, scalability, and integration with disparate data sources has driven the development of new technologies and approaches to data warehousing. Modern data warehouses now leverage cloud computing, artificial intelligence, and advanced data processing techniques to meet the needs of today&#39;s data-driven organizations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-lakes-warehouses-and-lakehouses-which-is-best&#34;&gt;数据仓库&lt;/a&gt;一直是基石数十年来一直致力于商业智能和分析，为组织提供了存储、管理和分析大量数据的结构化方法。然而，随着技术的不断发展，数据仓库系统的功能和期望也在不断发展。本文探讨了数据仓库技术的最新进展和未来趋势，重点介绍了塑造下一代数据仓库的创新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;大数据时代，传统数据仓库正在发生重大变化。对实时分析、可扩展性以及与不同数据源集成的需求推动了数据仓库新技术和方法的发展。现代数据仓库现在利用云计算、人工智能和先进的数据处理技术来满足当今数据驱动型组织的需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Security Challenges in AI-Powered Applications】人工智能应用程序中的安全挑战</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/security-challenges-in-ai-powered-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI is revolutionizing how Software-as-a-Service (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-develop-saas-application&#34;&gt;SaaS&lt;/a&gt;) applications work, making them more efficient and automated than ever before. However, this rapid progress has opened up a Pandora&#39;s box of new security threats. From the sly manipulation of data to the gradual decay of AI models, these vulnerabilities are unique to AI-powered SaaS and need our urgent attention. In this article, we&#39;re diving deep into these risks, looking at real-world examples, and discussing practical ways to protect these AI-driven solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;We&#39;ll focus on:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能正在彻底改变软件即服务 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-develop-saas-application&#34;&gt;SaaS&lt;/a &gt;) 应用程序正常工作，使其比以往更加高效和自动化。然而，这种快速进展却打开了新安全威胁的潘多拉魔盒。从数据的狡猾操纵到人工智能模型的逐渐衰退，这些漏洞是人工智能驱动的 SaaS 所特有的，需要我们紧急关注。在本文中，我们将深入探讨这些风险，查看现实世界的示例，并讨论保护这些人工智能驱动的解决方案的实用方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我们将重点关注：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Hands-On Guide to OpenTelemetry: Using Automatic Instrumentation】OpenTelemetry 实践指南：使用自动仪器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-opentelemetry-automatic-instrumentation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiB0g9TENTSo1x2JqkGeWaKklzNjNuCmOC1whPrX1fhNqPi2Ia87bEBSYZFy2PDzxrstIcvKlzBO4UEEnfq320n80kn3wvmkrdfgWzNtW0kxEYL-MskPtVUqP5LeZxSW__G3mwpdmTqxEgtX8v_gKFD2VWk1smGnKktmQ4x5ZiRlLz-5uk_3cGK3W1McfA/s1710/otel-collector.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Are you ready to start your journey on the road to collecting telemetry data from your applications? Great observability begins with great instrumentation!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiB0g9TENTSo1x2JqkGeWaKklzNjNuCmOC1whPrX1fhNqPi2Ia87bEBSYZFy2PDzxrstIcvKlzBO4UEEnfq320n80kn3wvmkrdfgWzNtW0kxEYL-MskPtVUqP5LeZxSW__G3mwpdmTqxEgtX8v_gKFD2VWk1smGnKktmQ4x5ZiRlLz-5uk_3cGK3W1McfA/s1710/otel-collector.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;30.5 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1721053356517&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;07/15/2024 02:22 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17796576-1721053356905.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;30536&#34; data-name=&#34;1721053356905.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17796576&#34; style=&#34;width: 575px;&#34; alt=&#34;OTel Collector&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17796576-1721053356905.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; In this series, you&#39;ll explore how to adopt &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; and how to instrument an application to collect tracing telemetry. You&#39;ll learn how to leverage out-of-the-box automatic instrumentation tools and understand when it&#39;s necessary to explore more advanced manual instrumentation for your applications. By the end of this series, you&#39;ll have an understanding of how telemetry travels from your applications to the OpenTelemetry Collector, and be ready to bring OpenTelemetry to your future projects. Everything discussed here is supported by &lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a hands-on, self-paced workshop&lt;/a&gt; authored &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;by Paige Cruze&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiB0g9TENTSo1x2JqkGeWaKklzNjNuCmOC1whPrX1fhNqPi2Ia87bEBSYZFy2PDzxrstIcvKlzBO4UEEnfq320n80kn3wvmkrdfgWz NtW0kxEYL-MskPtVUqP5LeZxSW__G3mwpdmTqxEgtX8v_gKFD2VWk1smGnKktmQ4x5ZiRlLz-5uk_3cGK3W1McfA/s1710/otel-collector.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;您准备好开始您的旅程了吗正在从您的应用程序收集遥测数据吗？出色的可观测性始于出色的仪器！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiB0g9TENTSo1x2JqkGeWaKklzNjNuCmOC1whPrX1fhNqPi2Ia87bEBSYZFy2PDzxrstIcvKlzBO4UEEnfq320n80kn3wvmkrdfgWz NtW0kxEYL-MskPtVUqP5LeZxSW__G3mwpdmTqxEgtX8v_gKFD2VWk1smGnKktmQ4x5ZiRlLz-5uk_3cGK3W1McfA/s1710/otel-collector.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib延迟加载” data-image =“ true” data-new =“ false” data-sizeformatted =“ 30.5 kB” data-mimetype =“ image / png” data-creationdate =“ 1721053356517” data-creationdateformatted =“ 07/15/2024 02:22 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17796576-1721053356905.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;30536 “数据名称=“1721053356905.png”数据id=“17796576”样式=“宽度：575px;” alt=&#34;OTel Collector&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17796576-1721053356905.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 在本系列中，您将探索如何采用&lt;a href =&#34;https://opentelemetry.io&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; 以及如何检测应用程序以收集跟踪遥测数据。您将学习如何利用开箱即用的自动仪表工具，并了解何时需要为您的应用探索更高级的手动仪表。在本系列结束时，您将了解遥测如何从应用程序传输到 OpenTelemetry Collector，并准备好将 OpenTelemetry 引入您未来的项目。这里讨论的所有内容均由&lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;动手、自定进度的研讨会支持&lt; /a&gt; 作者：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;作者：Paige Cruze&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shadow IT: The Unavoidable Reality and How To Embrace It Safely】影子 IT：不可避免的现实以及如何安全地拥抱它</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/shadow-it-how-to-embrace-it</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In a world where innovation and productivity are paramount, the rise of Shadow IT has become an unavoidable reality for many organizations. A recent survey by Next DLP revealed a startling statistic: 73% of security professionals admitted to using unauthorized SaaS applications in the past year. This finding underscores a critical challenge faced by CISOs, developers, engineers, and architects alike — balancing the need for productivity with the inherent security risks of Shadow IT.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/chris-dw/&#34;&gt;Chris Denbigh-White&lt;/a&gt;, CISO at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nextdlp.com/&#34;&gt;Next DLP&lt;/a&gt;, offers a refreshing perspective on this dilemma. &#34;The security risk is not knowing what&#39;s in use,&#34; he explains. Instead of viewing Shadow IT as an insurmountable threat, Denbigh-White advocates for a more nuanced approach.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在创新和生产力至关重要的世界中，影子 IT 的兴起已成为许多组织不可避免的现实。 Next DLP 最近的一项调查显示了一个令人震惊的统计数据：73% 的安全专业人员承认在过去一年中使用了未经授权的 SaaS 应用程序。这一发现凸显了首席信息安全官、开发人员、工程师和架构师等面临的一项关键挑战——平衡生产力需求与影子 IT 固有的安全风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/chris-dw/&#34;&gt;Chris Denbigh-White&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/chris-dw/&#34;&gt;首席信息安全官 (CISO) /www.nextdlp.com/&#34;&gt;Next DLP&lt;/a&gt;，为这一困境提供了令人耳目一新的视角。 “安全风险在于不知道正在使用什么，”他解释道。 Denbigh-White 并不将影子 IT 视为无法克服的威胁，而是主张采取更细致的方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build End-To-End RAG Applications Using Airbyte and Snowflake Cortex】使用 Airbyte 和 Snowflake Cortex 构建端到端 RAG 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-end-to-end-rag-applications-using-airbyte</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As a practical example, this article shows how to build an AI Product assistant — an AI chatbot capable of answering product-related questions using data from multiple sources. With the AI Product Assistant, you can ask questions across all your company’s data in one place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can utilize the Snowflake Cortex destination to load vector data into Snowflake, followed by leveraging Snowflake’s Cortex functions to perform Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG). &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.snowflake.com/en/user-guide/snowflake-cortex/overview&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cortex&lt;/a&gt; offers general-purpose ML functions and LLM-specific functions, along with vector functions for semantic search, each backed by multiple models, all without needing to manage or host the underlying models or infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为一个实际示例，本文展示了如何构建 AI 产品助手 - 一个能够使用多个来源的数据回答与产品相关的问题的 AI 聊天机器人。借助 AI 产品助手，您可以在一个地方针对公司的所有数据提出问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以利用 Snowflake Cortex 目标将矢量数据加载到 Snowflake 中，然后利用 Snowflake 的 Cortex 函数执行检索增强生成 (RAG)。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.snowflake.com/en/user-guide/snowflake-cortex/overview&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cortex&lt;/a&gt; 提供通用 ML 函数和 LLM 特定函数，以及用于语义搜索的矢量函数，每个函数都由多个模型支持，所有这些都不需要管理或托管底层模型或基础设施。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Event Sourcing Explained: Building Robust Systems With Immutable Event Logs】事件溯源解释：使用不可变事件日志构建稳健的系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/event-sourcing-explained-building-robust-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;An architectural pattern named &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-do-you-need-to-move-from-crud-to-event-sourcin&#34;&gt;Event Sourcing&lt;/a&gt; is gaining more and more recognition from developers who aim for strong and scalable systems. In this article, we’ll take a closer look at the concept of it: what it entails, its benefits, general flow, and key concepts. Moreover, we will discuss how to implement ES — some details on the technologies that make adoption easy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article is aimed at software architects, system developers, and project managers who might be contemplating or are already engaged in integrating Event Sourcing into their systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;名为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-do-you-need-to-move-from-crud-to-event-sourcin&#34;&gt; 的架构模式事件溯源&lt;/a&gt;正在获得越来越多以强大且可扩展的系统为目标的开发人员的认可。在本文中，我们将仔细研究它的概念：它的含义、好处、一般流程和关键概念。此外，我们将讨论如何实现 ES——一些使采用变得容易的技术的细节。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文面向可能正在考虑或已经参与将事件溯源集成到其系统中的软件架构师、系统开发人员和项目经理。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dynamic Pricing Implementation: Price Rules and QCP in Salesforce CPQ】动态定价实施：Salesforce CPQ 中的价格规则和 QCP</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dynamic-pricing-implementation-price-rules-and-qcp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In today&#39;s rapidly evolving go-to-market landscape, organizations with diverse product portfolios face intricate pricing and discounting challenges. The implementation of a robust, scalable pricing framework has become paramount to maintaining competitive edge and operational efficiency. This study delves into the strategic utilization of Salesforce CPQ&#39;s advanced features, specifically price rules and Quote Calculator Plugins (QCP), to address complex dynamic pricing scenarios.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This guide presents an in-depth analysis of ten sophisticated use cases, demonstrating how these automation tools can be harnessed to create agile, responsive pricing models. By emphasizing low-code and declarative configuration methodology, this comprehensive guide provides software developers and solution architects with a blueprint to accelerate development cycles and enhance the implementation of nuanced pricing strategies.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在当今快速发展的市场环境中，拥有多样化产品组合的组织面临着复杂的定价和折扣挑战。实施稳健、可扩展的定价框架对于保持竞争优势和运营效率至关重要。本研究深入探讨了 Salesforce CPQ 高级功能的战略利用，特别是价格规则和报价计算器插件 (QCP)，以解决复杂的动态定价场景。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;本指南对十个复杂的用例进行了深入分析，展示了如何利用这些自动化工具来创建敏捷、响应灵敏的定价模型。通过强调低代码和声明性配置方法，该综合指南为软件开发人员和解决方案架构师提供了加快开发周期并加强细致定价策略实施的蓝图。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Ultimate 5-Step Guide for Mobile App Testing Automation】移动应用测试自动化终极 5 步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/five-step-guide-for-mobile-app-testing-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The global mobile app market has been growing at more than 11.5% per year and is now worth more than $154.06 billion after the COVID-19 shift toward remote work has increased and time spent online has gone up. With over 10.97 billion mobile connections worldwide, the demand for sophisticated, high-performance B2B and B2C mobile apps is increasing. The main reason for app abandonment is poor user experience. This includes a perplexing UI/UX and an excessive number of bugs. Loading times are slow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Continuous testing for mobile applications is required to ensure that a mobile app functions properly on both iOS and Android. In addition, mobile app testing can be difficult, involving numerous platforms, operating systems, and network connections.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着 COVID-19 疫情导致远程工作转向以及上网时间增加，全球移动应用市场每年以超过 11.5% 的速度增长，目前价值超过 1,540.6 亿美元。全球移动连接数超过 109.7 亿，对复杂、高性能 B2B 和 B2C 移动应用程序的需求不断增长。应用程序被放弃的主要原因是用户体验不佳。这包括令人困惑的 UI/UX 和过多的错误。加载时间很慢。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需要对移动应用程序进行持续测试，以确保移动应用程序在 iOS 和 Android 上都能正常运行。此外，移动应用测试可能很困难，涉及众多平台、操作系统和网络连接。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>