<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Generic and Dynamic API: MuleSoft】通用和动态 API：MuleSoft</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generic-amp-dynamic-async-api-mulesoft</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An organization&#39;s employee journey will involve a number of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/event-streaming-with-mulesoft&#34;&gt;events&lt;/a&gt;, some of which need to be updated in various systems within the company.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Workday will notify downstream systems, such as D365, DocuSign, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/salesforce-application-design&#34;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/a&gt;, of events such as: &lt;code&gt;ON_BOARDING&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;OFF_BOARDING&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;DEPARTMENT_CHANGE&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;OFFICE_LOCATION&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;MANAGER_CHANGE&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;INDIVIDUAL_LEAVE&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;要求&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;组织的员工旅程将涉及许多&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/event-streaming-with-mulesoft&#34;&gt;事件&lt;/a&gt;，其中一些需要在公司内部的各种系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Workday 将向下游系统（例如 D365、DocuSign 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/salesforce-application-design&#34;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/a&gt;）通知以下事件：&lt;代码&gt;ON_BOARDING&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;OFF_BOARDING&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;DEPARTMENT_CHANGE&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;OFFICE_LOCATION&lt;/code&gt;、 &lt;code&gt;MANAGER_CHANGE&lt;/code&gt; 和 &lt;code&gt;INDIVIDUAL_LEAVE&lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【JavaScript in 2024: Exploring the Latest ECMAScript Updates】2024 年的 JavaScript：探索最新的 ECMAScript 更新</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/javascript-in-2024-exploring-the-latest-ecmascript-updates</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As we reach the end of 2024, JavaScript continues to dominate as the go-to programming language for web development, owing to its versatility and community-driven evolution. The latest ECMAScript updates introduce several powerful features aimed at improving developer productivity, code readability, and overall efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Pipeline Operator (&lt;code&gt;|&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The pipeline operator is one of the most anticipated features of ES2024. Borrowed from functional programming paradigms, this operator improves the readability and maintainability of complex function chains by enabling a linear, step-by-step flow of data through multiple functions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;到 2024 年底，JavaScript 由于其多功能性和社区驱动的发展，将继续作为 Web 开发的首选编程语言占据主导地位。最新的 ECMAScript 更新引入了多项强大的功能，旨在提高开发人员的工作效率、代码可读性和整体效率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;1。 &lt;strong&gt;管道运算符 (&lt;code&gt;|&gt;&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;管道运算符是 ES2024 最受期待的功能之一。该运算符借鉴函数式编程范式，通过多个函数实现线性、逐步的数据流，从而提高了复杂函数链的可读性和可维护性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing MuleSoft Performance With HikariCP: A Complete Guide】使用 HikariCP 优化 MuleSoft 性能：完整指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-mulesoft-performance-with-hikaricp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;MuleSoft is a powerful integration platform that often deals with high-throughput workloads that require robust database connection management. One solution that stands out in optimizing database interactions is HikariCP, a high-performance JDBC connection pool known for its speed and reliability. HikariCP is widely used in applications that require efficient connection management.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll discuss the integration of HikariCP with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-mulesoft-features-certifications-amp-integ&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MuleSoft&lt;/a&gt;, its benefits, and best practices for configuring it to maximize performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;MuleSoft 是一个功能强大的集成平台，通常处理需要强大数据库连接管理的高吞吐量工作负载。 HikariCP 是一种在优化数据库交互方面脱颖而出的解决方案，它是一种以其速度和可靠性而闻名的高性能 JDBC 连接池。 HikariCP 广泛应用于需要高效连接管理的应用中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将讨论 HikariCP 与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-mulesoft-features-certifications-amp-integ&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer 的集成“ target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MuleSoft&lt;/a&gt;、它的优点以及配置它以最大限度地提高性能的最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How and Why the Developer-First Approach Is Changing the Observability Landscape】开发者优先的方法如何以及为何改变可观察性格局</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-and-why-the-developer-first-approach-is-changing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Developers play a crucial role in modern companies. If we want our product to be successful, we need to have a developer-first approach and include observability from day one. Read on to understand why.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The World Has Changed&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many things have changed in the last decade. In our quest for greater scalability, resilience, and flexibility within the digital infrastructure of our organization, there has been a strategic pivot away from traditional monolithic application architectures towards embracing modern software engineering practices such as microservices architecture coupled with cloud-native applications. This shift acknowledges that in today&#39;s fast-paced technological landscape, building isolated and independently deployable services offers significant advantages over the legacy of intertwined codebases characteristic of monolithic systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;开发人员在现代公司中发挥着至关重要的作用。如果我们希望我们的产品取得成功，我们需要采用开发人员优先的方法，并从第一天起就包括可观察性。请继续阅读以了解原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;世界已经改变&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去十年里，很多事情都发生了变化。在我们组织的数字基础设施中寻求更大的可扩展性、弹性和灵活性的过程中，我们的战略重点是从传统的整体应用程序架构转向采用现代软件工程实践，例如微服务架构与云原生应用程序相结合。这种转变承认，在当今快节奏的技术环境中，构建独立且可独立部署的服务比单一系统的相互交织的代码库特征具有显着的优势。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Test PUT Requests for API Testing With Playwright Java】如何使用 Playwright Java 测试 API 测试的 PUT 请求</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/testing-put-requests-for-api-testing-with-playwright-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;API testing is a process that confirms that the API under test is working as expected. Generally, in Agile teams, due to shift left testing, API testing is performed earlier in the SDLC as it provides major benefits, like faster feedback and allowing the team to fix the bugs early in the phase.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are multiple tools and frameworks available these days that help perform API testing quickly. Playwright is one such test automation framework that has gained a lot of popularity. Backed by Microsoft, it supports web and API automation testing in multiple programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;API 测试是一个确认被测 API 是否按预期工作的过程。一般来说，在敏捷团队中，由于左移测试，API 测试在 SDLC 中较早执行，因为它提供了主要好处，例如更快的反馈并允许团队在阶段的早期修复错误。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在有多种工具和框架可以帮助快速执行 API 测试。 Playwright 就是这样一种非常受欢迎的测试自动化框架。在 Microsoft 的支持下，它支持多种编程语言的 Web 和 API 自动化测试。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What&#39;s New in PHP 8.4: Key Enhancements and Updates】PHP 8.4 的新增功能：关键增强和更新</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/whats-new-in-php-84-key-enhancements-and-updates</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;PHP 8.4 is the latest version of the PHP scripting language, and it is packed with improvements that can streamline development, enhance performance, and introduce powerful new features to the language. For developers, this release is more than an upgrade, as it&#39;s also a toolset for crafting modern, efficient, and scalable web applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article discusses the key enhancements in PHP 8.4 and focuses on how they impact developers and elevate the language&#39;s capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;PHP 8.4 是 PHP 脚本语言的最新版本，它进行了许多改进，可以简化开发、增强性能并为该语言引入强大的新功能。对于开发人员来说，此版本不仅仅是一次升级，因为它还是一个用于构建现代、高效且可扩展的 Web 应用程序的工具集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文讨论 PHP 8.4 中的关键增强功能，并重点讨论它们如何影响开发人员并提升语言的功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DuckDB Optimization: A Developer&#39;s Guide to Better Performance】DuckDB 优化：提高性能的开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-to-duckdb-optimization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you are already using DuckDB, this guide will help you with some optimization techniques that can improve your application&#39;s performance. If you are new to DuckDB, don&#39;t fret — you&#39;ll still learn something new. I will share some of the practical tips that helped me optimize my applications. Let&#39;s dive in!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why DuckDB?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we jump into optimization techniques, let&#39;s quickly discuss what makes DuckDB stand out. In the official &lt;a href=&#34;https://duckdb.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;DuckDB documentation&lt;/a&gt;, many benefits are listed. Give it a read.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您已经在使用 DuckDB，本指南将帮助您了解一些可以提高应用程序性能的优化技术。如果您是 DuckDB 新手，请不要担心 - 您仍然会学到新东西。我将分享一些帮助我优化应用程序的实用技巧。让我们开始吧！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么选择 DuckDB？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们开始讨论优化技术之前，让我们快速讨论一下是什么让 DuckDB 脱颖而出。在官方&lt;a href=&#34;https://duckdb.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;DuckDB文档&lt;/a&gt;中，列出了许多好处。读一读。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Setting Up DBT and Snowpark for Machine-Learning Pipelines】为机器学习管道设置 DBT 和 Snowpark</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/setting-up-dbt-and-snowpark-for-machine-learning-pipelines</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI/ML workflows excel on structured, reliable data pipelines. To streamline these processes, DBT and Snowpark offer complementary capabilities: DBT is for modular SQL transformations, and Snowpark is for programmatic Python-driven feature engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are some key benefits of using DBT, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-data-processing-with-snowpark-dataframes&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Snowpark, and Snowflake&lt;/a&gt; together:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;AI/ML 工作流程在结构化、可靠的数据管道上表现出色。为了简化这些流程，DBT 和 Snowpark 提供了互补的功能：DBT 用于模块化 SQL 转换，Snowpark 用于编程式 Python 驱动的特征工程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是使用 DBT 的一些主要优势，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-data-processing-with-snowpark-dataframes&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; &gt;Snowpark 和 Snowflake 一起：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Duration Bias in Video Recommendations: A Complete Guide to Fair Content Ranking】视频推荐中的时长偏差：公平内容排名的完整指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/duration-bias-in-video-recommendations</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The meteoric rise of short-form video platforms like YouTube Shorts, Facebook Reels, and TikTok has revolutionized how people consume digital content, drawing billions of daily users worldwide. These platforms rely on advanced &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystify-ai-based-recommender-systems-an-in-depth&#34;&gt;recommendation systems&lt;/a&gt; to keep users engaged by offering personalized video suggestions. However, ranking short and long-form videos together presents a significant challenge: duration bias.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Unlike traditional recommendation systems that rely on explicit user actions like likes or shares, video platforms primarily utilize watch time and completion rates as their core engagement metric. This shift stems from the limited availability of direct user feedback, making watch metrics a practical proxy for gauging interest. However, this approach introduces an inherent bias where shorter videos are favored over equally engaging longer content because they naturally achieve higher completion rates. For instance, if a user watches 15 seconds of a 30-second video (50% completion) but spends 30 seconds on a 2-minute video (25% completion), the recommender system may interpret the first interaction as more engaging and favor the shorter video, even though both could have been equally interesting to the user. This systematic skew toward shorter content impacts the entire ecosystem, affecting user satisfaction, limiting content diversity, and discouraging creators from producing longer videos.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;YouTube Shorts、Facebook Reels 和 TikTok 等短视频平台的迅速崛起彻底改变了人们消费数字内容的方式，吸引了全球数十亿日常用户。这些平台依靠先进的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystify-ai-based-recommender-systems-an-in-deep&#34;&gt;推荐系统&lt;/a&gt;通过提供个性化的内容来保持用户的参与度视频建议。然而，对短视频和长视频进行排名会带来一个重大挑战：时长偏差。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;与依赖点赞或分享等明确用户操作的传统推荐系统不同，视频平台主要利用观看时间和完成率作为核心参与度指标。这种转变源于直接用户反馈的可用性有限，使得观看指标成为衡量兴趣的实用指标。然而，这种方法引入了一种固有的偏见，即较短的视频比同样吸引人的较长内容更受青睐，因为它们自然会实现更高的完成率。例如，如果用户观看 30 秒视频中的 15 秒（完成度为 50%），但在 2 分钟视频上花费了 30 秒（完成度为 25%），则推荐系统可能会将第一次交互解释为更具吸引力并倾向于较短的视频，尽管用户对两者同样感兴趣。这种对较短内容的系统性偏向会影响整个生态系统，影响用户满意度，限制内容多样性，并阻止创作者制作较长的视频。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Processing With Python: Choosing Between MPI and Spark】使用 Python 进行数据处理：在 MPI 和 Spark 之间进行选择</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-processing-with-python-mpi-vs-spark</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Message Passing Interface (MPI) and Apache Spark are two popular frameworks used for parallel and distributed computing, and while both offer ways to scale applications across multiple machines, they are designed to meet different needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will highlight key differences between MPI and Spark with the aim of helping you choose the right tool for your big data processing.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;消息传递接口 (MPI) 和 Apache Spark 是用于并行和分布式计算的两个流行框架，虽然两者都提供了跨多台机器扩展应用程序的方法，但它们旨在满足不同的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将重点介绍 MPI 和 Spark 之间的主要区别，旨在帮助您选择适合大数据处理的工具。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>