<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS WAF Classic vs WAFV2: Features and Migration Considerations】AWS WAF经典与WAFV2：功能和迁移注意事项</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/comparing-aws-waf-classic-vs-waf-v-two</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Amazon Web Services Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF) protects web programs against widespread vulnerabilities including SQL injection and cross-scriptability. Amazon Web Services WAFV2, a new WAF Classic service, introduces with it increased agility, elasticity, and operational efficiency.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;In this article, we will compare WAF variants, emphasize their differences, and discuss migration guidance for WAFV2 in detail.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;P Data-PM-Slice =“ 1 1 []&gt; Amazon Web服务Web Services Web应用程序防火墙（AWS WAF）保护Web程序免受广泛的漏洞，包括SQL注入和交叉标记。 Amazon Web Services WAFV2是一款新的WAF经典服务，它提高了敏捷性，弹性和运营效率。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;在本文中，我们将比较WAF变体，强调它们的差异，并详细讨论WAFV2的迁移指南。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Stop Exposing Secrets! Secure Your APIs in Postman Like a Pro】停止暴露秘密！像专业人士一样将API固定在Postman中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/stop-exposing-secrets-secure-your-apis-in-postman</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;API security is crucial, as it directly impacts your business&#39;s success and safety. How well you secure your APIs can make or mar your product, and it is of utmost importance to spend time thinking about security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I have seen developers work in Postman without properly securing their credentials, often leaving API keys exposed in shared environments or logging sensitive data in the console. For example, some developers unknowingly expose credentials when they make their workspaces public, allowing anyone to access sensitive API keys and tokens that are not properly stored.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; API安全至关重要，因为它直接影响了您的业务成功和安全。您的API可以制造或损害您的产品的安全程度，花时间思考安全至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我已经看到开发人员在邮递员中工作，但没有适当地确保其凭据，通常将暴露于共享环境中的API键或在控制台中记录敏感数据。例如，一些开发人员在公开工作空间时在不知不觉中公开凭据，允许任何人访问未正确存储的敏感API键和令牌。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Product Design vs Platform Design for Software Development】产品设计与软件开发平台设计</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/product-vs-platform-for-software-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;An enterprise architect must understand the business&#39;s need for building either a platform or a product. A &lt;strong&gt;product&lt;/strong&gt; is software that has “off-the-shelf,” more generic features and functions. In contrast, a &lt;strong&gt;platform&lt;/strong&gt; is a software or service that allows external parties to extend and develop complementary functions and services. Choosing the right fit for business needs is extremely important after careful consideration of factors for driving product/platform development.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Platforms are more flexible in connecting two or more parties, usually called producers and consumers. In recent days, organizations have been more focused on building digital platforms or digital products based on the business vertical&#39;s needs. While anyone can build products on top of a platform, the platform itself is not the product. The program perspective difference between product and platform is important for project strategy, execution, and stakeholder management. The table below shows the difference between the product and the platform.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;企业建筑师必须了解企业建立平台或产品的需求。 &lt;strong&gt;产品&lt;/strong&gt;是具有“现成”，更通用功能的软件。相反，A &lt;strong&gt;平台&lt;/strong&gt;是一种软件或服务，允许外部方扩展和开发互补功能和服务。在仔细考虑驱动产品/平台开发因素后，选择适合业务需求的合适符合业务需求非常重要。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;平台在连接两个或多个聚会方面，通常称为生产者和消费者。最近几天，组织更加专注于根据业务垂直需求建立数字平台或数字产品。虽然任何人都可以在平台顶部构建产品，但平台本身不是产品。产品和平台之间的计划观点差异对于项目策略，执行和利益相关者管理很重要。下表显示了产品和平台之间的区别。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Production-Ready Kubernetes Service Checklist】准备生产的Kubernetes服务清单</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/production-ready-kubernetes-service-checklist</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Kubernetes has emerged as a powerful tool for managing and orchestrating containerized applications. It provides scalability and availability and manages workloads so you can focus on your software&#39;s core functionality. However, moving your application from a test environment to a production environment is not straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;The purpose of this article is to list the checks we use before pushing an application to production.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p数​​据选择 - 段=“”&gt; kubernetes已成为管理和编排容器化应用程序的强大工具。它提供可扩展性和可用性，并管理工作负载，因此您可以专注于软件的核心功能。但是，将您的应用程序从测试环境转移到生产环境并不直接。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据可选 - 段=“”&gt;本文的目的是在将应用程序推向生产之前列出我们使用的支票。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Ruby on Rails to Spring Boot】从轨道上的红宝石到弹簧靴</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/from-ruby-on-rails-to-spring-boot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Like Rails, Spring Boot also follows &lt;em&gt;Convention over Configuration&lt;/em&gt; principles. The goal of this tutorial is to focus on the similarities and differences between both frameworks to provide a quick guide for developers who are migrating from one to another.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Prerequisite&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oracle.com/java/technologies/downloads/#java23&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Java Development Kit 23&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Maven instalation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;On Ubuntu&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-wrapper&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeHeader&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div class=&#34;nameLanguage&#34;&gt;&#xA;    Shell&#xA;   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;icon-cancel-circled-1 cm-remove&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-code--wrapper&#34; data-code=&#34;sudo apt update&#xA;sudo apt install maven&#34; data-lang=&#34;text/x-sh&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;text/x-sh&#34;&gt;sudo apt update&#xA;sudo apt install maven&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;像轨道一样，弹簧靴也遵循&lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;对配置的约定&lt;/em&gt;原理。本教程的目的是关注两个框架之间的相似性和差异，以为从一个框架迁移到另一个框架的开发人员提供快速指南。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;先决条件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.oracle.com/java/technologies/downloads/downloads/#java23” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ _ blank”&gt; java开发套件23 &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Maven Instalation &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3&gt;在Ubuntu &lt;/h3&gt;上&#xA;&lt;div class =“ codemirror-wrapper” pontrentediable =“ false”&gt;&#xA; &lt;div contenteaditable =“ false”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class =“ codeheader”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div class =“ namelanguage”&gt;&#xA;    壳&#xA;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;i class =“ icon-cancel-circled-1 cm-remove”&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class =“ codemirror-code  -  wrapper” data-code =“ sudo apt更新&#xA;sudo apt安装maven“ data-lang =” text/x-sh&gt;&#xA;   &lt;pre&gt; &lt;code lang =“ text/x-sh”&gt; sudo apt更新&#xA;sudo apt安装maven &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Does Video Annotation Augment Computer Vision?】视频注释如何增强计算机视觉？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-does-video-annotation-augment-computer-vision</link>
      <description>【&lt;p align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Video annotation has become the central element for conducting research on AI and machine learning in computer vision. In essence, it equips the machines with the ability to comprehend and process visual information coming from video streams. This way, it contributes to the indispensable process of training models for applications like driverless cars or a surveillance system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;In this article, we will discuss the core aspects of video annotation, its role in computer vision, popular techniques, challenges, and how companies use outsourcing services to fulfill their labeling needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p align =“ left”&gt;视频注释已成为对计算机视觉中的AI和机器学习进行研究的核心要素。从本质上讲，它使机器能够理解和处理来自视频流的视觉信息的能力。这样，它为无人驾驶汽车或监视系统等应用的培训模型的必不可少的过程做出了贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p align =“ left”&gt;在本文中，我们将讨论视频注释的核心方面，其在计算机愿景中的作用，流行技术，挑战以及公司如何使用外包服务来满足其标签需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python and Open-Source Libraries for Efficient PDF Management】Python和开源库，用于有效的PDF管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-open-source-libraries-pdf-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Python has become a popular choice for developers working with PDF documents because it&#39;s flexible and has many free libraries available. Whether you need to create PDFs, edit them, extract information, or analyze them, Python has strong tools to help.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide looks at different Python libraries for handling PDFs, compares what they offer, and helps you choose the best one for various needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Python已成为使用PDF文档工作的开发人员的流行选择，因为它具有灵活性并且有许多免费的库。无论您需要创建PDF，编辑它们，提取信息还是分析它们，Python都有强大的工具可以提供帮助。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南查看用于处理PDF的不同Python库，比较它们提供的内容，并帮助您为各种需求选择最佳的库。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 21:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Database Consistency: A Key Concept in Distributed Systems】了解数据库一致性：分布式系统中的关键概念</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-database-consistency</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Database consistency is a fundamental property that ensures data remains accurate, valid, and reliable across transactions. In traditional databases, consistency is often associated with the ACID (atomicity, consistency, isolation, durability) properties, which guarantee that transactions transition the database from one valid state to another. However, in distributed databases, consistency takes on a broader meaning, balancing trade-offs with availability and partition tolerance, as described in the CAP theorem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the rise of cloud computing, global-scale applications, and distributed architectures, database consistency models have become critical for ensuring seamless and reliable data operations. This article explores different types of database consistency models, their trade-offs, and their relevance in modern distributed systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;数据库一致性是一个基本属性，可确保数据在整个交易中保持准确，有效和可靠。在传统数据库中，一致性通常与酸（原子能，一致性，隔离，耐用性）属性相关联，这些属性可以保证事务将数据库从一个有效状态转变为另一种状态。但是，在分布式数据库中，一致性具有更广泛的含义，平衡权衡与可用性和分区公差，如CAP定理中所述。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着云计算，全球规模应用程序和分布式体系结构的兴起，数据库一致性模型对于确保无缝和可靠的数据操作变得至关重要。本文探讨了不同类型的数据库一致性模型，它们的权衡以及它们在现代分布式系统中的相关性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Doris vs Elasticsearch: A Comparison and Practical Cost Case Study】Doris vs Elasticsearch：比较和实用的成本案例研究</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/doris-vs-elasticsearch-a-comprehensive-comparison</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the domain of big data real-time analytics and log search, enterprises frequently find themselves choosing between Elasticsearch and Apache Doris. Elasticsearch is well-known for its powerful full-text search and flexible aggregation capabilities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, Apache Doris, with its distributed MPP architecture, columnar storage, and continuously evolving inverted indexing mechanism, shines in complex aggregations and data analysis.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在大数据实时分析和日志搜索领域，企业经常发现自己在Elasticsearch和Apache Doris之间进行选择。 Elasticsearch以其强大的全文搜索和灵活的聚合功能而闻名。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一方面，Apache Doris及其分布式MPP架构，柱状存储以及不断发展的倒置索引机制，可在复杂的聚合和数据分析中发挥作用。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Supervised and Unsupervised Learning in Machine Learning】在机器学习中有监督和无监督的学习</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/supervised-vs-unsupervised-learning-machine-learning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Supervised and unsupervised learning are the most popular machine learning models that companies are widely using to make things easier. Whether you are seeking a new career in AI or just planning to deepen your expertise, it is important to understand these two models because both have different functions and applications. So, without wasting time, let’s find out what these models are and how to use them to guide decision-making. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Supervised Learning?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is one of the most used &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usaii.org/ai-insights/supervised-vs-unsupervised-machine-learning-understanding-the-contrasts&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;machine learning algorithms&lt;/a&gt; trained on labeled data sets to predict outcomes accurately. The model can measure correctness and learn over time using labeled inputs and outcomes. This algorithm has two types: classification and regression.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;监督和无监督的学习是公司广泛使用以使事情变得更容易的最受欢迎的机器学习模型。无论您是在AI领域寻求新的职业还是计划加深您的专业知识，重要的是要了解这两种模型，因为两者都具有不同的功能和应用程序。因此，在不浪费时间的情况下，让我们找出这些模型是什么以及如何使用它们来指导决策。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是监督学习？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它是最常用的&lt;a href =“ https://www.usaii.org/ai-insights/supervise-vs-unsupervise-machine-learning-machine-learning----------------结果准确。该模型可以使用标记的输入和结果来测量正确性并随着时间的流逝学习。该算法有两种类型：分类和回归。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>