<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Yes! I Can Finally Run My .NET Application on Heroku!】是的！我终于可以在Heroku上运行.NET应用程序！</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/yes-i-can-finally-run-my-net-application-on-heroku</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Heroku now officially supports .NET!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;.NET developers now have access to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/heroku/heroku-buildpack-dotnet&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;officially supported buildpack for .NET&lt;/a&gt;, which means you can now deploy your .NET apps onto Heroku with just one command: &lt;code&gt;git push heroku main&lt;/code&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Heroku现在正式支持.net！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; .net开发人员现在可以访问&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/heroku/heroku/heroku-buildpack-dotnet” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ _ black”&gt;正式支持.net的buildpack for .net for .net &lt;/a&gt;，这意味着您现在可以使用一个命令将.NET应用程序部署到Heroku：&lt;code&gt; git push heroku主&lt;/code&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Scalable GenAI Applications in the Cloud: From Data Preparation to Deployment】在云中构建可扩展的Genai应用程序：从数据准备到部署</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-scalable-genai-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The cloud has proven to be a main enabler for large AI deployments because it provides AI-native APIs for rapid prototyping, elastic computing, and storage to address scaling problems. This article covers how to build and scale GenAI applications in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Importance of the Cloud in GenAI&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The cloud is critical for contemporary &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;GenAI applications&lt;/a&gt; because it can accommodate vast processing power, data storage, and distributed processes necessary for AI models. Traditional deployments often need more flexibility and performance to adapt to changing business requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;云已被证明是大型AI部署的主要促进器，因为它为快速原型制作，弹性计算和存储提供了AI本性API来解决缩放问题。本文涵盖了如何在云中构建和扩展Genai应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt; genai &lt;/h2&gt;中云的重要性&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;云对于当代&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-empopering-enterprises”&gt; genai应用程序&gt; AI模型所需的庞大处理能力，数据存储和分布式流程。传统部署通常需要更高的灵活性和性能来适应不断变化的业务需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Pattern Automation With AI and Machine Learning】通过AI和机器学习的数据模式自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-pattern-automation-ai-machine-learning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In the age of information that we live in today, every company faces challenges using data to its full potential. One technique for removing those hurdles is pattern recognition, a method by which automated processes are applied. With the amazing progress of AI, new methods of identifying relationships that were previously unobtainable, as well as identifying trends and establishing data-driven strategies, have emerged.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In this article, we describe the methods and tools necessary for automated pattern recognition and how, combined with AI, they can help unlock business process automation and improve the data management workflow within companies.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在我们今天生活的信息时代，每个公司都面临着具有全部潜力的挑战。消除这些障碍的一种技术是模式识别，这是应用自动过程的方法。随着人工智能的惊人进展，已经出现了以前无法获得的关系的新方法，以及识别趋势和建立数据驱动策略的关系。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在本文中，我们描述了自动模式识别所需的方法和工具，以及如何与AI结合使用，它们可以帮助解锁业务流程自动化并改善公司内的数据管理工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agentic Workflows for Unlocking User Engagement Insights】用于解锁用户参与见解的代理工作流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-workflows-unlocking-user-engagement-insights</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;What Are Agentic Workflows?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Agentic workflows are systems or processes where we define the goal and the role and provide some context around both of them, and the AI agents determine the steps to fulfill the goal. They differ slightly from AI automation, where we define the goal and role and provide the steps to accomplish the goal.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Advantages of Agentic Workflows&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;There are a lot of advantages to using agentic workflows. Here are a few that are showcased in our article today.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;什么是代理工作流？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;代理工作流是我们定义目标和角色的系统或过程，并在它们围绕它们围绕两个方面提供了一些上下文，并且AI代理确定了实现目标的步骤。它们与AI自动化略有不同，在该自动化中，我们定义了目标和角色，并提供了实现目标的步骤。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;代理工作流程的优势&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;使用代理工作流有很多优点。这是我们今天的文章中展示的一些。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Observability and DevTool Platforms for AI Agents】AI代理的可观察性和DevTool平台</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/observability-and-devtool-platforms-for-ai-agents</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the past years, AI agents have been everywhere across industries, autonomously and independently operating over extended periods using various tools to accomplish complex tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the advent of numerous frameworks for building these AI agents, observability and DevTool platforms for AI agents have become essential in artificial intelligence. These platforms provide developers with powerful tools to monitor, debug, and optimize AI agents, ensuring their reliability, efficiency, and scalability. Let&#39;s explore the key features of these platforms and examine some code examples to illustrate their practical applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在过去的几年中，AI代理商在各个行业中到处都是，在长时间内独立运行，使用各种工具来完成复杂的任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着众多用于构建这些AI代理的框架的出现，AI代理的可观察性和DevTool平台在人工智能中变得至关重要。这些平台为开发人员提供了强大的工具来监视，调试和优化AI代理，从而确保其可靠性，效率和可扩展性。让我们探讨这些平台的关键功能并检查一些代码示例以说明其实际应用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Enable Sybil Resistance in Your dApps on Avalanche】如何在雪崩中启用sybil抗性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-enable-sybil-resistance-in-dapps-on-avalanche</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If there’s one thing Web3 devs can agree on, it’s that Sybils suck. Bots and fake accounts are ruining airdrops, gaming economies, DAOs, and DeFi incentives. Everyone’s trying to fight them, but the solutions are either too centralized and non-private (KYC) or too easy to game (staking-based anti-Sybil tricks).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;That’s where Biomapper comes in handy — an on-chain tool that links one EVM account to one human for verifying that users are real, unique humans without KYC or exposing personal data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;如果Web3开发人员可以同意一件事，那就是Sybils很烂。机器人和虚假帐户破坏了气水，游戏经济体，Daos和Defi激励措施。每个人都在试图与之抗争，但是解决方案要么太集中和非私有化（KYC），要么太容易玩游戏（基于固定的反间隔者技巧）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这就是生物应用程序派上用场的地方 - 一种链上的工具，它将一个EVM帐户链接到一个人，以验证用户是真正，独特的人，而无需KYC或公开个人数据。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Use Terraform Import Block for Importing Resources】如何使用TerraForm导入块导入资源</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-terraform-import-block</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With Terraform 1.5 and later, you can use the &lt;code&gt;import&lt;/code&gt; block to manage the import of resources directly in your configuration. This feature simplifies the process of importing existing infrastructure into Terraform state, eliminating the need for a separate CLI &lt;code&gt;terraform import&lt;/code&gt; command.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we explain the import block and how to use it to import different resources.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用Terraform 1.5及以后，您可以使用&lt;code&gt; import &lt;/code&gt;块直接在配置中直接管理资源导入。此功能简化了将现有基础架构导入Terraform状态的过程，从而消除了对单独的CLI &lt;code&gt; Terraform Import的需求&lt;/code&gt;命令。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们解释了导入块以及如何使用它来导入不同的资源。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Recursive Prerequisite [Comic]】递归先决条件[漫画]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-quicksort-paradox</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;The New Developer Interview Tactic&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Interviewing for a new job in software development? Be aware of the recent uptick in interview questions about Quicksort. Hiring managers and recruiters really are taking &#34;divide-and-conquer&#34; to the next level.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt;新开发人员面试策略&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;面试软件开发方面的新工作？请注意有关QuickSort的面试问题的最新提升。招聘经理和招聘人员确实将“分裂和争议”提升到一个新的水平。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Impact of Edge Computing on Mobile App Development】边缘计算对移动应用程序开发的影响</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/impact-edge-computing-mobile-app-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Edge computing has revolutionized how people use mobile apps and how those offerings function. It has also increased opportunities for application development professionals. How does edge computing support their work and broaden their ability to meet consumers’ needs?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;1. Enhanced Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Since &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-edge-computing-delving-into-amazon-and-f&#34;&gt;edge computing&lt;/a&gt; enables data processing closer to its source, user information travels shorter distances and may not leave a person’s device. Those advantages significantly reduce the chances of malicious parties compromising it. Using edge computing to strengthen cybersecurity is an excellent way to build people’s trust and position app developers at the forefront of proactive measures to protect user details.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Edge Computing已彻底改变了人们如何使用移动应用程序以及这些产品的运作方式。它还增加了应用程序开发专业人员的机会。边缘计算如何支持他们的工作并扩大满足消费者需求的能力？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt; 1。增强的隐私&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;因为&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-edge-computing-delving-into-into-amazon-and-f-----&gt; edge Computing &lt;/a&gt;启用数据处理更接近其来源，用户信息会传播较短的距离，并且可能不会离开一个人的设备。这些优势大大减少了恶意政党损害危害的机会。使用边缘计算来增强网络安全是建立人们信任和位置应用程序开发人员在主动措施的最前沿保护用户详细信息的绝佳方法。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamline Microservices Development With Dapr and Amazon EKS】使用DAPR和Amazon EKS的简化微服务开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/streamline-microservices-development-with-dapr-amazon-eks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Microservices and containers are revolutionizing how modern applications are built, deployed, and managed in the cloud. However, developing and operating microservices can introduce significant complexity, often requiring developers to spend valuable time on cross-cutting concerns like service discovery, state management, and observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dapr, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/curating-efficient-dapr-workflows&#34;&gt;Distributed Application Runtime&lt;/a&gt;, is an open-source runtime for building microservices on cloud and edge environments. It provides platform-agnostic building blocks like service discovery, state management, pub/sub messaging, and observability out of the box. Dapr moved to the graduated maturity level of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/dapr/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CNCF&lt;/a&gt; (Cloud Native Computing Foundation) and is currently used by many enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;微服务和容器正在彻底改变现代应用程序在云中的构建，部署和管理的方式。但是，开发和操作微服务可能会引入重大的复杂性，通常要求开发人员花费宝贵的时间来进行跨记录问题，例如服务发现，州管理和可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; dapr，或&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/curating-felfforited-felficited-dapr-workflows”&gt;分布式应用程序运行时&lt;/a&gt;，是在云和云上构建微服务的开放式运行时边缘环境。它提供了诸如服务发现，州管理，酒吧/子消息传递以及开箱即用的可观察性，例如服务发现，州管理，酒吧/子消息传递。 DAPR移至&lt;a href =“ https://www.cncf.io/projects/dapr/”的成熟度级别的成熟度），目前由许多企业使用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>