<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Solving the Cold Start Problem in Edge AI: A Guide to Data-Saving Learning】解决边缘人工智能中的冷启动问题：数据保存学习指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/solving-the-cold-start-problem-in-edge-ai-a-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We have all seen the demo: a computer vision model achieves 99% accuracy on a test dataset. Then, we deploy it to an edge device — a drone, a security camera, or an industrial robot — and performance crashes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;633&#34; data-start=&#34;357&#34;&gt;The problem is &lt;strong data-end=&#34;388&#34; data-start=&#34;372&#34;&gt;domain shift&lt;/strong&gt;. The lighting is different, the camera angle is skewed, or the background noise has changed. In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mlops-architectural-models-advanced-guide&#34;&gt;traditional MLOps&lt;/a&gt;, the solution is to collect thousands of new images from the edge device, label them manually, and retrain the model from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们都看过演示：计算机视觉模型在测试数据集上实现了 99% 的准确率。然后，我们将其部署到边缘设备（无人机、安全摄像头或工业机器人），然后性能崩溃。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;633&#34; data-start=&#34;357&#34;&gt;问题是&lt;strong data-end=&#34;388&#34; data-start=&#34;372&#34;&gt;域名转移&lt;/strong&gt;。照明不同、摄像机角度倾斜或背景噪音发生变化。在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mlops-architectural-models-advanced-guide&#34;&gt;传统 MLOps&lt;/a&gt; 中，解决方案是从边缘设备收集数千张新图像，手动标记它们，然后从头开始重新训练模型。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Developer Tools That Actually Matter in 2026】2026 年真正重要的开发者工具</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/developer-tools-that-actually-matter-in-2026</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;650&#34; data-start=&#34;210&#34;&gt;Though I am an architect, I am a developer at heart. I explore developer tools every year and publish my favorites here. As developers, we’ve all been through the hype cycles. Every year brings a new wave of tools that promise to change everything. Most fade away within months. But 2026 is different — and not because of buzzwords. The tools that are making real differences now are the ones solving actual problems we face every single day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;972&#34; data-start=&#34;652&#34;&gt;I’ve spent the last few months testing what’s actually working in production environments, talking to teams across different tech stacks, and trying tools that claim to make our lives easier. Here’s what I found: the best tools aren’t the flashiest ones. They’re the ones that disappear into your workflow and just work.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;650&#34; data-start=&#34;210&#34;&gt;虽然我是一名架构师，但我本质上是一名开发人员。我每年都会探索开发者工具并在这里发布我最喜欢的工具。作为开发人员，我们都经历过炒作周期。每年都会出现一波新的工具，它们有望改变一切。大多数在几个月内就会消失。但 2026 年有所不同——并不是因为流行语。现在真正发挥作用的工具是那些解决我们每天面临的实际问题的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;972&#34; data-start=&#34;652&#34;&gt;在过去的几个月里，我一直在测试生产环境中实际运行的功能，与不同技术堆栈的团队进行交流，并尝试声称可以让我们的生活更轻松的工具。我的发现是这样的：最好的工具并不是最华丽的工具。它们会消失在您的工作流程中并且正常工作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Metadata, Not Data Volume, Is the Real Bottleneck in Modern Data Lakes】元数据，而不是数据量，是现代数据湖的真正瓶颈</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/metadata-not-data-volume-is-the-real-bottleneck-in</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;288&#34; data-start=&#34;141&#34;&gt;For more than a decade, data engineering best practices have revolved around a single assumption: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cost-optimization-strategies-for-high-volume-data&#34;&gt;data volume&lt;/a&gt; is the primary scalability challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;538&#34; data-start=&#34;290&#34;&gt;We optimized Parquet sizes, tuned partitioning strategies, compressed aggressively, and scaled compute to handle terabytes and petabytes of data. As long as queries scanned fewer files and clusters had enough memory, performance generally improved.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;288&#34; data-start=&#34;141&#34;&gt;十多年来，数据工程最佳实践一直围绕着一个假设：&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cost-optimization-strategies-for-high-volume-data&#34;&gt;数据量&lt;/a&gt;是主要的可扩展性挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;538&#34; data-start=&#34;290&#34;&gt;我们优化了 Parquet 大小、调整了分区策略、积极压缩并扩展了计算以处理 TB 和 PB 的数据。只要查询扫描的文件较少并且集群有足够的内存，性能通常会提高。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Data Engineers Need to Think Like Product Managers】为什么数据工程师需要像产品经理一样思考</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-data-engineers-must-think-like-product-managers</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, the work of a data engineer is more complex than simply building pipelines and platforms. Data engineers are no longer just builders; they are now vital parts of value creation in a data driven organization. However, many engineers continue to evaluate success using the number of completed jobs and created tables, rather than their actual worth to the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is where a Product Manager (PM) mindset comes in handy. Adopting a product manager’s way of thinking is not about managing Jira boards and marketing roadmaps. It is about thinking of data assets as products complete with customers, lifecycle, and tangible results.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如今，数据工程师的工作比简单地构建管道和平台更加复杂。数据工程师不再只是建设者；它们现在是数据驱动型组织中价值创造的重要组成部分。然而，许多工程师继续使用已完成的作业和创建的表的数量来评估成功，而不是它们对业务的实际价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是产品经理 (PM) 思维方式派上用场的地方。采用产品经理的思维方式并不是管理 Jira 看板和营销路线图。它将数据资产视为包含客户、生命周期和有形结果的产品。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【BYOLM with Spring AI &amp;amp; MCP: Secure, Swappable AI Everywhere】BYOLM 与 Spring AI 和 MCP：安全、可交换的 AI 无处不在</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/byolm-with-spring-ai-and-mcp</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence has rapidly moved from research labs into everyday tools. Yet, most users remain locked into vendor‑controlled ecosystems, where the choice of language model (LM) is dictated by the provider. This creates friction for developers, educators, and organizations who want flexibility, privacy, and control. The &lt;strong&gt;Bring Your Own Language Model (BYOLM)&lt;/strong&gt; paradigm challenges this status quo. By designing a configurable middleware layer, extensions for Chrome, Word, and other applications can seamlessly integrate with swappable LLMs. Combined with &lt;strong&gt;Spring AI&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP)&lt;/strong&gt;, this architecture empowers users to safeguard sensitive data, authenticate access securely, and orchestrate reproducible AI labs. This article may be referred to as a sequel to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/private-ai-home-rag-chatbot&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;this article on DZone&lt;/a&gt;, and readers are encouraged to read it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The motivation behind BYOLM is simple yet powerful: &lt;strong&gt;freedom of choice&lt;/strong&gt;. Traditional AI assistants often operate as black boxes, offering little transparency into how data is processed or stored. For developers and mentors, this lack of control is unacceptable. BYOLM allows individuals and organizations to:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能已迅速从研究实验室转变为日常工具。然而，大多数用户仍然被锁定在供应商控制的生态系统中，其中语言模型 (LM) 的选择由供应商决定。这给需要灵活性、隐私和控制的开发人员、教育工作者和组织带来了摩擦。 &lt;strong&gt;自带语言模型 (BYOLM)&lt;/strong&gt; 范式挑战了这一现状。通过设计可配置的中间件层，Chrome、Word 和其他应用程序的扩展可以与可交换的 LLM 无缝集成。该架构与&lt;strong&gt;Spring AI&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;模型上下文协议(MCP)&lt;/strong&gt;相结合，使用户能够保护敏感数据、安全地验证访问权限并编排可重复的人工智能实验室。本文可能被称为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/private-ai-home-rag-chatbot&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;这篇有关 DZone 的文章&lt;/a&gt;的续集，鼓励读者阅读。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;动机&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;BYOLM 背后的动机简单而强大：&lt;strong&gt;选择自由&lt;/strong&gt;。传统的人工智能助手通常作为黑匣子运行，对数据的处理或存储方式几乎不透明。对于开发人员和导师来说，这种缺乏控制的情况是不可接受的。 BYOLM 允许个人和组织：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Parquet Scans: How Readers Skip Work and Stay Fast】了解镶木地板扫描：读者如何跳过工作并保持快速</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-parquet-scans</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://parquet.apache.org/docs/overview/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Parquet&lt;/a&gt; is a columnar file format designed for efficient data storage and retrieval. On disk, it is organized around row groups, column chunks, and pages. Along with that, each file also has a footer that describes how everything fits together. A Parquet reader that understands this layout can avoid a lot of work during the scan, such as skipping entire row groups, column chunks, and pages, and decoding only the values that matter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article uses a single sample &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/securing-parquet-files-vulnerabilities-mitigations&#34;&gt;Parquet file&lt;/a&gt; to explain exactly what happens during column reads and some common optimization techniques.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://parquet.apache.org/docs/overview/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Parquet&lt;/a&gt; 是一种柱状文件格式，专为高效数据存储和检索而设计。在磁盘上，它是围绕行组、列块和页面进行组织的。除此之外，每个文件还有一个页脚，描述所有内容如何组合在一起。了解这种布局的 Parquet 读取器可以避免扫描期间的大量工作，例如跳过整个行组、列块和页面，并仅解码重要的值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文使用单个示例&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/securing-parquet-files-vulnerability-mitigations&#34;&gt;Parquet 文件&lt;/a&gt;来准确解释列读取期间会发生什么以及一些常见的优化技术。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【6 Software Development and DevOps Trends Shaping 2026】6 2026 年软件开发和 DevOps 趋势</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-devops-trends-shaping-2026</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In 2025, many teams tried new things in software development and DevOps — AI copilots, new platforms, more automation, and more security checks. Some of it worked great, some of it created new mess (tool sprawl, unclear ownership, higher cloud bills, and “we ship faster but break more”).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Heading into 2026, the focus is shifting from experimentation to ensuring reliability and repeatability. Leaders and practitioners are asking the same questions: How do we move fast without losing quality? How do we keep systems secure without slowing teams down? How do we reduce toil, control costs, and still deliver features that matter?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;2025 年，许多团队在软件开发和 DevOps 方面尝试了新事物 - AI 副驾驶、新平台、更多自动化和更多安全检查。其中一些效果很好，另一些则造成了新的混乱（工具蔓延、所有权不明确、云费用更高，以及“我们发货速度更快，但破坏更多”）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;进入 2026 年，重点将从实验转向确保可靠性和可重复性。领导者和实践者都在问同样的问题：我们如何快速行动而不失去质量？我们如何在不减慢团队速度的情况下保证系统安全？我们如何减少辛苦工作、控制成本并仍然提供重要的功能？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Practical Guide to Semantic Caching With Redis LangCache】Redis LangCache 语义缓存实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/semantic-caching-redis-langcache-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/llm-integration-unleashed-elevating-efficiency-and&#34;&gt;Semantic cache&lt;/a&gt; is an advanced caching mechanism that differs from traditional caching, which relies on exact keyword matching; it stores and retrieves data based on semantic similarity. &lt;strong&gt;Redis LangCache&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;is a fully hosted semantic caching service that helps cache LLM prompts and responses semantically, thereby reducing LLM usage costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In this tutorial, let&#39;s learn how to quickly create a simple application and use LangCache for caching LLM queries. Also, see if we can combine fuzzy logic to improve the responses. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/llm-integration-unleashed-elevating-efficiency-and&#34;&gt;语义缓存&lt;/a&gt;是一种高级缓存机制，不同于传统缓存，传统缓存依赖于精确的关键字匹配；它根据语义相似性存储和检索数据。 &lt;strong&gt;Redis LangCache&lt;/strong&gt;是一种完全托管的语义缓存服务，可帮助缓存 LLM 提示和语义响应，从而降低 LLM 使用成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在本教程中，我们将学习如何快速创建一个简单的应用程序并使用 LangCache 来缓存 LLM 查询。另外，看看我们是否可以结合模糊逻辑来改进响应。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Effectively Managing AI Agents for Testing】有效管理用于测试的 AI 代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/effectively-managing-ai-agents-for-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Large language models and AI agents have already transformed many fields and are changing our lives in fundamental ways. In the &lt;strong&gt;testing domain&lt;/strong&gt;, AI agents have a clear path for making immediate improvements in process and quality, and ultimately for producing reliable, performant, secure, and compliant software. Check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-agentic-test-automation-for-qa-teams&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Demystifying Agentic Test Automation: What It Means for QA Teams&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; But it’s not obvious&amp;nbsp;how&amp;nbsp;to take advantage of these capabilities. While AI agents are not fully predictable, they can be managed reliably via robust control mechanisms. Let&#39;s see how.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Does It Mean to Manage AI Agents in QA?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;There are several important aspects to managing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agents-future-of-automation-or-overhyped-buzzword&#34;&gt;AI agents&lt;/a&gt;, both in general and specifically in the testing domain.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;大型语言模型和人工智能代理已经改变了许多领域，并从根本上改变了我们的生活。在&lt;strong&gt;测试领域&lt;/strong&gt;，人工智能代理有一条明确的路径，可以立即改进流程和质量，并最终生成可靠、高性能、安全且合规的软件。请查看&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-agentic-test-automation-for-qa-teams&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;揭秘代理测试自动化：这对 QA 团队意味着什么&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; 但如何利用这些功能并不明显。虽然人工智能代理不能完全预测，但可以通过强大的控制机制对其进行可靠管理。让我们看看如何。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在 QA 中管理 AI 代理意味着什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;管理&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agents-future-of-automation-or-overhyped-buzzword&#34;&gt;AI 代理&lt;/a&gt;有几个重要方面，无论是在一般情况下还是在测试领域。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking Hidden Value in Dirty Data: A Practical NLP Pattern for Legacy Records】解锁脏数据中的隐藏价值：遗留记录的实用 NLP 模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-hidden-value-in-dirty-data-a-practical-n</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;370&#34; data-start=&#34;199&#34;&gt;In the era of Digital Transformation (DX), we are often told that &lt;em data-end=&#34;289&#34; data-start=&#34;265&#34;&gt;&#34;data is the new oil.&#34;&lt;/em&gt; However, for many enterprises, that oil is crude, unrefined, and full of sludge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;775&#34; data-start=&#34;372&#34;&gt;Consider the automotive, manufacturing, or healthcare industries. For decades, technicians and operators have been typing notes into free-text fields. These millions of records contain critical information about asset health, maintenance history, and compliance. But because they are unstructured, full of typos, and riddled with domain-specific slang, they remain invisible to standard analytics tools.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;370&#34; data-start=&#34;199&#34;&gt;在数字化转型 (DX) 时代，我们经常被告知&lt;em data-end=&#34;289&#34; data-start=&#34;265&#34;&gt;“数据就是新石油。”&lt;/em&gt;然而，对于许多企业来说，这种石油是未经提炼的、充满污泥的原油。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;775&#34; data-start=&#34;372&#34;&gt;考虑汽车、制造或医疗保健行业。几十年来，技术人员和操作员一直在自由文本字段中输入注释。这数百万条记录包含有关资产运行状况、维护历史记录和合规性的重要信息。但由于它们是非结构化的、充满拼写错误并且充满了特定领域的俚语，因此标准分析工具仍然看不到它们。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>