<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【DevSecConflict: How Google Project Zero and FFmpeg Went Viral For All the Wrong Reasons】DevSecConflict：Google 零项目和 FFmpeg 如何因各种错误原因而传播开来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devsecconflict-google-project-zero-ffmpeg</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Security research isn’t a stranger to controversy. The small community of dedicated niche security teams, independent researchers, and security vendors working on new products finds vulnerabilities in software and occasionally has permission to find and exploit them. This security industry has always had a fraught relationship with the law and the terms of service of the organisations they target, as notoriety is prioritized over legalities. Regardless of the true motives of security researchers, it is difficult to argue that this vulnerability hunting is done with no genuine desire to improve security, in addition to producing a conference talk or two.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;To avoid legal threats, many researchers opt to avoid commercial software, products, and applications and instead turn their attention to open source. Open-source teams welcome contributions to improve security, offer transparency through pull requests, and are used throughout the industry. Where closed-source software may respond with a legal threat, open source responds with an enthusiastic thank-you, allowing security researchers to make an impact and talk about their work.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;安全研究对争议并不陌生。由专门的利基安全团队、独立研究人员和致力于新产品的安全供应商组成的小社区发现软件中的漏洞，并且偶尔有权发现和利用它们。这个安全行业一直与法律和其目标组织的服务条款有着令人担忧的关系，因为恶名优先于合法性。无论安全研究人员的真实动机如何，很难说这种漏洞搜寻除了进行一两场会议演讲外，并没有真正提高安全性的愿望。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为了避免法律威胁，许多研究人员选择避免商业软件、产品和应用程序，而是将注意力转向开源。开源团队欢迎为提高安全性做出贡献，通过拉取请求提供透明度，并在整个行业中使用。闭源软件可能会以法律威胁来回应，而开源软件则以热情的感谢来回应，让安全研究人员能够产生影响并谈论他们的工作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When Chatbots Go Rogue: Securing Conversational AI in Cyber Defense】当聊天机器人失控时：确保网络防御中对话式人工智能的安全</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/securing-conversational-ai-chatbot-cyber-defense</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The evolution of conversational AI has introduced another dimension of interaction between businesses and users on the internet. AI chatbots have become an inseparable part of the digital ecosystem, which is no longer restricted to customer service or personalized suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Chatbots have the potential to share sensitive data, break user trust, and even create an entry point to cyberattacks. This renders the security of conversational AI a matter of urgent concern to enterprises that embrace AI chatbot development services for websites.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;对话式人工智能的发展引入了互联网上企业和用户之间互动的另一个维度。人工智能聊天机器人已成为数字生态系统不可分割的一部分，不再局限于客户服务或个性化建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;聊天机器人有可能共享敏感数据、破坏用户信任，甚至创建网络攻击的入口点。这使得对话式人工智能的安全性成为采用人工智能网站聊天机器人开发服务的企业迫切关注的问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build Real-Time Transaction Monitoring Systems With Streaming Data】如何使用流数据构建实时交易监控系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-transaction-monitoring-streaming-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The rate at which financial transactions are conducted in the United States has been increasing at a tremendous rate over the last few years. Billions of dollars flow through networks in seconds as digital wallets, instant peer-to-peer payments, and online banking emerge. This presents opportunity as well as risk. Real-time transaction monitoring systems with streaming data have become a security and compliance priority in financial institutions due to the importance of detecting suspicious behavior in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Although the traditional monitoring model typically assumes the use of batch processes to analyze the data hours after it was captured, the recent threat landscape does not tolerate any speed. In the year 2023, the Federal Trade Commission reported that the American people had lost over $10 billion to fraud, the highest recorded amount. Even one day of delay can be converted into millions of avoidable losses. Streaming data technologies offer a way forward, where financial systems will be able to process and assess transactions in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;过去几年，美国的金融交易进行速度一直在大幅增长。随着数字钱包、即时点对点支付和在线银行的出现，数十亿美元在几秒钟内通过网络流动。这既带来了机遇，也带来了风险。由于实时检测可疑行为的重要性，具有流数据的实时交易监控系统已成为金融机构的安全和合规优先事项。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;虽然传统的监控模型通常假设使用批处理在捕获数据数小时后对其进行分析，但最近的威胁形势无法容忍任何速度。 2023 年，联邦贸易委员会报告称，美国人民因欺诈损失超过 100 亿美元，创历史最高纪录。即使一天的延误也可能转化为数百万可避免的损失。流数据技术提供了一条前进的道路，金融系统将能够实时处理和评估交易。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) System in Java With Spring AI, Vertex AI, and BigQuery】使用 Spring AI、Vertex AI 和 BigQuery 在 Java 中构建检索增强生成 (RAG) 系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rag-system-java-spring-ai-vertex-bigquery</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;756&#34; data-start=&#34;333&#34;&gt;Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) is quickly becoming one of the most powerful design patterns for AI applications. It bridges the gap between general-purpose large language models (LLMs) and your specific enterprise data. In this article, we’ll walk through how to build a complete RAG pipeline in Java using Spring Boot, Vertex AI’s Gemini embeddings, Apache PDFBox, and BigQuery Vector Search.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;776&#34; data-start=&#34;758&#34;&gt;You will see how to do the following, wrapped in a Spring Boot app with a simple web UI:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;756&#34; data-start=&#34;333&#34;&gt;检索增强生成 (RAG) 正在迅速成为 AI 应用程序最强大的设计模式之一。它弥合了通用大型语言模型 (LLM) 和特定企业数据之间的差距。在本文中，我们将介绍如何使用 Spring Boot、Vertex AI 的 Gemini 嵌入、Apache PDFBox 和 BigQuery Vector Search 在 Java 中构建完整的 RAG 管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;776&#34; data-start=&#34;758&#34;&gt;您将了解如何使用简单的 Web UI 封装在 Spring Boot 应用程序中执行以下操作：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating an MCP Client With Spring AI】使用 Spring AI 创建 MCP 客户端</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-an-mcp-client-with-spring-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;MCP servers extend the functionality of a large language model (LLM). Inference engines allow you to define the MCP servers, but often you will need to write an MCP client yourself. In this blog, you will learn how to do so using Spring AI. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/creating-an-mcp-server-with-spring-ai&#34;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;, you learnt how to create an MCP server using Spring Boot and Spring AI. The MCP server provides four tools:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;MCP 服务器扩展了大型语言模型 (LLM) 的功能。推理引擎允许您定义 MCP 服务器，但通常您需要自己编写 MCP 客户端。在本博客中，您将学习如何使用 Spring AI 来做到这一点。享受吧！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/creating-an-mcp-server-with-spring-ai&#34;&gt;上一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;中，您学习了如何使用 Spring Boot 和 Spring AI 创建 MCP 服务器。 MCP服务器提供四种工具：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Right to Be Forgotten in Event-Driven Data Products】事件驱动数据产品中被遗忘的权利</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/right-to-be-forgotten-event-driven-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Companies operating under regulatory frameworks such as GDPR, CPPA, and other privacy laws increasingly find themselves under pressure to enforce strict and timely retention and deletion policies for customer data. These regulations not only require data to be stored securely but also mandate that organizations delete customer information wherever it exists when the customer requests deletion, upon customer exit, or when retention windows expire. In practice, this &#34;right to be forgotten&#34; means that every copy, transformation, and analytical artifact referencing that individual must be identified and purged within defined timeframes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In many organizations, especially those with complex analytical ecosystems, this is far more difficult than it sounds. Operational systems often have clear deletion semantics, but analytical platforms (data lakes, warehouses, dashboards, machine learning pipelines) tend to accumulate replicated and transformed copies of customer data that sit outside the operational flow. When a deletion occurs upstream, downstream analytical systems may not hear about it, may not react in time, or may not have a reliable mechanism to trace lineage and apply deletions consistently. This gap creates compliance risk, audit failures, and fragmentation across analytical domains.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在 GDPR、CPPA 和其他隐私法等监管框架下运营的公司越来越发现自己面临着强制执行严格、及时的客户数据保留和删除政策的压力。这些法规不仅要求安全存储数据，还要求组织在客户请求删除、客户退出或保留窗口到期时删除存在的客户信息。实际上，这种“被遗忘的权利”意味着引用该个人的每个副本、转换和分析工件都必须在规定的时间范围内被识别和清除。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在许多组织中，尤其是那些拥有复杂分析生态系统的组织，这比听起来要困难得多。操作系统通常具有明确的删除语义，但分析平台（数据湖、仓库、仪表板、机器学习管道）往往会积累位于操作流程之外的客户数据的复制和转换副本。当上游发生删除时，下游分析系统可能不会听到它，可能不会及时做出反应，或者可能没有可靠的机制来跟踪谱系并一致地应用删除。这种差距造成了合规风险、审计失败以及分析领域的碎片化。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Architectural Evidence in Enterprise Java: Making Domain-Driven Design Visible】Enterprise Java 中的架构证据：使领域驱动设计变得可见</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enterprise-java-domain-driven-design</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;One subtle challenge in software architecture is that architectural thinking can feel detached from the codebase. We draw diagrams, define layers, identify responsibilities, and craft a coherent structure — yet the moment implementation begins, those architectural ideas fade into the background. Over time, systems drift not because developers ignore design, but because the code itself provides almost no way to express that design.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This tension is well documented. In Just Enough Software Architecture, George Fairbanks argues that programming languages lack constructs for directly representing architectural concepts. Java lets us model types, fields, methods, and packages, but offers no native way to encode ideas such as “presentation layer,” “domain logic,” “aggregate root,” or “infrastructure boundary.” Without these cues in the code, architecture becomes optional, verbal, and fragile.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;软件架构中的一个微妙挑战是架构思维可能会感觉与代码库分离。我们绘制图表，定义层次，确定职责，并制定一个连贯的结构——然而，一旦开始实施，这些架构思想就会消失在背景中。随着时间的推移，系统发生漂移并不是因为开发人员忽视了设计，而是因为代码本身几乎没有提供表达该设计的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种紧张局势是有据可查的。在《Just Enough Software Architecture》一书中，George Fairbanks 认为编程语言缺乏直接表示架构概念的构造。 Java 允许我们对类型、字段、方法和包进行建模，但没有提供本地方式来编码“表示层”、“域逻辑”、“聚合根”或“基础设施边界”等概念。如果代码中没有这些提示，架构就会变得可选、口头且脆弱。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When Leadership Blocks Your Pre-Mortem】当领导层阻止你进行事前剖析时</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/when-leadership-blocks-your-pre-mortem</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR: The Pre-Mortem&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Leadership resistance to your pre-mortem reveals whether your organization’s operating model prioritizes comfortable narratives over preventing failure. This article shows you how to diagnose cultural dysfunction and decide which battles to fight.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Magic Of Risk Mitigation Without Passing Blame&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a risk technique that takes 60 minutes, costs nothing, and surfaces problems other planning methods miss. It’s been field-tested for nearly two decades. Teams that use it catch catastrophic issues while there’s still time to act.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR：事前剖析&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;领导层对事前剖析的抵制揭示了您组织的运营模式是否优先考虑舒适的叙述而不是防止失败。本文向您展示如何诊断文化功能障碍并决定进行哪些战斗。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;在不推卸责任的情况下缓解风险的魔力&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有一种风险技术需要 60 分钟，无需任何成本，并且可以解决其他规划方法所忽略的问题。它已经经过了近二十年的现场测试。使用它的团队在仍有时间采取行动时发现了灾难性问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why the MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK Framework Actually Works】为什么 MITRE ATT&amp;CK 框架确实有效</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-the-mitre-attampck-framework-actually-works</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The alert goes off at 2:17 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;You count yourself lucky that this one’s in the afternoon, not morning. You drop what you’re doing, open the console, and start digging in.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;警报于下午 2:17 响起&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;你很幸运，这是在下午，而不是早上。您放下手头的事情，打开控制台，然后开始深入研究。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Multimodal Agents with Google ADK — Practical Insights from My Implementation Journey】使用 Google ADK 构建多模式代理 - 来自我的实施之旅的实用见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-multimodal-agents-google-adk</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:115%;font-size:16px;font-family:&amp;quot;Calibri&amp;quot;,sans-serif;&#34;&gt;The landscape of AI agents is rapidly evolving, moving far beyond the early days of simple language models and retrieval-augmented generation (RAG). The diagram below depicts the evolution in the last two years:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;fr-inner&#34; contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div style=&#34;margin-left: 280px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;AI Agents Evolution&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:115%;font-size:16px;font-family:&#34;Calibri&#34;,sans-serif;&#34;&gt;AI 代理的前景正在迅速发展，远远超出了早期的简单语言模型和检索增强生成 (RAG)。下图描绘了过去两年的演变：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;fr-inner&#34; contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div style=&#34;margin-left: 280px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;人工智能代理的演变&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图标题&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>