<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【A Framework for Securing Open-Source Observability at the Edge】确保边缘开源可观察性的框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-open-source-observability-edge</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Edge Observability Security Challenge&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134245417&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:240}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Deploying an open-source observability solution to distributed retail edge locations creates a fundamental security challenge. With thousands of locations processing sensitive data like payments and customers&#39; p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;ersonally identifiable information (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;PII), every telemetry component running on the edge becomes a potential&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;entry point for&amp;nbsp;attackers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;. Edge environments operate in spaces where there is limited physical security, bandwidth constraints shared with business-critical application traffic, and no technical staff on-site for incident response.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Therefore, traditional centralized monitoring security models do not fit in these conditions because they require abundant resources, dedicated security teams, and controlled physical environments. None of them exists on the edge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559685&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:240}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;边缘可观测性安全挑战&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;134233117&#34;：假，&#34;134233118&#34;：假，&#34;134245417&#34;：假，&#34;2 01341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559738&#34;:0,&#34;335559739&#34;:160,&#34;335559740&#34;:240}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;将开源可观测性解决方案部署到分布式零售边缘站点会带来根本性的安全挑战。由于数千个地点处理付款和客户个人信息等敏感数据&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;个人身份信息 (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;PII)，每个在边缘运行的遥测组件都成为潜在的入口点&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;对于攻击者&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;。边缘环境在物理安全有限、与关键业务应用程序流量共享的带宽限制以及没有现场技术人员进行事件响应的空间中运行。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;因此，传统的集中监控安全模型不适合这些条件，因为它们需要丰富的资源、专门的安全团队和受控的物理环境。它们都不存在于边缘。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;134233117&#34;:false,&#34;134233118&#34;:false,&#34;201341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559685&#34;:0,&#34;335559738&#34;:0,&#34;335559739&#34;:0,&#34;335559740&#34;:240}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Series (3/4): Toward a Shared Language Between Humans and Machines —Quantum Language and the Limits of Simulation】系列（3/4）：迈向人机共享语言——量子语言与模拟的极限</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-language-and-limits-of-simulation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Imagine compressing thousands of dimensions of meaning into a few qubits capable of processing all that information in parallel. That is the promise of Quantum Natural Language Processing. But can we truly translate the richness of human language into the abstract logic of quantum mechanics, without any grounding in reality? This article explores that frontier where science fiction and fundamental research meet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Research in this field experiments with translations by leveraging quantum parallelism and entanglement. In other words, it uses the unique properties of qubits to process multiple meanings simultaneously and to establish connections between them.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;想象一下将数千个维度的意义压缩到几个能够并行处理所有信息的量子位中。这就是量子自然语言处理的承诺。但我们真的能在没有任何现实基础的情况下，将人类语言的丰富性转化为量子力学的抽象逻辑吗？本文探讨了科幻小说和基础研究相遇的前沿。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;该领域的研究利用量子并行性和纠缠进行翻译实验。换句话说，它利用量子位的独特属性来同时处理多种含义并在它们之间建立联系。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamlining Real-Time Ad Tech Systems: Techniques to Prevent Performance Bottlenecks】简化实时广告技术系统：防止性能瓶颈的技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/streamlining-real-time-ad-tech-systems-techniques</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Ad tech platforms operate at the bleeding edge of scale. Every millisecond counts as billions of requests flow through auctions, targeting services, and delivery pipelines. With net margins slim—most revenue is passed on to publishers — every CPU cycle saved can translate directly into profit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Optimizing these systems is not simply about shaving latency; it is about building architectures that remain efficient as workloads multiply and business pressures intensify. Minor inefficiencies, invisible in isolation, compound into significant overhead when magnified across thousands of servers. In a domain where revenue depends on speed and precision, the difference between sustainable growth and runaway costs often comes down to how carefully systems are engineered at the micro-level.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;广告技术平台处于规模前沿。每一毫秒都意味着数十亿个请求流经拍卖、定位服务和交付管道。由于净利润微薄（大部分收入都转嫁给了发行商），节省的每个 CPU 周期都可以直接转化为利润。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;优化这些系统不仅仅是为了缩短延迟；还在于减少延迟。它涉及构建在工作负载倍增和业务压力加剧时保持高效的架构。微小的效率低下，单独来看是不可见的，当在数千台服务器上放大时，就会产生巨大的开销。在收入取决于速度和精度的领域中，可持续增长和失控成本之间的差异通常取决于微观层面上系统设计的精心程度。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Developer’s Experience of Onboarding to a Platform】开发人员加入平台的经历</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/developer-onboarding-to-platform</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;After years of managing cloud services in a traditional setting — manually provisioning clusters, setting up networks, managing credentials, and navigating deployment scripts — I thought I had mastered the rhythm of delivery. Dashboards, support tickets, and carefully planned change windows were the most important things in my life. It was safe, predictable, and well-organized, but it was also slow, tiring, and full of dependencies that only worked after a lot of planning and careful changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Then came the shift.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;经过多年在传统环境中管理云服务（手动配置集群、设置网络、管理凭据和导航部署脚本），我认为我已经掌握了交付节奏。仪表板、支持票证和精心计划的变更窗口是我一生中最重要的事情。它是安全的、可预测的、组织良好的，但它也很慢、很累，而且充满了依赖性，只有在大量的计划和仔细的改变之后才能发挥作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;然后是转变。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Zero-Downtime Upgrades in an Enterprise SaaS Application】在企业 SaaS 应用程序中实施零停机升级</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ero-downtime-upgrades-in-enterprise-saas-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Ensuring your enterprise SaaS application remains always available is more than just a technical objective; it’s a fundamental business requirement. Even short periods of downtime, such as those during routine software updates, can disrupt customers’ operations, erode their trust, and lead to contractual penalties if service-level agreements aren’t met. SaaS applications serve users across multiple time zones. Scheduling downtime that accommodates all users is impractical, making zero-downtime upgrades essential for global businesses. Zero-downtime processes allow for quicker deployment of features, bug fixes, and security patches, supporting agile development and reducing time-to-market.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mastering zero-downtime upgrade procedures, in tandem with robust multi-cloud and multi-region architectures, is essential in maintaining service availability. Recent high-profile outages on major cloud platforms have underscored the disruptive impact of unexpected downtime, affecting organizations worldwide across industries. By distributing workloads across multiple cloud providers and hosting applications in multiple geographic regions, organizations can reduce single points of failure and improve resilience against large-scale outages. If one cloud provider or region experiences issues, traffic can be quickly rerouted to healthy environments, minimizing the impact on end users.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;确保您的企业 SaaS 应用程序始终可用不仅仅是一个技术目标；这是一项基本的业务需求。即使是很短的停机时间（例如例行软件更新期间的停机时间）也可能会扰乱客户的运营，削弱他们的信任，并在未满足服务级别协议的情况下导致合同处罚。 SaaS 应用程序为跨多个时区的用户提供服务。安排适合所有用户的停机时间是不切实际的，因此零停机升级对于全球企业至关重要。零停机流程可以更快地部署功能、错误修复和安全补丁，支持敏捷开发并缩短上市时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;掌握零停机升级程序，与强大的多云和多区域架构相结合，对于维持服务可用性至关重要。最近主要云平台上发生的备受瞩目的中断凸显了意外停机的破坏性影响，影响着全球各行业的组织。通过在多个云提供商之间分配工作负载并在多个地理区域托管应用程序，组织可以减少单点故障并提高针对大规模中断的恢复能力。如果一个云提供商或区域遇到问题，流量可以快速重新路由到健康的环境，从而最大限度地减少对最终用户的影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Lessons Learned From Running Disaster Recovery Drills】从灾难恢复演习中汲取的经验教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/lessons-learned-from-disaster-recovery-drills</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Disaster recovery (DR) is not just about backing up data — it’s also about ensuring that when the unexpected issue strikes, systems, people, and processes can recover quickly and efficiently. While planning and documentation are essential, the true test of a DR strategy comes from running drills.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Through multiple exercises across organizations, here are the critical learnings that can significantly improve the effectiveness of DR initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;灾难恢复 (DR) 不仅仅是备份数据，还在于确保当意外问题发生时，系统、人员和流程能够快速有效地恢复。虽然规划和记录很重要，但灾难恢复策略的真正测试来自于演练。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;通过跨组织的多次练习，以下是可以显着提高灾难恢复计划有效性的重要经验教训。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Deployable Architecture: The Cornerstone of Scalable Platform Engineering】可部署架构：可扩展平台工程的基石</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deployable-architecture-scalable-platform-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As architects, you’ve likely seen the same story unfold across growing organizations: teams move fast, each solving problems in their own way — building pipelines, wiring infrastructure, and embedding security into their services from scratch. Initially, it works. But as the organization scales, the cracks begin to show.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;750&#34; data-start=&#34;553&#34;&gt;Environments drift. Deployments become brittle. Governance becomes reactive. And suddenly, the well-intentioned architecture you’ve crafted becomes challenging to replicate, secure, or evolve consistently across teams.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为架构师，您可能会在不断发展的组织中看到同样的故事：团队快速行动，每个团队都以自己的方式解决问题 - 构建管道、布线基础设施，以及从头开始将安全性嵌入到他们的服务中。最初，它有效。但随着组织规模的扩大，裂缝开始显现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;750&#34; data-start=&#34;553&#34;&gt;环境漂移。部署变得脆弱。治理变得被动。突然之间，您精心设计的良好架构变得难以在团队之间复制、保护或持续发展。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Modern Developers Use AI-Assisted Coding to Validate Products Faster】现代开发人员如何使用人工智能辅助编码更快地验证产品</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-assisted-coding-validate-products-faster</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Software development has changed a lot in the past two years. I&#39;ve been working with AI coding assistants since they first appeared. The most interesting part? It&#39;s not just about writing code faster. AI has changed how we validate our products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My co-founder and I noticed something strange on our latest project. Our team was shipping features super fast. But we also had more edge cases and security issues. This is the new reality. You move faster, but things get more complex. Most teams using AI tools face this.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;过去两年软件开发发生了很大变化。自从人工智能编码助手首次出现以来，我就一直在使用它们。最有趣的部分？这不仅仅是为了更快地编写代码。人工智能改变了我们验证产品的方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我和我的联合创始人注意到我们最新的项目有些奇怪。我们的团队以超快的速度交付功能。但我们也遇到了更多的边缘情况和安全问题。这就是新的现实。你行动得更快，但事情变得更复杂。大多数使用人工智能工具的团队都会面临这个问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【An Open-Source ChatGPT App Generator】开源 ChatGPT 应用程序生成器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/open-source-chatgpt-app-generator</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;OpenAI released &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/introducing-apps-in-chatgpt/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ChatGPT apps&lt;/a&gt; just a couple of days ago. Such apps are incredibly interesting from a UX perspective, because sometimes a chat user interface simply won&#39;t cut it. Sometimes, you simply need a graphical user interface. For such cases, there are &lt;em&gt;&#34;ChatGPT apps.&#34;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, what is a ChatGPT app? Well, it&#39;s a fully functional user interface with buttons, dropdown lists, checkboxes, and everything you can create on the web. It can be as complex as Google Maps or as simple as a collect email form. It is basically &lt;em&gt;&#34;an app&#34;&lt;/em&gt; hosted inside your &lt;a href=&#34;https://ainiro.io/ai-chatbots&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AI chatbot&lt;/a&gt;. You can try a simple such app by clicking &lt;a href=&#34;https://ainiro.io/blog/open-source-chatgpt-app-generator#&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;OpenAI 几天前发布了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://openai.com/index/introducing-apps-in-chatgpt/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ChatGPT 应用&lt;/a&gt;。从用户体验的角度来看，此类应用程序非常有趣，因为有时聊天用户界面根本无法解决问题。有时，您只需要一个图形用户界面。对于这种情况，有“ChatGPT 应用程序”。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那么，什么是 ChatGPT 应用程序？嗯，它是一个功能齐全的用户界面，带有按钮、下拉列表、复选框以及您可以在网络上创建的所有内容。它可以像 Google 地图一样复杂，也可以像收集电子邮件表单一样简单。它基本上是托管在您的&lt;a href=&#34;https://ainiro.io/ai-chatbots&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AI 聊天机器人&lt;/a&gt;内的&lt;em&gt;“应用程序”&lt;/em&gt;。您可以点击&lt;a href=&#34;https://ainiro.io/blog/open-source-chatgpt-app-generator#&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;尝试一个简单的此类应用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When Coalesce Is Slower Than Repartition: A Spark Performance Paradox】当合并慢于重新分区时：Spark 性能悖论</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spark-coalesce-vs-repartition-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;ve worked with Apache Spark, you&#39;ve probably heard the conventional wisdom: &#34;Use &lt;code&gt;coalesce()&lt;/code&gt; instead of &lt;code&gt;repartition()&lt;/code&gt; when reducing partitions — it&#39;s faster because it avoids a shuffle.&#34; This advice appears in documentation, blog posts, and is repeated across Stack Overflow threads. But what if I told you this isn&#39;t always true?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a recent production workload, I discovered that using &lt;code&gt;repartition()&lt;/code&gt; instead of &lt;code&gt;coalesce()&lt;/code&gt; resulted in a &lt;strong&gt;33% performance improvement&lt;/strong&gt; (16 minutes vs. 23 minutes) when writing data to fewer partitions. This counterintuitive result reveals an important lesson about Spark&#39;s Catalyst optimizer that every Spark developer should understand.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您使用过 Apache Spark，您可能听说过这样的传统观点：“减少分区时使用 &lt;code&gt;coalesce()&lt;/code&gt; 而不是 &lt;code&gt;repartition()&lt;/code&gt; — 它更快，因为它避免了洗牌。”此建议出现在文档、博客文章中，并且在 Stack Overflow 线程中重复出现。但如果我告诉你这并不总是正确的呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在最近的生产工作负载中，我发现在将数据写入较少的分区时，使用 &lt;code&gt;repartition()&lt;/code&gt; 而不是 &lt;code&gt;coalesce()&lt;/code&gt; 可以实现&lt;strong&gt;33% 的性能提升&lt;/strong&gt;（分别为 16 分钟和 23 分钟）。这个违反直觉的结果揭示了每个 Spark 开发人员都应该了解的有关 Spark Catalyst 优化器的重要教训。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>