<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Your First AI Model in Python: A Beginner&#39;s Guide (1 of 3)】在Python中构建您的第一个AI模型：初学者指南（第3个）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-ai-model-python-beginner</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-in-2024-year-in-review-and-predictions-for-2025&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt; (AI) brings fundamental changes to healthcare, finance, manufacturing and customer service through automatic information processing and data-driven insights that lead to smarter business decisions. Artificial learning systems and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/explainability-of-machine-learning-models-increasi&#34;&gt;machine learning models&lt;/a&gt; power this shift, identifying patterns and large datasets even without direct human intervention.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In order to enhance AI models and optimize solutions, it is important to grasp the fundamentals of AI model development and have a basic understanding of pre-trained AI models. Hands-on experience in building AI systems allows professionals and aspiring AI developers like you to refine your skills, enabling you to customize models based on specific needs or requirements, solve problems more efficiently and achieve better model performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-in-in-2024-年 -  in-review-and-predictions-for-2025”&gt;人工智能&lt;/a&gt;（ai）通过自动处理，通过自动进行信息处理和数据处理，将基本变化带入医疗保健，金融，制造和客户服务的基本变化。人工学习系统和&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/explainability-of-machine-learning-models-increasi”&gt;机器学习模型&lt;/a&gt;即使没有直接人类干预，也可以识别这种转变，识别模式和大型数据集。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;为了增强AI模型并优化解决方案，重要的是要掌握AI模型开发的基本原理并对预训练的AI模型有基本的理解。实践AI系统方面的动手经验使专业人士和有抱负的AI开发人员能够完善自己的技能，使您能够根据特定需求或需求自定义模型，更有效地解决问题并实现更好的模型性能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Fluent Bit: Installing and Configuring Fluent Bit Using Container Images (Part 2)】掌握流利位：使用容器图像安装和配置流利位（第2部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/install-fluent-bit-from-source-part-two</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This series is a general-purpose getting-started guide for those of us wanting to learn about the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) project Fluent Bit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each article in this series addresses a single topic by providing insights into &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; the topic is, &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; we are interested in exploring that topic, &lt;em&gt;where&lt;/em&gt; to get started with the topic, and &lt;em&gt;how&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;to get hands-on with learning about the topic as it relates to the Fluent Bit project.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本系列是我们想要了解Cloud Native Computing Foundation（CNCF）项目Fluent Fluent Pluent Pluent lit的通用指南。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本系列中的每篇文章都通过向&lt;em&gt;提供洞察力来解决一个主题。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python curses, Part 3: Working With Windowed Content】Python诅咒，第3部分：使用窗户内容</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-curses-windowed-content</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Welcome back to the third — and final — installment in our series on how to work with the &lt;code&gt;curses&lt;/code&gt; library in Python to draw with text. If you missed the first two parts of this programming tutorial series — or if you wish to reference the code contained within them — you can read them here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-curses-drawing-text&#34;&gt;Python curses, Part 1: Drawing With Text&lt;/a&gt;&#34;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-curses-library-example&#34;&gt;Python curses, Part 2: How to Create a Python curses-Enabled Application&lt;/a&gt;&#34;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once reviewed, let’s move on to the next portion: how to decorate windows with borders and boxes using Python’s &lt;code&gt;curses&lt;/code&gt; module.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;欢迎回到我们的系列中的第三部分，也是最后的分期付款，介绍了如何使用python中的&lt;code&gt;诅咒&lt;/code&gt;库绘制文本。如果您错过了本编程教程系列的前两个部分（或者您想引用其中包含的代码），则可以在此处阅读：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“ &lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/python-curses-drawing-text&#39;&gt; Python诅咒，第1部分：用文本绘制&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“ &lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/python-curses-library-example“&gt; python诅咒，第2部分：如何创建一个python cursses-nabled应用程序&lt;/a&gt;”&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦进行了评论，让我们继续下一个部分：如何使用Python的&lt;code&gt; curses &lt;/code&gt;模块来装饰窗口和框。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Modern Stack for Building Scalable Systems】现代建筑可扩展系统的堆栈</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/modern-stack</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In software engineering, we have a lot of tools—tens or hundreds of different tools, products, and platforms. We have SQL DBs, we have NoSQL DBs with multiple subtypes, we have queues, data streaming platforms, caches, orchestrators, cloud, cloud versions of all the previous. We have enough ....&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, I want to describe a “basic” modern stack that will allow you to build robust and scalable systems. They are language agnostic and can be easily integrated into most of the modern day programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在软件工程中，我们有很多工具 - 六个或数百种不同的工具，产品和平台。我们有SQL DBS，具有带有多个子类型的NOSQL DB，我们有队列，数据流平台，Caches，Orchestrators，Cloud，云，云版本。我们有够了.... &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我想描述一个“基本”现代堆栈，该堆栈将使您能够构建强大而可扩展的系统。它们是语言不可知论的，可以轻松地集成到现代的大多数编程语言中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 12:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Failure Handling Mechanisms in Microservices and Their Importance】微服务中的故障处理机制及其重要性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/failure-handling-mechanisms-in-microservices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;5e4d&#34;&gt;Microservices architecture has gained significant popularity due to its scalability, flexibility, and modular nature. However, with multiple independent services communicating over a network, failures are inevitable. A robust failure-handling strategy is crucial to ensure reliability, resilience, and a seamless user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;8699&#34;&gt;In this article, we will explore different failure-handling mechanisms in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-real-world-guide-to-event-driven-microservices&#34;&gt;microservices&lt;/a&gt; and understand their importance in building resilient applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name =“ 5E4D”&gt;微服务体系结构由于其可扩展性，灵活性和模块化性质而获得了很大的普及。但是，随着通过网络通过多个独立服务进行通信，失败是不可避免的。强大的故障处理策略对于确保可靠性，弹性和无缝用户体验至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name =“ 8699”&gt;在本文中，我们将探索&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-real-world-guide-to-guide-to-vent-to-vent-microservices”&gt; microservices中的不同故障处理机制。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Documentation Matters More Than You Think】为什么文档比您想象的重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-documentation-matters-more-than-you-think</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Software engineers love to ship. There’s something exhilarating about writing code, pushing it to production, and watching it solve real-world problems. But in the rush to build, we often overlook one of the most powerful tools in our engineering toolbox: &lt;strong&gt;documentation&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Documentation isn’t just about writing things down. It’s about building a system that others can understand, improve, and trust — even when the original developers have moved on. And when documentation is missing or poorly maintained, the consequences can be devastating.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;软件工程师喜欢发货。写代码，将其推向生产以及观看它解决了现实世界中的问题，这是令人振奋的。但是，在急于建造的过程中，我们经常忽略工程工具箱中最强大的工具之一：&lt;strong&gt;文档&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;文档不仅仅是写下来。这是关于建立其他人可以理解，改进和信任的系统 - 即使原始开发人员继续前进。当缺少文档或维护不佳时，后果可能是毁灭性的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Concept to Cloud: Building With Cursor and the Heroku MCP Server】从概念到云：使用光标和Heroku MCP服务器构建</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-with-cursor-heroku-mcp-server</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I’ve been experimenting with Cursor as a development tool, and it’s been surprisingly helpful in my day-to-day workflow. It’s not just that it writes code — it understands context, offers suggestions in the right moments, and even anticipates what I’m about to do next.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I saw the &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heroku.com/introducing-official-heroku-mcp-server&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;announcement&lt;/a&gt; about the Heroku MCP Server, I got curious. &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Could I use &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cursor.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cursor&lt;/a&gt; to go beyond just writing code, and actually build and deploy an app to Heroku, primarily via chat prompts and responses?&lt;/span&gt; I decided to try it out.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我一直在将光标作为开发工具进行实验，这对我的日常工作流程非常有帮助。它不仅是编写代码 - 它可以理解上下文，在正确的时刻提供建议，甚至预期我接下来要做的事情。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我看到&lt;a href =“ https://blog.heroku.com/introducing-fincial-heroku-mcp-server” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;公告&lt;/a&gt;关于heroku mcp服务器的宣布，我很刺激。 &lt;span style =“边距：0px; padding：0px;“&gt;我可以使用&lt;a href =“ https：//www.cursor.com/” target =“ _ black”&gt;游标&lt;/a&gt;超越仅仅编写代码，并且实际上是通过聊天和响应来构建和部署一个应用程序，主要是通过聊天和响应来构建和部署应用程序？</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Role of AI in Enhancing DevOps Processes】AI在增强DevOps流程中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-enhancing-devops-processes</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;An Introduction to DevOps and AI Integration&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DevOps is this awesome mix of teamwork and tech that’s all about getting software developers and IT operations on the same page. It’s less about silos and more about chatting openly, working together, and using automation to pump out top-notch software faster than ever. In today’s wild, fast-moving digital world, DevOps is your ticket to staying ahead, cranking out products quicker, and always tweaking them to be better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But here’s the thing: as software delivery gets fancier with microservices, cloud setups, and slick CI/CD pipelines, DevOps teams are stuck wrestling with mountains of data, crazy-complex systems, and stuff that needs to happen right now. That’s where artificial intelligence (AI) swoops in like a superhero sidekick. With AI in the mix, teams can ditch the repetitive grunt work, spot trouble brewing before it hits, and keep everything flowing smoothly. The payoff? Software drops faster and works like a dream.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; DevOps和AI集成简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; devOps是团队合作和技术的绝妙组合，它旨在在同一页面上获得软件开发人员和IT操作。这与孤岛无关，而是公开聊天，一起工作，并使用自动化比以往任何时候都更快地抽出一流的软件。在当今狂野的，快速发展的数字世界中，DevOps是您保持领先地，更快地启动产品并始终调整产品以使其更好的票。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但这是事实：随着软件交付的微服务，云设置和光滑的CI/CD管道变得更加典型，DevOps团队陷入了摔跤，这些数据，疯狂的复杂系统以及现在需要发生的事情。那就是人工智能（AI）像超级英雄搭档一样摇摆的地方。随着AI的混合，团队可以抛弃重复的咕unt声，在击球之前酿造麻烦，并保持一切顺利。收益？软件掉落得更快，工作就像梦一样。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Model Evaluation: Metrics, Visualization and Performance (2 of 3)】AI模型评估：指标，可视化和性能（第2个，共3）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-evaluation-metrics-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;An Artificial Intelligence (AI) model, despite going through constant and rigorous training, may not function as intended. It is important to observe strict and continuous evaluations to measure its accuracy and reliability in real-world applications. Assessing key metrics such as precision, recall, and F1-score allows the AI model to apply its learned patterns across different datasets successfully. Without sufficient evaluation, even advanced AI models may not reach their full potential.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The effectiveness of an AI model is evaluated through a combination of measurement techniques, visual representation, and analysis of failures. These include the following:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;一个人工智能（AI）模型，尽管经过了持续而严格的训练，但可能无法按预期运行。重要的是要观察严格持续的评估，以衡量其在现实世界应用中的准确性和可靠性。评估诸如精确度，召回和F1得分之类的关键指标允许AI模型成功地在不同的数据集中应用其学习模式。没有足够的评估，即使是先进的AI模型也可能无法发挥其全部潜力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;通过测量技术，视觉表示和故障分析的结合来评估AI模型的有效性。其中包括以下内容：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build Local LLM RAG Apps With Ollama, DeepSeek-R1, and SingleStore】如何使用Ollama，DeepSeek-R1和Singlestore构建本地LLM RAG应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/local-llm-rag-apps-ollama-deepseek-r1-singlestore</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@VeryFatBoy/quick-tip-how-to-build-local-llm-apps-with-ollama-deepseek-r1-and-singlestore-34252b86d52f&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;previous article&lt;/a&gt;, we explored how to use Ollama and DeepSeek-R1 with SingleStore for a simple example. In this article, we&#39;ll build on that example by working with a PDF document from the internet. We&#39;ll store the document and its vector embeddings in SingleStore, then use DeepSeek-R1 to identify blockchain investment opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The notebook file used in this article is available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/ollama-deepseek-demo/blob/main/ollama_langchain_deepseek_rag_demo.ipynb&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;a a href =“ https://medium.com/@veryfatboy/quick-tip-tho-t-how-to-to-build-local-local-local-local-local-llm-apps-with-olama-deepseek-deepseek-r1-r1-r1- and-sing一下---34252b86d52f52f52f e DeepSeek-r1与单闸有关。在本文中，我们将通过与Internet中的PDF文档合作来基于该示例。我们将将该文档及其矢量嵌入在单闸中存储，然后使用DeepSeek-R1确定区块链投资机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文中使用的笔记本文件可在&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/veryfatboy/veryfatboy/ollama-deepseek-demo/blob/main/main/main/main/main/main/main/olama_langchain_deepseek_rag_rag_rag_rag_demo.ipynb”中</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>