<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【The End of “Good Enough Agile”】“足够敏捷”的结尾</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-end-of-good-enough-agile</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: The End of “Good Enough Agile”&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Good Enough Agile” is ending as AI automates mere ceremonial tasks and Product Operating Models demand outcome-focused teams. Agile professionals must evolve from process facilitators to strategic product thinkers or risk obsolescence as organizations adopt AI-native approaches that embody Agile values without ritual overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Perfect Storm Coming After Good Enough Agile&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For two decades, many of us have participated in, or at least witnessed, a prolonged performance of “Agile-as-theater.” Now, the curtain is falling. Mechanical Scrum, stand-ups — or Daily Scrum, if you prefer that term — without tangible purpose, estimation rituals that pretend to forecast the future, Jira-as-performance-art; we’ve normalized &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-guide-to-agile-methodologies-and-their&#34;&gt;Agile&lt;/a&gt; as a checklist. Useful, perhaps, if you blinked hard enough and never dared ask about the return on investment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; TL; DR：“足够敏捷”的结尾&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“足够好的敏捷”即将结束，随着AI自动化的仪式任务和产品操作模型需要以结果为中心的团队。敏捷的专业人员必须从过程促进者到战略产品思想家或风险过时演变，因为组织采用了敏捷的方法，这些方法体现了没有仪式开销的敏捷价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;在足够好敏捷之后出现的完美风暴&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;二十年来，我们中的许多人参加了或至少见证了“敏捷剧院”的长期表现。现在，窗帘落下了。机械混乱，站立式的 - 或每天的混乱，如果您喜欢这个术语，则没有明显的目的，假装预测未来的估计仪式，jira-as as performance-art；我们已经将&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-guide-to-methodologies-and-their”&gt;敏捷&lt;/a&gt;作为清单。也许有用，如果您眨眨眼，从不敢于询问投资回报率。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging Natural Language Processing for Enhancing Sales Chatbots】利用自然语言处理来增强销售聊天机器人</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/leverage-natural-language-processing-for-sales-chatbots</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With natural language processing (NLP) capabilities, sales representatives can drive engagement, personalize interactions and boost sales conversions. How can developers incorporate these techniques into their sales chatbots?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;How Developers Can Use NLP to Improve Sales Chatbots&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Many sales departments use artificial intelligence chatbots. According to McKinsey &amp;amp; Company, sales is the most common application of generative technology, with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/quantumblack/our-insights/the-state-of-ai&#34;&gt;around 34% of respondents&lt;/a&gt; stating they regularly use it for this function.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;具有自然语言处理（NLP）功能，销售代表可以推动参与度，个性化互动并促进销售转换。开发人员如何将这些技术纳入其销售聊天机器人？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;开发人员如何使用NLP改善销售聊天机器人&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;许多销售部门都使用人工智能聊天机器人。根据McKinsey＆Company的说法，销售是生成技术的最常见应用，&lt;a href =“ https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/capabilities/quantumblack/quantumblack/quantumblack/our-intights/the-state/the-state-of-ai-&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advancing Robot Vision and Control】推进机器人视觉和控制</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/robotic-hand-eye-coordination-fusion</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction: Enhancing Robotic Capabilities&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good hand-eye coordination is essential for robotic systems, most notably in the context of engaging with objects in tasks that involve reaching, manipulation, and/or pick-and-place tasks. This paper reviews approaches utilizing visual servoing and deep reinforcement learning (RL) to improve control of robots with a comparison of the two approaches and suggests a hybrid method for optimal control performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem Statement and Significance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Robotic tasks often involve coordination of visual perception with motion of the robot. Classic methods that rely on visual servoing can achieve good accuracy with limited training data, while methods based on reinforcement learning can generalize globally but require a large amount of training data. There is a possible synergy to bring together the best of both worlds—a hybrid approach that avoids the problems of each method and yields good accuracy, robustness, and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt;简介：增强机器人功能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;良好的手眼协调对于机器人系统至关重要，最著名的是，在涉及到达到，操纵和/或挑选任务的任务中的对象中。本文审查了利用视觉致毒和深度加固学习（RL）的方法来改善对机器人的控制，并比较两种方法，并提出了一种用于最佳控制性能的混合方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;问题陈述和意义&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;机器人任务通常涉及与机器人运动的视觉感知协调。依靠视觉陶器的经典方法可以通过有限的培训数据实现良好的准确性，而基于强化学习的方法可以在全球范围内概括，但需要大量的培训数据。有一种协同作用可以使两全其美的最好的方法融合在一起 - 这种混合方法避免了每种方法的问题并产生良好的准确性，鲁棒性和效率。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Navigating and Modernizing Legacy Codebases: A Developer&#39;s Guide to AI-Assisted Code Understanding】导航和现代化遗产代码库：AI辅助代码理解的开发指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/modernizing-legacy-codebases-ai-assisted-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Legacy codebases present unique challenges for modern development teams. Whether you&#39;re dealing with a decade-old monolithic application or attempting to modernize an e-commerce platform, the complexity of understanding and updating &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-make-legacy-code-more-testable&#34;&gt;legacy code&lt;/a&gt; can significantly impact development velocity. This article provides practical strategies and technical approaches for effectively navigating, understanding, and modernizing legacy systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the Legacy Code Challenge&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Modern development teams frequently encounter several critical challenges when working with legacy systems. As Scott Dietzen, CEO of Augment Code notes in a written Q&amp;amp;A I conducted with him, &#34;Reality is typically tens to hundreds of engineers collaborating to modify code spread across thousands of files built on numerous dependencies. Understanding contextual knowledge in your software—your APIs, how it&#39;s built, your policies and best practices, and where functionality is implemented—is crucial for effective modernization.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;传统代码库为现代开发团队带来了独特的挑战。无论您是处理一个十年历史的单片应用程序还是试图现代化电子商务平台，理解和更新的复杂性&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-make-make-legacy-code-code-more-testable-- legacy代码”&gt;旧代码&lt;/a&gt;可能会对开发速度产生重大影响。本文提供了有效导航，理解和现代化遗产系统的实用策略和技术方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;了解旧代码挑战&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;现代开发团队在使用旧系统时经常遇到一些关键挑战。 As Scott Dietzen, CEO of Augment Code notes in a written Q&amp;A I conducted with him, &#34;Reality is typically tens to hundreds of engineers collaborating to modify code spread across thousands of files built on numerous dependencies. Understanding contextual knowledge in your software—your APIs, how it&#39;s built, your policies and best practices, and where functionality is implemented—is crucial for effective modernization.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Supervised Fine-Tuning (SFT) on VLMs: From Pre-trained Checkpoints To Tuned Models】VLMS上有监督的微调（SFT）：从预先训练的检查点到调谐模型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/supervised-fine-tuning-sft-on-vlms</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Vision-Language Models (VLMs) like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/leveraging-generative-ai-for-video-creation-a-deep&#34;&gt;LLaMA&lt;/a&gt; are becoming increasingly powerful at understanding and generating text grounded in visual content. They excel at tasks like image captioning, visual question answering (VQA), and multimodal reasoning—making them highly useful in a wide range of real-world applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But while these models perform impressively out of the box, domain-specific or task-specific use cases often demand additional tuning. This is where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-developing-llms-pretraining&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supervised Fine-Tuning (SFT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; comes in. By fine-tuning a pre-trained VLM on curated image–question–answer (QA) pairs, we can significantly improve its performance for specific applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;视觉 - 语言模型（VLMS），例如&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/leveraging-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generation-for-videio-creation-a-deep-”&gt; llama&gt; llama &lt;/a&gt;在理解和生成的文本中，越来越强大。他们在图像字幕，视觉询问（VQA）和多模式推理等任务中表现出色 - 使它们在各种现实世界中都非常有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，尽管这些模型的表现令人印象深刻，但特定于域或特定于任务的用例通常需要额外调整。这就是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-developing-llms-proterain”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;有监督的微调（sft）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。通过对预先训练的vlm进行精细的vlm on Cretated Image-QueStion – QueStion – QueStion – Qa/pairs perswor，我们可以在pection-prippation-pecripation-pecripation-pecription -queStion – queStion-qa inswer（qa）中进行了显着改进。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Evolution of Scalable and Resilient Container Infrastructure】可扩展和弹性容器基础架构的演变</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-birth-of-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes has taken over the world by storm. You could unconditionally say that it has won the container war. Docker has similar offering with Docker Swarm but &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; offers a lot more in the form of resiliency, scale, ecosystem and production readiness.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, what does Kubernetes solve? And why does its demand grow drastically? In order to understand this we need to go back in history.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;库伯尼特（Kubernetes）席卷了世界。您可以无条件地说它赢得了集装箱战争。 Docker与Docker Swarm有类似的产品，但&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refting-started-kubernetes”&gt; kubernetes &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;提供了更多的形式，以弹性，规模，生态系统和生产准备。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那么，Kubernetes解决了什么？为什么它的需求会大幅增长？为了理解这一点，我们需要回到历史上。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding the Shift: Why Companies Are Migrating From MongoDB to Aerospike Database?】了解转变：为什么公司从MongoDB迁移到Aerospike数据库？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-the-shift-why-companies-are-migratin</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As businesses evolve, their database needs to become more sophisticated, demanding higher performance, scalability, and cost-efficiency. While &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/mongodb&#34;&gt;MongoDB&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;has been a cornerstone in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-nosql-and-data&#34;&gt;NoSQL database&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;ecosystem, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-reference-architecture-for-a-demand-sid&#34;&gt;Aerospike&lt;/a&gt; is emerging as a preferred alternative for organizations with specific high-performance and real-time use cases. This article dives into the technical reasons driving this shift and examines why Aerospike is gaining traction as the database of choice for modern enterprises.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Architecture Differences&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MongoDB&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MongoDB is a document-oriented NoSQL database that stores data in BSON (Binary JSON) format. It relies heavily on a primary-secondary replication model for high availability and uses memory-mapped files for storage. While this architecture works well for general-purpose workloads, it can struggle with scaling and performance under heavy transactional loads or real-time data requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着企业的发展，其数据库需要变得更加复杂，要求更高的性能，可扩展性和成本效益。而&lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/refcardz/mongodb“&gt; mongodb &lt;/a&gt;一直是&lt;a a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-nosql-and-data&gt; nosql-and-data”&gt; nosql database &lt;/database &lt;/refcardz&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-reference-architecture-for-a-demand-sid”&gt; aerospike &lt;/a&gt;正在成为具有特定高性能和实时用例的组织的首选替代方案。本文深入研究了推动这一转变的技术原因，并研究了为什么Aerospike成为现代企业首选数据库的原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;架构差异&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt; &lt;strong&gt; mongodb &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; mongoDB是一个面向文档的NOSQL数据库，可将数据存储在BSON（Binary JSON）格式中。它在很大程度上依赖于主要的大专复制模型，用于高可用性，并使用内存映射的文件进行存储。尽管该体系结构在通用工作负载方面效果很好，但在重大交易负载或实时数据要求下它可能会在缩放和性能方面遇到困难。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advancing Your Software Engineering Career in 2025】在2025年推进您的软件工程职业</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advancing-your-software-engineering-career-in-2025</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Key Industry Trends&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;You’ve probably heard of &#34;The Great Flattening.&#34; In 2024, companies like Amazon, Google, and Meta started cutting middle management to make things more efficient. As a manager, I’ve felt this shift firsthand. Suddenly, there are fewer layers, and while it’s streamlined decision-making, it’s also changed how we think about career growth. But here’s the good news: for engineers, this doesn’t directly impact our day-to-day work. We’re still building, innovating, and solving problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Then there’s GenAI. I was skeptical initially when I first heard tech leaders like Mark Zuckerberg predict that &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forbes.com/sites/quickerbettertech/2025/01/26/business-tech-news-zuckerberg-says-ai-will-replace-mid-level-engineers-soon/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AI could replace mid-level engineers by 2025&lt;/a&gt; or when &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.businessinsider.com/google-earnings-q3-2024-new-code-created-by-ai-2024-10&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Google CEO mentioned that 25% of Google’s new code is already AI-generated&lt;/a&gt; but as of now, you may have also experienced this first hand on what Gen AI coding agents can do. As per &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cio.com/article/3567138/ai-native-software-engineering-may-be-closer-than-developers-think.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;this article from CIO&lt;/a&gt;, AI coding agents will take over the world by 2027. So how do you thrive in this world and advance your career? Here is some of my advice which is equally applicable in the normal or challenging times.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;关键行业趋势&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您可能已经听说过“巨大的扁平化”。 2024年，像亚马逊，Google和Meta这样的公司开始削减中层管理，以提高事情的效率。作为一名经理，我亲身感觉到了这一转变。突然，层次较少，尽管它精简了决策，但它也改变了我们对职业增长的看法。但这是个好消息：对于工程师来说，这不会直接影响我们的日常工作。我们仍在建立，创新和解决问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;然后是Genai。最初，当我第一次听到像马克·扎克伯格（Mark Zuckerberg）这样的科技领导者预测，&lt;a href =“ https://www.forbes.com/sites/quickerbettertech/2025/2025/201/26/business-tech-news-tech-news-zuckerg-says--zays--say---------------------------------------------------------------------replace-meop---- NoreFerrer“ target =” _ black“&gt; AI可以在2025年到2025 &lt;/a&gt;或当&lt;a href =“ https：//wwwww.businessinsider.com/google-earnings-q.3-2024-q3-2024-new-new-new-code-code-code-crot-creat--by-by-by-by-ai-ai-2024-10-2024-10 rel =” noore =“ Google的新代码中有25％已经是AI生成的&lt;/a&gt;，但是到目前为止，您可能还经历了AI Gen Gen Gen Gener编码代理可以做什么的第一手。按照&lt;a href =“ https://www.cio.com/article/3567138/ai-native-native-software-eendware-eendering-may-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-be-than-developers-think.htink.html” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ target =” _ black target =“ _ black” _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _您在这个世界上蓬勃发展并促进您的职业生涯吗？这是我的一些建议，同样适用于正常或具有挑战性的时间。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing for Sustainability: The Rise of Green Software】为可持续性设计：绿色软件的兴起</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/green-software-sustainability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The software industry is one of the fastest-growing sectors in the world, with an estimated 20% annual growth rate. The rapid growth, however, incurs a substantial environmental cost. The production and operation of software systems consume vast amounts of energy, resulting in substantial greenhouse gas emissions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article provides an overview of the green software movement, including its key principles and benefits. We&#39;ll also explore some real-world examples of companies that have successfully implemented green software design principles, resulting in significant energy reductions and cost savings.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;软件行业是世界上增长最快的领域之一，估计年增长率为20％。然而，快速增长会带来巨大的环境成本。软件系统的生产和运行消耗大量能源，从而产生大量的温室气体排放。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文概述了绿色软件运动，包括其关键原则和收益。我们还将探索一些成功实施绿色软件设计原则的公司的现实示例，从而大大降低能源和节省成本。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Perfection Trap: Rethinking Parkinson&#39;s Law for Modern Engineering Teams】完美陷阱：重新思考帕金森氏派法律现代工程团队</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rethinking-parkinsons-law-modern-engineering-teams</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Great engineering leadership isn’t measured by output squeezed from teams, but by value unlocked through the right conditions. After years guiding engineering teams through challenges, I’ve come to re-evaluate some classic management principles through a modern engineering lens.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One concept I frequently encounter in discussions about productivity is &lt;strong&gt;Parkinson’s Law&lt;/strong&gt;. This seemingly simple principle has profound implications for how we lead engineering teams—but not necessarily in the way many think.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;伟大的工程领导力不是通过从团队中挤出的产出来衡量的，而是通过正确条件下释放的价值来衡量的。经过多年的指导工程团队应对挑战，我来重新评估了一些经典的管理原则。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我在讨论生产力的讨论中经常遇到的一个概念是&lt;strong&gt;帕金森定律&lt;/strong&gt;。这个看似简单的原则对我们如何领导工程团队具有深远的影响，但不一定以许多人的思维方式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>