<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Tableau Dashboard Development Best Practices】Tableau仪表板开发最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/tableau-development-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-data-visualization-techniques-for-business&#34;&gt;Tableau&lt;/a&gt; is a great tool for turning data into clear, interactive visuals. But to get the most out of it, it’s important to follow a few best practices. These help keep dashboards clean, fast, and easy to understand. Whether you&#39;re building reports for yourself or a wider team, sticking to some core development habits can save time, avoid headaches, and make your work more impactful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Data Sources and Extracts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is the main section of Tableau where you begin the configuration to pull the data from any source from this &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.tableau.com/current/pro/desktop/en-us/exampleconnections_overview.htm&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;list&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-data-visalization-techniques-for-business”&gt; Tableau &lt;/a&gt;是将数据转换为清晰，交互式视觉效果的绝佳工具。但是，为了充分利用它，遵循一些最佳实践很重要。这些有助于保持仪表板清洁，快速且易于理解。无论您是为自己建立报告还是更广泛的团队，坚持一些核心发展习惯都可以节省时间，避免头痛并使您的工作更具影响力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;数据源和提取&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是Tableau的主要部分，您可以在其中开始配置以从此&lt;a href =“</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Blockchain in Healthcare: Enhancing Data Security and Interoperability】医疗保健区块链：增强数据安全性和互操作性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/blockchain-healthcare-digital-infrastructure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt; Healthcare systems around the world are at a critical juncture, navigating the pressures of digital transformation, rising cybersecurity threats, and fragmented data landscapes. While the volume of healthcare data grows exponentially, the capacity to manage it securely and effectively across stakeholders remains limited. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-management-and-blockchain-technology&#34;&gt;Blockchain&lt;/a&gt;, a decentralized ledger technology known for transparency and immutability, is emerging as a viable framework for improving data integrity, patient control, and system interoperability&lt;strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;This whitepaper explores blockchain as a promising, decentralized solution to redefine the digital infrastructure of healthcare. This paper discusses current challenges, the mechanics of blockchain, real-world applications, and future directions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today’s digitized world, the healthcare sector is inundated with data: electronic health records (EHRs), diagnostic results, insurance claims, and wearable device outputs. Yet, this data is often siloed, poorly secured, and inaccessible to both patients and providers. A lack of interoperability leads to redundant tests, delayed diagnoses, and increased healthcare costs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt;世界各地的医疗保健系统处于关键时刻，导致数字转换的压力，网络安全威胁的上升和碎片数据景观。尽管医疗保健数据的数量呈指数增长，但在利益相关者之间可以安全有效地管理它的能力仍然有限。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/data-management-and-blockchain-technology”&gt;区块链&lt;/a&gt;是一种以透明度和不可变性而闻名的分类分类帐技术，它是一种可行的框架，可改善数据完整性，患者控制和系统互操作性，且可操作性&lt;strong &lt;强&gt;。 &lt;/strong&gt;此白皮书探索区块链是一种有希望的，分散的解决方案，以重新定义医疗保健的数字基础设施。本文讨论了当前的挑战，区块链的机制，现实世界应用以及未来的方向。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。简介&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在当今数字化的世界中，医疗保健领域被数据淹没：电子健康记录（EHR），诊断结果，保险索赔和可穿戴设备输出。然而，这些数据通常是孤立的，固定效果不佳，并且对患者和提供者都无法访问。缺乏互操作性会导致冗余测试，延迟诊断和增加医疗保健成本。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【CORS Misconfigurations: The Simple API Header That Took Down Our Frontend】CORS错误配置：删除我们前端的简单API标头</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/troubleshooting-cors-node-angular</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;837&#34; data-start=&#34;137&#34;&gt;Imagine deploying a new Angular frontend with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/debugging-a-node-js-express-api-in-vs-code-debugge&#34;&gt;Node.js/Express API backend&lt;/a&gt;, only to find that none of the API calls work once it’s live. Our team faced exactly that scenario – the app was effectively broken due to one missing HTTP response header. Everything worked fine locally, but in production, the browser console showed CORS errors because our API responses lacked the &lt;strong data-end=&#34;543&#34; data-start=&#34;512&#34;&gt;Access-Control-Allow-Origin&lt;/strong&gt; header. That one “simple” header made the difference between a fully functional app and a seemingly broken frontend. In this article, we’ll explore how a misconfigured &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-cors&#34;&gt;CORS policy&lt;/a&gt; can break an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/3-angular-app-examples-you-can-use-right-away&#34;&gt;Angular application&lt;/a&gt; and how to diagnose and fix it on the server side (with a Node/Express example).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;888&#34; data-start=&#34;839&#34;&gt;How CORS Issues Appear in Angular Applications&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1217&#34; data-start=&#34;890&#34;&gt;The Angular app on &lt;code data-end=&#34;1003&#34; data-start=&#34;980&#34;&gt;http://localhost:4200&lt;/code&gt; requests data from an API on &lt;code data-end=&#34;1056&#34; data-start=&#34;1033&#34;&gt;http://localhost:3000&lt;/code&gt;. The server responds without the required &lt;strong data-end=&#34;1130&#34; data-start=&#34;1099&#34;&gt;Access-Control-Allow-Origin&lt;/strong&gt; header, so the browser’s CORS policy blocks the Angular app from seeing the response.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 837” data-start =“ 137”&gt;想象一下用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/debugging-a-node-a-node-js-js-js-js-api--apiress-api-in--vs-code-code-code-code-code-debugge，-我们的团队正好面对这种情况 - 由于一个缺少HTTP响应标头，该应用程序实际上被打破了。一切在本地工作良好，但是在生产中，浏览器控制台显示了CORS错误，因为我们的API响应缺乏&lt;strong data-end =“ 543” data-start =“ 512”&gt; access-control-wall-allow-allow-allow-hola-holder-ofrigin &lt;/strong&gt;标头。一个“简单”的标头使功能齐全的应用程序和看似破裂的前端之间的区别。 In this article, we’ll explore how a misconfigured &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-cors&#34;&gt;CORS policy&lt;/a&gt; can break an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/3-angular-app-examples-you-can-use-right-away&#34;&gt;Angular application&lt;/a&gt; and how to diagnose and fix it on the server side （带有节点/Express示例）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end =“ 888” data-start =“ 839”&gt; CORS问题在Angular应用程序中如何出现&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1217” data-start =“ 890”&gt; &lt;code data-end =“ 1003” data-data-start =“ 980”&gt; http：// localHost：4200 &lt;/code&gt;请求来自&lt;code data-end =“ 1056” data-start =“ data-start =“ 1033”&gt; http：/http pp：3 000 &lt;/httpp pp的http：// code&gt;的角度。服务器响应而无需&lt;strong data-end =“ 1130” data-start =“ 1099”&gt;访问控制 - 允许 - 奥林基蛋白&lt;/strong&gt;标题，因此浏览器的CORS策略阻止了Angular App。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Rust: The Must-Adopt Language for Modern Software Development】生锈：现代软件开发的必备语言</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-rust-modern-software-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;article data-scroll-anchor=&#34;true&#34; data-testid=&#34;conversation-turn-4&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div data-message-author-role=&#34;assistant&#34; data-message-id=&#34;2bbddb9e-4448-461a-80b3-8d23507f1402&#34; data-message-model-slug=&#34;gpt-4o&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/segmentation-violation-rust-solution&#34;&gt;Rust&lt;/a&gt; brings together safety, speed, and solid support for concurrency, three things that are often hard to get all at once in a programming language. Here&#39;s how it stacks up against some of the popular ones:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Rust Stands Out&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;文章data-scroll-andor =“ true” data-testid =“对话 -  turn-4” dir =“ auto”&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex =“  -  1”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div div data-message-author-role =“助手” data-message-id =“ 2bbddb9e-4448-461a-80b3-80b3-8d23507f1402” data-message-model-slug =“ gpt-4o”&#xA;   &lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/segentication-violation-violation-rust-solution”&gt; Rust &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;将安全性，速度和稳固的支持汇集在一起​​，这通常很难在编程语言中立即获得三件事。这是它与一些受欢迎的方式堆叠的方式：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;   &lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么生锈脱颖而出&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamlining DevOps: How Containers and Kubernetes Deliver】简化DevOps：容器和Kubernetes如何交付</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/streamlining-devops-how-containers-and-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The software development landscape is rapidly evolving, with many organizations embracing containerized applications. Technologies like containers and Kubernetes have revolutionized &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/devops-and-cicd&#34;&gt;DevOps&lt;/a&gt; and automation services. According to a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redhat.com/en/resources/state-of-enterprise-open-source-report-2022&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Red Hat survey&lt;/a&gt;, containers assist organizations in fostering innovation, modernizing infrastructure, and enhancing IT support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Teams now develop, deploy, and manage applications differently because of containers in DevOps. These tools provide the consistency and scalability needed for success. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; leads the charge with faster deployment cycles and zero-downtime updates. The platform also offers automated scaling that responds to live traffic needs. This combination solves the common &#34;it works on my machine&#34; issue and ensures reliable application performance across development, testing, and production environments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;软件开发格局正在迅速发展，许多组织都采用集装箱应用程序。诸如容器和Kubernetes之类的技术已经彻底改变了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/devops-and-cicd”&gt; devops &lt;/a&gt;和自动化服务。根据&lt;a href =“ https://www.redhat.com/en/resources/state-of-enterprise-open-source-rept--report-2022” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black” _ _ blank“ _ _ blank”&gt;红帽“&gt;红色帽子”&gt;红帽调查，集装箱促进&lt;/a&gt;促进&lt;/&#xA;&lt;p&gt;团队现在由于DevOps中的容器而开发，部署和管理应用程序。这些工具提供了成功所需的一致性和可扩展性。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes”&gt; kubernetes &lt;/a&gt;以更快的部署周期和零下降时间更新来领导费用。该平台还提供了自动缩放，以满足实时流量需求。该组合解决了常见的“它在我的机器上工作”问题，并确保在开发，测试和生产环境中可靠的应用程序性能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero-Trust AI: Applying Cybersecurity Best Practices to AI Model Development】零信任AI：将网络安全最佳实践应用于AI模型开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-ai-cybersecurity-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Large language models are fast-developing and transforming the way we use technology. The rise of generative AI tools like ChatGPT and Gemini in 2022 has led to common business exploration and employee adoption, frequently including unapproved use of tools such as ChatGPT, Gemini, and multiple third-party add-ons. Beyond its origins, artificial intelligence has expanded to encompass a broad range of capabilities, including computer vision, natural language processing, problem-solving, and decision-making.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As of today, AI is a powerful tool for improving business processes, enhancing user experiences, and delivering personalized solutions. High potential often comes with important risks, so AI needs better capabilities to manage them effectively. Successfully implementing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-for-ai-building-security-from-the-ground-up&#34;&gt;zero-trust AI&lt;/a&gt; requires dealing with several meaningful LLM security, responsibility, and moral concerns as organizations improve their AI strategies.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;大语言模型正在快速开发和改变我们使用技术的方式。 2022年Chatgpt和Gemini等生成AI工具的兴起导致了常见的业务探索和员工的采用，通常包括未经批准的使用工具，例如Chatgpt，Gemini和多个第三方附加组件。除了其起源外，人工智能还扩展到了广泛的功能，包括计算机视觉，自然语言处理，解决问题和决策。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;截至今天，AI是改善业务流程，增强用户体验和提供个性化解决方案的强大工具。高潜力通常会带来重要的风险，因此AI需要更好的能力来有效地管理它们。成功实施&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-for-ai-building-security-security-from-the-thequorm-up-------------&gt;零 -  trust ai &lt;/a&gt;需要处理几种有意义的LLM安全性，责任和道德问题，以提高其AI策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Threat Modeling for Developers: Identifying Security Risks in Software Projects】开发人员的威胁建模：确定软件项目中的安全风险</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/threat-modeling-for-developers-identifying-security-risks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Software projects can have disastrous breaches resulting from security flaws that expose private information and compromise user confidence. Preventive security measures become critical as applications get more sophisticated. One of the best ways to find and reduce possible hazards before they turn into exploitable weaknesses is threat modeling. Structured approaches such as STRIDE and DREAD let developers methodically examine security concerns and create strong programs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Understanding Threat Modeling in Software Development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A methodical strategy for spotting and assessing security vulnerabilities in a software system is threat modeling. Developers foresee possible risks and use mitigating techniques during the development procedure rather than reacting to weaknesses following an attack. Good threat modeling improves security by guiding teams toward where their applications might be weak and what steps they might take to reduce risks.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;软件项目可能会因安全缺陷而导致私人信息并损害用户信心而产生灾难性的漏洞。随着应用程序变得更加复杂，预防安全措施变得至关重要。在变成可剥削的弱点之前发现和减少可能危害的最佳方法之一是威胁建模。诸如步伐和恐惧之类的结构化方法让开发人员有条不紊地检查安全问题并创建强大的程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;了解软件开发中的威胁建模&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;一种有条理的策略，用于在软件系统中发现和评估安全漏洞是威胁建模。开发人员会预见，在开发过程中可能会冒险并使用缓解技术，而不是对攻击后的弱点做出反应。良好的威胁建模通过指导团队向其应用可能较弱的地方提高安全性，以及他们可能采取的措施来降低风险。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maximizing Productivity: GitHub Copilot With Custom Instructions in VS Code】最大化生产力：github副副词，用自定义说明与代码中的自定义说明</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/github-copilot-custom-instructions-vs-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;AI code assistants really shine when they&#39;re integrated into an integrated development environment (IDE). Imagine an IDE as the ultimate workspace where everything a developer could want is right at their fingertips, like syntax highlighting that makes code a breeze to read, error detection that spots issues before they escalate, and version control that tracks every little change. In this dynamic setting, AI assistants become incredibly adept at understanding what you&#39;re trying to create. They can analyze your existing code, recognize the patterns you&#39;re using, and provide suggestions that feel like they&#39;re coming from a teammate who truly understands your project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;What really makes this partnership between &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-guide-to-modern-ai-developer-tools&#34;&gt;AI and IDEs&lt;/a&gt; so effective is how effortlessly they come together to remove the usual hurdles that slow developers down. Instead of constantly bouncing between different tools and losing your focus, you can maintain your coding rhythm while the AI takes care of the repetitive tasks, like generating boilerplate code or suggesting the next logical step in your function. If you hit a snag or need to tidy up a messy section, you can just ask your AI assistant for help without ever stepping out of your development environment. It’s like having a savvy coding buddy right there with you, ready to lend a hand whenever you need it, making the whole software-building process feel more like a team effort and less like a lonely battle against complexity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; AI代码助理在集成到集成的开发环境（IDE）中时确实会发光。想象一下，IDE是一个终极工作区，开发人员想要的一切都触手可及，例如语法突出显示，使代码变得轻而易举地阅读，错误检测在升级之前发现问题的错误，并且可以控制每一个小更改的版本。在这种动态的环境中，AI助手变得非常擅长理解您要创建的东西。他们可以分析您的现有代码，识别您使用的模式，并提供感觉就像是真正了解您项目的队友的建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;真正使&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-gulide-to-modern-ai-developer-tools-tools”&gt; ai and ides &lt;/a&gt;如此有效地毫不费力地使他们毫不费力地消除了慢速的开发者，这是什么真正使这种伙伴关系。您可以在AI负责重复任务时保持编码节奏，而不是在不同的工具之间不断弹跳并失去焦点，而是保持了编码节奏，例如生成样板代码或建议您功能中的下一个逻辑步骤。如果您遇到了障碍或需要整理一整部分，则可以向您的AI助手寻求帮助，而无需走出开发环境。这就像与您一起有一个精明的编码好友，随时准备伸出援手，使整个软件构建过程更像是团队的努力，而不再像孤独的斗争。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DevOps Remediation Architecture for Azure CDN From Edgio】Edgio的Azure CDN的DevOps修复体系结构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/azure-cdn-edgio-devops-remediation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Some ongoing projects are currently leveraging Azure CDN from Edgio (formerly Verizon), which is officially being retired. Notably, the&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;shutdown date has been moved up to &lt;strong&gt;January 7, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;, meaning users must take action sooner than initially planned.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To understand the implications of this retirement, we recommend reviewing Microsoft’s official guidance in the article: &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cdn/edgio-retirement-faq?toc=%2Fazure%2Ffrontdoor%2FTOC.json&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Azure CDN from Edgio retirement FAQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;目前，一些正在进行的项目正在利用Edgio（以前是Verizon）的Azure CDN，该项目正式退休。值得注意的是，&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;关闭日期已移至2025年1月7日&lt;strong&gt;，这意味着用户必须比最初计划的更快采取行动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解这次退休的含义，我们建议您在文章中审查Microsoft的官方指导：&lt;a href =“ https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/en-us/azure/cdn/cdn/edgio-retirirlement-faq?toc--faq?toc?toc=%2fazure； target =“ _ blank”&gt;来自Edgio退休常见问题的Azure CDN &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transform Settlement Process Using AWS Data Pipeline】使用AWS数据管道转换解决过程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-data-pipeline-modernization-settlement-etl</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Data modernization involves simplifying, automating, and orchestrating data pipelines, as well as improving the claim and settlement process using various &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/multi-tenant-architecture-for-a-saas-application-on-aws&#34;&gt;AWS SaaS services&lt;/a&gt;, converting large data settlement files to a new business-required format. The task involves processing settlement files from various sources using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-overview-of-key-components-of-a-data-pipeline&#34;&gt;AWS data pipelines&lt;/a&gt;. These files may be received as zip files, Excel sheets, or database tables. The pipeline applies business logic to transform inputs (often Excel) into outputs (also in Excel).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our inputs typically come from a variety of sources. Utilize inputs from existing AWS tables and external inputs in Excel format. These diverse inputs are ultimately converted to Parquet format. This documentation outlines the process and includes the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/etl-data-modeling-for-sample-crypto-data&#34;&gt;AWS data pipeline ETL jobs architecture&lt;/a&gt; for replication purposes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Data modernization involves simplifying, automating, and orchestrating data pipelines, as well as improving the claim and settlement process using various &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/multi-tenant-architecture-for-a-saas-application-on-aws&#34;&gt;AWS SaaS services&lt;/a&gt;, converting large data settlement files to a new business-required format.该任务涉及使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/an-overview-of-key-components-of-a-a-data-pipeline”&gt; aws data Pipeelines &lt;/a&gt;的任务。这些文件可以作为zip文件，excel表或数据库表接收。该管道将​​业务逻辑应用于将输入（通常是Excel）转换为输出（也在Excel中）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的输入通常来自各种来源。以Excel格式利用现有AWS表和外部输入的输入。这些不同的输入最终将转换为镶木格式。本文档概述了该过程，并包括&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/etl-data-modeling-for-sample-crypto-data”&gt; aws data data podaipe etl eTl jobs架构&lt;/a&gt;用于复制目的。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>