<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Popular DevOps Automation Tools】流行的 DevOps 自动化工具</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/popular-devops-automation-tools</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DevOps automation tools streamline the path from idea to deployment by turning repetitive, error-prone steps into reliable, repeatable workflows that reduce toil and shorten mean time to recovery (MTTR).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article walks through five categories of DevOps automation tools. Expanding your tool stack thoughtfully is less about quantity and more about reducing change failure rate and increasing deployment frequency in a safe way.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DevOps 自动化工具将重复、容易出错的步骤转变为可靠、可重复的工作流程，从而减少繁琐工作并缩短平均恢复时间 (MTTR)，从而简化从创意到部署的路径。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文将介绍五类 DevOps 自动化工具。深思熟虑地扩展工具堆栈不在于数量，而在于以安全的方式降低变更失败率并提高部署频率。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using LLMs to Automate Root Cause Analysis in Incident Response】使用法学硕士在事件响应中自动进行根本原因分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llms-automated-root-cause-analysis-incident-response</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Executive Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today’s complex cloud and microservices-based systems, it’s no surprise that things break. While we’ve made huge strides in detecting issues quickly with modern observability tools, getting to the actual root of a problem — what really caused the incident — is still a tough, manual, and time-consuming task.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s where large language models (LLMs) step in. These AI models are trained to understand logs, alerts, documentation, and natural language — all of which are crucial during incidents. By tapping into the power of LLMs, teams can significantly speed up &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/root-cause-analysis-in-software-development-teams&#34;&gt;root cause analysis&lt;/a&gt; (RCA), reduce downtime, and even lay the foundation for self-healing systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;执行摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在当今复杂的云和基于微服务的系统中，出现问题也就不足为奇了。尽管我们在利用现代可观测性工具快速检测问题方面取得了巨大进步，但找出问题的真正根源（真正导致事件的原因）仍然是一项艰巨的手动且耗时的任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是大型语言模型 (LLM) 发挥作用的地方。这些 AI 模型经过训练可以理解日志、警报、文档和自然语言 - 所有这些在事件发生时都至关重要。通过利用法学硕士的力量，团队可以显着加快&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/root-cause-analysis-in-software-development-teams&#34;&gt;根本原因分析&lt;/a&gt; (RCA)，减少停机时间，甚至为自我修复系统奠定基础。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Evaluating LLM-Powered Voice Assistants: A Guide Beyond Traditional Metrics】评估法学硕士支持的语音助手：超越传统指标的指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/evaluating-llm-powered-voice-assistants</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Voice assistants have evolved from being simple, rule-based systems to advanced conversational agents driven by large language models (LLMs). Early versions of voice assistants could only handle specific tasks with pre-defined commands. In contrast, modern LLM-powered assistants can now engage in long and open-ended conversations, follow complex instructions, and perform multi-step reasoning. These improved capabilities bring new evaluation challenges. Traditional metrics like intent classification accuracy, slot-filling accuracy/recall, and goal completion rates can no longer capture the overall quality of a voice assistant.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assistant responses can sound fluent and plausible, even when they contain factual errors or unsafe content. For example, an LLM assistant might correctly identify a user’s request to “find Italian restaurants” (intent) and extract the location “downtown” (slot), but then respond with a restaurant name that doesn’t even exist. Traditional benchmarks would mark the intent/slot task as successful, without accounting for the factual error. Therefore, new metrics and techniques are needed to assess factuality, safety, reasoning ability, instruction following, and user experience.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;语音助手已经从简单的、基于规则的系统发展成为由大型语言模型 (LLM) 驱动的高级对话代理。早期版本的语音助手只能使用预定义的命令处理特定任务。相比之下，现代法学硕士支持的助理现在可以进行长时间且开放式的对话，遵循复杂的指令，并执行多步骤推理。这些改进的能力带来了新的评估挑战。意图分类准确性、槽位填充准确性/召回率和目标完成率等传统指标无法再衡量语音助手的整体质量。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;助理的回复听起来流畅且可信，即使其中包含事实错误或不安全的内容。例如，法学硕士助理可能会正确识别用户“查找意大利餐馆”（意图）的请求并提取“市中心”位置（位置），但随后会使用甚至不存在的餐馆名称进行响应。传统基准会将意图/槽任务标记为成功，而不考虑事实错误。因此，需要新的指标和技术来评估真实性、安全性、推理能力、指令遵循和用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Supply Chain Digital Twin Technology】构建供应链数字孪生技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-supply-chain-digital-twin-technology</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;About Supply Chain&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Supply chain means that the entire system is involved, from the producer to the customer. This process involves producing and delivering a product or service to the customer. It includes all the methods, systems, organizations, people, activities, information, and resources.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;The following are some of the steps involved in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/software-supply-chain-security&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;supply chain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;关于供应链&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;供应链意味着涉及从生产者到客户的整个系统。此过程涉及生产并向客户提供产品或服务。它包括所有的方法、系统、组织、人员、活动、信息和资源。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;以下是 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/software-supply-chain-security&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;供应链&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span 中涉及的一些步骤 data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;：&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How GenAI Can Eliminate SME Bottlenecks in Enterprise Systems】GenAI 如何消除中小企业企业系统瓶颈</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/genai-for-sme-knowledge-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In large-scale enterprises, tribal knowledge often stalls developer productivity and slows operational agility. Subject matter experts (SMEs) become bottlenecks when critical business logic and configuration decisions live only in legacy codebases or in the minds of a few veterans.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article presents an architecture that leverages GraphCodeBERT embeddings, FAISS vector search, and large language models (LLMs) like Sonnet or Claude to transform complex enterprise logic into conversational explanations. Drawing on real-world use cases in asset lifecycle processing and internal platform operations, it outlines a scalable, GenAI-driven approach to overcoming SME bottlenecks and accelerating engineering velocity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在大型企业中，部落知识常常会阻碍开发人员的生产力并降低运营敏捷性。当关键业务逻辑和配置决策仅存在于遗留代码库或少数资深人士的头脑中时，主题专家 (SME) 就会成为瓶颈。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文提出了一种架构，该架构利用 GraphCodeBERT 嵌入、FAISS 向量搜索和大型语言模型 (LLM)（例如 Sonnet 或 Claude）将复杂的企业逻辑转换为会话解释。它借鉴资产生命周期处理和内部平台操作中的实际用例，概述了一种可扩展的、GenAI 驱动的方法，以克服中小企业瓶颈并加快工程速度。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Low Code, High Impact: A Solution Architect’s Guide to Building Scalable Community Platforms With AI and Low-Code Tools】低代码，高影响力：解决方案架构师使用人工智能和低代码工具构建可扩展社区平台的指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-scalable-platforms-with-AI-low-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As a solution architect, I’ve spent most of my career building massive enterprise systems — cloud-native platforms, scalable APIs, and robust infrastructure. So when I took it upon myself to build a digital hub for our Chhath Puja community in Southern California, it was a refreshing shift from the corporate grind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This time, there was no project team, no IT budget, and no stakeholder meetings. Just me — and the need to launch something meaningful, quickly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为一名解决方案架构师，我职业生涯的大部分时间都花在构建大型企业系统上——云原生平台、可扩展的 API 和强大的基础设施。因此，当我亲自为南加州的 Chhath Puja 社区建立一个数字中心时，这是从企业苦差事中令人耳目一新的转变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这一次，没有项目团队，没有 IT 预算，也没有利益相关者会议。只有我——以及快速推出一些有意义的东西的需要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Virtualization Meets Acceleration: Powering AI Workloads】虚拟化与加速：为 AI 工作负载提供动力</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/from-virtualization-to-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence has quickly moved from buzzword to business driver. From chatbots and fraud detection to medical imaging and predictive analytics, AI has found a home in nearly every industry. But as AI evolves, so do the infrastructure demands that support it. Training large models or running real-time inference pipelines isn’t trivial — it takes serious compute, bandwidth, and orchestration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Here’s the good news: most enterprises already have the core building blocks needed for an AI-ready &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/architecting-high-performance-supercomputers-for-t&#34;&gt;high-performance computing&lt;/a&gt; (HPC) environment sitting quietly in their data centers. We&#39;re talking about Cisco UCS servers, Cisco network switches, and VMware virtualization — technologies that are already deeply embedded in IT ecosystems across industries.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能已迅速从流行词转变为业务驱动力。从聊天机器人和欺诈检测到医学成像和预测分析，人工智能几乎在每个行业都找到了立足之地。但随着人工智能的发展，支持它的基础设施需求也在不断增长。训练大型模型或运行实时推理管道并非易事 - 它需要大量的计算、带宽和编排。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;好消息是：大多数企业已经在其数据中心内安静地拥有 AI 就绪的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/architecting-high-performance-supercomputers-for-t&#34;&gt;高性能计算&lt;/a&gt; (HPC) 环境所需的核心构建块。我们谈论的是思科 UCS 服务器、思科网络交换机和 VMware 虚拟化，这些技术已经深深嵌入到各行业的 IT 生态系统中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Efficiently Reading Large Excel Files (Over 1 Million Rows) Using the Open-Source Sjxlsx Java API】使用开源 Sjxlsx Java API 高效读取大型 Excel 文件（超过 100 万行）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/read-large-excel-files-in-java-with-sjxlsx</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you are a developer, regardless of the technologies you use, at some point, you will face the challenge of handling large Excel files.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most commonly, you will see the &#34;&lt;strong&gt;out of memory&lt;/strong&gt;&#34;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;error&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;when handling these files.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您是一名开发人员，无论您使用什么技术，在某些时候，您都会面临处理大型 Excel 文件的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最常见的是，在处理这些文件时，您会看到“&lt;strong&gt;内存不足&lt;/strong&gt;”&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;错误&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Theia Deep Dive, Part 2: Mastering Customization】Theia 深入探讨，第 2 部分：掌握定制</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/theia-deep-dive-mastering-customization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;355&#34; data-start=&#34;144&#34;&gt;In the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/theia-deep-dive-build-your-own-ide&#34;&gt;first part&lt;/a&gt;, we set up the basics: Theia runs in the browser, plugins work, themes and icons load, and we even added a splash screen. That gives us a functional IDE, but it’s still pretty close to stock.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;549&#34; data-start=&#34;357&#34;&gt;This part is about shaping it into our own product. We’ll start by stripping out what we don’t need, then adjust the UI and wire up contributions so the editor feels focused and intentional.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;355&#34; data-start=&#34;144&#34;&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/theia-deep-dive-build-your-own-ide&#34;&gt;第一部分&lt;/a&gt;中，我们设置了基础知识：Theia 在浏览器中运行、插件工作、主题和图标加载，我们甚至添加了启动屏幕。这为我们提供了一个实用的 IDE，但它仍然非常接近库存。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;549&#34; data-start=&#34;357&#34;&gt;这部分是关于将其塑造成我们自己的产品。我们将首先删除不需要的内容，然后调整 UI 并连接贡献，以便编辑人员感到专注和有意。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Top 20 Problems With Batch Processing (and How to Fix Them With Data Streaming)】批处理的 20 大问题（以及如何通过数据流解决这些问题）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fix-batch-processing-problems-using-data-streaming</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Batch processing has long been the default approach for moving and transforming data in enterprise systems. It works on fixed schedules, processes data in large chunks, and often relies on complex chains of jobs that run overnight. While this was acceptable in the past, today’s digital businesses operate in real time — and can’t afford to wait hours for fresh insights.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Delays, errors, and inconsistencies caused by batch workflows lead to poor decisions, missed opportunities, and growing operational costs. In this post, we’ll look at common issues with batch processing and show why data streaming is the modern alternative for fast, reliable, and scalable data infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;批处理长期以来一直是企业系统中移动和转换数据的默认方法。它按固定的时间表工作，处理大块数据，并且通常依赖于夜间运行的复杂作业链。虽然这在过去是可以接受的，但如今的数字业务是实时运营的，不能等待数小时才能获得新的见解。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;批处理工作流程造成的延迟、错误和不一致会导致决策失误、错失机会以及运营成本增加。在这篇文章中，我们将讨论批处理的常见问题，并展示为什么数据流是快速、可靠和可扩展的数据基础设施的现代替代方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>