<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes in the Cloud: A Guide to Observability】云中的 Kubernetes：可观察性指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-must-have-guide-to-kubernetes-observability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As per the saying “&lt;em&gt;If you don’t measure it, you can’t manage it&lt;/em&gt;” by &lt;a href=&#34;https://pnhp.org/news/berenson-on-the-fallacy-of-if-you-cant-measure-it-you-cant-manage-it/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Deming&lt;/a&gt;, observability and monitoring is our way to measure our services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Kubernetes is pretty revolutionary when it comes to the way it handles deployments and scales. But the way containers are continuously created and destroyed can sometimes present challenges with monitoring. This is where&amp;nbsp;observability&amp;nbsp;comes into play, offering critical insights into how your system is performing and why issues occur.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;正如&lt;a href=&#34;https://pnhp.org/news 所说的“&lt;em&gt;如果你不衡量它，你就无法管理它&lt;/em&gt;” /berenson-on-the-fallacy-of-if-you-cant-measure-it-you-cant-manage-it/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;戴明&lt;/a&gt;，可观察性和监控是我们的方式衡量我们的服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 在处理部署和扩展的方式方面是相当革命性的。但容器不断创建和销毁的方式有时会给监控带来挑战。这就是可观察性发挥作用的地方，它可以提供有关系统性能以及问题发生原因的重要见解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Troubleshooting Kubernetes Pod Crashes: Common Causes and Effective Solutions】排除 Kubernetes Pod 崩溃问题：常见原因和有效解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/troubleshooting-kubernetes-pod-crashes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Kubernetes has become the de facto standard for container orchestration, offering scalability, resilience, and ease of deployment. However, managing Kubernetes environments is not without challenges. One common issue faced by administrators and developers is pod crashes. In this article, we will explore the reasons behind pod crashes and outline effective strategies to diagnose and resolve these issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Common Causes of Kubernetes Pod Crashes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Out-of-Memory (OOM) Errors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/root-causes-of-OOM-issues-in-Java-containers&#34;&gt;Insufficient memory allocation&lt;/a&gt; in resource limits. Containers often consume more memory than initially estimated, leading to termination.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 已成为容器编排的事实上的标准，提供可扩展性、弹性和易于部署。然而，管理 Kubernetes 环境并非没有挑战。管理员和开发人员面临的一个常见问题是 Pod 崩溃。在本文中，我们将探讨 Pod 崩溃背后的原因，并概述诊断和解决这些问题的有效策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Pod 崩溃的常见原因&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1。内存不足 (OOM) 错误&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;原因&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/root-causes-of-OOM-issues-in-Java-containers&#34;&gt;资源限制中内存分配不足&lt;/a&gt;。容器消耗的内存通常比最初估计的要多，从而导致终止。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering High-Risk GitHub Pull Requests: Review, Rollout Strategies, and Lessons Learned】掌握高风险 GitHub Pull 请求：回顾、推出策略和经验教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-high-risk-github-pull-requests</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In modern software development, GitHub has emerged as a cornerstone platform for version control and collaborative coding. The practice of creating and reviewing pull requests (PRs) on GitHub ensures that teams can collaborate effectively while maintaining code quality.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;However, the review and rollout of high-risk &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-pull-request-paradox-merge-faster-by-promoting&#34;&gt;pull requests&lt;/a&gt; (PRs) on GitHub present significant challenges to software development teams, particularly when the changes involve critical system components, security implications, performance optimization, or major updates to third-party dependencies. These PRs have a higher probability of introducing unforeseen issues into the codebase, which could compromise the stability, security, and performance of the system. Consequently, addressing high-risk pull requests requires a disciplined and rigorous approach to ensure successful integration with minimal disruption.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在现代软件开发中，GitHub 已成为版本控制和协作编码的基石平台。在 GitHub 上创建和审查拉取请求 (PR) 的做法可确保团队能够有效协作，同时保持代码质量。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;但是，审查和推出高风险&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-pull-request-paradox-merge-faster-by-promoting&#34;&gt; GitHub 上的拉取请求 (PR) 给软件开发团队带来了重大挑战，特别是当更改涉及关键系统组件、安全影响、性能优化或第三方依赖项的重大更新时。这些 PR 更有可能将不可预见的问题引入代码库，这可能会损害系统的稳定性、安全性和性能。因此，解决高风险拉取请求需要采用严格的方法，以确保成功集成并最大程度地减少干扰。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Resolve SQL Server &#39;Database cannot be Opened&#39; Issue Due to MDF Corruption?】如何解决由于 MDF 损坏而导致 SQL Server“无法打开数据库”的问题？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/resolve-sql-server-database-cannot-be-opened-mdf-issue</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Master Database File (MDF) is the primary database file in MS SQL Server that stores all the data, including views, tables, stored procedures, foreign keys, and primary keys. Sometimes, while opening the MDF file, you may face an issue where the SQL Server database cannot be opened and encounter an error, like the one given below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;SQL Server error 5171: MDF is not a primary database file&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Unable to open the file xxxxx.mdf. Operating system error 5: (Access is denied)”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Event ID 824: SQL Server detected a logical consistency-based I/O error&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Msg 8114, Level 16, State 5, Line 2: Error converting data type varchar to numeric&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Such errors usually occur when there is corruption in the MDF file. In this article, we&#39;ll explain the possible &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-repair-mdf-file-in-sql-server-database&#34;&gt;reasons behind the corruption of MDF files&lt;/a&gt; and show how to repair corrupted MDF files and resolve the issue.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;主数据库文件（MDF）是MS SQL Server中的主数据库文件，它存储所有数据，包括视图、表、存储过程、外键和主键。有时，在打开MDF文件时，您可能会遇到无法打开SQL Server数据库并遇到错误的问题，如下所示：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;SQL Server 错误 5171：MDF 不是主数据库文件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;无法打开文件 xxxxx.mdf。操作系统错误 5：（访问被拒绝）”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;事件 ID 824：SQL Server 检测到基于逻辑一致性的 I/O 错误&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;消息 8114，级别 16，状态 5，第 2 行：将数据类型 varchar 转换为数字时出错&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此类错误通常在 MDF 文件损坏时发生。在本文中，我们将解释 MDF 损坏背后的可能原因文件&lt;/a&gt;并展示如何修复损坏的 MDF 文件并解决问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Demystifying Big O Notation】揭秘大 O 表示法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-big-o-notation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Understanding how efficient your code is just by looking at it can be tricky. Thankfully, the brilliant minds before us have come up with a neat trick: &lt;strong&gt;Big O notation&lt;/strong&gt;. This fancy little concept helps us measure how much &lt;strong&gt;time&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;space&lt;/strong&gt; an algorithm will consume based on its input.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, why should we care? Well, as engineers, our job boils down to two things: solving problems that have never been solved before or solving problems that &lt;strong&gt;have&lt;/strong&gt; been solved but in a more efficient way. Knowing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-big-o-notation&#34;&gt;Big O&lt;/a&gt; helps us make smarter decisions about which algorithms to use. It’s like having a cheat sheet for predicting how much time and memory your code will need, depending on the input size. Sounds good, right? Let’s break it down with a simple example: &lt;strong&gt;O(n)&lt;/strong&gt;, also known as linear time complexity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;仅通过查看代码来了解代码的效率可能很棘手。值得庆幸的是，我们面前的聪明人想出了一个巧妙的技巧：&lt;strong&gt;大 O 表示法&lt;/strong&gt;。这个奇特的小概念可以帮助我们衡量算法根据其输入将消耗多少&lt;strong&gt;时间&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;空间&lt;/strong&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那么，我们为什么要关心呢？那么，作为工程师，我们的工作可以归结为两件事：解决以前从未解决过的问题或解决&lt;strong&gt;已经&lt;/strong&gt;已经解决但以更有效的方式解决的问题。了解 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-big-o-notation&#34;&gt;Big O&lt;/a&gt; 有助于我们就使用哪些算法做出更明智的决策。这就像有一个备忘单来预测您的代码将需要多少时间和内存，具体取决于输入大小。听起来不错，对吧？让我们用一个简单的例子来分解它：&lt;strong&gt;O(n)&lt;/strong&gt;，也称为线性时间复杂度。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unsupervised Learning Methods for Analyzing Encrypted Network Traffic】用于分析加密网络流量的无监督学习方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unsupervised-learning-methods-for-analyzing-network-traffic</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Unsupervised learning methods have emerged as invaluable tools for analyzing encrypted network traffic. These techniques are particularly useful because they don&#39;t require labeled data, which is often difficult or impossible to obtain for encrypted communications. Let&#39;s explore how unsupervised learning methods are applied to encrypted traffic analysis:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clustering Algorithms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/k-means-and-som-gentle-introduction-to-worlds-most&#34;&gt;Clustering algorithms&lt;/a&gt; are widely used for encrypted traffic analysis due to their ability to group similar traffic flows without prior knowledge of their classification.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;无监督学习方法已成为分析加密网络流量的宝贵工具。这些技术特别有用，因为它们不需要标记数据，而对于加密通信来说，标记数据通常很难或不可能获得。我们来探讨一下无监督学习方法如何应用于加密流量分析：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;聚类算法&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/k-means-and-som-gentle-introduction-to-worlds-most&#34;&gt;聚类算法&lt;/a&gt;广泛应用用于加密流量分析，因为它们能够在不事先了解其分类的情况下对类似的流量进行分组。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Performance in Azure Cosmos DB: Best Practices and Tips】优化 Azure Cosmos DB 的性能：最佳实践和技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-performance-in-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When we are working with a database, optimization is crucial and key in terms of application performance and efficiency. Likewise, in Azure Cosmos DB, optimization is crucial for maximizing efficiency, minimizing costs, and ensuring that your application scales effectively. Below are some of the best practices with coding examples to optimize performance in Azure Cosmos DB.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Selection of Right Partition Key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Choosing an appropriate partition key is vital for distributed databases like&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/tips-on-performance-optimization-of-cosmos-db&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cosmos DB&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. A good partition key ensures that data is evenly distributed across partitions, reducing hot spots&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;and improving performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;当我们使用数据库时，优化对于应用程序性能和效率至关重要。同样，在 Azure Cosmos DB 中，优化对于最大限度地提高效率、最大限度地降低成本并确保应用程序有效扩展至关重要。以下是优化 Azure Cosmos DB 性能的一些最佳实践和编码示例。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1。选择正确的分区键&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;选择合适的分区键对于分布式数据库（如 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/tips-on-performance-optimization-of-cosmos-db&#34;）至关重要&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cosmos DB&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;。良好的分区键可确保数据在分区之间均匀分布，从而减少热点&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;并提高性能。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Decoding the Role of a Delivery Manager: Ensuring Smooth Operations Across the Software Development Lifecycle】解读交付经理的角色：确保整个软件开发生命周期的顺利运营</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-the-role-of-a-delivery-manager</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In software development, the term “delivery” often sparks a range of interpretations. Ask ten people what it means, and you might receive ten distinct answers. Yet, despite these varied perspectives, one thing remains constant: the role of a delivery manager is pivotal in turning ideas into reality. They are the glue that holds projects together, ensuring every step of the journey — from concept to launch — unfolds as smoothly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article explores the delivery manager’s responsibilities, their role within a team, and the profound impact they have on ensuring project success.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在软件开发中，“交付”一词经常引发一系列的解释。问十个人这意味着什么，你可能会得到十个不同的答案。然而，尽管观点各异，但有一件事始终不变：交付经理的角色对于将想法变为现实至关重要。它们是将项目粘合在一起的粘合剂，确保从概念到发布的每一步都尽可能顺利地展开。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文探讨了交付经理的职责、他们在团队中的角色以及他们对确保项目成功的深远影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing GitHub Access Management for Enterprises: Enhancing Security, Scalability, and Continuity with Jenkins GitHub App Authentication and Load Balancing】优化企业的 GitHub 访问管理：使用 Jenkins GitHub 应用程序身份验证和负载平衡增强安全性、可扩展性和连续性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-github-access-management-for-enterprises</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As enterprises expand their software development practices and scale their DevOps pipelines, effective management of continuous integration (CI) and continuous deployment (CD) processes becomes increasingly important. GitHub, as one of the most widely used source control platforms, plays a central role in modern development workflows. It is critical for managing code repositories, automating tasks, and enabling collaboration among development teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;To streamline CI/CD activities and ensure smoother operations, many organizations implement a centralized GitHub admin account that oversees repository management, integrations, and automation. This method helps maintain control and consistency across development environments. However, such an approach can introduce security vulnerabilities, scalability challenges, and operational risks, particularly when it comes to handling increasing complexity and ensuring high availability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着企业扩展其软件开发实践并扩展其 DevOps 管道，持续集成 (CI) 和持续部署 (CD) 流程的有效管理变得越来越重要。 GitHub 作为最广泛使用的源代码控制平台之一，在现代开发工作流程中发挥着核心作用。它对于管理代码存储库、自动化任务以及实现开发团队之间的协作至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为了简化 CI/CD 活动并确保操作更顺畅，许多组织实施了集中式 GitHub 管理员帐户来监督存储库管理、集成和自动化。此方法有助于保持跨开发环境的控制和一致性。然而，这种方法可能会带来安全漏洞、可扩展性挑战和操作风险，特别是在处理日益增加的复杂性和确保高可用性时。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Efficient Asynchronous Processing Using CyclicBarrier and CompletableFuture in Java】在 Java 中使用 CyclicBarrier 和 CompletableFuture 进行高效异步处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/efficient-asynchronous-processing-using-cyclicbarr</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In today’s world enterprise applications increasingly require the ability to asynchronously process large datasets. The processing of data must correlate and compute results at the same time. This article illustrates how CyclicBarrier and CompletableFuture, combined, perform efficiently in processing and producing desired results from large datasets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why to Use Asynchronous Processing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Asynchronous processing lets tasks run without blocking others. Unlike synchronous processing, which runs tasks in order, it allows multiple tasks to proceed at once. This method is handy for tasks that need to wait for external resources, like network requests. It boosts efficiency and responsiveness in applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;当今世界，企业应用程序越来越需要异步处理大型数据集的能力。数据处理必须同时关联和计算结果。本文说明了 CyclicBarrier 和 CompletableFuture 的结合如何在处理大型数据集并生成所需结果时高效执行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么要使用异步处理？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;异步处理让任务运行时不会阻塞其他任务。与按顺序运行任务的同步处理不同，它允许同时执行多个任务。对于需要等待外部资源（例如网络请求）的任务，此方法非常方便。它提高了应用程序的效率和响应能力。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>