<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Scrape Amazon Product Reviews With Python】用Python刮擦亚马逊产品评论</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scrape-amazon-product-reviews-with-python</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Amazon is a well-known e-commerce platform with a large amount of data available in various formats on the web. This data can be invaluable for gaining business insights, particularly by analyzing product reviews to understand the quality of products provided by different vendors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In this guide, we will look into &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/best-python-libraries-for-web-scraping&#34;&gt;web scraping&lt;/a&gt; steps to extract Amazon reviews of a particular product and save them in Excel or CSV format. Since manually copying information online can be tedious, we’ll focus on scraping reviews from Amazon. This hands-on experience will enhance our practical understanding of web scraping techniques.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p数​​据可选 - 段落=“”&gt;亚马逊是一个著名的电子商务平台，在网络上以各种格式可用。这些数据对于获得业务见解是无价的，特别是通过分析产品评论以了解不同供应商提供的产品质量。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph =“”&gt;在本指南中，我们将研究&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/best-python-libraries-for-web-scraping&gt; web刮擦&lt;&lt; /a&gt;提取亚马逊评论特定产品的步骤，并以Excel或CSV格式保存它们。由于在线手动复制信息可能很乏味，因此我们将重点介绍亚马逊的评论。这种动手经验将增强我们对网络刮擦技术的实际理解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Expert Guide: How to Slash Cloud Cost in 2025】专家指南：如何在2025年削减云成本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-slash-cloud-cost</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Cloud computing has revolutionized the way companies scale and innovate, but cost control is one hurdle. According to Precedence Research, the cloud computing market size is going to increase to $2.3 trillion by 2032, which necessitates prioritizing cost optimizations as many organizations move to Cloud computing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;fr-inner&#34; contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;Image: Cloud Computing Market Size Projections from 2022 to 2032&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;云计算彻底改变了公司规模和创新的方式，但成本控制是一个障碍。根据先例研究，到2032年，云计算市场规模将增加到2.3万亿美元，这需要优先考虑成本优化，因为许多组织都转移到云计算。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class =“ fr-inner” contenteaditable =“ true”&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption contentedible =“ true”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;图像：云计算市场规模的预测从2022年到2032年&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Passing JSON Variables in Azure Pipelines】通过Azure管道中的JSON变量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/passing-json-variables-azure-pipelines</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When working with Azure DevOps pipelines, there are situations where you need to use JSON as a variable — whether it&#39;s for dynamically passing configurations, triggering APIs, or embedding JSON data into scripts. A common use case is creating a pipeline that triggers an API requiring a JSON payload.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/azure-devops-insights-advantages-and-challenges&#34;&gt;Azure DevOps&lt;/a&gt; treats all variables as plain strings, and when you attempt to pass JSON, it often results in malformed data due to improper escaping. This can break APIs or other components expecting valid JSON.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用Azure DevOps管道时，在某些情况下，您需要将JSON用作变量 - 无论是用于动态传递配置，触发API还是将JSON数据嵌入到脚本中。常见用例是创建触发需要JSON有效载荷的API的管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/azure-devops-insights-andvantages-and-anderges-and-anlenges”&gt; azure devops &lt;/a&gt;通过JSON，由于不当逃脱，它通常会导致畸形数据。这可能会破坏API或其他期望有效JSON的组件。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Predicting Diabetes Types: A Deep Learning Approach】预测糖尿病类型：一种深度学习方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/predicting-diabetes-types-deep-learning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Diabetes has become a significant health concern in India, particularly among young adults. In this article, we&#39;ll explore a comprehensive analysis of diabetes prediction using machine learning techniques, working with a dataset that contains various health and lifestyle factors of young adults in India.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the Dataset&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The dataset comprises 100,000 records with 22 features, including demographic information, health metrics, and lifestyle factors. The key features include age, gender, BMI, family history of diabetes, genetic risk scores, and various lifestyle indicators such as physical activity level, dietary habits, and sleep patterns. What makes this dataset particularly interesting is its focus on young adults and the inclusion of both Type 1 and Type 2 diabetes cases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;糖尿病已成为印度的重大健康问题，尤其是在年轻人中。在本文中，我们将使用机器学习技术探讨对糖尿病预测的全面分析，并与包含印度年轻人的各种健康和生活方式因素的数据集一起工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解数据集&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据集包含100,000个记录，其中包含22个功能，包括人口统计信息，健康指标和生活方式因素。关键特征包括年龄，性别，BMI，糖尿病家族史，遗传风险评分以及各种生活方式指标，例如身体活动水平，饮食习惯和睡眠方式。使该数据集特别有趣的是，它的重点是年轻人，并包括1型和2型糖尿病病例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why You Don’t Need That New JavaScript Library】为什么您不需要新的JavaScript库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-you-dont-need-that-new-javascript-library</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Libraries can rise to stardom in months, only to crash and fade into obscurity within months. We’ve all seen this happen in the software development world, and my own journey has been filled with “must-have” JavaScript libraries, each claiming to be more revolutionary than the one before.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But over the years, I’ve come to realize that the tools we need have been with us all along, and in this article, I’ll explain why it’s worth sticking to the fundamentals, how new libraries can become liabilities, and why stable, proven solutions usually serve us best in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;图书馆可以在几个月内上升到明星，只会在几个月内崩溃并逐渐消失。我们都看到了这在软件开发世界中发生的事情，我自己的旅程充满了“必备”的JavaScript库，每个库都声称比以前更具革命性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，但是多年来，我已经意识到我们一直需要的工具一直与我们在一起，在本文中，我将解释为什么值得坚持基本面，新图书馆如何成为负债，以及为什么从长远来看，稳定，经过验证的解决方案通常为我们提供最佳服务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Publishing Flutter Packages to JFrog Artifactory】出版给Jfrog Artifactory的Flutter包装</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/publishing-flutter-packages-to-jfrog-artifactory</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;JFrog is a comprehensive package manager designed to centralize and secure all the packages required for internal development within an organization, including applications, libraries, and components. It also facilitates the management of open-source libraries with robust security guardrails. This centralized approach provides enterprises with a structured and transparent method for managing open-source software and securing internally developed packages&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is well-defined documentation available for incubating &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/delivering-your-code-to-the-cloud-with-jfrog-artifactory-and-github-actions&#34;&gt;JFrog&lt;/a&gt; for Java Technology and JavaScript/npm. With respect to the Flutter packages, I didn’t find detailed documentation, so I thought of outlining the scenarios and the resolution that I came up with.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt; JFrog是一家综合的软件包管理器，旨在集中和保护组织内部开发所需的所有软件包，包括应用程序，库和组件。它还可以通过强大的安全护栏来促进开源库的管理。这种集中式方法为企业提供了一种结构化和透明的方法，用于管理开源软件并确保内部开发的软件包&lt;/span&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有明确的文档可用于孵化&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/delivering-your-code-code-to-the-cloud-with-with-jfrog--jfrog-artifactory-and-gitactory-and-github-actions “&gt; Jfrog &lt;/a&gt;用于Java技术和JavaScript/NPM。关于颤抖的软件包，我没有找到详细的文档，所以我想到了概述了我想出的方案和分辨率。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Custom React Hooks to Simplify Complex Scenarios】使用自定义React钩子简化复杂方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/custom-react-hooks-simplify-complex-scenarios</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the world of React, hooks have revolutionized the way we build components and manage state. The introduction of hooks like &lt;code&gt;useState&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;useEffect&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;useContext&lt;/code&gt; gave developers more flexibility in writing clean and reusable code. However, there are scenarios where built-in hooks alone aren&#39;t enough to handle complex logic or provide the desired abstraction. That&#39;s where custom React hooks come in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Custom hooks allow you to encapsulate logic into reusable functions, making your codebase cleaner and more maintainable. In this article, let us explore advanced techniques and strategies for building custom React hooks to handle complex scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在React世界中，Hooks彻底改变了我们建立组件和管理状态的方式。引入&lt;code&gt; usestate &lt;/code&gt;，&lt;code&gt; useffect &lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt; usecontext &lt;/code&gt;之类的挂钩的引入使开发人员在编写清洁和可重复使用的代码方面具有更大的灵活性。但是，在某些情况下，仅内置钩子就不足以处理复杂的逻辑或提供所需的抽象。那是自定义式钩子的来源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自定义挂钩使您可以将逻辑封装到可重复使用的功能中，从而使您的代码库清洁器更可维护。在本文中，让我们探索高级技术和构建自定义React钩子以处理复杂方案的策略。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Metal and the Simulated Annealing Algorithm】金属和模拟退火算法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/metal-and-the-simulated-annealing-algorithm</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, I’ll walk you through Bryan Luke’s Simulated Annealing Algorithm, a powerful probabilistic approach to finding optimal solutions among numerous possibilities. We’ll explore its implementation using the classic N-Queens problem as an example. Unlike greedy algorithms, simulated annealing intelligently explores the solution space to avoid being trapped in poor solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Simulated Annealing?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simulated annealing is inspired by the physical process of annealing metals, where a material is heated and then cooled slowly to improve its internal structure. The algorithm mimics this process to find solutions in complex problem spaces.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将引导您浏览Bryan Luke的模拟退火算法，这是一种有力的概率方法，可以在许多可能性中找到最佳解决方案。我们将以经典的N-Quens问题为例探索其实现。与贪婪的算法不同，模拟退火智能地探索了解决方案空间，以避免被困在不良的解决方案中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是模拟退火？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;模拟退火受到退火金属的物理过程的启发，在该金属的物理过程中，将材料加热然后缓慢冷却以改善其内部结构。该算法模拟此过程以在复杂的问题空间中找到解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Gemini 2.0 Flash (Experimental): A Deep Dive for Developers】Gemini 2.0 Flash（实验）：对开发人员的深入潜水</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gemini-20-flash-experimental-a-deep-dive-for-devel</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Gemini 2.0 Flash, Google’s latest LLM, pushes the boundaries of AI capabilities. This blog delves deeper, focusing on key features and how they differentiate Gemini 2.0 Flash from other prominent models.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/unleashing-the-power-of-gemini-with-llamaindex&#34;&gt;Gemini&lt;/a&gt; distinguishes itself from other LLMs primarily through its multi-modal capabilities and advanced reasoning abilities. Unlike many LLMs that primarily focus on text, Gemini can process and generate various forms of data, including images, audio, and code. This multimedia nature allows Gemini to tackle a wider range of tasks and applications, such as image-based question answering, video summarization, and even generating creative content across different modalities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ auto”&gt; Gemini 2.0 Flash，Google最新的LLM，推动了AI功能的界限。该博客更深入研究，重点介绍关键功能以及它们如何区分Gemini 2.0闪光灯与其他突出的模型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ auto”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/unleashing-the-power-the-power-of-gemini-with-llamaindex”&gt; gemini &lt;/a&gt;它的多模式能力和高级推理能力。与许多主要关注文本的LLM不同，双子座可以处理并生成各种形式的数据，包括图像，音频和代码。这种多媒体性质使双子座可以解决更广泛的任务和应用程序，例如基于图像的问题答案，视频摘要，甚至在不同方式上生成创意内容。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Split PDF Files into Separate Documents Using Java】如何使用Java将PDF文件拆分为单独的文档</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/split-pdf-files-into-separate-documents-using-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Asking our Java file-processing applications to manipulate PDF documents can only increase their value in the long run. PDF is by far the most popular, widely used file type in the world today, and that’s unlikely to change any time soon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll specifically learn how to divide PDF files into a series of separate PDF documents in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-21-features-a-detailed-look&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; — resulting in exactly one new PDF per page of the original file — and we’ll discuss open-source and third-party web API options to facilitate implementing that programmatic workflow into our code. We’ll start with a high-level overview of how PDF files are structured to make this type of workflow possible.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;从长远来看，要求我们的Java文件处理应用程序操纵PDF文档只能增加其价值。 PDF是当今世界上最受欢迎，最广泛使用的文件类型，这不太可能很快改变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将专门学习如何将PDF文件分为&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/java-21-features-a-detailed--看“&gt; java &lt;/a&gt;  - 正好导致原始文件的一个新PDF  - 我们将讨论开放式和第三方Web API选项，以促进将该程序化工作流程实现到我们的代码中。我们将从高级概述开始，概述PDF文件的结构以使此类型的工作流程成为可能。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>