<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【ITBench, Part 1: Next-Gen Benchmarking for IT Automation Evaluation】ITBench，第1部分：IT自动化评估的下一代基准测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/itbench-next-gen-benchmarking-it-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;The remarkable promise of GenAI-based agentic (AI agents) solutions, coupled with recent improvements in their ability to handle intricate tasks, &amp;nbsp;has increased the potential for AI agents to manage IT systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Given the complexity and criticality of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/potential-benefits-of-using-generative-ai-in-the-d&#34;&gt;IT systems&lt;/a&gt;, a key challenge in IT automation is finding reliable ways to evaluate agents before using them in production. The successful adoption of AI agents for IT automation thus depends on the ability to measure and rank their reliability and efficiency in predefined and standard ways.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;基于Genai的代理（AI代理）解决方案的显着承诺，再加上其处理复杂任务的能力的最新提高，增加了AI代理管理IT系统的潜力。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;给定&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/potential-benefits-of-using-generative-generative-inerative-in-in-the-the-d”&gt; IT Systems &lt;/a&gt;的复杂性和关键性&lt;/a&gt;，IT自动化的关键挑战是在生产中进行评估的质量。因此，成功地采用了AI代理以自动化的代理取决于测量和对预定义和标准方式的可靠性和效率的能力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Memory-Optimized Tables: Implementation Strategies for SQL Server】内存优化表：SQL Server的实现策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sql-server-memory-optimized-tables</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Throughout my 15-year journey as a SQL Server DBA, I&#39;ve encountered numerous technologies promising revolutionary performance improvements, but few have delivered as convincingly as memory-optimized tables.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First appearing in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/fixed-database-in-recovery-mode-sql-server-2014&#34;&gt;SQL Server 2014&lt;/a&gt; as part of the in-memory OLTP feature (codenamed &#34;&lt;strong&gt;Hekaton&lt;/strong&gt;&#34;), this technology has matured significantly in subsequent releases. The fundamental concept is elegantly simple: while traditional tables live on disk and must be loaded into memory for processing, memory-optimized tables permanently reside in memory with disk storage serving only as a persistence mechanism.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我担任SQL Server DBA的15年旅程中，我遇到了许多有望改善革命性绩效的技术，但是很少有像内存优化的表那样令人信服。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先出现在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/fixed-database-in-recovery-sql-server-2014”&gt; sql Server 2014 &lt;/a&gt;作为内存OLTP功能的一部分（Codenamed“ &lt;strong&gt; Hekaton &lt;/hekaton &lt;/strong&gt;”）基本概念非常简单：虽然传统桌子在磁盘上使用，并且必须将其加载到内存中以进行处理，但内存优化的表永久驻留在记忆中，磁盘存储仅作为持久机制。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Accuracy: A Product-Led Case for State Space Models Over Transformers】超越准确性：针对变形金刚的国家空间模型的产品主导的案例</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/state-space-models-ssm-over-transformers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;The AI industry’s obsession with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-of-data-lies-in-transformer-models-vs-b&#34;&gt;Transformers&lt;/a&gt; might finally be waning. While OpenAI and Google, with their extensive language models capture the public attention, there is a more discreet change taking place in the way AI is implemented into production systems, or how it is AI is utilized within industry processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Among practitioners who are less concerned with competition metrics and more focused on speed, efficiency, and scalable solutions, newer versions such as Mamba of State Space Models (SSMs) appear to be winning some favor. The theoretical base for the SSM approach has existed for some time, but its practical application in competition against Transformers is relatively recent.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;P Data-selectable-paragraph =“”&gt; AI行业对&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-of-data-lies-in--transformer-models-vs-vs-b”&gt;变形金刚&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;最终可能是在减弱。尽管Openai和Google及其广泛的语言模型引起了公众的关注，但在生产系统中实施AI或如何在行业流程中使用AI的方式发生了更加谨慎的变化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据选择性 - 段落=“”&gt;在不太关心竞争指标并更专注于速度，效率和可扩展解决方案的从业者中，诸如国家空间模型的Mamba（SSM）等新版本似乎赢得了一些青睐。 SSM方法的理论基础已经存在一段时间了，但是它在针对变形金刚的竞争中的实际应用是相对较新的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Comparing Managed Postgres Options on The Azure Marketplace】比较Azure市场上的托管Postgres选项</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/managed-postgres-options-azure-marketplace</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Azure is expanding their Postgres portfolio, now offering a range of managed Postgres services to suit the needs of developers and teams of all sizes. In this post, we’ll walk through the main Postgres options available on the Azure Marketplace, so you can find the one that works best for your application.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Why Deploy Postgres Through the Azure Marketplace?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If your company runs on Azure infra, using the Azure Marketplace to set up your database makes things simple and efficient. Here’s why:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Azure正在扩大其Postgres产品组合，现在提供一系列托管的Postgres服务，以适应各种规模的开发人员和团队的需求。在这篇文章中，我们将浏览Azure Marketplace上可用的主要Postgres选项，因此您可以找到最适合您的应用程序的选项。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;为什么要通过Azure Marketplace部署Postgres？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;如果您的公司在Azure Instra上运行，使用Azure Marketplace设置您的数据库，则可以简单有效。原因是：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Simpler Data Transfer Objects With Java Records】带有Java记录的简单数据传输对象</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/simpler-data-transfer-objects-with-java-records</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In very general terms, data transfer objects (DTOs) are structures that allow packing data when information is exchanged among applications or processes. While business objects or even entities own both state and behavior, DTOs should have only state. I personally see them as the apparel that the domain, the application&#39;s “center of purity,” puts on when engaging in interactions with the “exterior.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java records, on the other hand, prove very useful when data-oriented structures are needed, as a lot of boilerplate code is removed.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在非常一般的术语中，数据传输对象（DTO）是在应用程序或过程之间交换信息时允许包装数据的结构。尽管业务对象甚至实体都拥有状态和行为，但DTO只能具有状态。我个人认为它们是应用程序（应用程序的“纯度中心”）的服装。&#xA;另一方面，&lt;p&gt; Java记录在需要数据的结构时非常有用，因为删除了许多样板代码。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Agents: A New Era for Integration Professionals】AI代理：整合专业人士的新时代</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agents-new-era-integration-professionals</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;•&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Timeless patterns, smarter tools:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;AI agents may seem revolutionary, but they are built on timeless integration patterns like those in ESBs and ETLs, enhanced with smarter capabilities like dynamic parsing and semantic routing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;•&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Evolving roles and teams:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;They unify application and data integration efforts, dissolving silos. Traditional roles like middleware specialists, ETL developers, and data scientists evolve into&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;agentic workflow engineers&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;applied AI specialists.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt; &lt;em&gt;•&lt;/em&gt;•&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;永恒的模式，更智能的工具：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; ai代理人似乎具有革命性的革命性，但它们似乎是基于永恒的集成模式，但是像ESB中的eSB一样，具有像动态的pp &lt;/eTl一样，具有动态式&lt;/emposibility pp &lt;/em p。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;•&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;不断发展的角色和团队：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;他们统一了应用程序和数据集成工作，消除了孤岛。诸如中间件专家，ETL开发人员和数据科学家之类的传统角色演变为&lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;代理工作流程师&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;和&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; applied ai专家。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/prong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Strategies for Securing E-Commerce Applications】确保电子商务应用程序的策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/strategies-for-securing-e-commerce-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Electronic commerce or e-commerce has changed the way we transact, invest, purchase, communicate from virtually anywhere in the world as long as you have internet connectivity. Over the past decade, it has been creating many new exciting opportunities for businesses worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;However, e-commerce web sites are vulnerable to intruder attacks due to reasons aplenty. If there are loopholes or weaknesses in your design, implementation, testing and maintenance phases you&#39;ll land yourself into trouble.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;电子商务或电子商务已经改变了我们交易，投资，购买，几乎从世界任何地方进行交流的方式，只要您拥有互联网连接。在过去的十年中，它为全球企业创造了许多新的激动人心的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;但是，由于原因有很多原因，电子商务网站很容易受到入侵攻击的影响。如果您的设计，实施，测试和维护阶段中存在漏洞或弱点，您将陷入困境。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Graph Concepts in Java With Eclipse JNoSQL, Part 2: Understanding Neo4j】使用Eclipse Jnosql在Java中引入图形概念，第2部分：了解Neo4J</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/graph-concepts-java-eclipse-jnosql-neo4j</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Graph databases have rapidly gained popularity in modern software architecture, as systems increasingly rely on relationships, recommendations, and connected data. From social media platforms and fraud detection systems to recommendation engines and knowledge graphs, graph databases offer a powerful way to model and traverse complex relationships that are hard to express efficiently in relational databases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This second part of the series narrows the focus to Neo4j, the market&#39;s most prominent graph database engine. We&#39;ll explore its architecture, query language (Cypher), and see how Java developers can leverage Eclipse JNoSQL 1.1.8 to integrate it seamlessly into Java applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;图形数据库在现代软件体系结构中迅速越来越受欢迎，因为系统越来越依赖关系，建议和连接的数据。从社交媒体平台和欺诈检测系统到推荐引擎和知识图，图形数据库提供了一种强大的方式来建模和遍历复杂关系，这些关系在关系数据库中很难有效地表达。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该系列的第二部分将重点缩小到Neo4j，Neo4J是市场最突出的图形数据库引擎。我们将探索其架构，查询语言（Cypher），并查看Java开发人员如何利用Eclipse JNOSQL 1.1.8将其无缝集成到Java应用程序中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Use AWS Aurora Database for a Retail Point of Sale (POS) Transaction System】如何将AWS Aurora数据库用于零售点（POS）交易系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-aws-aurora-database-for-retail-pos</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;point of sale (POS) transaction system&lt;/strong&gt; is a crucial component of retail and hospitality businesses, as&lt;/span&gt; it handles sales, payments, inventory management, and customer data. These systems need to process transactions efficiently, ensure data integrity, and be highly available, particularly in high-traffic environments like retail stores or restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;摘要：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; a &lt;span style =“边距：0px; padding：0px;“&gt; &lt;strong&gt;销售点（POS）交易系统&lt;/strong&gt;是零售和酒店业务的关键组成部分，因为&lt;/span&gt;它处理销售，付款，付款，库存，库存管理和客户数据。这些系统需要有效地处理交易，确保数据完整性并高度可用，尤其是在零售店或餐馆等高流量环境中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is Big Data Dying?】大数据死了吗？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/is-big-data-dying</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;e323&#34;&gt;In recent years, the notion that “big data is dying” seems to be gaining traction. Some say the big data craze has faded, while others lament the shrinking job opportunities, the increasing complexity of platforms, and the growing intricacy of business demands. But does this really mean big data is dying?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;fdf5&#34;&gt;I don’t think so. In my view, what’s truly dying is not big data itself, but rather the outdated “dragon-slaying techniques” that no longer have any “dragons” to slay. The “dragon” has evolved, while our weapons remain stuck in the past. Technology needs to evolve, architectures need to be restructured, and capabilities need to be upgraded.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name =“ e323”&gt;近年来，“大数据正在垂死”的概念似乎正在引起关注。有人说，大数据热潮已经消失，而另一些人则感叹了不断变化的工作机会，平台的复杂性日益增加以及商业需求的不复杂性。但这真的意味着大数据快死了吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name =“ fdf5”&gt;我不这么认为。在我看来，真正垂死的不是大数据本身，而是过时的“浪费技术”，这些技术不再有任何“龙”可以杀死。 “龙”进化了，而我们的武器过去仍然陷入困境。技术需要发展，需要重组体系结构，并且需要升级功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>