<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Scholcast: Generating Academic Paper Summaries With AI-Driven Audio】Scholcast：使用人工智能驱动的音频生成学术论文摘要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generating-academic-paper-summaries-with-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Keeping up with the latest research is a critical part of the job for most data scientists. Faced with this challenge myself, I often struggled to maintain a consistent habit of reading academic papers and wondered if I could design a system that would lower the barrier to exploring new research making it easier to engage with developments in my field without the need for extensive time commitments. Given my long commute to work and an innate lack of motivation to perform weekend chores, an audio playlist that I could listen to while doing both sounded like the obvious option.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This led me to build Scholcast, a simple &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-python&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; package that creates detailed audio summaries of academic papers. While I had previously built versions using language models, the recent advancements in expanded context lengths for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-transformer-algorithm-data-and-attention&#34;&gt;Transformers&lt;/a&gt; and improved vocalization finally aligned with all my requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;跟上最新研究的步伐对于大多数数据科学家来说是工作的重要组成部分。面对这一挑战，我经常努力保持阅读学术论文的一贯习惯，并想知道我是否可以设计一个系统来降低探索新研究的障碍，从而更容易地参与我的领域的发展，而不需要广泛的研究时间承诺。考虑到我上班的时间很长，而且天生缺乏做周末家务的动力，所以我可以在做这两件事的同时听音频播放列表，这听起来是显而易见的选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;这促使我构建了 Scholcast，这是一个简单的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-python&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; 包，可以创建详细的学术音频摘要文件。虽然我之前使用语言模型构建了版本，但最近在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-transformer-algorithm-data-and-attention&#34;&gt;Transformer&lt;/a 扩展上下文长度方面取得了进展&gt; 改进的发声终于符合我的所有要求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Formulating a Robust Strategy for Storage in Amazon Relational Database Service PostgreSQL Deployments】在 Amazon Relational Database Service PostgreSQL 部署中制定稳健的存储策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/amazon-rds-postgresql-storage-strategies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you are using the AWS Relational Database Service (RDS) offered managed database services, you may wonder how to strategize database storage size. Strategizing database storage includes understanding the key components of RDS storage, optimizing these storage factors, and capping storage growth by using retention periods.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/rds/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AWS RDS&lt;/a&gt; offers managed database services for Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL, and SQL Server. These managed services include automated backups, single-click upgrades, replication and high availability, and disaster recovery solutions. Under the hood, all these &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-aws-rds-databases&#34;&gt;RDS databases&lt;/a&gt; use Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) volumes for storage. This post discusses the storage components, optimization steps for these storage components using automation, and utilizing various retention period mechanisms to control storage growth.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您使用 AWS Relational Database Service (RDS) 提供的托管数据库服务，您可能想知道如何制定数据库存储大小策略。制定数据库存储策略包括了解 RDS 存储的关键组件、优化这些存储因素以及使用保留期限制存储增长。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/rds/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AWS RDS&lt;/a&gt; 为 Oracle、MySQL、PostgreSQL、和 SQL Server。这些托管服务包括自动备份、单击升级、复制和高可用性以及灾难恢复解决方案。在底层，所有这些 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-aws-rds-databases&#34;&gt;RDS 数据库&lt;/a&gt;都使用 Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) 卷进行存储。这篇文章讨论了存储组件、使用自动化对这些存储组件进行优化的步骤，以及利用各种保留期机制来控制存储增长。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maximizing AI Agents for Seamless DevOps and Cloud Success】最大化 AI 代理以实现无缝 DevOps 和云成功</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/maximizing-ai-agents-for-seamless-devops-and-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The fast growth of artificial intelligence (AI) has created new opportunities for businesses to improve and be more creative. A key development in this area is &lt;strong&gt;intelligent agents&lt;/strong&gt;. These agents are becoming critical in transforming DevOps and cloud delivery processes. They are designed to complete specific tasks and reach specific goals. This changes how systems work in today&#39;s dynamic tech environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/what-are-ai-agents-and-why-do-they-matter/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;generative AI agents&lt;/a&gt;, organizations can get real-time insights and automate their processes. This helps them depend less on manual work and be more efficient and scalable. These agents are not just simple tools — they are &lt;strong&gt;flexible systems&lt;/strong&gt; that can make informed decisions by using the data they collect and their knowledge base. As a result, they provide great value, by optimizing how resources are used, lowering the risk of errors, and boosting overall productivity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能 (AI) 的快速发展为企业改进和提高创造力创造了新的机会。该领域的一个关键发展是&lt;strong&gt;智能代理&lt;/strong&gt;。这些代理对于转变 DevOps 和云交付流程变得至关重要。它们旨在完成特定任务并实现特定目标。这改变了系统在当今动态技术环境中的工作方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.blog/ai-and-ml/generative-ai/what-are-ai-agents-and-why-do-they-matter/&#34; target=&#34; _blank&#34;&gt;生成式人工智能代理&lt;/a&gt;，组织可以获取实时洞察并自动化其流程。这有助于他们减少对手动工作的依赖，提高效率和可扩展性。这些代理不仅仅是简单的工具 - 它们是&lt;strong&gt;灵活的系统&lt;/strong&gt;，可以通过使用它们收集的数据和知识库做出明智的决策。因此，它们通过优化资源的使用方式、降低错误风险并提高整体生产力来提供巨大的价值。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Retrieval Augmented Generation: From Fundamentals to Advanced Techniques】掌握检索增强生成：从基础到高级技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Despite their remarkable capabilities in generating text, answering complex questions, and performing a wide range of tasks, Large Language Models (LLMs) have notable limitations that hinder their real-world applicability. One significant challenge is their inability to consistently provide precise, up-to-date responses. This issue is especially critical in fields like healthcare, law, and finance, where the accuracy and explainability of information are paramount. For instance, imagine a financial analyst querying the latest market trends or a doctor seeking updated medical guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag&#34;&gt;Retrieval-augmented generation&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) addresses these limitations by combining the strengths of LLMs with information retrieval systems, ensuring more accurate, reliable, and contextually grounded outputs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;尽管大型语言模型 (LLM) 在生成文本、回答复杂问题和执行广泛任务方面具有出色的能力，但其存在明显的局限性，阻碍了其在现实世界中的适用性。一项重大挑战是他们无法始终如一地提供准确、最新的响应。这个问题在医疗保健、法律和金融等领域尤其重要，这些领域信息的准确性和可解释性至关重要。例如，想象一下金融分析师查询最新的市场趋势或医生寻求更新的医疗指南。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented- Generation-rag&#34;&gt;检索增强生成&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) 通过结合以下优势解决了这些限制拥有信息检索系统的法学硕士，确保输出更准确、可靠且基于上下文。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Mistakes Made by IT Architects】IT 架构师最容易犯的错误</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-mistakes-made-by-it-architects</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In a previous article, &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/top-mistakes-made-by-product-owners-in-agile-proje&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Top Mistakes Made by Product Owners in Agile Projects&lt;/a&gt;,&#34; I highlighted some of the worst mistakes a Product Owner (PO) can make.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, it’s time for introspection and an analysis of the most common errors I’ve observed in architectural practices throughout my career.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在上一篇文章中，“&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/top-mistakes-made-by-product-owners-in-agile-proje&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target= “_blank&#34;&gt;产品负责人在敏捷项目中犯的主要错误&lt;/a&gt;”，我强调了产品负责人 (PO) 可能犯的一些最严重的错误。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，是时候进行反思并分析我在整个职业生涯中在架构实践中观察到的最常见错误了。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Hands-On Guide to Enable Amazon GuardDuty on AWS Account】在 AWS 账户上启用 Amazon GuardDuty 的实践指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enable-amazon-guardduty-on-aws-account</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital era, cybersecurity is a cornerstone of maintaining trust and reliability in cloud operations. A managed threat detection service by AWS, like Amazon GuardDuty, can help secure your environment by analyzing activity and identifying potential risks. This hands-on guide will help you enable Amazon GuardDuty on your AWS account and begin monitoring your resources for security threats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Amazon GuardDuty is a threat detection service that uses machine learning, anomaly detection, and integrated threat intelligence to protect your AWS environment. It continuously monitors for malicious activity, unauthorized access, and security vulnerabilities by analyzing data sources like AWS CloudTrail logs, VPC Flow Logs, and DNS logs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的数字时代，网络安全是维持云运营信任和可靠性的基石。 AWS 的托管威胁检测服务（例如 Amazon GuardDuty）可以通过分析活动和识别潜在风险来帮助保护您的环境。本实践指南将帮助您在 AWS 账户上启用 Amazon GuardDuty 并开始监控您的资源是否存在安全威胁。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Amazon GuardDuty 是一项威胁检测服务，它使用机器学习、异常检测和集成威胁情报来保护您的 AWS 环境。它通过分析 AWS CloudTrail 日志、VPC 流日志和 DNS 日志等数据源，持续监控恶意活动、未经授权的访问和安全漏洞。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Quantum Machine Learning for Large-Scale Data-Intensive Applications】适用于大规模数据密集型应用的量子机器学习</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-ml-for-large-scale-data-intensive-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The convergence of quantum computing and machine learning offers a promising pathway for tackling large-scale, data-intensive challenges across various domains. This article examines how quantum machine learning (QML) can harness the principles of quantum mechanics to achieve significant computational advantages over classical approaches.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By employing quantum algorithms such as Grover&#39;s search, quantum annealing, and quantum principal component analysis, the study explores the potential of QML to accelerate tasks like data clustering, optimization, and dimensionality reduction. The paper further investigates the integration of quantum and classical techniques, highlighting how hybrid quantum-classical models can address the limitations of current quantum hardware in the Noisy Intermediate-Scale Quantum (NISQ) era. Emphasizing the potential of QML to revolutionize fields that demand high data processing power, such as finance, genomics, and artificial intelligence, this work provides a comprehensive analysis of the advancements, challenges, and future prospects of leveraging quantum computing in machine learning applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;量子计算和机器学习的融合为解决各个领域的大规模数据密集型挑战提供了一条有前途的途径。本文探讨了量子机器学习 (QML) 如何利用量子力学原理来实现相对于经典方法的显着计算优势。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过采用 Grover 搜索、量子退火和量子主成分分析等量子算法，该研究探索了 QML 加速数据聚类、优化和降维等任务的潜力。该论文进一步研究了量子和经典技术的集成，强调混合量子经典模型如何解决嘈杂中尺度量子（NISQ）时代当前量子硬件的局限性。这项工作强调了 QML 彻底改变需要高数据处理能力的领域（例如金融、基因组学和人工智能）的潜力，对在机器学习应用中利用量子计算的进展、挑战和未来前景进行了全面分析。&lt; /p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guide to Installing Fedora 41 on Macbook Pro 13 Inch (Late 2011)】在 Macbook Pro 13 英寸（2011 年末）上安装 Fedora 41 的指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-installing-fedora-41-on-macbook-pro-13-in</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This weekend, I decided to update my old Macbook Pro 13 inch from late 2011, with 125GB SSD and 8GB RAM. It&#39;s a machine I&#39;ve taken on trips around the world and back in the day ran many sessions, workshops, and demos sharing all that developer goodness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last time we checked, this was &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/installing-or-upgrading-to-fedora-37-on-macbook-pr&#34;&gt;installed using Fedora 37&lt;/a&gt;, so how about an update to Fedora 41?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这个周末，我决定更新我的 2011 年底的旧 Macbook Pro 13 英寸，配备 125GB SSD 和 8GB RAM。我带着这台机器环游世界，并在当天举办了许多会议、研讨会和演示，分享了开发人员的所有优点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上次我们检查时，这是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/installing-or-upgrading-to-fedora-37-on-macbook-pr&#34;&gt;使用 Fedora 37 安装的&lt;/ a&gt;，那么更新到 Fedora 41 怎么样？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Governance: Building Ethical and Transparent Systems for the Future】人工智能治理：为未来构建道德和透明的系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-governance-build-ethical-transparent-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is AI Data Governance?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) governance refers to the frameworks, policies, and ethical standards that guide AI technologies&#39; development, deployment, and management. It encompasses a range of considerations, such as data privacy, algorithmic transparency, accountability, and fairness in AI systems, aiming to ensure that these technologies operate according to societal values and legal standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Is the Significance of AI Data Governance?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As AI continues to permeate various aspects of life, from healthcare to finance, a pressing need emerges to address inherent ethical concerns, such as bias, discrimination, and the potential for misuse. Effective governance structures help establish accountability by clarifying who is responsible when AI systems perform poorly or cause harm. They also promote transparency by ensuring that the methodologies behind AI decision-making are clear to users, fostering trust and allowing for informed scrutiny.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是人工智能数据治理？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能 (AI) 治理是指指导人工智能技术开发、部署和管理的框架、政策和道德标准。它涵盖了一系列考虑因素，例如人工智能系统的数据隐私、算法透明度、问责制和公平性，旨在确保这些技术按照社会价值观和法律标准运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI数据治理的意义是什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着人工智能继续渗透到从医疗保健到金融等生活的各个方面，迫切需要解决固有的道德问题，例如偏见、歧视和滥用的可能性。有效的治理结构有助于明确人工智能系统表现不佳或造成损害时的责任方，从而建立问责制。他们还通过确保用户清楚人工智能决策背后的方法、培养信任并允许进行知情审查来提高透明度。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Non-Human Identity Security Strategy for Zero Trust Architecture】零信任架构的非人类身份安全策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/nhi-security-strategy-zta</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Security comes down to trust. In DevOps and our applications, it really is a question of &#34;should this entity be allowed to do that action?&#34; In an earlier time in IT, we could assume that if something was inside a trusted perimeter, be it in our private network or on a specific machine, then we could assume entities were trustworthy and naturally should be able to access resources and data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, as applications became more complex, spanning not just machines but also different data centers and continents, and reliance on third-party services via APIs became the norm, we could no longer rely on trusted perimeters.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;安全归根结底在于信任。在 DevOps 和我们的应用程序中，这实际上是一个“是否应该允许该实体执行该操作？”的问题。在 IT 的早期，我们可以假设，如果某些东西位于受信任的边界内，无论是在我们的专用网络中还是在特定的机器上，那么我们可以假设实体是值得信赖的，并且自然应该能够访问资源和数据。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，随着应用程序变得越来越复杂，不仅跨越机器，还跨越不同的数据中心和大陆，并且通过 API 依赖第三方服务成为常态，我们不能再依赖可信边界。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>