<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Chain of Thought Prompting for LLMs】LLM 的思路提示</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/chain-of-thought-prompting-for-llms</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The advent of ChatGPT and Large Language Models has already affected education. With mixed results and a spectrum of ethical acceptability, students can use chat-tuned LLMs to plan, as a starting point for research, to edit and suggest stylistic or grammatical improvements, or even as a ghostwriter to write assignments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The well-known non-profit Khan Academy offers its own personalized tutor, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.khanmigo.ai/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Khanmigo&lt;/a&gt;, developed in partnership with OpenAI to guide learners using an inductive approach. But despite impressive capabilities in many domains, even the largest and most advanced LLMs exhibit surprising failures, especially in math. If LLMs are prone to glaring mistakes befitting learning students themselves, how can they be expected to act as a trustworthy teaching tool by Khan Academy?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;ChatGPT 和大型语言模型的出现已经影响了教育。凭借好坏参半的结果和一系列道德可接受性，学生可以使用聊天调整的法学硕士来计划，作为研究的起点，编辑和建议文体或语法改进，甚至作为代笔撰写作业。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;著名的非营利性可汗学院提供自己的个性化导师，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.khanmigo.ai/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Khanmigo&lt;/a &gt; 与 OpenAI 合作开发，用于使用归纳法指导学习者。尽管在许多领域都拥有令人印象深刻的能力，但即使是最大、最先进的法学硕士也表现出令人惊讶的失败，尤其是在数学方面。如果法学硕士很容易犯适合学生本身的明显错误，那么他们怎么能成为可汗学院值得信赖的教学工具呢？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 19:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging Seekable OCI: AWS Fargate for Containerized Microservices】利用 Seekable OCI：AWS Fargate 实现容器化微服务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/seekable-oci-aws-fargate-for-containerized-microservices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS Fargate&#39;s Seekable OCI (SOCI) introduces significant performance enhancement for containerized applications by enabling lazy loading of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; container images. This reduces startup time for Fargate tasks, particularly for large container images, and makes it ideal for applications that need rapid scaling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS Fargate is a serverless compute engine that offers many different capabilities:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS Fargate 的 Seekable OCI (SOCI) 通过启用延迟加载 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker- ，显着增强了容器化应用程序的性能1&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; 容器镜像。这减少了 Fargate 任务的启动时间，特别是大型容器映像的启动时间，使其成为需要快速扩展的应用程序的理想选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS Fargate 是一个无服务器计算引擎，提供许多不同的功能：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【An Overview of TCPCopy for Beginners】TCPCopy 初学者概述</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/an-overview-of-tcpcopy-for-beginners</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With the rapid development of Internet technology, server-side architectures have become increasingly complex. It is now difficult to rely solely on the personal experience of developers or testers to cover all possible business scenarios. Therefore, real online traffic is crucial for server-side testing. TCPCopy [1] is an open-source traffic replay tool that has been widely adopted by large enterprises. While many use TCPCopy for testing in their projects, they may not fully understand its underlying principles. This article provides a brief introduction to how TCPCopy works, with the hope of assisting readers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The architecture of TCPCopy has undergone several upgrades, and this article introduces the latest 1.0 version. As shown in the diagram below, TCPCopy consists of two components: &lt;code&gt;tcpcopy&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;intercept&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;code&gt;tcpcopy&lt;/code&gt; runs on the online server, capturing live TCP request packets, modifying the TCP/IP header information, and sending them to the test server, effectively &#34;tricking&#34; the test server. &lt;code&gt;intercept&lt;/code&gt; runs on an auxiliary server, handling tasks such as relaying response information back to &lt;code&gt;tcpcopy&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着互联网技术的快速发展，服务器端架构变得越来越复杂。现在仅仅依靠开发人员或测试人员的个人经验很难覆盖所有可能的业务场景。因此，真实的在线流量对于服务器端测试至关重要。 TCPCopy[1]是一种开源流量重放工具，已被大型企业广泛采用。虽然许多人在项目中使用 TCPCopy 进行测试，但他们可能并不完全理解其底层原理。本文简单介绍了TCPCopy的工作原理，希望对读者有所帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;架构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TCPCopy的架构经历了多次升级，本文介绍最新的1.0版本。如下图所示，TCPCopy 由两个组件组成：&lt;code&gt;tcpcopy&lt;/code&gt; 和 &lt;code&gt;intercept&lt;/code&gt;。 &lt;code&gt;tcpcopy&lt;/code&gt;运行在在线服务器上，捕获实时TCP请求数据包，修改TCP/IP头信息，并发送给测试服务器，有效“欺骗”测试服务器。 &lt;code&gt;intercept&lt;/code&gt; 在辅助服务器上运行，处理诸如将响应信息中继回 &lt;code&gt;tcpcopy&lt;/code&gt; 等任务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Augmenting the Client With HTMX】使用 HTMX 增强客户端</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/augmenting-the-client-with-htmx</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This post is part of a series comparing different ways to implement asynchronous requests on the client to augment the latter. So far, I described the process with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/augmenting-the-client-with-vuejs&#34;&gt;Vue.js&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/augmenting-the-client-with-alpinejs&#34;&gt;Alpine.js&lt;/a&gt;. Both are similar from the developers&#39; point of view: they involve JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, I&#39;ll focus on &lt;a href=&#34;https://htmx.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;HTMX&lt;/a&gt;, whose approach is quite different.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这篇文章是一系列比较在客户端上实现异步请求以增强后者的不同方法的一部分。到目前为止，我使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/augmenting-the-client-with-vuejs&#34;&gt;Vue.js&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https:/ 描述了该过程/dzone.com/articles/augmenting-the-client-with-alpinejs&#34;&gt;Alpine.js&lt;/a&gt;。从开发人员的角度来看，两者很相似：它们都涉及 JavaScript。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我将重点关注 &lt;a href=&#34;https://htmx.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;HTMX&lt;/a&gt;，其方法非常不同。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MariaDB Vector Edition: Designed for AI】MariaDB 矢量版：专为 AI 设计</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mariadb-vector-edition-hands-on-review</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As a solutions architect with over two decades of experience in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-look-at-the-history-of-rdbms&#34;&gt;relational database systems&lt;/a&gt;, I recently started exploring MariaDB&#39;s new Vector Edition to see if it could address some of the AI data challenges we&#39;re facing. A quick look seemed pretty convincing, especially with how it could bring AI magic right into a regular database setup. However, I wanted to test it with a simple use case to see how it performs in practice.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, I will share my hands-on experience and observations about MariaDB&#39;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-vector-databases&#34;&gt;vector capabilities&lt;/a&gt; by running a simple use case. Specifically, I will be loading sample customer reviews into MariaDB and performing fast similarity searches to find related reviews.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;作为一名在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-look-at-the-history-of-rdbms&#34;&gt;关系数据库方面拥有二十多年经验的解决方案架构师数据库系统&lt;/a&gt;，我最近开始探索 MariaDB 的新矢量版本，看看它是否可以解决我们面临的一些人工智能数据挑战。快速浏览一下似乎很有说服力，特别是它如何将人工智能魔法直接带入常规数据库设置中。但是，我想用一个简单的用例来测试它，看看它在实践中的表现如何。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我将分享我对 MariaDB &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-vector-databases&#34;&gt; 的实践经验和观察通过运行一个简单的用例来实现矢量功能&lt;/a&gt;。具体来说，我将把示例客户评论加载到 MariaDB 中，并执行快速相似性搜索来查找相关评论。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 18:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Network Guardians: Crafting a Spring Boot-Driven Anomaly Detection System】网络守护者：打造 Spring Boot 驱动的异常检测系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/craft-a-spring-boot-driven-anomaly-detection-system</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We’re going to set out on a mind-blowing tour around network security. Upon considering the nearness and risk posed by cyber threats in this epoch, it is important to prevent the threats so that they do not cause irreversible damage within the network. This three-part article series will take you through the process of developing a network anomaly detection system using the Spring Boot framework in a robust manner. The series is organized as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 1:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;We’ll concentrate on the foundation and basic structure of our detection system, which has to be created.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 2:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The second volume deals with how to assist in controlling the diffusion of sensitive network information as it targets advanced techniques for actively monitoring the network at the present time.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Part 3:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;In the last part, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; methods will be applied to the developed system, including algorithms, which will increase the system&#39;s performance in terms of accuracy and ability to detect anomalies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By the end of this series, you will have acquired quite a lot of knowledge in developing a strong-based network anomaly detection system using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-nice-amp-easy-video-8&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt; and making use of technologies to improve your organization’s security level.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们将围绕网络安全展开一次令人兴奋的之旅。考虑到这个时代网络威胁所带来的临近性和风险，重要的是要预防这些威胁，以免它们在网络内造成不可逆转的损害。这个由三部分组成的文章系列将带您完成使用 Spring Boot 框架以稳健的方式开发网络异常检测系统的过程。该系列的组织如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 1 部分：&lt;/strong&gt;我们将专注于必须创建的检测系统的基础和基本结构。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 2 部分：&lt;/strong&gt;第二卷介绍如何协助控制敏感网络信息的传播，因为它的目标是当前主动监控网络的先进技术。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第 3 部分：&lt;/strong&gt;最后一部分将应用&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习&lt;/a&gt;方法开发的系统，包括算法，这将提高系统在准确性和检测异常的能力方面的性能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本系列结束时，您将获得使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-nice 开发强大的网络异常检测系统的大量知识-amp-easy-video-8&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt;并利用技术来提高组织的安全级别。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Custom Domains for HTTP/2 on Heroku】Heroku 上 HTTP/2 的自定义域</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/custom-domains-for-http2-on-heroku</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Several months ago, &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heroku.com/heroku-http2-public-beta&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Heroku announced HTTP/2 support&lt;/a&gt; from browser to router. This is pretty awesome, as it means our Heroku applications can now reap the benefits of multiplexing and stream prioritization. It looks like Heroku’s roadmap will eventually get HTTP/2 all the way to the dyno, which means we’ll get &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/grpc-basics&#34;&gt;gRPC&lt;/a&gt; down the road, too. Sweet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But, as I read the announcement more closely, I noticed something that’s worth paying attention to:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;几个月前，&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heroku.com/heroku-http2-public-beta&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Heroku 宣布了 HTTP /2 支持&lt;/a&gt;从浏览器到路由器。这非常棒，因为这意味着我们的 Heroku 应用程序现在可以获得多路复用和流优先级的好处。看起来 Heroku 的路线图最终将把 HTTP/2 一直带到 dyno，这意味着我们将使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/grpc-basics&#34;&gt;gRPC&lt;/a&gt;道路也是如此。甜甜的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;但是，当我更仔细地阅读该公告时，我注意到一些值得关注的事情：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Test-Driven Generation: Adopting TDD Again, This Time With Gen AI】测试驱动的一代：再次采用 TDD，这次是 Gen AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/test-driven-generation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;You know, over the past few years, software development has gone through some pretty exciting changes. New tools and methodologies have popped up, all aiming to make our lives easier, streamline processes, and boost code quality. One of the big players in this space has been &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Test-driven_development&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Test-Driven Development (TDD)&lt;/a&gt;. If you&#39;re not familiar, TDD is where developers write test cases for functionality &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; they actually write the code. It&#39;s a neat idea, but let&#39;s be real — TDD can be tough to get the hang of!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From my own experiences, I gotta admit: TDD is hard! It demands time, practice, and a whole lot of discipline to master. But here&#39;s the thing — the rise of Generative AI is opening up some awesome new possibilities to make this technique even better. By combining 1) TDD, 2) Pair Programming, and 3) Generative AI, I want to introduce you to a new approach: &lt;strong&gt;Test-Driven Generation (TDG)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;您知道，在过去几年中，软件开发经历了一些非常令人兴奋的变化。新的工具和方法不断涌现，其目的都是为了让我们的生活更轻松、简化流程并提高代码质量。这个领域的主要参与者之一是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Test-driven_development&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;测试驱动开发 (TDD) &lt;/a&gt;。如果您不熟悉，TDD 是开发人员在实际编写代码之前编写功能测试用例的地方。这是一个很棒的想法，但让我们面对现实吧——TDD 可能很难掌握！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从我自己的经历来看，我必须承认：TDD 很难！它需要时间、练习和大量的纪律来掌握。但事情是这样的——生成式人工智能的兴起开辟了一些令人敬畏的新可能性，使这项技术变得更好。通过结合 1) TDD、2) 结对编程和 3) 生成式 AI，我想向您介绍一种新方法：&lt;strong&gt;测试驱动生成 (TDG)&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 14:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Operationalize a Scalable AI With LLMOps Principles and Best Practices】利用 LLMOps 原则和最佳实践实施可扩展的人工智能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llmops-principles-and-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Organizations are fully adopting Artificial Intelligence (AI) and proving that AI is valuable. Enterprises are looking for valuable AI use cases that abound in their industry and functional areas to reap more benefits. Organizations are responding to opportunities and threats, gain improvements in sales, and lower costs. Organizations are recognizing the special requirements of AI workloads and enabling them with purpose-built infrastructure that supports the consolidated demands of multiple teams across the organization. Organizations adopting a shift-left paradigm by planning for good governance early in the AI process will minimize AI efforts for data movement to accelerate model development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In an era of rapidly evolving AI, data scientists should be flexible in choosing platforms that provide flexibility, collaboration, and governance to maximize adoption and productivity. Let&#39;s dive into the workflow automation and pipeline orchestration world. Recently, two prominent terms have appeared in the artificial intelligence and machine learning world: MLOps and LLMOps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;各组织正在全面采用人工智能 (AI)，并证明人工智能的价值。企业正在寻找其行业和功能领域中丰富的有价值的人工智能用例，以获得更多收益。组织正在应对机遇和威胁，提高销售并降低成本。组织正在认识到人工智能工作负载的特殊要求，并为其提供专门构建的基础设施，以支持组织内多个团队的综合需求。通过在人工智能流程的早期规划良好的治理来采用左移范式的组织将最大限度地减少人工智能在数据移动方面的工作，从而加速模型开发。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在人工智能快速发展的时代，数据科学家应该灵活地选择提供灵活性、协作和治理的平台，以最大限度地提高采用率和生产力。让我们深入了解工作流自动化和管道编排世界。最近，人工智能和机器学习领域出现了两个著名术语：MLOps 和 LLMOps。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating PMO Meetings With n8n Automation】使用 n8n Automation 自动化 PMO 会议</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-pmo-meetings-with-n8n-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s world data and time are two of the most valuable things. The power of data is always in the news, but what about time? There are a ton of operations that are still being done manually which can easily be automated. Today, I am going to talk about one of those manual tasks that take an eternity to be completed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, I am talking about the prep for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/10-project-manager-objectives-to-improve-performan&#34;&gt;PMO&lt;/a&gt; meetings. But you may ask: how can you automate it? Well, here is how I did it using n8n automation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今世界，数据和时间是最有价值的两个东西。数据的力量总是出现在新闻中，但时间呢？有大量操作仍然需要手动完成，但可以轻松实现自动化。今天，我将讨论一项需要花费很长时间才能完成的手动任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;是的，我说的是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/10-project-manager-objectives-to-improve-performan&#34;&gt;PMO&lt;/a&gt;会议的准备工作。但您可能会问：如何实现自动化？嗯，这是我使用 n8n 自动化的方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>