<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing AI-Generated Code: Preventing Phantom APIs and Invisible Vulnerabilities】保护人工智能生成的代码：防止幻像 API 和隐形漏洞</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/securing-ai-generated-code-preventing-phantom-apis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;740&#34; data-start=&#34;247&#34;&gt;The conference room went silent when the fintech&#39;s CISO pulled up the logs. There, buried in production traffic, sat an endpoint nobody had documented: &lt;code data-end=&#34;417&#34; data-start=&#34;399&#34;&gt;/api/debug/users&lt;/code&gt;. It was leaking customer data with every ping. The engineer who&#39;d committed the module swore he&#39;d only asked GitHub Copilot for a &#34;basic user lookup function.&#34; Somewhere between prompt and pull request, the AI had dreamed up an entire debugging interface — and nobody caught it until a pentester found it three months later.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;937&#34; data-start=&#34;742&#34;&gt;That incident, which happened at a Series B startup in Austin last spring, isn&#39;t an outlier anymore. It’s a preview of what happens when we let machines write code faster than humans can read it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;740&#34; data-start=&#34;247&#34;&gt;当金融科技的 CISO 调出日志时，会议室一片寂静。在那里，埋藏在生产流量中的是一个无人记录的端点：&lt;code data-end=&#34;417&#34; data-start=&#34;399&#34;&gt;/api/debug/users&lt;/code&gt;。每次 ping 操作都会泄露客户数据。提交该模块的工程师发誓，他只是向 GitHub Copilot 询问了“基本用户查找功能”。在提示和拉取请求之间的某个地方，人工智能设想了一个完整的调试界面——直到三个月后渗透测试人员发现它为止，没有人发现它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;937&#34; data-start=&#34;742&#34;&gt;去年春天在奥斯汀的一家 B 轮初创公司发生的这一事件已不再是异常情况。这是当我们让机器编写代码的速度比人类阅读代码的速度快时会发生什么的预览。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DevSecOps for MLOps: Securing the Full Machine Learning Lifecycle】MLOps 的 DevSecOps：保护整个机器学习生命周期</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devsecops-for-mlops-securing-the-full-ml-lifecycle</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I still remember the Slack message that arrived at 2:47 AM last March. A machine learning engineer at a healthcare AI startup, someone I&#39;d interviewed six months prior about their ambitious diagnostic model, was having what could only be described as an existential crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#34;Our fraud detection model just started flagging every transaction from zip codes beginning with &#39;9&#39; as high-risk,&#34; he wrote. &#34;We can&#39;t figure out why. It wasn&#39;t doing this yesterday. We&#39;ve rolled back twice. Same behavior. We think someone poisoned our training pipeline but we have no audit trail. No signatures. Nothing. We don&#39;t even know when the data changed.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我还记得去年 3 月凌晨 2:47 收到的 Slack 消息。六个月前，我就他们雄心勃勃的诊断模型采访了一家医疗保健人工智能初创公司的一位机器学习工程师，他正面临着一场只能被描述为生存危机的情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们的欺诈检测模型刚刚开始将邮政编码以“9”开头的每笔交易标记为高风险，”他写道。 “我们无法弄清楚为什么。昨天它没有这样做。我们已经回滚了两次。同样的行为。我们认为有人毒害了我们的训练管道，但我们没有审计跟踪。没有签名。什么都没有。我们甚至不知道数据何时发生变化。”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Aspects to Advisors: Design Modular Cross-Cutting Features with Spring AI】从方面到顾问：使用 Spring AI 设计模块化横切功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aspects-to-advisors-modular-cross-cutting-spring-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;938&#34; data-start=&#34;202&#34;&gt;In a nutshell, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/magic-of-aspects-how-aop-works-in-spring&#34;&gt;aspect-oriented programming (AOP)&lt;/a&gt; is a way of adding extra behavior to existing code without needing to change it. At its core, AOP is a programming paradigm that helps separate cross-cutting concerns (security checks, caching, transaction management, error handling, monitoring, logging, etc.) from the core logic of an application. By leveraging it, behavior that is needed in various layers or modules of an application is modularized and defined in a single place—an aspect—instead of being scattered across various components, which leads to duplicated and hard-to-maintain code or to a mix of business and infrastructure logic. With AOP, such concerns are written once and applied automatically whenever needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1406&#34; data-start=&#34;940&#34;&gt;Similarly to AOP, when it comes to Spring AI applications, interaction requests and responses can be intercepted, modified, or augmented on the fly by using the Advisors API. Specifically, when sending or receiving data to or from a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-llm-technology&#34;&gt;large language model (LLM)&lt;/a&gt; via a &lt;code data-end=&#34;1218&#34; data-start=&#34;1206&#34;&gt;ChatClient&lt;/code&gt; instance, existing or custom advisors may be plugged in, and well-defined actions can be performed either before or after passing the request or response further down the execution chain.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;938&#34; data-start=&#34;202&#34;&gt;简而言之，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/magic-of-aspects-how-aop-works-in-spring&#34;&gt;面向方面编程 (AOP)&lt;/a&gt; 是一种无需更改现有代码即可向其添加额外行为的方法。从本质上讲，AOP 是一种编程范例，有助于将横切关注点（安全检查、缓存、事务管理、错误处理、监视、日志记录等）与应用程序的核心逻辑分开。通过利用它，应用程序的各个层或模块所需的行为被模块化并在一个地方（一个方面）定义，而不是分散在各个组件中，否则会导致重复且难以维护的代码，或者导致业务和基础设施逻辑的混合。使用 AOP，此类关注点只需编写一次，并在需要时自动应用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1406&#34; data-start=&#34;940&#34;&gt;与 AOP 类似，对于 Spring AI 应用程序，可以使用 Advisors API 即时拦截、修改或增强交互请求和响应。具体来说，当通过 &lt;code data-end=&#34;1218&#34; data-start=&#34;1206&#34;&gt;ChatClient&lt;/code&gt; 实例向&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-llm-technology&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/a&gt; 发送或接收数据时，可以插入现有或自定义顾问程序，并且可以在将请求或响应进一步传递到执行链之前或之后执行明确定义的操作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Taming Reinforcement Learning Chaos: An MLOps Architecture for Experiment Management】驯服强化学习混乱：用于实验管理的 MLOps 架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/taming-reinforcement-learning-chaos-an-mlops-archi</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rl-agents-in-action&#34;&gt;Reinforcement learning&lt;/a&gt; (RL) has achieved superhuman performance in domains ranging from Go (AlphaGo) to complex robotics control. However, unlike supervised learning, where data is static, RL is dynamic. It relies on an agent interacting with an environment through massive trial and error.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For engineering teams, this &#34;trial and error&#34; nature creates a significant MLOps bottleneck. A single viable model might require hundreds of experiments, each with slight variations in reward functions, learning rates, or environment physics.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rl-agents-in-action&#34;&gt;强化学习&lt;/a&gt; (RL) 在围棋 (AlphaGo) 到复杂的机器人控制等领域取得了超人的表现。然而，与数据是静态的监督学习不同，强化学习是动态的。它依赖于代理通过大量试验和错误与环境交互。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于工程团队来说，这种“反复试验”的性质造成了重大的 MLOps 瓶颈。一个可行的模型可能需要数百次实验，每个实验在奖励函数、学习率或环境物理方面都有细微的变化。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Resilient API Consumption in Unreliable Enterprise Networks (TypeScript/React)】不可靠企业网络中的弹性 API 消耗 (TypeScript/React)</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/resilient-api-consumption-enterprise-networks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Enterprise networks are often noisy. VPNs, WAFs, proxies, mobile hotspots, and transient gateway hiccups can cause timeouts, packet loss, throttling, and abrupt connection resets. Designing resilient clients minimizes checkout/MACD friction, prevents duplicate actions, and keeps the UI responsive even when backends or the network are unstable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have a strong toolkit for making &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-are-events-api-calls&#34;&gt;API calls&lt;/a&gt;, but how do we make them safe for users and painless for developers? Which stack should we choose? How do we cut duplication and keep code maintainable at enterprise scale? These questions matter when you have hundreds of endpoints: some triggered by CTAs, some on page load, others quietly prefetching data in the background, and a few that need streaming. There’s no one-size-fits-all — each job has a best-fit approach.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;企业网络通常很嘈杂。 VPN、WAF、代理、移动热点和短暂的网关故障可能会导致超时、数据包丢失、限制和连接突然重置。设计有弹性的客户端可以最大限度地减少结帐/MACD 摩擦，防止重复操作，并在后端或网络不稳定时保持 UI 响应。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们有一个强大的工具包来进行 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-are-events-api-calls&#34;&gt;API 调用&lt;/a&gt;，但我们如何确保它们对用户来说是安全的，对开发人员来说是轻松的？我们应该选择哪个堆栈？我们如何减少重复并使代码在企业范围内保持可维护性？当您有数百个端点时，这些问题很重要：一些由 CTA 触发，一些在页面加载，另一些在后台悄悄预取数据，还有一些需要流式传输。没有一刀切的方法——每项工作都有最适合的方法。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Time Recommendation AI Architecture: Streaming Events and On-Device Ranking】实时推荐人工智能架构：流媒体事件和设备上排名</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-recommendation-ai-architecture-streaming</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;You log in, browse, maybe buy something, and the app keeps showing basically the same items. Personalization is driven by a nightly batch job in the backend, and recommendation calls are slow trips to a cloud service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern apps need recommendations that react to behavior in seconds, not days — and still feel snappy and private on flaky mobile networks.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您登录、浏览、也许购买一些东西，应用程序会不断显示基本相同的商品。个性化是由后端每晚的批处理作业驱动的，而推荐调用是对云服务的缓慢访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代应用需要能够在几秒钟而不是几天内对行为做出反应的建议，并且在不稳定的移动网络上仍然感觉敏捷和私密。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【9 Tips for Building Apps to Withstand AI-Driven Bot Attacks】构建应用程序抵御 AI 驱动的机器人攻击的 9 个技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-bot-attack-app-tips</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;DDoS and other bot-driven cyberattacks don’t seem to be going away. If anything, the rise of AI is making them harder to thwart, turning bot protection into a new challenge for security-minded software development teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recent industry studies indicate that AI bot traffic &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/akamai-research-ai-bots-threaten-the-foundation-of-web-based-business-models-302603734.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;surged over 300%&lt;/a&gt; last year, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20250415432215/en/Artificial-Intelligence-Fuels-Rise-of-Hard-to-Detect-Bots-That-Now-Make-up-More-Than-Half-of-Global-Internet-Traffic-According-to-the-2025-Imperva-Bad-Bot-Report&#34;&gt;37% of all internet traffic&lt;/a&gt; was attributed to malicious bots. Stopping AI-powered bot attacks is hardly a straightforward undertaking. The simplest move is just to block all &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/non-human-identity-security-in-the-age-of-ai&#34;&gt;AI-driven requests&lt;/a&gt;, but that’s not an option, as many have legitimate use cases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;DDoS 和其他机器人驱动的网络攻击似乎不会消失。如果说有什么不同的话，那就是人工智能的崛起使它们更难被阻止，从而将机器人防护变成了具有安全意识的软件开发团队的新挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近的行业研究表明，去年人工智能机器人流量&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/akamai-research-ai-bots-threaten-the-foundation-of-web-based-business-models-302603734.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;激增超过 300%&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20250415432215/en/Artificial-Intelligence-Fuels-Rise-of-Hard-to-Detect-Bots-That-Now-Make-up-More-Than-Half-of-Global-Internet-Traffic-According-to-the-2025-Imperva-Bad-Bot-Report&#34;&gt;占所有互联网的 37%流量&lt;/a&gt;被归因于恶意机器人。阻止人工智能驱动的机器人攻击并不是一件简单的事情。最简单的举措就是阻止所有&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/non- human-identity-security-in-the-age-of-ai&#34;&gt;人工智能驱动的请求&lt;/a&gt;，但这不是一个选择，因为许多请求都有合法的用例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Assist, Automate, Avoid: How Agile Practitioners Stay Irreplaceable】协助、自动化、避免：敏捷实践者如何保持不可替代性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/assist-automate-avoid-agile-practitioners</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR: The A3 Framework by AI4Agile&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Without a decision system, every task you delegate to AI is a gamble on your credibility and your place in your organization’s product model. AI4Agile’s A3 Framework addresses this with three categories: what to delegate, what to supervise, and what to keep human.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Future of Agile in the Era of AI&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s January 2026. The AI hype phase is over. We&#39;ve all seen the party tricks: ChatGPT writing limericks about &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/scrum&#34;&gt;Scrum&lt;/a&gt;, Claude drafting generic Retrospective agendas. Nobody&#39;s impressed anymore.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR：AI4Agile 的 A3 框架&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果没有决策系统，您委托给 AI 的每项任务都是对您的信誉以及您在组织产品模型中的地位的赌博。 AI4Agile 的 A3 框架通过三个类别解决了这个问题：委托什么、监督什么以及保持人性化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;人工智能时代敏捷的未来&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在是 2026 年 1 月。人工智能炒作阶段已经结束。我们都见过派对技巧：ChatGPT 写有关 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/scrum&#34;&gt;Scrum&lt;/a&gt; 的打油诗，Claude 起草通用回顾议程。没有人再印象深刻了。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Your Product Doesn’t Need Another AI Feature; It Needs an AI Guardrail】您的产品不需要其他人工智能功能；它需要一个人工智能护栏</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-your-product-needs-ai-guardrails</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;There’s a growing pressure in tech companies to “add AI” to every product or feature. Executives and stakeholders often ask for an “AI assistant” or a ChatGPT-style feature on every screen, assuming more AI automatically makes products better. But the truth is, the most important AI work right now isn’t building more AI, it’s designing guardrails around it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI isn’t magic. Left unchecked, it can quietly make products worse, frustrate users, and introduce risk. Before adding AI for the sake of AI, teams need a framework to decide where it adds value and where it doesn’t.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;科技公司在每项产品或功能中“添加人工智能”的压力越来越大。高管和利益相关者经常要求在每个屏幕上安装“人工智能助手”或类似 ChatGPT 的功能，假设更多的人工智能会自动使产品变得更好。但事实是，目前最重要的人工智能工作不是构建更多人工智能，而是围绕它设计护栏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能不是魔法。如果不加以控制，它可能会悄悄地使产品变得更糟、让用户感到沮丧并带来风险。在为了人工智能而添加人工智能之前，团队需要一个框架来决定哪些地方可以增加价值，哪些地方不能增加价值。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating AI-Enhanced Microservices in SAFe 5.0 Framework】将人工智能增强型微服务集成到 SAFe 5.0 框架中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-ai-enhanced-microservices-in-safe-50-f</link>
      <description>【&lt;h3&gt;Abstract&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The integration of AI-enhanced microservices within the SAFe 5.0 framework presents a novel approach to achieving scalability in enterprise solutions. This article explores how AI can serve as a lean portfolio ally to enhance value stream performance, reduce noise, and automate tasks such as financial forecasting and risk management.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The cross-industry application of AI, from automotive predictive maintenance to healthcare, demonstrates its potential to redefine processes and improve outcomes. Moreover, the shift towards &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decentralized-artificial-intelligence-the-future-o&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;decentralized AI models&lt;/a&gt; fosters autonomy within Agile Release Trains, eliminating bottlenecks and enabling seamless adaptation to changing priorities. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devops-trends-2024-business-impact&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AI-augmented DevOps&lt;/a&gt; challenges the traditional paradigms, offering richer, more actionable insights throughout the lifecycle. Despite hurdles in transitioning to microservices, the convergence of AI and microservices promises dynamic, self-adjusting systems crucial for maintaining competitive advantage in a digital landscape.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h3&gt;摘要&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SAFe 5.0 框架中人工智能增强型微服务的集成提供了一种在企业解决方案中实现可扩展性的新颖方法。本文探讨了人工智能如何充当精益投资组合的盟友，以提高价值流绩效、减少噪音以及自动化财务预测和风险管理等任务。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从汽车预测性维护到医疗保健，人工智能的跨行业应用展示了其重新定义流程和改善结果的潜力。此外，向&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decentralized-artificial-intelligence-the-future-o&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;去中心化人工智能模型&lt;/a&gt;的转变促进了敏捷发布列车的自主性，消除了瓶颈，并能够无缝适应不断变化的优先事项。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devops-trends-2024-business-impact&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AI 增强型 DevOps&lt;/a&gt; 挑战传统范式，在整个生命周期中提供更丰富、更可行的见解。尽管向微服务过渡存在障碍，但人工智能和微服务的融合有望带来动态、自我调整的系统，这对于在数字环境中保持竞争优势至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>