<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Driven Alpha: Building Equity Models That Survive Emerging Markets】人工智能驱动的阿尔法：建立在新兴市场中生存的股票模型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-driven-alpha-building-equity-models-survive-markets</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence is now embedded into nearly every corner of modern financial markets. From reinforcement learning systems optimizing order execution to deep learning models parsing thousands of quarterly transcripts in seconds, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/quality-engineering-design-for-ai-platform-adoption&#34;&gt;AI adoption&lt;/a&gt; in equities has become mainstream. However, the story becomes more complicated once these tools leave controlled environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A model that performs elegantly in a backtest built on U.S. equities or European indices can falter within days when applied to markets with thinner liquidity, sharper retail flows, or policy-driven interventions. The real challenge isn&#39;t whether AI works — it clearly does — but whether the way we engineer AI makes it capable of surviving unpredictable market conditions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能现已融入现代金融市场的几乎每个角落。从优化订单执行的强化学习系统到在几秒钟内解析数千份季度记录的深度学习模型，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/quality-engineering-design-for-ai-platform-adoption&#34;&gt;人工智能采用&lt;/a&gt;在股票领域已成为主流。然而，一旦这些工具离开受控环境，情况就会变得更加复杂。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在基于美国股票或欧洲指数的回溯测试中表现良好的模型，在应用于流动性较弱、零售流量较大或政策驱动的干预的市场时，可能会在几天内变得不稳定。真正的挑战不是人工智能是否有效——它显然有效——而是我们设计人工智能的方式是否使其能够在不可预测的市场条件下生存。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing Java Web Services That Recover From Failure Instead of Breaking Under Load】设计能够从故障中恢复而不是在负载下崩溃的 Java Web 服务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/design-java-web-services-that-recover-from-failure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Web applications depend on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/supercharge-your-java-apps-with-ai&#34;&gt;Java-based services&lt;/a&gt; more than ever. Every request that comes from a browser, a mobile app, or an API client eventually reaches a backend service that must respond quickly and consistently. When traffic increases or a dependency slows down, many Java services fail in ways that are subtle at first and catastrophic later. A delay becomes a backlog. A backlog becomes a timeout. A timeout becomes a full service outage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The goal of a reliable web service is not to avoid every failure. The real goal is to recover from failure fast enough that users never notice. What matters is graceful recovery.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Web 应用程序比以往任何时候都更加依赖&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/supercharge-your-java-apps-with-ai&#34;&gt;基于 Java 的服务&lt;/a&gt;。来自浏览器、移动应用程序或 API 客户端的每个请求最终都会到达必须快速且一致地响应的后端服务。当流量增加或依赖性减慢时，许多 Java 服务会以起初微妙、后来灾难性的方式失败。延误就会变成积压。积压变成了超时。超时会导致全面服务中断。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;可靠网络服务的目标并不是避免每次失败。真正的目标是从故障中恢复得足够快，以至于用户不会注意到。重要的是优雅的恢复。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reproducibility as a Competitive Edge: Why Minimal Config Beats Complex Install Scripts】可重复性作为竞争优势：为什么最小配置胜过复杂安装脚本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/reproducibility-as-a-competitive-edge-minimal-config</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;The Reproducibility Problem&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Software teams consistently underestimate &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reproducible-builds-in-java&#34;&gt;reproducibility&lt;/a&gt; until builds fail inconsistently, environments drift, and install scripts become unmaintainable. In enterprise contexts, these failures translate directly into lost time, higher costs, and eroded trust.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Complex install scripts promise flexibility but deliver fragility. They accumulate technical debt, introduce subtle environment variations, and create debugging nightmares that consume developer productivity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;再现性问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;软件团队始终低估&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reproducible-builds-in-java&#34;&gt;可重复性&lt;/a&gt;，直到构建不一致失败、环境漂移以及安装脚本变得无法维护。在企业环境中，这些失败会直接转化为时间损失、成本上升和信任受损。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;复杂的安装脚本保证了灵活性，但也带来了脆弱性。它们会积累技术债务，引入微妙的环境变化，并造成调试噩梦，从而消耗开发人员的生产力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Achieve and Maintain Cloud Compliance With System Initiative】如何通过系统计划实现并保持云合规性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/achieve-maintain-cloud-compliance-with-system-initiative</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If you’re responsible for keeping a production cloud stack both fast and compliant, you already know that compliance is rarely an engineering problem at first. It usually shows up later — as tickets, spreadsheets, and audits — long after the infrastructure has already been built. With &lt;strong&gt;System Initiative&lt;/strong&gt;, compliance becomes something you design into your infrastructure model from day one, verify continuously, and prove on demand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;System Initiative builds a live &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/digital-twins-reborn-as-ai-fulfills-iot-promise&#34;&gt;digital twin&lt;/a&gt; of your infrastructure and lets you express policy at three layers: native cloud policy, component-level qualifications, and high-level control documents evaluated by AI agents. Together, these layers provide preventive guardrails, continuous detection, and real-time audit evidence — without bolting on yet another brittle toolchain.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果您负责保持生产云堆栈快速且合规，那么您已经知道合规性一开始很少是工程问题。它通常会在基础设施建成很久之后才以票据、电子表格和审计的形式出现。通过&lt;strong&gt;系统计划&lt;/strong&gt;，合规性成为您从第一天起就设计到基础设施模型中、持续验证并按需证明的内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;System Initiative 构建基础设施的实时&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/digital-twins-reborn-as-ai-fulfills-iot-promise&#34;&gt;数字孪生&lt;/a&gt;，并让您可以在三个层面上表达策略：本机云策略、组件级资格以及由 AI 代理评估的高级控制文档。这些层共同提供预防性护栏、持续检测和实时审计证据，而无需附加另一个脆弱的工具链。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI SDLC Transformation, Part 2: How to Measure Impact (and Avoid Vanity Metrics)】AI SDLC 转型，第 2 部分：如何衡量影响（并避免虚荣指标）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-sdlc-measure-impact-avoid-vanity-metrics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When organizations begin adopting AI across their software delivery lifecycle, the first question is always the same: “&lt;em&gt;How do we measure success?&lt;/em&gt;” It sounds straightforward, but it’s one of the hardest parts of the transformation. What looks like success on a dashboard often hides the real story underneath.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Most teams still rely on familiar &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-complete-guide-to-sdlc&#34;&gt;SDLC&lt;/a&gt; metrics: velocity, cycle time, and defect counts. These numbers look objective, but in AI-driven delivery, they become vanity metrics when interpreted the old way. They show motion, not progress.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;当组织开始在其软件交付生命周期中采用人工智能时，第一个问题始终是相同的：“&lt;em&gt;我们如何衡量成功？&lt;/em&gt;”这听起来很简单，但却是转型中最困难的部分之一。仪表板上看似成功的事情往往隐藏着真正的故事。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;大多数团队仍然依赖熟悉的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-complete-guide-to-sdlc&#34;&gt;SDLC&lt;/a&gt; 指标：速度、周期时间和缺陷计数。这些数字看起来很客观，但在人工智能驱动的交付中，当以旧方式解释时，它们就变成了虚荣指标。它们显示的是运动，而不是进度。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agile Is Dead, Long Live Agility】敏捷已死，敏捷万岁</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agile-is-dead-long-live-agility</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Why the Brand Failed While the Ideas Won&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your LinkedIn feed is full of it: Agile is dead. They’re right. And, at the same time, they’re entirely wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The word is dead. The brand is almost toxic in many circles; check the usual subreddits. But the principles? They’re spreading faster than ever. They just dropped the name that became synonymous with consultants, certifications, transformation failures, and the enforcement of rituals.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR：为什么品牌失败而创意获胜&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;你的 LinkedIn feed 中充满了这样的内容：敏捷已死。他们是对的。而且，与此同时，他们完全错了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个词已经死了。这个品牌在很多圈子里几乎是有毒的。检查常用的子版块。但原则是什么？它们的传播速度比以往任何时候都快。他们只是放弃了这个后来成为顾问、认证、转型失败和仪式执行的代名词的名字。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【An Analysis of Modern Distributed SQL】现代分布式SQL分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/analysis-of-modern-distributed-sql</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor’s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone’s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-database-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Database Systems: Fusing Transactional Speed and Analytical Insight in Modern Data Ecosystems&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Distributed SQL merges traditional RDBMS reliability with cloud-native elasticity. The approach combines ACID semantics, SQL interface, and relational integrity with multi-region resilience, disaggregated compute-storage, and adaptive sharding.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2025 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-database-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;数据库系统：融合事务速度和分析洞察力现代数据生态系统&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;分布式 SQL 将传统 RDBMS 可靠性与云原生弹性融为一体。该方法将 ACID 语义、SQL 接口和关系完整性与多区域弹性、分解计算存储和自适应分片相结合。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top 5 Tips to Shrink and Secure Docker Images】缩小和保护 Docker 镜像的 5 个重要技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/shrink-secure-docker-images-top-tips</link>
      <description>【&lt;section name=&#34;b855&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;71fe&#34;&gt;I used to settle for Docker images that were massive, sometimes in GBs. I realized that every megabyte matters, impacting everything from deployment speed and cloud costs to security. With time, I realize there are well-known best practices and advanced techniques to achieve the ultimate goal: a tiny, hardened 10 MB image.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;6b11&#34;&gt;Here’s my comprehensive guide on how I achieve this using minimal base images, mastering layers, and implementing strong security protocols.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;节名称=“b855”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;71fe&#34;&gt;我曾经习惯于使用巨大的 Docker 镜像，有时甚至达到 GB 级。我意识到每一兆字节都很重要，它会影响从部署速度、云成本到安全性的一切。随着时间的推移，我意识到有众所周知的最佳实践和先进技术可以实现最终目标：一个微小的、硬化的 10 MB 图像。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;6b11&#34;&gt;这是我的综合指南，介绍如何使用最少的基础映像、掌握层和实施强大的安全协议来实现这一目标。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Prevent Quality Failures in Enterprise Big Data Systems】如何预防企业大数据系统中的质量故障</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/big-data-quality-failure-prevention</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-start-index=&#34;277&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern enterprises run on data pipelines, and the quality of these pipelines directly determines the quality of business decisions. Many organizations, a critical flaw persists: data quality checks still happen at the very end, after data has already passed through multiple systems, transformations, and dashboards. By the time issues finally surface, they have already spread across layers and become much harder to diagnose. This systemic lag directly undermines the reliability of mission-critical decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-start-index=&#34;796&#34;&gt;&lt;b data-start-index=&#34;812&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Solution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-you-need-medallion-architecture-clickhouse&#34;&gt;Medallion architecture&lt;/a&gt; (Bronze, Silver, Gold)&lt;span data-start-index=&#34;857&#34;&gt;, shown in the diagrams, has become a preferred approach for building reliable pipelines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-start-index=&#34;945&#34;&gt;. The true power of this architecture is the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b data-start-index=&#34;1027&#34;&gt;opportunity it creates for predictable data quality checkpoints&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span data-start-index=&#34;1090&#34;&gt;. By embedding specific quality checks early and consistently, data teams can catch issues immediately and explain changes to prevent bad data from moving downstream&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-start-index=&#34;1282&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-start-index=&#34;277&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;问题&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代企业运行在数据管道上，这些管道的质量直接决定业务决策的质量。许多组织仍然存在一个严重缺陷：在数据已经通过多个系统、转换和仪表板之后，数据质量检查仍然发生在最后。当问题最终浮出水面时，它们已经跨层扩散并且变得更加难以诊断。这种系统性滞后直接损害了关键任务决策的可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-start-index=&#34;796&#34;&gt;&lt;b data-start-index=&#34;812&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;解决方案&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-you-need-medallion-architecture-clickhouse&#34;&gt;Medallion 架构&lt;/a&gt;（铜牌、银牌、金牌）&lt;span data-start-index=&#34;857&#34;&gt;，如图所示，已成为构建可靠管道的首选方法&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-start-index=&#34;945&#34;&gt;。此架构的真正强大之处在于它为可预测的数据质量检查点创造了机会&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span data-start-index=&#34;1090&#34;&gt;。通过尽早并一致地嵌入特定的质量检查，数据团队可以立即发现问题并解释更改，以防止不良数据向下游移动&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-start-index=&#34;1282&#34;&gt;。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamlining Incident Management with IBM Cloud Logs, Event Notifications, and PagerDuty】使用 IBM Cloud Logs、事件通知和 PagerDuty 简化事件管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/streamlining-incident-management-ibm-cloud-logs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today’s fast-paced cloud environments, efficient incident management is crucial for reducing downtime and improving the customer experience. In this article, we’ll walk through a practical use case where a fictional company, &lt;strong&gt;ABC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ltd.&lt;/strong&gt;, leverages &lt;strong&gt;IBM Cloud Logs&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Event Notifications&lt;/strong&gt; to streamline their incident alerts to &lt;strong&gt;PagerDuty&lt;/strong&gt;, ensuring timely responses to critical events. We’ll also cover how to integrate notifications with &lt;strong&gt;Slack&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt; for different team members.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Use case: Managing application logs in a hybrid cloud environment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABC Ltd.&lt;/strong&gt; hosts its web application across multiple cloud regions, ensuring high availability for its global customers. Monitoring logs for errors and performance issues in real time is essential to maintaining uptime. To automate incident responses, they want:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今快节奏的云环境中，高效的事件管理对于减少停机时间和改善客户体验至关重要。在本文中，我们将介绍一个实际用例，其中一家虚构的公司 &lt;strong&gt;ABC&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; 有限公司&lt;/strong&gt; 利用 &lt;strong&gt;IBM Cloud Logs&lt;/strong&gt; 和&lt;strong&gt;事件通知&lt;/strong&gt;来简化向 &lt;strong&gt;PagerDuty&lt;/strong&gt; 发出的事件警报，确保及时响应关键事件。我们还将介绍如何为不同的团队成员将通知与 &lt;strong&gt;Slack&lt;/strong&gt; 和&lt;strong&gt;电子邮件&lt;/strong&gt;集成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;用例：在混合云环境中管理应用程序日志&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABC Ltd.&lt;/strong&gt; 在多个云区域托管其 Web 应用程序，确保其全球客户的高可用性。实时监控日志中的错误和性能问题对于维持正常运行时间至关重要。为了实现事件响应自动化，他们希望：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>