<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Event-Driven Chaos Engineering: From Failure to Resilience in Kubernetes】事件驱动的混沌工程：Kubernetes 从故障到恢复能力</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/event-driven-chaos-engineering-for-kubernetes-resilience</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Imagine a ship sailing through unpredictable seas. Traditional chaos engineering is like scheduling fire drills on calm days — useful practice, but not always reflective of real storms. Kubernetes often faces turbulence in the moment: pods fail, nodes crash, or workloads spike without warning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Event-driven chaos engineering is like training the crew with surprise drills triggered by real conditions. Instead of waiting for disaster, it turns every unexpected wave into a chance to strengthen resilience.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;想象一艘船在不可预测的海洋中航行。传统的混沌工程就像在平静的日子安排消防演习——有用的做法，但并不总是反映真正的风暴。 Kubernetes 经常面临当下的动荡：pod 失败、节点崩溃或工作负载在没有警告的情况下激增。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;事件驱动的混沌工程就像通过真实条件触发的突击演习来训练船员。不是等待灾难，而是将每一次意外的浪潮都变成增强韧性的机会。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Cybersecurity: Inside Google’s Gemini and Microsoft’s Security Copilot】人工智能驱动的网络安全：谷歌 Gemini 和微软安全副驾驶的内部</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-cybersecurity-inside-gemini-and-security-copilot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;934&#34; data-start=&#34;247&#34;&gt;The digital sphere keeps changing at a rapid rate, and cyber threats become more and more refined. With the growth of artificial intelligence (AI), tech giants are now embracing this revolutionary innovation to fortify their digital defences. In this area, leaders including Google and Microsoft have rolled out sophisticated AI-based cybersecurity systems: Google’s Gemini and Microsoft’s Security Copilot . Not only do these platforms improve threat detection and response, but they also drastically change the model for managing security in consumer and enterprise landscapes. This blog examines the recent developments in these tools and their implication for the future of cybersecurity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;971&#34; data-start=&#34;941&#34;&gt;Rise of AI in Cybersecurity&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1623&#34; data-start=&#34;973&#34;&gt;AI has become a game-changer in cybersecurity because it is capable of doing threat detection more quickly and accurately, automating repetitive functions, and allowing predictive analysis. Established security measures tend to be foundationally signature-based or require manual handling of incidents, slow to keep up with the fast advancement of modern threats. AI, on the contrary, is capable of analyzing enormous amounts of data in real time, detecting patterns, and adjusting to new forms of attack. Google and Microsoft have integrated AI into their systems to form potent security solutions for both the individual and the organization.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;934&#34; data-start=&#34;247&#34;&gt;数字领域不断快速变化，网络威胁变得越来越精细。随着人工智能 (AI) 的发展，科技巨头现在正在采用这一革命性创新来加强他们的数字防御。在这一领域，包括谷歌和微软在内的领先者已经推出了复杂的基于人工智能的网络安全系统：谷歌的 Gemini 和微软的 Security Copilot。这些平台不仅改进了威胁检测和响应，而且还极大地改变了消费者和企业环境中的安全管理模型。本博客探讨了这些工具的最新发展及其对网络安全未来的影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;971&#34; data-start=&#34;941&#34;&gt;人工智能在网络安全领域的崛起&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1623&#34; data-start=&#34;973&#34;&gt;人工智能已成为网络安全领域的游戏规则改变者，因为它能够更快速、更准确地进行威胁检测、自动化重复功能并允许进行预测分析。既定的安全措施往往基本上是基于签名的，或者需要手动处理事件，无法跟上现代威胁的快速发展。相反，人工智能能够实时分析大量数据、检测模式并适应新的攻击形式。 Google 和 Microsoft 已将人工智能集成到他们的系统中，为个人和组织形成有效的安全解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Taming the Storm: How Chaotic Exploration Shapes Big Picture Event Storming】驯服风暴：混沌探索如何塑造大局事件风暴</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/taming-the-storm-how-chaotic-exploration-shapes-bi</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Having delved into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/event-storming-workshops-a-closer-look-at-differen&#34;&gt;intricacies of event storming&lt;/a&gt;, its various types, and effective workshop facilitation, it’s now time to embark on our first practical example.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initial requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our customer requested that we implement a platform to support their training center. Although &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/smalaca/training-center-microservices?tab=readme-ov-file#high-level-requirements&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;the list of requirements&lt;/a&gt; they provided was somewhat limited, it gave us a starting point for our work:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在深入研究了&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/event-storming-workshops-a-closer-look-at-differen&#34;&gt;事件风暴的复杂性&lt;/a&gt;、其各种类型以及有效的研讨会促进之后，现在是时候开始我们的第一个实际示例了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;初始要求&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的客户要求我们实施一个平台来支持他们的培训中心。尽管他们提供的&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/smalaca/training-center-microservices?tab=readme-ov-file#high-level-requirements&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;要求列表&lt;/a&gt;有些有限，但它为我们的工作提供了一个起点：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Keywords: Modernizing Enterprise Search with Vector Databases】超越关键词：利用矢量数据库实现企业搜索现代化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/beyond-keywords-modernizing-enterprise-search-with</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the modern enterprise, data is everywhere — in emails, documents, customer records, support tickets, code repositories, and more. But as the volume and complexity of data grow exponentially, so does the challenge of finding the right information when you need it. Traditional search engines, based on keyword matching, are often frustrating and inefficient, returning irrelevant or incomplete results.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Fortunately, a new approach is transforming enterprise search:&amp;nbsp;semantic search powered by vector databases. By understanding&amp;nbsp;meaning&amp;nbsp;rather than just matching words, this technology enables organizations to unlock deeper insights and dramatically improve efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在现代企业中，数据无处不在 - 在电子邮件、文档、客户记录、支持票证、代码存储库等中。但随着数据的数量和复杂性呈指数级增长，在需要时找到正确信息的挑战也随之增加。基于关键字匹配的传统搜索引擎通常令人沮丧且效率低下，返回不相关或不完整的结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;幸运的是，一种新方法正在改变企业搜索：由矢量数据库提供支持的语义搜索。通过理解含义而不仅仅是匹配单词，该技术使组织能够获得更深入的见解并显着提高效率。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Level Up Your Engineering Workflow with Copilot Templates】使用 Copilot 模板提升您的工程工作流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/level-up-your-engineering-workflow-with-copilot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Software engineers often find themselves writing the same patterns of code again and again. Unit tests, API endpoints, error handling wrappers, and configuration files — these are essential parts of building robust applications, but they are also repetitive and time-consuming.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Enter GitHub Copilot. Many engineers already use Copilot as a “pair programmer” to autocomplete functions and suggest code snippets. But Copilot becomes far more powerful when you combine it with structured templates. Templates allow you to guide Copilot, enforce best practices, and generate high-quality, standardized code quickly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;软件工程师经常发现自己一次又一次地编写相同的代码模式。单元测试、API 端点、错误处理包装器和配置文件——这些是构建健壮应用程序的重要部分，但它们也是重复且耗时的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;进入 GitHub Copilot。许多工程师已经使用 Copilot 作为“结对程序员”来自动完成功能并建议代码片段。但是，当将 Copilot 与结构化模板结合使用时，它会变得更加强大。模板可让您指导 Copilot、实施最佳实践并快速生成高质量的标准化代码。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PostgreSQL Full-Text Search vs. Pattern Matching: A Performance Comparison】PostgreSQL 全文搜索与模式匹配：性能比较</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-full-text-search-vs-pattern-matching</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-full-text-search-vs-pattern-search&#34;&gt;previous article&lt;/a&gt; explains why PostgreSQL full-text search (FTS) is not a good candidate for implementing a general find functionality, where the user is expected to provide a pattern to be looked up and matched against the fields of one or multiple entities. Considering the previously explained technical challenges, it is clear that FTS is great for semantic and language-aware search, although it cannot cover raw searches in detail for various use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the field of software development, it isn’t uncommon for us to need to accept trade-offs. Actually, almost every decision that we make when architecting and designing a product is a compromise. The balance is tilted depending on the purpose, requirements, and specifics of the developed product so that the solution and the value delivery are ensured, and the customers are helped to accomplish their needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-full-text-search-vs-pattern-search&#34;&gt;上一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;解释了为什么 PostgreSQL 全文搜索 (FTS) 不适合实现一般查找功能，在该功能中，用户需要提供一种模式来查找并与一个或多个实体的字段进行匹配。考虑到前面解释的技术挑战，很明显，FTS 非常适合语义和语言感知搜索，尽管它无法详细涵盖各种用例的原始搜索。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在软件开发领域，我们需要接受权衡的情况并不罕见。事实上，我们在架构和设计产品时所做的几乎每一个决定都是一种妥协。根据所开发产品的目的、要求和具体情况倾斜平衡，以确保解决方案和价值交付，并帮助客户实现其需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Anypoint Mulesoft Masking Sensitive Data With DataWeave Custom Function in Logging】Anypoint Mulesoft 在日志记录中使用 DataWeave 自定义功能屏蔽敏感数据</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mulesoft-mask-sensitive-data-dataweave-logging</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When working with Mulesoft integration applications,&lt;strong data-end=&#34;41&#34; data-start=&#34;18&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;especially when exchanging data between services, APIs, or third-party applications. It&#39;s important to mask sensitive data while logging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Masking specific fields in payloads refers to the process of obfuscating sensitive information (like personal identifiers, financial data, or authentication tokens) before it&#39;s logged.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用 Mulesoft 集成应用程序时，&lt;strong data-end=&#34;41&#34; data-start=&#34;18&#34;&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;尤其是在服务、API 或第三方应用程序之间交换数据时。记录时屏蔽敏感数据非常重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;屏蔽有效负载中的特定字段是指在记录敏感信息（例如个人标识符、财务数据或身份验证令牌）之前对其进行混淆的过程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【We Tested Context7 With ZK Documentation: Here&#39;s What We Learned】我们使用 ZK 文档测试了 Context7：以下是我们学到的内容</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/testing-context7-with-zk-documentation</link>
      <description>【&lt;section itemprop=&#34;text&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;AI coding assistants have become increasingly capable in understanding not only code but also project-specific documentation. In this experiment, we tested Context7, a new MCP server, to see how well it could work with a large-scale, real-world documentation set — &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zkoss.org/documentation&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zkoss.org/documentation&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ZK Framework’s developer documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;For readers unfamiliar with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zkoss.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ZK&lt;/a&gt;, it’s a Java-based web framework that allows developers to build rich web applications with minimal JavaScript by providing server-side components. Because ZK documentation covers both UI and server-side concepts, it serves as a good benchmark for evaluating how AI models handle complex, domain-specific technical text.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;节itemprop =“文本”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;人工智能编码助手不仅能够理解代码，还能理解特定于项目的文档。在本实验中，我们测试了新的 MCP 服务器 Context7，以了解它与大规模的真实文档集配合使用的效果如何 - &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zkoss.org/documentation&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zkoss.org/documentation&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ZK Framework 开发者文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;对于不熟悉 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.zkoss.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ZK&lt;/a&gt; 的读者来说，它是一个基于 Java 的 Web 框架，允许开发人员通过提供服务器端组件，使用最少的 JavaScript 构建丰富的 Web 应用程序。由于 ZK 文档涵盖了 UI 和服务器端概念，因此它可以作为评估 AI 模型如何处理复杂的特定领域技术文本的良好基准。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DevEx Ambient Agent With Advanced Knowledge Graph】具有高级知识图的 DevEx 环境代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devex-ambient-agent-advanced-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;As developers, we all face friction points throughout the day — from repetitive tasks to sifting through documentation or getting stuck on a challenging bug. The Agentic DevEx Assistant was built to help with these challenges by acting as a developer’s co-pilot. Instead of just generating code, this tool works alongside you, proactively offering contextual assistance, automating common tasks, and helping you navigate your team’s collective knowledge.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;My aim is to reduce that friction, speed up feedback loops, and create a more efficient and enjoyable development environment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;作为开发人员，我们每天都会面临摩擦点 - 从重复性任务到筛选文档或陷入具有挑战性的错误。 Agentic DevEx Assistant 旨在通过充当开发人员的副驾驶来帮助应对这些挑战。该工具不仅仅是生成代码，而是与您一起工作，主动提供上下文帮助，自动执行常见任务，并帮助您驾驭团队的集体知识。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;我的目标是减少摩擦、加快反馈循环并创建一个更高效、更愉快的开发环境。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Ticking Time Bomb to Trustworthy AI: A Cohesive Blueprint for AI Safety】从定时炸弹到值得信赖的人工智能：人工智能安全的统一蓝图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agent-safety-blueprint-trustworthy-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The emergence of AI agents has created a &#34;security ticking time bomb.&#34; Unlike earlier models that primarily generated content, these agents interact directly with user environments, giving them freedom to act. This creates a large and dynamic attack surface, making them vulnerable to sophisticated manipulation from a myriad of sources, including website texts, comments, images, emails, and downloaded files.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The potential consequences are severe, ranging from tricking the agent into executing malicious scripts and downloading malware to falling for simple scams and enabling full account takeovers. This new reality of interactive agents renders traditional safety evaluations insufficient and demands a more comprehensive blueprint — one that connects foundational strategy to practical defense and scales through industry-wide collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能代理的出现制造了一颗“安全定时炸弹”。与主要生成内容的早期模型不同，这些代理直接与用户环境交互，赋予他们行动的自由。这创建了一个巨大且动态的攻击面，使它们容易受到来自无数来源的复杂操纵，包括网站文本、评论、图像、电子邮件和下载的文件。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;潜在的后果是严重的，从欺骗代理执行恶意脚本和下载恶意软件到陷入简单的诈骗并实现完全帐户接管。交互式代理的这一新现实使得传统的安全评估变得不够充分，需要一个更全面的蓝图——一个将基础战略与实际防御联系起来并通过全行业协作进行扩展的蓝图。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>