<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Improve Your Agile Processes With Artificial Intelligence】利用人工智能改进您的敏捷流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/improve-your-agile-processes-with-AI</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Implementing agile methodologies during the development of software applications has become an industry norm today. They allow the teams to develop better products through iterative cycles with the help of feedback.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;However, it should be mentioned that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agile-development-tutorial-comprehensive-guide-wit&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Agile&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt; has actually reshaped project management for the better, and at the same time, it is actually rather complex to master its processes. It is capital at its finest, which brings AI into play here. Everyone knows that artificial intelligence has revolutionized the way we execute Agile and makes our processes more efficient, adaptive, and data-driven.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:240,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:240}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;在软件应用程序开发过程中实施敏捷方法已成为当今的行业规范。它们允许团队在反馈的帮助下通过迭代周期开发更好的产品。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;但是，应该提到&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agile-development- tutorial-compressive-guide-wit&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;敏捷&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt; 实际上重塑了项目管理，使其变得更好，同时，掌握其流程实际上相当复杂。这是最好的资本，让人工智能在这里发挥作用。众所周知，人工智能彻底改变了我们执行敏捷的方式，使我们的流程更加高效、适应性强且由数据驱动。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;134233117&#34;:false,&#34;134233118&#34;:false,&#34;335551550&#34;:6,&#34;335551620&#34;:6,&#34;335559738&#34;:240,&#34;335559739&#34;:240}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Laravel vs. Next.js: What&#39;s the Right Framework for Your Web App?】Laravel 与 Next.js：什么是适合您的 Web 应用程序的框架？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/laravel-vs-nextjs-whats-the-right-framework-for-your-web-app</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;When it comes to building dynamic, scalable, and feature-rich web applications, selecting the right framework can make all the difference. Laravel, a PHP-based back-end framework, and Next.js, a React-based front-end framework, are two of the most popular choices among developers. While both are powerful in their domains, the question arises: which one is better for your project?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog, we’ll compare Laravel and Next.js, exploring their core features, strengths, weaknesses, and use cases. With detailed examples and code snippets, this article will help you decide which platform suits your needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;在构建动态、可扩展且功能丰富的 Web 应用程序时，选择正确的框架可以发挥重要作用。 Laravel（基于 PHP 的后端框架）和 Next.js（基于 React 的前端框架）是开发人员中最流行的两个选择。虽然两者在各自的领域都很强大，但问题来了：哪一个更适合您的项目？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本博客中，我们将比较 Laravel 和 Next.js，探索它们的核心功能、优点、缺点和用例。本文通过详细的示例和代码片段，将帮助您确定哪个平台适合您的需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How and Why the Developer-First Approach Is Changing the Observability Landscape】开发者优先的方法如何以及为何改变可观察性格局</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-and-why-the-developer-first-approach-is-changing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Developers play a crucial role in modern companies. If we want our product to be successful, we need to have a developer-first approach and include observability from day one. Read on to understand why.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The World Has Changed&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many things have changed in the last decade. In our quest for greater scalability, resilience, and flexibility within the digital infrastructure of our organization, there has been a strategic pivot away from traditional monolithic application architectures towards embracing modern software engineering practices such as microservices architecture coupled with cloud-native applications. This shift acknowledges that in today&#39;s fast-paced technological landscape, building isolated and independently deployable services offers significant advantages over the legacy of intertwined codebases characteristic of monolithic systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;开发人员在现代公司中发挥着至关重要的作用。如果我们希望我们的产品取得成功，我们需要采用开发人员优先的方法，并从第一天起就包括可观察性。请继续阅读以了解原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;世界已经改变&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去十年里，很多事情都发生了变化。在我们组织的数字基础设施中寻求更大的可扩展性、弹性和灵活性的过程中，我们的战略重点是从传统的整体应用程序架构转向采用现代软件工程实践，例如微服务架构与云原生应用程序相结合。这种转变承认，在当今快节奏的技术环境中，构建独立且可独立部署的服务比单一系统的相互交织的代码库特征具有显着的优势。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enabling Behavior-Driven Service Discovery: A Lightweight Approach to Augment Java Factory Design Pattern】启用行为驱动的服务发现：增强 Java 工厂设计模式的轻量级方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enabling-behaviour-driven-service-discovery-a-ligh</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-the-factory-pattern&#34;&gt;Factory Pattern&lt;/a&gt; is one of the popular creational design patterns in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;. It provides a single access point to obtain the suitable implementation of a service that is exposed as an abstract class or interface by using a service identifier that’s often the shorthand name of the implementation type and represented by a String or Enum. This pattern is used to create objects without specifying the exact class of object that will be created in the runtime and many of the frameworks and Java APIs developers come across every day use this pattern.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article aims to augment the design pattern to provide better readability and maintainability. It illustrates how the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservices-architectures-what-is-service-discov&#34;&gt;service discovery&lt;/a&gt; is automated by the proposed approach without requiring the factory method to manually accommodate code for the creation of a new service implementation every time a new service implementation is created for a different business need. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-the-factory-pattern&#34;&gt;工厂模式&lt;/a&gt;是&lt;a href=&#34;https: //dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;。它提供了一个单一的访问点来获取服务的适当实现，该服务通过使用服务标识符公开为抽象类或接口，该服务标识符通常是实现类型的简写名称并由字符串或枚举表示。此模式用于创建对象，而无需指定将在运行时创建的确切对象类，并且许多框架和 Java API 开发人员每天都会遇到使用此模式的情况。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文旨在增强设计模式以提供更好的可读性和可维护性。它说明了如何通过所提出的方法自动化&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservices-architectures-what-is-service-discov&#34;&gt;服务发现&lt;/a&gt;，而不需要工厂方法每次为不同的业务需求创建新的服务实现时，手动调整用于创建新服务实现的代码。   &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Which Flow Is Best for Your Data Needs: Time Series vs. Streaming Databases】哪种流程最适合您的数据需求：时间序列与流数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/time-series-vs-streaming-databases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Data is being generated from various sources, including electronic devices, machines, and social media, across all industries. However, unless it is processed and stored effectively, it holds little value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A significant evolution is taking place in the way data is organized for further analysis. Some databases prioritize organizing data based on its time of generation, while others focus on different functionalities.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据是从各个行业的各种来源生成的，包括电子设备、机器和社交媒体。然而，除非得到有效的处理和存储，否则它没有什么价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用于进一步分析的数据组织方式正在发生重大演变。一些数据库根据数据的生成时间优先组织数据，而其他数据库则侧重于不同的功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Idempotency and Reliability in Event-Driven Systems: A Practical Guide】事件驱动系统中的幂等性和可靠性：实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/idempotency-and-reliability-in-event-driven-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction to Event-Driven Architectures and Idempotency&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;The Rise of Event-Driven Architectures&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern e-commerce systems often depend on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/event-driven-architecture-as-a-strategy&#34;&gt;event-driven architectures&lt;/a&gt; to ensure scalability and responsiveness. For instance, when a user places an order, events like &#34;Order Placed,&#34; &#34;Payment Processed,&#34; and &#34;Inventory Updated&#34; are triggered asynchronously. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Why Idempotency Matters in Distributed Systems&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-distributed-systems-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;distributed systems&lt;/a&gt;, events can be duplicated or retried due to network failures, leading to problems like duplicate orders or incorrect inventory adjustments. Idempotency ensures that processing an event multiple times yields the same result as processing it once. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;事件驱动架构和幂等性简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;事件驱动架构的兴起&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代电子商务系统通常依赖&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/event-driven-architecture-as-a-strategy&#34;&gt;事件驱动架构&lt;/a&gt;来确保可扩展性和反应能力。例如，当用户下订单时，会异步触发“订单已下”、“付款已处理”和“库存已更新”等事件。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;为什么幂等性在分布式系统中很重要&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-distributed-systems-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;分布式系统&lt;/a&gt;中，事件可能会因网络故障而重复或重试，导致重复订单或不正确的库存调整等问题。幂等性确保多次处理事件会产生与处理一次相同的结果。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Databricks 101: An Introductory Guide on Navigating and Optimizing This Data Powerhouse】Databricks 101：有关导航和优化此数据中心的入门指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/databricks-101-an-introductory-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In an era where data reigns supreme, the tools and platforms that businesses utilize to harness and analyze their data can make or break their competitive edge. Among these, Databricks stands out as a powerhouse, yet navigating its complexities often feels like deciphering cryptic code. With businesses generating an average of 2.5 quintillion bytes of data daily, the need for a robust, efficient, and cost-effective data cloud has never been more critical.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 808px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;419.5 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1731443061654&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;11/12/2024 08:24 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18035878-hero.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;419463&#34; data-name=&#34;hero.png&#34; data-id=&#34;18035878&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18035878-hero.png&#34; alt=&#34;Dev relaxing at desk&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we demystify Databricks, with a focus on Job Clusters. Readers will gain insight into the platform’s workspace, the pivotal role of workflows, and the nuanced world of compute resources including All-Purpose Compute (APC) clusters vs Jobs Compute clusters. We’ll also shed light on how to avoid costly errors and optimize resource allocation for data workloads.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在数据占主导地位的时代，企业用来利用和分析数据的工具和平台可以创造或破坏其竞争优势。其中，Databricks 作为一个强大的工具脱颖而出，但驾驭其复杂性通常感觉就像破译神秘的代码。随着企业每天平均生成 2.5 万亿字节的数据，对强大、高效且经济高效的数据云的需求变得前所未有的迫切。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 808px;&#34; class =“fr-fic fr-dib lazyload”data-image =“true”data-new =“false”data-sizeformatted =“419.5 kB”data-mimetype =“image / png”data-creationdate =“1731443061654”数据-creationdateformatted =“11/12/2024 08:24 PM”数据类型=“temp” data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18035878-hero.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;419463&#34; data-name=&#34;hero.png&#34; data- id =“18035878”data-src =“https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18035878-hero.png” alt=&#34;开发人员在办公桌前放松&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将揭开 Databricks 的神秘面纱，重点关注作业集群。读者将深入了解平台的工作区、工作流程的关键作用以及计算资源的微妙世界，包括通用计算 (APC) 集群与作业计算集群。我们还将阐明如何避免代价高昂的错误并优化数据工作负载的资源分配。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Solving Parallel Writing Issues in MuleSoft With Distributed Locking】使用分布式锁定解决 MuleSoft 中的并行写入问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/parallel-writing-issues-in-mulesoft-with-distributed-locking</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In MuleSoft applications running in &lt;strong&gt;multi-threaded&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;multi-worker environments&lt;/strong&gt;, the risk of &lt;strong&gt;parallel writing issues&lt;/strong&gt; arises when multiple threads or workers attempt to access or update the same shared resource simultaneously. These issues can lead to data corruption, inconsistencies, or unexpected behavior, especially in distributed systems where Mule applications are deployed across multiple workers in a cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Problem: Parallel Writing&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Let me illustrate the problem first. I created a simple &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nahidshahin/lock-poc/blob/main/counter/src/main/mule/counter.xml&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;counter application&lt;/a&gt; that supports &lt;code&gt;/inc&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;/get&lt;/code&gt; operations. The &lt;code&gt;/inc&lt;/code&gt; operation increases the counter by 1, and the &lt;code&gt;/get&lt;/code&gt; operation returns the current value.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在&lt;strong&gt;多线程&lt;/strong&gt;或&lt;strong&gt;多工作环境&lt;/strong&gt;中运行的 MuleSoft 应用程序中，当多个线程或工作人员时，会出现&lt;strong&gt;并行写入问题&lt;/strong&gt;的风险尝试同时访问或更新同一共享资源。这些问题可能会导致数据损坏、不一致或意外行为，尤其是在 Mule 应用程序跨集群中的多个工作进程部署的分布式系统中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;问题：并行写入&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;让我先说明一下问题。我创建了一个简单的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nahidshahin/lock-poc/blob/main/counter/src/main/mule/counter.xml&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; &gt;支持&lt;code&gt;/inc&lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt;/get&lt;/code&gt;操作的计数器应用程序&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;code&gt;/inc&lt;/code&gt; 操作将计数器加 1，&lt;code&gt;/get&lt;/code&gt; 操作返回当前值。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Seamless Single Sign-On: Design, Challenges, and Implementation】掌握无缝单点登录：设计、挑战和实施</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-seamless-single-sign-on</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Being a backend developer and having worked for years in the jungle of authentication and identity management, I can attest to the fact that implementing seamless SSO is often way more complex than it seems. I have witnessed how organizations struggle to integrate diverse applications, balance strict security requirements with user expectations, and maintain system performance across a heterogeneous enterprise environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I want to share what I have learned about the design of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identity-federation-and-sso-the-fundamentals&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SSO systems&lt;/a&gt;, understand the main protocols like OAuth2 and SAML, address challenges in integration (legacy infrastructures are the most tricky,) and eventually provide an authentication ecosystem that would balance the needs of security mandates with user convenience.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;作为一名后端开发人员，在身份验证和身份管理的丛林中工作了多年，我可以证明实现无缝 SSO 通常比看起来复杂得多。我亲眼目睹了组织如何努力集成不同的应用程序、平衡严格的安全要求与用户期望以及在异构企业环境中维护系统性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我想分享我所学到的关于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identity-federation-and-sso-the-fundamentals&#34; rel=&#34; 设计的知识noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SSO 系统&lt;/a&gt;，了解 OAuth2 和 SAML 等主要协议，解决集成挑战（遗留基础设施是最棘手的），并最终提供一个平衡需求的身份验证生态系统安全要求与用户方便。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Evolution of Software Architecture】软件架构的演变</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/evaluation-of-software-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In recent years, software architecture has evolved dramatically, reshaping the technological landscape and influencing development practices. From the early days of monolithic designs to today’s distributed microservices and serverless architectures, software architecture has shifted to accommodate the growing needs for scalability, resilience, and agility. This article dives into key elements in evaluating software architecture, guiding architects, engineers, and business stakeholders in choosing the best architectural approach for specific project needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Evolution of Software Architecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Software architecture began with structured programming, where applications were simple and the codebase relatively straightforward. As business demands grew, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-the-need-of-object-oriented-programming&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;object-oriented programming&lt;/a&gt; (OOP) introduced modular designs, allowing developers to encapsulate data and logic in classes and objects. This evolution continued with component-based software engineering (CBSE), which emphasized reusability and independent development cycles.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;近年来，软件架构发生了巨大的发展，重塑了技术格局并影响了开发实践。从早期的整体设计到今天的分布式微服务和无服务器架构，软件架构已经发生转变，以满足对可扩展性、弹性和敏捷性不断增长的需求。本文深入探讨了评估软件架构的关键要素，指导架构师、工程师和业务利益相关者选择满足特定项目需求的最佳架构方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;软件架构的演变&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;软件架构始于结构化编程，其中应用程序很简单，代码库也相对简单。随着业务需求的增长，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-the-need-of-object-oriented-programming&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;面向对象编程&lt;/a&gt; (OOP) 引入了模块化设计，允许开发人员将数据和逻辑封装在类和对象中。这种演变在基于组件的软件工程 (CBSE) 中得以延续，它强调可重用性和独立的开发周期。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>