<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【UX Research in Agile Product Development: Making AI Workflows Work for People】敏捷产品开发中的用户体验研究：让人工智能工作流程为人们服务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ux-research-in-agile-product-development-making-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;During my eight years working in agile product development, I have watched sprints move quickly while real understanding of user problems lagged. Backlogs fill with paraphrased feedback. Interview notes sit in shared folders collecting dust. Teams make decisions based on partial memories of what users actually said. Even when the code is clean, those habits slow delivery and make it harder to build software that genuinely helps people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI is becoming part of the everyday toolkit for developers and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-developers-and-ux-designers-should-work-togeth&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;UX researchers alike&lt;/a&gt;. As stated in an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/technology-media-and-telecommunications/our-insights/unlocking-the-value-of-ai-in-software-development&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;analysis by McKinsey&lt;/a&gt;, UX research with AI can improve both speed (by 57%) and quality (by 79%) when teams redesign their product development lifecycles around it, unlocking more user value.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在我从事敏捷产品开发的八年中，我看到冲刺进展迅速，而对用户问题的真正理解却滞后。待办事项中充满了经过释义的反馈。采访记录放在共享文件夹中，积满了灰尘。团队根据用户实际所说内容的部分记忆做出决策。即使代码是干净的，这些习惯也会减慢交付速度，并使构建真正帮助人们的软件变得更加困难。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能正在成为开发者和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-developers-and-ux-designers-should-work-togeth&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;用户体验研究人员&lt;/a&gt;的日常工具包的一部分。正如&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mckinsey.com/industries/technology-media-and-te communications/our-insights/unlocking-the-value-of-ai-in-software-development&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;麦肯锡分析&lt;/a&gt;中所述，当团队重新设计产品开发时，使用人工智能进行用户体验研究可以提高速度（提高 57%）和质量（提高 79%）围绕它的生命周期，释放更多的用户价值。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kotlin Code Style: Best Practices for Former Java Developers】Kotlin 代码风格：前 Java 开发人员的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kotlin-code-style-best-practices-for-former-java-d</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Many Kotlin codebases are written by developers with a Java background. The syntax is Kotlin, but the mindset is often still Java, resulting in what can be called &#34;Java with a Kotlin accent.&#34; This style compiles and runs, but it misses the core advantages of Kotlin: conciseness, expressiveness, and safety.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Common symptoms include:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;许多 Kotlin 代码库都是由具有 Java 背景的开发人员编写的。语法是 Kotlin，但思维方式通常仍然是 Java，这就是所谓的“带有 Kotlin 口音的 Java”。这种风格编译并运行，但它错过了 Kotlin 的核心优势：简洁、表现力和安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;常见症状包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Apache Spark 4.0: What’s New for Data Engineers and ML Developers】Apache Spark 4.0：数据工程师和机器学习开发人员的新增功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/apache-spark-40-whats-new-for-data-engineers-and-ml-devs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Undoubtedly one of the most anticipated updates in the world of big-data engines, the release of Apache Spark 4.0 is a big step in the right direction. According to the release notes, this shift involved closing more than 5,100 sprint tickets, facilitated by the negligence of over 390 active contributors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Machine learning and data engineering professionals, the new features of SQL, additional capabilities for Python, management of streaming states, and the newly introduced &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/beginners-guide-to-spark-concepts&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Spark Connect&lt;/a&gt; framework in Spark 4.0 will further reinforce the trend of high-performance, easy-to-use, scalable data analytics.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;毫无疑问，Apache Spark 4.0 的发布是大数据引擎领域最受期待的更新之一，它是朝着正确方向迈出的一大步。根据发行说明，由于 390 多名活跃贡献者的疏忽，这一转变涉及关闭 5,100 多份冲刺票。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;机器学习和数据工程专业人员、SQL 的新功能、Python 的附加功能、流状态管理以及 Spark 4.0 中新推出的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/beginners-guide-to-spark-concepts&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Spark Connect&lt;/a&gt; 框架将进一步强化高性能、易于使用、可扩展的数据分析的趋势。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Night We Split the Brain: A Telling of Control &amp;amp; Data Planes for Cloud Microservices】我们分裂大脑之夜：讲述云微服务的控制平面和数据平面</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/control-and-data-planes-for-cloud-microservices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;You know those pages you receive in the middle of the night? Not a full-blown fire, mind you, but rather a slow-burning panic? Let me tell you one of those stories that changed the way my team built software forever. It was 2 a.m., and the graphs looked bad. Not dead, mind you, but sick. Our microservices were still talking, but P95 latencies were rising high in the sky, like a lazy balloon. And retries were starting to cascade. The whole system felt like it was in a swamp.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;So what was the problem? A “&lt;strong&gt;safe&lt;/strong&gt;” configuration change to our API gateway, a new rate limit, and slight change of routing. It turned out that this change and a previous deploy of an unrelated service that occurred at least an hour earlier had collided in some silent serpentine handshake. The result was a slow, luscious, and irresistible drain on performance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;您知道您在半夜收到的那些页面吗？请注意，这不是一场全面的火灾，而是一场缓慢燃烧的恐慌？让我告诉你一个永远改变了我的团队构建软件方式的故事。当时是凌晨 2 点，图表看起来很糟糕。请注意，不是死了，而是病了。我们的微服务仍在通话，但 P95 延迟在天空中不断上升，就像一个懒惰的气球。并且重试开始级联。整个系统感觉就像是在沼泽中一样。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;那么问题出在哪里呢？我们的 API 网关的“&lt;strong&gt;安全&lt;/strong&gt;”配置更改、新的速率限制以及路由的轻微更改。事实证明，这一更改与至少一小时前发生的一项不相关服务的先前部署在某种无声的蛇形握手中发生了冲突。结果是性能的缓慢、甜美且不可抗拒的消耗。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging AI-Based Authentication Factors in Modern Identity and Access Management Solutions】在现代身份和访问管理解决方案中利用基于人工智能的身份验证因素</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-based-authentication-modern-identity-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It is not an understatement that identity is the new perimeter. With cyberattacks on the rise across industries, from finance and governments to healthcare, the protection of user identities has become more crucial than ever before.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taking a look at some of the traditional authentication methods — passwords, PINs, security tokens, and basic biometrics, there is a need to innovate within this sphere. Since their inception, all these methods have formed the robust backbone of an effective Identity and Access Management solution. However, it is increasingly important to revamp these methods as cyberattacks become more widespread and increasingly sophisticated.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;毫不夸张地说，身份是新的边界。随着从金融、政府到医疗保健等各行业网络攻击的增加，保护用户身份变得比以往任何时候都更加重要。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;看看一些传统的身份验证方法——密码、PIN、安全令牌和基本生物识别技术，需要在这个领域进行创新。自诞生以来，所有这些方法都构成了有效身份和访问管理解决方案的强大支柱。然而，随着网络攻击变得更加广泛和日益复杂，改进这些方法变得越来越重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Lakehouse vs. Data Mesh: Rethinking Scalable Data Architectures in 2026】Data Lakehouse 与 Data Mesh：重新思考 2026 年的可扩展数据架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-lakehouse-vs-data-mesh-rethinking-scalable-da</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the last decade, the data ecosystem has changed immensely. Data warehouses, the core of analytics, faced issues with unstructured data and scaling. Meanwhile, early data lakes offered some level of flexibility, but poorly governed data and schema drift led to numerous problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, there are two new contenders to the data paradigm: the Data Lakehouse and the Data Mesh. Both are futuristic scalable data architectures, but each has a different approach to the core problem. In 2026, enterprises will continue to face the question of whether to modernize with a centralized Lakehouse or a decentralized Mesh.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在过去十年中，数据生态系统发生了巨大变化。数据仓库是分析的核心，面临着非结构化数据和扩展的问题。与此同时，早期的数据湖提供了一定程度的灵活性，但管理不善的数据和模式漂移导致了许多问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，数据范式出现了两个新的竞争者：Data Lakehouse 和 Data Mesh。两者都是未来的可扩展数据架构，但每种架构都有不同的解决核心问题的方法。 2026年，企业将继续面临是采用中心化的Lakehouse还是去中心化的Mesh进行现代化的问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why PostgreSQL Vacuum Matters More Than You Think】为什么 PostgreSQL Vacuum 比您想象的更重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-postgresql-vacuum-matters-more-than-you-think</link>
      <description>【&lt;h1&gt;Why PostgreSQL Vacuum Matters More Than You Think&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Keeping PostgreSQL fast and stable is not just about good schema design or indexing. One of the most overlooked pillars of database health is the Vacuum process. It is easy to ignore because it operates quietly in the background, yet it is crucial for long-term performance, storage efficiency, and even preventing database outages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will walk through why &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-performance-tuning&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Vacuum&lt;/a&gt; exists, what happens when it is neglected, and when it makes sense to tune or run it manually.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h1&gt;为什么 PostgreSQL Vacuum 比您想象的更重要&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;保持 PostgreSQL 的快速和稳定不仅仅是良好的模式设计或索引。数据库健康状况最容易被忽视的支柱之一是 Vacuum 过程。它很容易被忽视，因为它在后台安静地运行，但它对于长期性能、存储效率，甚至防止数据库中断至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将介绍 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-performance-tuning&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Vacuum&lt;/a&gt; 存在的原因、忽略它时会发生什么，以及手动调整或运行它何时有意义。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Pragmatic Paths to On-Device AI on Android with ML Kit】使用 ML Kit 在 Android 上实现设备端 AI 的实用路径</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/Permalinkpragmatic-paths-to-on-device-ai-on-android-with-ml-kit</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;There isn’t a single canonical way to add on-device AI to Android apps. Your ideal path depends on latency, privacy, UX, and maintainability. Google’s ML Kit gives you interchangeable building blocks — text recognition, barcode scanning, object/pose detection, translation, and more — that you can compose to fit your constraints. This guide lays out a pragmatic architecture, drop-in code, and a performance checklist you can ship in a sprint. The theme is intentional minimalism: pick one capability, wrap it behind a tiny interface, wire it to CameraX if needed, and iterate with metrics instead of speculative complexity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;885&#34; data-start=&#34;851&#34;&gt;When ML Kit Is the Smart Choice&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;1177&#34; data-start=&#34;887&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;912&#34; data-start=&#34;887&#34;&gt;On-device by default:&lt;/strong&gt; You get low latency, offline reliability, and strong privacy because images and text don’t need to leave the device for common tasks. This dramatically reduces legal/compliance risk and eliminates network tail latency that can frustrate users during capture flows.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;1401&#34; data-start=&#34;1179&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1210&#34; data-start=&#34;1179&#34;&gt;Production-hardened models:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The bundled models handle rotation, noise, motion blur, and imperfect lighting better than most “roll-your-own” attempts. You benefit from years of tuning without owning a training pipeline.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;1600&#34; data-start=&#34;1403&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1424&#34; data-start=&#34;1403&#34;&gt;Modular adoption:&lt;/strong&gt; Add exactly one capability at a time; you don’t need a model server, autoscaling, or a feature-flagged rollout of custom models. That simplicity keeps your blast radius small.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;1859&#34; data-start=&#34;1602&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1631&#34; data-start=&#34;1602&#34;&gt;Great Android ergonomics:&lt;/strong&gt; ML Kit works cleanly with CameraX, coroutines, and lifecycle components. That means less boilerplate and fewer foot-guns when you integrate with the camera stack, orientation changes, or backgrounding/foregrounding transitions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1879&#34; data-start=&#34;1861&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1877&#34; data-start=&#34;1861&#34;&gt;Common wins:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;目前还没有一种规范的方法可以将设备上的 AI 添加到 Android 应用中。您的理想路径取决于延迟、隐私、用户体验和可维护性。 Google 的 ML Kit 为您提供了可互换的构建块——文本识别、条形码扫描、对象/姿势检测、翻译等等——您可以根据自己的限制进行组合。本指南列出了实用的架构、插入代码以及可以在冲刺中交付的性能检查表。主题是有意的极简主义：选择一种功能，将其包装在一个微小的接口后面，如果需要，将其连接到 CameraX，并使用指标而不是推测的复杂性进行迭代。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;885&#34; data-start=&#34;851&#34;&gt;什么时候 ML Kit 是明智的选择&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;1177&#34; data-start=&#34;887&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;912&#34; data-start=&#34;887&#34;&gt;默认在设备上&lt;/strong&gt;：您可以获得低延迟、离线可靠性和强大的隐私性，因为图像和文本不需要离开设备即可执行常见任务。这极大地降低了法律/合规风险，并消除了网络尾部延迟，这种延迟可能会在捕获流期间让用户感到沮丧。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;1401&#34; data-start=&#34;1179&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1210&#34; data-start=&#34;1179&#34;&gt;生产强化模型：&lt;/strong&gt;捆绑模型比大多数“自己动手”尝试更好地处理旋转、噪点、运动模糊和不完美光照。您无需拥有训练管道即可从多年的调优中受益。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;1600&#34; data-start=&#34;1403&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1424&#34; data-start=&#34;1403&#34;&gt;模块化采用：&lt;/strong&gt;一次仅添加一项功能；您不需要模型服务器、自动缩放或带有功能标记的自定义模型的推出。这种简单性使您的爆炸半径很小。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;1859&#34; data-start=&#34;1602&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1631&#34; data-start=&#34;1602&#34;&gt;出色的 Android 人体工程学设计&lt;/strong&gt;：ML Kit 可以与 CameraX、协程和生命周期组件完美配合。这意味着当您与相机堆栈、方向变化或背景/前景过渡集成时，可以减少样板文件和脚枪。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1879&#34; data-start=&#34;1861&#34; style=&#34;margin-left: 40px;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;1877&#34; data-start=&#34;1861&#34;&gt;共同胜利：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Serverless Spark Isn&#39;t Always the Answer: A Case Study】无服务器 Spark 并不总是答案：案例研究</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-spark-isnt-always-the-answer-a-case-study</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Processing billions of records with strict latency requirements isn&#39;t a &#34;pick your favorite database&#34; problem. It&#39;s an architectural decision that will define system scalability, team velocity, and operational budgets for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The challenge involves multiple competing constraints:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;处理具有严格延迟要求的数十亿条记录并不是“选择您最喜欢的数据库”问题。这是一项架构决策，将定义未来几年的系统可扩展性、团队速度和运营预算。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;挑战涉及多个相互竞争的限制：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Encryption Alone Is Not Enough in Cloud Security】为什么云安全中仅加密还不够</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-encryption-alone-is-not-enough-in-cloud-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;645&#34; data-start=&#34;237&#34;&gt;It is often assumed that &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/fundamentals-of-cryptography&#34;&gt;encryption&lt;/a&gt; is the gold standard method for securing assets in the cloud. Cloud providers give assurances that all their services are “encrypted by default.” Several regulatory and cloud compliance policies mandate that organizations encrypt data at rest, in use, and in transit. All of this should make cloud environments secure, right? However, the reality is slightly more nuanced.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1020&#34; data-start=&#34;647&#34;&gt;Many breaches occur not because encryption algorithms are weak or because attackers can crack them. They occur because attackers never need to. Instead, attackers exploit other weaknesses. Access may be over-permissive, key governance may be poorly managed, configurations may be exposed, and there may be an overall lack of visibility into how data is actually being used.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;645&#34; data-start=&#34;237&#34;&gt;人们通常认为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/fundamentals-of-cryptography&#34;&gt;加密&lt;/a&gt;是保护云中资产的黄金标准方法。云提供商保证他们的所有服务都是“默认加密的”。多项监管和云合规性策略要求组织对静态、使用中和传输中的数据进行加密。所有这些都应该使云环境安全，对吗？然而，现实情况稍微微妙一些。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1020&#34; data-start=&#34;647&#34;&gt;许多漏洞的发生并不是因为加密算法较弱，也不是因为攻击者可以破解它们。它们的发生是因为攻击者从来不需要这样做。相反，攻击者会利用其他弱点。访问可能过于宽松，关键治理可能管理不善，配置可能会暴露，并且可能总体上缺乏对数据实际使用方式的可见性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>