<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Design Guards: The Missing Layer in Your Code Quality Strategy】设计后卫：您的代码质量策略中缺少层</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/maintainable-code-with-design-guards</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;795&#34; data-start=&#34;428&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In any fast-growing software team, the pressures of delivery often come at the expense of code quality. As codebases expand and contributors change in experience, inconsistencies naturally begin to surface: formatting mess, increasing complexity, duplication, and subtle design flaws. Over time, these small cracks lead to fragile systems and increasing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/agile-adoption-reducing-cost&#34;&gt;maintenance costs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1001&#34; data-start=&#34;797&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;To counter this, many engineering teams rely on few tools integrated into their development workflow. These tools are used to work on some repeated churns, but they sometimes have an outsized impact.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 795” data-start =“ 428”样式=“ text-align：left;”&gt;在任何快速增长的软件团队中，交付的压力通常以代码质量为代价。随着代码库的扩展和贡献者的经验变化，不一致自然开始浮出水面：格式化混乱，复杂性，重复和微妙的设计缺陷。随着时间的流逝，这些小裂缝会导致脆弱的系统，并增加&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/agile-adoption-reducing-cost-Cost”&gt;维护费用&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1001” data-start =“ 797” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;为了对抗这一点，许多工程团队依靠将几个集成到其开发工作流程中的工具。这些工具用于处理一些重复的流失，但有时会产生巨大的影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building an AI-Powered Text Analysis App With React: A Step-by-Step Guide】用React构建AI驱动的文本分析应用程序：逐步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-build-ai-text-analysis-app-react-vite-openai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, we will walk through the step-by-step implementation of an AI Text Analysis App using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/usestate-vs-useref-understand-the-technical-differ&#34;&gt;React&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/next-generation-front-end-tooling-vite&#34;&gt;Vite&lt;/a&gt;, and OpenAI&#39;s GPT-3.5. This app will allow users to input text and analyze it for sentiment, topics, summary, and language detection. By the end of this guide, even beginners will be able to build and understand this application. We will also explain each feature in detail and provide examples to ensure clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The AI Text Analysis App is a powerful tool that leverages OpenAI&#39;s GPT-3.5 to analyze text. It provides insights into the emotional tone of the text (sentiment), identifies the main topics, generates a concise summary, and detects the language of the input text. This app is built using React for the front end, Vite for fast development, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-tailwind-css-with-tailwind-merge-and-clsx?fromrel=true&#34;&gt;Tailwind CSS&lt;/a&gt; for styling.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在本文中，我们将使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/usestate-vs-vs-useref-useref-userf-understand-the-technical-differ“ href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/next-generation-front-end-tooling-vite-”&gt; vite &lt;/a&gt;和Openai的GPT-3.5。该应用程序将允许用户输入文本并分析其情感，主题，摘要和语言检测。到本指南的结尾，即使是初学者也能够构建和理解此应用程序。我们还将详细说明每个功能并提供示例以确保清晰度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; AI文本分析应用程序是一种强大的工具，它利用OpenAI的GPT-3.5分析文本。它提供了对文本情感语调（情感）的见解，标识了主要主题，产生简洁的摘要并检测输入文本的语言。该应用程序是为前端的React构建的，用于快速开发的Vite，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-tailwind-css-with-tailwind-tailwind-merge-and-merge-and-clsx?fromrel= fromrel=true”&gt; tailwind css &lt;/a&gt;用于样式。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DevOps at the Edge: Deploying Machine Learning Models on IoT Devices】边缘的DevOps：在物联网设备上部署机器学习模型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deploying-machine-learning-models-iot-devices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Edge computing is redefining how we deploy and manage &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/machine-learning-unleashing-the-power-of-artificia&#34;&gt;machine learning (ML)&lt;/a&gt; models. Instead of sending every data point to the cloud, DevOps at the edge brings model inference directly onto IoT devices — enabling low-latency predictions, offline operation, and improved privacy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, pushing AI to a fleet of heterogeneous, resource-constrained devices introduces new complexities. This article explores how DevOps practices can be applied to edge ML deployments on IoT hardware. We will discuss key tools, walk through a hands-on example of deploying a model to an IoT device with CI/CD, and address common challenges (model versioning, limited compute, intermittent connectivity) along the way.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;边缘计算正在重新定义我们如何部署和管理&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/machine-learning-unleashing-unleashing-the-power-the-power-oftificia”&gt;机器学习（ML）&lt;/a&gt;模型。 Edge的DevOps没有将每个数据点发送到云中，而是将模型推断直接推向IoT设备，从而实现了低延迟的预测，离线操作和改进的隐私。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，将AI推向一批异质，资源约束的设备的舰队引入了新的复杂性。本文探讨了如何将DEVOPS实践应用于IoT硬件上的Edge ML部署。我们将讨论关键工具，详细介绍将模型部署到具有CI/CD的物联网设备的示例，并沿途解决共同的挑战（模型版本管理，有限的计算，间歇性连接）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Machine Learning for CI/CD: Predicting Deployment Durations and Improving DevOps Agility】CI/CD的机器学习：预测部署持续时间并改善DevOps敏捷性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/predict-ci-cd-deployment-duration-using-ml</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;The speed and reliability of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-need-to-know-about-cicd-pipeline-pa&#34;&gt;CI/CD pipelines&lt;/a&gt; directly impact developer velocity and release quality. However, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/deploy-like-a-pro-mastering-the-best-practices-for&#34;&gt;deployment durations&lt;/a&gt; can vary widely due to factors like code complexity, pipeline structure, testing strategies, and environment configurations. This article explores how to build a machine learning regression model that predicts deployment time based on features derived from &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/cicd-with-containers&#34;&gt;CI/CD&lt;/a&gt; metadata, code metrics, and infrastructure events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Why Predict Deployment Duration?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Predicting deployment time can:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-need-to-need-to-know-about-cicd-pipeline-pa-&gt; ci/cd Pipelines &lt;/a&gt;直接影响开发者的速度和发行质量。但是，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/deploy-like-a-pro-mastering-the-best-practices-for”&gt;部署持续时间&lt;/a&gt;可能会因代码复杂性，管道复杂性，管道结构，测试策略和环境配置等因素而变化很大。本文探讨了如何构建机器学习回归模型，该模型根据&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/cicd-with-containers”衍生的特征来预测部署时间。&#xA;&lt;h2 data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []”&gt;为什么要预测部署持续时间？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;预测部署时间可以：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Trustworthy Is Big Data? A Guide to Real-World Challenges and Solutions】大数据有多值得信赖？现实世界挑战和解决方案指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-trustworthy-is-big-data-a-practical-guide-with</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Big data systems are growing in size, speed, and complexity — but the trust we place in them often lags behind. While engineers and analysts build pipelines to move petabytes of data, there&#39;s an unspoken assumption: that the data is clean, correct, and complete. Unfortunately, that assumption often breaks in production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From AI models trained on incorrect labels to business dashboards displaying misleading KPIs, untrustworthy data leads to real-world failures. In healthcare, it can misinform critical alerts. In e-commerce, it skews demand forecasts. And in finance, it triggers incorrect trades or noncompliance issues. That&#39;s why &lt;strong&gt;data veracity&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;— the accuracy and reliability of data — is not just a backend concern, but a business-critical one.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大数据系统的规模，速度和复杂性正在增长 - 但是我们对它们的信任经常落后。工程师和分析师构建了移动数据的管道，但存在一个不言而喻的假设：数据是干净，正确且完整的。不幸的是，这种假设经常在生产中破裂。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从在不正确标签上训练的AI模型到表现出误导性KPI的业务仪表板，不信任的数据导致现实世界中的失败。在医疗保健中，它可能会误导临界警报。在电子商务中，它要求预测。在金融中，它会触发不正确的交易或不合规问题。这就是为什么&lt;strong&gt;数据真实性&lt;/strong&gt;（数据的准确性和可靠性）不仅是后端问题，而且是关键业务的问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Unreasonable Effectiveness of the Actor Model for Creating Agentic LLM Applications】演员模型创建代理LLM应用程序的不合理效力</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/actor-model-agentic-llm-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Given the title we need to define what we mean by agentic applications and actors, and then we can move ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Agentic Applications (AAs)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This term seems to have many definitions as appearances in articles, so I&#39;ll add the one I am using here. I hope you&#39;ll agree it captures most of the important stuff:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;给定标题，我们需要定义代理应用程序和参与者的含义，然后我们可以向前迈进。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;代理应用程序（AAS）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个术语似乎有很多定义作为文章中的外观，因此我将在此处添加我使用的定义。希望您会同意它捕获大多数重要的东西：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【IBM App Connect Enterprise 13 Installation on Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)】IBM App Connect Enterprise 13在Azure Kubernetes服务（AKS）上安装</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ibm-app-connect-enterprise-installation-aks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This article describes how to install &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ibm-app-connect-ent-kerberos-auth-against-iis&#34;&gt;App Connect Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; 13 in an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-cluster-deploy-1&#34;&gt;Azure Kubernetes Service Cluster&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This document assumes you have a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-the-power-of-robust-kubernetes-clusters&#34;&gt;Kubernetes cluster&lt;/a&gt; in Azure Kubernetes Service running on Microsoft Azure cloud and it has access from your workstation. You should have kubectl configured to access the AKS cluster from a command line window. Verify the access to your cluster is working with the following command;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本文介绍了如何安装&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ibm-papp-connect-connect-ent-ent-ent-kerberos-kerberos-auth-against-iis”&gt; app app connect connect Enterprise &lt;/a&gt; 13在&lt;a a href =“服务集群&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;先决条件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文档假设您有一个&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-the-power-the-power-obust-robust-kubernetes-clusters”&gt; kubernetes群集&lt;/a&gt;在Azure Kubernetes在Microsoft Azure azure Cloud Cloud和IT上运行的Azure Kubernetes服务中，IT可以访问您的Workestation。您应该将kubectl配置为从命令行窗口访问AKS群集。验证对群集的访问正在使用以下命令; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Essential JVM Tools for Garbage Collection Debugging】基本的JVM垃圾收集工具调试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-gc-analysis-tools-overview</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Java garbage collection is a boon to programmers, but it can cause headaches in production. Poorly-tuned GC is extremely resource-hungry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tuning and troubleshooting GC is therefore an important skill. How do you obtain information on how GC is performing? What tools can you use to identify bottlenecks and inefficiencies?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Java垃圾收集对程序员来说是一个福音，但可能会引起生产的头痛。调整不良的GC是极其渴望的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;调整和故障排除GC是一项重要技能。您如何获得有关GC表现的信息？您可以使用哪些工具来识别瓶颈和效率低下？ &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Synergy of Event-Driven Architectures With the Model Context Protocol】事件驱动架构与模型上下文协议的协同作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/synergy-of-event-driven-architectures-with-mcp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In cloud architectures, two paradigms have emerged as pivotal in enhancing system responsiveness and AI integration, namely Event-driven architecture and the Model Context Protocol (MCP). While event-based systems have been instrumental in building scalable micro services, MCP represents a novel approach to standardizing interactions between AI models and external tools.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;While my previous article covers the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-services-mcp-a2a-ai&#34;&gt;evolution of cloud services&lt;/a&gt; for MCP/A2A Protocols, this article delves into the intricacies of the above-mentioned paradigms, exploring their individual contributions and the potential synergies when combined.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在云体系结构中，在增强系统响应能力和AI集成方面已经出现了两个范式，即事件驱动的体系结构和模型上下文协议（MCP）。虽然基于事件的系统在构建可扩展的微服务方面发挥了作用，但MCP代表了一种标准化AI模型和外部工具之间相互作用的新方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;While my previous article covers the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-services-mcp-a2a-ai&#34;&gt;evolution of cloud services&lt;/a&gt; for MCP/A2A Protocols, this article delves into the intricacies of the above-mentioned paradigms, exploring their individual contributions and the potential synergies when合并。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Provider-Agnostic OIDC Auth Flow for Your Apps (PyJWT + FastAPI)】您的应用程序（pyjwt + fastapi）的提供商 - 敏捷的OIDC验证</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/provider-agnostic-oidc-auth-flow-for-your-apps-pyj</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When building web applications, handling authentication securely and reliably is critical. That&#39;s where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/securing-your-cicd-an-oidc-tutorial&#34;&gt;OpenID Connect (OIDC)&lt;/a&gt; comes in. OIDC is a thin identity layer built on top of &lt;a href=&#34;https://oauth.net/2/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OAuth 2.0&lt;/a&gt;, and it gives your app the ability to verify who a user is and get some basic info about them, without the developer having to store passwords or build their own login systems from scratch. Things like passwords and access control will be managed by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/standardization-of-access-management-using-idp-fed&#34;&gt;Identity provider (IdP)&lt;/a&gt; thereby giving us a clear separation of responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, we will:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在构建Web应用程序时，安全可靠地处理身份验证至关重要。那就是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/securing-your-cicd-an-oidc-tutorial”&gt; openID connect（oidc）&lt;/a&gt;进来。OIDC是一个薄薄的身份层，建立在&lt;a href =“ href =”的顶部， target =“ _ blank”&gt; oauth 2.0 &lt;/a&gt;，它使您的应用程序能够验证用户是谁并获取有关它们的一些基本信息，而开发人员无需存储密码或从头开始构建自己的登录系统。诸如密码和访问控制之类的事情将由&lt;a a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/standardization-oc--occess-management-management-management-using-idp-fed”&gt; Identity提供者（IDP）&lt;/a&gt;，从而使我们明确地分离了职责。&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在本文中，我们将：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>