<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【What Is Voice AI and How Does It Work?】什么是声音AI，它如何工作？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-voice-ai-how-does-it-work</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;684&#34; data-start=&#34;360&#34;&gt;In a world where customer expectations are higher than ever, businesses are under pressure to deliver fast, personalized, and seamless support experiences. One technology rising to that challenge is &lt;strong data-end=&#34;571&#34; data-start=&#34;559&#34;&gt;Voice AI&lt;/strong&gt;—an AI-powered solution that enables machines to understand, interpret, and respond to human speech in real time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;835&#34; data-start=&#34;686&#34;&gt;But beyond the buzzwords, what exactly is Voice AI? What sets it apart from legacy IVR systems?&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;And why are more companies embracing it in 2025?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 684” data-start =“ 360”&gt;在一个客户期望比以往任何时候都高的世界中，企业承受着快速，个性化和无缝的支持体验的压力。这一挑战的一项技术是&lt;strong data-end =“ 571” data-start =“ 559”&gt;语音AI &lt;/strong&gt;  - 一种由AI驱动的解决方案，使机器能够实时理解，解释和对人的言论。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 835” data-start =“ 686”&gt;，但是在流行语之外，语音ai到底是什么？是什么使它与传统IVR系统区分开来？&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;为什么更多的公司在2025年接受它？</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Banish Anxiety, Lower MTTR, and Stay on Budget During Incident Response】如何消除焦虑，降低MTTR并在事件响应期间保持预算</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/banish-anxiety-lower-mttr-budget-incident-response</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Since I started in technology in 1992 (over three decades ago!), I’ve encountered countless scenarios where I was expected to “do more with less.” Whether it meant delivering more with fewer team members or working within constrained hardware resources, this mindset has been a recurring theme.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;One experience stands out from my time as a backend architect on a cloud modernization project. To reduce costs, we were asked to &lt;strong&gt;minimize or eliminate &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;service-level logging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;— logging that we relied on heavily for debugging and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/insights-from-incident-management&#34;&gt;incident analysis&lt;/a&gt;. The decision was driven by the high cost of log ingestion on our observability platform.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;自从我从1992年开始技术（三十多年前！）以来，我遇到了无数的场景，我期望“做更多的事情”。无论是意味着与更少的团队成员交付更多或在约束硬件资源中工作，这种心态一直是一个反复出现的主题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;一个经验从我作为云现代化项目的后端建筑师的时间中脱颖而出。为了降低成本，我们被要求&lt;strong&gt;最小化或消除&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;服务级记录&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;  - 记录我们依靠重大调试和&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articlecom/articles/articles/articles/insights-from-incights-from-incident-incent--ininsights-incint--ininsights-insights-insights-incent-incent-incent--incent-cant-ranagement-anteragement-antery Anallyspects&#39;&gt; indersancaight&gt;“&gt;”&gt;。该决定是由我们的可观察性平台上的原木摄入成本驱动的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Monitor and Optimize Node.js Performance】如何监视和优化node.js性能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-monitor-and-optimize-nodejs-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Node.js is a powerful, fast, and lightweight runtime environment to build high-speed apps. But its event-driven and single-threaded nature can cause performance bottlenecks. As a result, issues like memory leaks, CPU congestion, and slow performance may appear. However, there are some methods by which you can take this optimization to the next level.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this guide, we will talk about some popular methods to optimize a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/watch-a-writer-learn-nodejs-part-1&#34;&gt;Node.js app&#39;s performance&lt;/a&gt;, and for this, you don&#39;t need to hire Node.js developers, as you can apply these settings on your own.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; node.js是一个功能强大，快速且轻巧的运行时环境，用于构建高速应用程序。但是，其事件驱动的和单线程的性质可能会导致性能瓶颈。结果，可能会出现内存泄漏，CPU充血和缓慢的性能等问题。但是，有一些方法可以将此优化提高到一个新的水平。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在本指南中，我们将讨论一些流行的方法，以优化&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/watch-a-warter-liter-liter-liter-nodejs-part-part-1”&gt; node.js app app的绩效</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multi-Channel Notification Patterns for Security-Critical Events】关键事件的多通道通知模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/multi-channel-notification-patterns-security-events</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As the degree of account takeovers and unauthorized access attempts continues to be more and more sophisticated, the time to notify users about security-critical situations has become a vital issue. The moment when a system becomes aware of irregular behavior — such as a log from a new device or suspicious activity — it is necessary that the corporation ensures users are immediately notified and receive the notice through a reliable channel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;One source of a channel (such as email only) is not enough. When they are sent, shortcomings in the technology of delivery arise. Multi-channel approaches, in contrast, increase the likelihood of the messages&#39; delivery and further action by the users who improve their accounts by this and reduce the possible compromise risk.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;随着帐户收购程度和未经授权的访问尝试越来越复杂，通知用户关键安全情况的时间已成为一个至关重要的问题。当系统意识到不规则行为（例如新设备的日志或可疑活动的日志）时，公司有必要确保立即通知用户并通过可靠的渠道接收通知。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;频道的一个来源（例如电子邮件）是不够的。当它们发送时，交付技术的缺点就会出现。相比之下，多渠道方法增加了通过此信息提高帐户并降低可能折衷风险的用户的交付和进一步行动的可能性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond the Checklist: A Security Architect&#39;s Guide to Comprehensive Assessments】超越清单：安全建筑师的全面评估指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/security-architect-guide-comprehensive-assessments</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;41:1-41:381&#34;&gt;A security architect&#39;s role extends far beyond designing secure systems. It demands a continuous, vigilant approach to assessing the effectiveness of implemented controls against evolving threats. With the proliferation of cloud-native architectures, microservices, and distributed environments, a mere checklist approach falls woefully short.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;43:1-43:186&#34;&gt;This guide provides a framework for security architects to conduct holistic and impactful security assessments, delving into critical control areas that define a robust security posture.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 41：1-41：381”&gt;安全架构师的角色远远超出了设计安全系统的范围。它需要一种持续，警惕的方法来评估实施控制的有效性，以防止不断发展的威胁。随着云本地体系结构，微服务和分布式环境的扩散，仅清单方法非常短。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 43：1-43：186”&gt;本指南为安全架构师进行整体和有影响力的安全评估提供了一个框架，并深入研究了定义强大安全姿势的关键控制领域。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Knowledge: LlamaIndex and Apache Tika for Enterprises】AI驱动的知识：企业的Llamaindex和Apache Tika</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llamaindex-apache-tika-ai-word-documents</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;LlamaIndex is an open-source &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-web-frameworks-everything-you-need-to-know&#34;&gt;Python framework&lt;/a&gt; that’s like an intelligent librarian for your data, supercharging AI with your documents. It’s built for retrieval-augmented generation (RAG), where AI searches your files, databases, or records to find the right info before answering questions or generating content. This makes AI answers more accurate, unlike generic chatbots that lean on pre-trained knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;LlamaIndex works in three steps:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []” dir =“ ltr”&gt; llamaindex是一个开放式source &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/articles/python-web-frameworks-everytherworks-everyting-to-to-you-need-you-ney-skoic--know--know--know-- wekot-- python Framework &lt;/a&gt; python framework &lt;/a&gt;与您的智能图书馆一样，您的数据是您的数据，您的数据是您的数据，超高了您的AI，超级超过您的数据。它是用于检索授权生成（RAG）的，AI在回答问题或生成内容之前搜索您的文件，数据库或记录以查找正确的信息。与依靠预训练的知识的通用聊天机器人不同，这使得AI的答案更加准确。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; llamaindex分为三个步骤：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Serverless vs Containers: Choosing the Right Architecture for Your Application】无服务器与容器：选择适合您应用程序的架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-vs-containers-choosing-right-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Choosing the right architecture for your application is crucial to make it low-cost, performant, and scalable. Two of the leading software development methods today, serverless and container-based architectures, have distinct patterns for application release and application processing. In this article, we discuss their technical intricacies, key distinctions, and under which conditions to make use of each, with code examples to illustrate specific application uses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Serverless Architecture?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-computing-the-future-of-scalable-cloud-applications&#34;&gt;Serverless computing&lt;/a&gt; eliminates infrastructure administration, leaving developers to write code alone. Provisioning, scaling, and servicing are controlled by cloud platforms such as AWS Lambda, Azure Functions, and Google Cloud Functions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;为您的应用程序选择正确的体系结构对于使其低成本，性能和可扩展性至关重要。如今，两种领先的软件开发方法，无服务器和基于容器的架构，具有不同的模式用于应用程序发布和应用程序处理。在本文中，我们讨论了它们的技术复杂性，关键区别，以及在哪些条件下使用每个条件，并用代码示例说明特定的应用程序用途。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是无服务器体系结构？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-computing-computing-the-the-future-of-scalable-cloud-applications”&gt;无服务器计算&lt;/a&gt;消除基础架构管理，使开发人员仅编写代码。供应，缩放和维修由AWS Lambda，Azure功能和Google Cloud Functions等云平台控制。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Essential Steps to Building a Robust Cybersecurity Team】建立强大的网络安全团队的重要步骤</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/essential-steps-to-building-a-robust-cybersecurity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Cybersecurity doesn’t fail because someone forgot to patch a server. It fails because no one asked the right questions early enough, and because the wrong people were trusted to find the answers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Most companies start building a cybersecurity team only after something breaks. A breach hits. Logs go missing. Customer data leaks. Then suddenly, there’s a mad rush to find “cyber talent” — as if throwing more engineers at the fire will fix a decade of neglected fundamentals.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;网络安全不会失败，因为有人忘记了修补服务器。它失败了，因为没有人能尽早提出正确的问题，并且因为错误的人被信任找到答案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;大多数公司只有在某些事情破裂之后才开始建立一个网络安全团队。违反命中。日志丢失了。客户数据泄漏。然后突然，发现“网络人才”很疯狂 - 仿佛在大火上投掷更多的工程师会解决十年的被忽视的基本面。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating E2E Tests With MFA: Streamline Your Testing Workflow】使用MFA自动化E2E测试：简化测试工作流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-e2e-tests-with-mfa</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In software development, efficiency and security are key, especially for applications that require multi-factor authentication (MFA). MFA enhances security but complicates automated testing, particularly for key business processes like logins or transaction validations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Altering testing environments to handle MFA differently (either by disabling it or re-routing) can risk misconfigurations that may affect production systems. Following my &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/overcoming-mfa-test-automation-challenges&#34;&gt;previous article on MFA issues&lt;/a&gt; when testing, here is the description on how to use an API tool that has been super helpful for my team.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在软件开发，效率和安全性中是关键，尤其是对于需要多因素身份验证（MFA）的应用程序。 MFA增强了安全性，但使自动测试复杂化，特别是对于关键业务流程（例如登录或交易验证）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;改变测试环境以不同的方式处理MFA（通过禁用或重新布置）可能会冒可能会影响生产系统的构造错误。跟随我的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/overcoming-mfa-test-automation-challenges”&gt;上一篇关于MFA问题的文章&lt;/a&gt;测试时，以下是有关如何使用对我的团队超级帮助的API工具的描述。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Serverless Machine Learning: Running AI Models Without Managing Infrastructure】无服务器的机器学习：运行AI模型而无需管理基础架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-machine-learning-ai-models</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;385&#34; data-start=&#34;65&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-ai-aws-strategies&#34;&gt;Serverless machine learning&lt;/a&gt; refers to deploying ML inference code without provisioning or managing servers. Developers use &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/different-types-of-cloud-computing-models&#34;&gt;Function-as-a-Service (FaaS) platforms&lt;/a&gt; (e.g., AWS Lambda, Azure Functions) to run model predictions on demand. This approach provides automatic scaling, pay-per-use billing, and low operational overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;432&#34; data-start=&#34;387&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;431&#34; data-start=&#34;387&#34;&gt;Key advantages of serverless ML include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 385” data-start =“ 65”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-ai-ai-aws-strategies”&gt; serverless机器学习&lt;/a&gt;是指在不配备或管理服务器的情况下部署ML推进代码。开发人员使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/different-ytypes-of-cloud-computing-models”&gt; function-as-as-a-service（faas）平台&lt;/a&gt;（例如，AWS Lambda，Azure，Azure功能）以运行需求模型预测。这种方法提供自动缩放，按使用付费计费和低操作开销。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 432” data-start =“ 387”&gt; &lt;strong data-end =“ 431” data-start =“ 387”&gt;无服务器ML的关键优势包括：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>