<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating an Application With a Personality】创建具有个性的应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/application-with-a-personality</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Many years ago, one of my favorite former colleagues left the company where we worked together, and he wrote a goodbye email. I&#39;ve seen a few, but this was the most imaginative of them all. He wrote it in the form of a Jenkins notification email about a failed Maven build. If you read the build logs carefully, you could see that the build failed because my colleague left the company.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This memory gave me the idea of what an application would say about itself if we could ask.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;很多年前，我最喜欢的前同事之一离开了我们一起工作的公司，他写了一封再见电子邮件。我看过几个，但这是所有人中最想象力的。他以詹金斯通知电子邮件的形式编写了有关Maven构建失败的通知电子邮件。如果您仔细阅读构建日志，您会发现构建失败了，因为我的同事离开了公司。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个记忆使我想到了一个应用程序会说的话，如果我们可以问。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Moving PeopleSoft ERP Data Between Databases With Data Mover Scripts】将PeopleSoft ERP数据移动到具有数据移动脚本的数据库之间</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/peoplesoft-erp-data-move-data-mover-scripts</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Why Transfer or Move Data?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Transferring PeopleSoft application data between databases is necessary for various business needs, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Application upgrades&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;User or system testing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Training environment setup&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article covers the essential commands and step-by-step instructions needed to perform data transfer effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;为什么要传输或移动数据？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于各种业务需求，必须在数据库之间传输PeopleSoft应用程序数据，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;应用程序升级&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;用户或系统测试&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;培训环境设置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文涵盖了有效执行数据传输所需的基本命令和分步说明。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Heap Dumps to Find Memory Leaks】使用堆转储查找内存泄漏</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/using-heap-dumps-to-find-memory-leaks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A JVM (Java Virtual Machine) runs programs in Java and many other languages and provides the runtime environment, CPU, memory, and security management. At any particular moment, the running JVM has many objects, and a heap dump is a snapshot of the memory allocated to all these objects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this post, we will discuss how to use heap dumps to find memory leaks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; JVM（Java Virtual Machine）以Java和许多其他语言运行程序，并提供运行时环境，CPU，内存和安全管理。在任何特定时刻，运行的JVM都有许多对象，并且堆转储是分配给所有这些对象的内存的快照。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将讨论如何使用堆转储查找内存泄漏。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【XAI: Making ML Models Transparent for Smarter Hiring Decisions】XAI：使ML模型透明以智能招聘决策</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/xai-transparent-ml-models-smarter-hiring</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Recruiting is extremely tough as outsiders may disagree with you — I’ve been there, sifting through resumes, trying to spot the perfect fit for a role. I’ve noticed more companies using machine learning to screen candidates and predict job success lately. The problem? When an algorithm rejects someone, there’s often no clear reason why.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-humanizing-artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;explainable AI&lt;/a&gt; (XAI) changes the game. Think of it as a recruiter’s secret weapon — it takes the mystery out of AI decisions and turns machine learning into a real hiring partner. Let’s dive into why this matters and how to use it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;招募非常艰难，因为局外人可能会不同意您 - 我去过那里，筛选简历，试图发现最适合角色的人。我注意到越来越多的公司使用机器学习来筛选候选人并预测工作成功。问题？当算法拒绝某人时，通常没有明确的理由。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-humanizing-andercover-intelligence”&gt;可解释的ai &lt;/a&gt;（xai）改变了游戏。可以将其视为招聘人员的秘密武器 - 它使AI的决策脱颖而出，并将机器学习变成了真正的招聘伙伴。让我们了解为什么这很重要以及如何使用它。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automatic Versioning in Mobile Apps】移动应用中的自动版本控制</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automatic-versioning-in-mobile-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Picture this: Your mobile app is evolving quickly, with new features requiring changes to the local database. Your users expect seamless upgrades, and your stakeholders want new functionality delivered fast. The challenge becomes even trickier when you realize you need to update the app&#39;s database schema without disrupting existing data or forcing users into error-prone migrations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, I’ll share a practical, automatic versioning approach I developed that simplifies database versioning and migration for mobile apps. This system lets developers focus on data models instead of manually scripting version changes, while making sure users’ data stays intact across updates.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;图片：您的移动应用程序正在快速发展，新功能需要更改本地数据库。您的用户期望无缝升级，您的利益相关者希望快速提供新的功能。当您意识到需要更新应用程序的数据库架构而不破坏现有数据或强迫用户迁移迁移时，挑战就变得更加棘手。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在本文中，我将共享一种实用的自动版本管理方法，我开发了简化移动应用程序的数据库版本控制和迁移。该系统使开发人员可以专注于数据模型，而不是手动脚本版本更改，同时确保用户的数据在更新中保持完整。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Breaking the Context Barrier of LLMs: InfiniRetri vs RAG】打破LLM的上下文障碍：Infiniretri与抹布</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/breaking-context-barrier-llms-infiniretriever-vs-rag</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Large language models (LLMs) are reshaping the landscape of artificial intelligence, yet they face an ongoing challenge — retrieving and utilizing information beyond their training data. Two competing methods have emerged as solutions to this problem: &lt;strong&gt;InfiniRetri&lt;/strong&gt;, an approach that exploits the LLM’s own attention mechanism to retrieve relevant context from within long inputs, and &lt;strong&gt;retrieval-augmented generation&lt;/strong&gt; (RAG), which dynamically fetches external knowledge from structured databases before generating responses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Each of these approaches presents unique strengths, limitations, and trade-offs. While InfiniRetri aims to maximize efficiency by working within the model’s existing architecture, RAG enhances factual accuracy by integrating real-time external information. But which one is superior?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;大语言模型（LLM）正在重塑人工智能的景观，但他们面临着持续的挑战 - 检索和利用超出培训数据的信息。已经出现了两种竞争方法作为解决此问题的解决方案：&lt;strong&gt; infiniretri &lt;/strong&gt;，一种利用LLM自己的注意力机制从长期输入中检索相关上下文的方法，&lt;strong&gt;检索发电量&lt;/strong&gt;（RAG）（RAG）（RAG），从结构的数据库中动态从结构的数据库中获取外部知识。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;这些方法中每种方法都列出了独特的优势，限制和权衡。尽管Infiniretri旨在通过在模型的现有体系结构中工作来最大程度地提高效率，但RAG通过集成实时外部信息来提高事实准确性。但是哪一个是优越的？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Self-Healing Data Pipelines: The Next Big Thing in Data Engineering?】自我修复数据管道：数据工程中的下一个大事？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-self-healing-data-pipeline-a-data-engin</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m an enthusiastic data engineer who always looks out for various challenging problems and tries to solve them with a simple POC that everyone can relate to. Recently, I have thought about an issue that most data engineers face daily. I have set alerts on all the batch and streaming data pipelines. When the errors reach a threshold limit or if the data pipeline fails, we get failure notifications immediately in the email inbox.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Everything seemed fine until I noticed one of our critical datasets could not be loaded into &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/control-access-to-google-bigquery-data&#34;&gt;BigQuery&lt;/a&gt;. After investigating the error logs, I found several messages with &#34;missing required data.&#34; I felt ‘lost’ seeing these frequent raw data issues from a user-inputted file.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我是一位热情的数据工程师，他总是寻找各种具有挑战性的问题，并试图通过每个人都可以与之联系的简单POC解决它们。最近，我考虑了大多数数据工程师每天都面临的问题。我已经在所有批处理和流数据管道上设置了警报。当错误达到阈值限制或数据管道失败时，我们会在电子邮件收件箱中立即获得故障通知。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;直到我注意到我们的一个关键数据集无法将其加载到&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/control-access-to-google-bigquery-data”&gt; bigquery &lt;/a&gt;之前。研究错误日志后，我发现了几条消息，上面有“缺少所需数据”。从用户输入的文件中看到这些频繁的原始数据问题，我感到“丢失”。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 18:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Accurate Quantitative Analysis With ChatGPT and Azure AI Hub】使用Chatgpt和Azure AI Hub进行准确的定量分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/using-llms-like-chatgpt-for-accurate-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;256&#34; data-start=&#34;96&#34;&gt;LLMs are not very good at quantitative analysis. For example, when I asked ChatGPT, &#34;Which number is bigger, 9.9 or 9.11?&#34; it incorrectly responded with 9.11.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;935&#34; data-start=&#34;258&#34;&gt;In another example, I have an Excel file containing a large amount of quantitative data. The maximum word count for a single prompt that &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-must-be-aware-of-about-chatgpt&#34;&gt;ChatGPT&lt;/a&gt; can handle is around 4,000 words (approximately 16,000 characters). If I try to query this data, it may not fit within the context window.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 256” data-start =“ 96”&gt; llms在定量分析方面不是很好。例如，当我问chatgpt时，“哪个数字更大，9.9或9.11？”它以9.11。&lt;/p&gt;做出了错误的响应。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 935” data-start =“ 258”&gt;在另一个示例中，我有一个包含大量定量数据的Excel文件。单个提示的最大单词计数&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/everything-youthy-must-be-aware-aware-of-about-about-chatgpt”&gt; chatgpt &lt;/a&gt;可以处理约4,000个单词（大约16,000个字符）。如果我尝试查询此数据，则可能不适合上下文窗口。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Future of DevOps】DevOps的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-the-future-of-devops</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When I was asked to think about my technology predictions for 2025, it occurred to me how much happened from 2023 until now, where the dust is still settling and the reverberations from these seismic shifts in our ecosystem are still taking hold of our industry.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/infrastructure-as-code-everything-you-need-to-know&#34;&gt;Infrastructure as Code&lt;/a&gt; (IaC) landscape is entering an era of transformation. The ubiquitous tools we came to know and love are being replaced with newer more open options — if we just recap all of the major milestones from then until now: Terraform is losing ground to other more open solutions after closing its license in August 2023, the fork of OpenTofu and its contribution to the Linux Foundation, and the consequent acquisition of Hashicorp by IBM, as well as the growing momentum around other IaC tooling like Crossplane, Pulumi and even ARM templates.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当我被要求考虑我的2025年技术预测时，我想到了从2023年到目前为止发生了多少事情，那里的灰尘仍在沉降，我们生态系统中这些地震转变的回响仍在掌握我们的行业。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/infrastructure-as-code-verything-you-need-need-need-news-know-”&gt;基础架构作为代码&lt;/a&gt;（IAC）景观正在进入转型时代。我们知道和爱的无处不在的工具将被更新的更开放的选择所取代 - 如果我们从那时起就回顾了所有主要里程碑，直到现在到现在为止：Terraform在2023年8月在2023年8月关闭其许可证后，opentofu及其对Linux基金会的贡献，以及其他企图以及其他工具的贡献，以及临时的企业，以及IB的贡献，以及IB的贡献，以及IB的其他工具。跨平面，脉冲机甚至手臂模板。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimized Metrics Generation With Metadata-Driven Dynamic SQL】通过元数据驱动的动态SQL优化的度量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimized-metrics-with-metadata-driven-sql</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The creation of precise and adaptable metrics remains crucial for successful monitoring, auditing, and reporting in present-day data-centric settings. This article describes an optimized method to create metrics and dynamic SQL with metadata-based techniques using Oracle packages. This process combines configuration tables, dynamic SQL templates, and merge operations to create a metrics generation framework that scales well and remains easy to maintain and adjust.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-parastyle=&#34;heading 2&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134245418&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;134245529&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:299,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:299}&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;The process is built around an audit package&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;and a set of&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-ddl-dml-and-dcl-commands-in-mys&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Data Definition Language&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;(DDL) statements that define critical tables for storing audit facts, dynamic SQL templates, and metric results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;创建精确和适应性的指标对于在当今以数据为中心的设置中成功监视，审核和报告仍然至关重要。本文介绍了一种使用Oracle软件包的基于元数据的技术创建指标和动态SQL的优化方法。此过程结合了配置表，动态SQL模板和合并操作，以创建一个指标生成框架，该框架可以很好地缩放，并且保持易于维护和调整。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ en-us”&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-parestyle =“ heading 2”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;背景&lt;/stronk&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {” 134233117“：false，” 134233118“：false，” 134245418“：true，” 134245529“：true，” 3 35551550“：0，” 335551620“：0，” 335559738“：299，” 3355559739“：299}”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p lang =“ en-us”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;该过程围绕审核软件包&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” auto“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;和一组&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-ddl-dml-and-dml-and-dcl-commands-in-mys”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” auto“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;数据定义语言&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;动态SQL模板和度量结果。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>