<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【MuleSoft: Best Practices for API Management】MuleSoft：API 管理的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mulesoft-best-practices-for-api-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In today’s digital landscape, APIs have become the backbone of modern software architecture, enabling seamless integration and communication among disparate systems. Effective API management is critical to ensuring that these interfaces are secure, scalable, and maintainable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This article explores the essential best practices for API management, providing insights into design principles, security measures, performance optimization, lifecycle management, documentation strategies, etc. Whether you are a seasoned developer or an API newcomer, these guidelines will help you navigate the complexities of API Management and achieve success in your integration efforts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在当今的数字环境中，API 已成为现代软件架构的支柱，支持不同系统之间的无缝集成和通信。有效的 API 管理对于确保这些接口的安全、可扩展和可维护至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;本文探讨了 API 管理的基本最佳实践，提供了对设计原则、安全措施、性能优化、生命周期管理、文档策略、等等。无论您是经验丰富的开发人员还是 API 新手，这些指南都将帮助您应对 API 管理的复杂性并在集成工作中取得成功。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PlatformCon 2024 Session Recap: Platform Engineering and AI】PlatformCon 2024 会议回顾：平台工程和人工智能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/platformcon-recap-platform-engineering-and-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Are you curious what experienced practitioners are saying about AI and platform engineering — and its growing impact on development workflows? Look no further than DZone’s latest event with&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://platformcon.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PlatformCon 2024&lt;/a&gt; where our global software community answers these vital questions in an expert panel on all things platform engineering, AI, and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Developers Must Know About AI and Platform Engineering&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Moderated by DZone Core member and Director of Data and AI at Silk, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/authors/dbakevlar&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kellyn Pot’Vin-Gorman&lt;/a&gt;, panelists&lt;a href=&#34;https://platformcon.com/speakers/ryan-murray&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ryan Murray&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://platformcon.com/speakers/sandra-borda&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Sandra Borda&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://platformcon.com/speakers/chiradeep-vittal&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Chiradeep Vittal&lt;/a&gt; discussed the most probing questions and deliberations facing AI and platform engineering today.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;您是否好奇经验丰富的从业者对人工智能和平台工程的看法及其对开发工作流程日益增长的影响？ DZone 举办的最新活动 &lt;a href=&#34;https://platformcon.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PlatformCon 2024&lt;/a&gt; 就是您的最佳选择，我们的全球软件社区将在其中回答这些重要问题一个涵盖所有平台工程、人工智能等领域的专家小组。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;开发人员必须了解的有关人工智能和平台工程的知识&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;由 DZone 核心成员兼 Silk 数据和人工智能总监 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/authors/dbakevlar&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; 主持&gt;Kellyn Pot&#39;Vin-Gorman&lt;/a&gt;，小组成员&lt;a href=&#34;https://platformcon.com/speakers/ryan-murray&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; Ryan Murray&lt;/a&gt; 、&lt;a href=&#34;https://platformcon.com/speakers/sandra-borda&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Sandra Borda&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://platformcon .com/speakers/chiradeep-vittal&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Chiradeep Vittal&lt;/a&gt; 讨论了当今人工智能和平台工程面临的最具挑战性的问题和审议。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dynamic Watermarking on the JVM】JVM 上的动态水印</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dynamic-watermarking-on-the-jvm</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Displaying images on your website makes for an interesting problem: on one side, you want to make them publicly available; on the other, you want to protect them against undue use. The age-long method to achieve it is watermarking:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;digital watermark&lt;/strong&gt; is a kind of marker covertly embedded in a noise-tolerant signal such as audio, video or image data. It is typically used to identify ownership of the copyright of such signal. &#34;Watermarking&#34; is the process of hiding digital information in a carrier signal; the hidden information should, but does not need to, contain a relation to the carrier signal. Digital watermarks may be used to verify the authenticity or integrity of the carrier signal or to show the identity of its owners. It is prominently used for tracing copyright infringements and for banknote authentication.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在您的网站上显示图像会产生一个有趣的问题：一方面，您希望将它们公开可用；另一方面，您希望将它们公开。另一方面，您希望保护它们免遭不当使用。实现这一目标的长期方法是水印：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA; &lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数字水印&lt;/strong&gt;是一种隐蔽地嵌入音频、视频或图像数据等耐噪信号中的标记。它通常用于识别此类信号的版权所有权。 “水印”是在载波信号中隐藏数字信息的过程；隐藏信息应该但不需要包含与载波信号的关系。数字水印可用于验证载波信号的真实性或完整性或显示其所有者的身份。它主要用于追踪版权侵权和钞票认证。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How BERT Enhances the Features of NLP】BERT 如何增强 NLP 的特性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-bert-enhances-the-features-of-nlp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-llm-technology&#34;&gt;Large language models&lt;/a&gt; have played a catalytic role in how human language is comprehended and processed. NLP has bridged the communication gap between humans and machines, leading to seamless customer experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NLP is great for interpreting simple languages with straightforward intent. But it still has a long way to go when it comes to interpreting ambiguity in text arising from homonyms, synonyms, irony, sarcasm, and more.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-llm-technology&#34;&gt;大型语言模型&lt;/a&gt;在人类语言的理解和处理方面发挥了催化作用。 NLP 弥合了人与机器之间的沟通鸿沟，带来无缝的客户体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NLP 非常适合解释具有简单意图的简单语言。但在解释文本中由同音异义词、同义词、反讽、讽刺等引起的歧义时，还有很长的路要走。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【regreSSHion: Should We Panic About the New OpenSSH Vulnerability?】regreSSHion：我们应该对新的 OpenSSH 漏洞感到恐慌吗？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-the-regresshion-vulnerability</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Is the regreSSHion Vulnerability (CVE-2024-6387)?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;regreSSHion is a newly discovered vulnerability in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-openssh-1&#34;&gt;OpenSSH&lt;/a&gt; that affects glibc-based Linux systems. regreSSHion (CVE-2024-6387) may allow arbitrary code execution with root privileges on systems with default configurations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Why Is Everyone Worried About the regreSSHion Vulnerability?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Everyone is worried about the regreSSHion vulnerability because OpenSSH is a widely used utility for remote connection to different devices around the world. It implements the SSH (Secure Shell) protocol, which is integrated into most &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/top-ten-lightweight-linux-distributions&#34;&gt;Linux distributions&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;as well as macOS, OpenBSD, and FreeBSD. Furthermore, SSH is integrated into almost every device connected to the internet, from WiFi routers to baby monitors.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;什么是 regreSSHion 漏洞 (CVE-2024-6387)？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;regreSSHion 是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-openssh-1&#34;&gt;OpenSSH&lt;/a&gt; 中新发现的漏洞，影响基于 glibc 的 Linux系统。 regreSSHion (CVE-2024-6387) 可能允许在具有默认配置的系统上以 root 权限执行任意代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为什么每个人都担心 regreSSHion 漏洞？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;每个人都担心 regreSSHion 漏洞，因为 OpenSSH 是一种广泛使用的实用程序，用于远程连接世界各地的不同设备。它实现了 SSH（安全外壳）协议，该协议已集成到大多数 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/top-ten-lightweight-linux-distributions&#34;&gt;Linux 发行版&lt;/a&gt;以及macOS、OpenBSD 和 FreeBSD。此外，从 WiFi 路由器到婴儿监视器，几乎所有连接到互联网的设备都集成了 SSH。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【LLMs Progression and Path Forward】法学硕士的进步和前进道路</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llms-progression-and-path-forward</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In recent years, there have been significant advancements in language models. This progress is a result of extensive training and tuning on billions of parameters, along with benchmarking for commercial use. The origins of this work can be traced back to the 1950s when research in Natural Language Understanding and Processing began.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article aims to provide an overview of the history and evolution of language models over the last 70 years. It will also examine the current available Large Language Models (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/custom-training-of-large-language-models-a-compreh&#34;&gt;LLMs&lt;/a&gt;), including their architecture, tuning parameters, enterprise readiness, system configurations, and more, to gain a high-level understanding of their training and inference processes. This exploration will allow us to appreciate the progress in this field and assess the options available for commercial use.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;近年来，语言模型取得了显着的进步。这一进展是对数十亿个参数进行广泛训练和调整以及商业用途基准测试的结果。这项工作的起源可以追溯到 20 世纪 50 年代，当时自然语言理解和处理的研究就开始了。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文旨在概述过去 70 年来语言模型的历史和演变。它还将检查当前可用的大型语言模型（&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/custom-training-of-large-language-models-a-compreh&#34;&gt;LLM&lt;/a&gt;），包括其架构、调整参数、企业准备情况、系统配置等，以获得对其训练和推理过程的高级理解。这种探索将使我们能够了解该领域的进展并评估可用于商业用途的选项。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Interactive PDF Q&amp;amp;A: A Retrieval-Augmented Generation Approach】交互式 PDF 问答：检索增强生成方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/interactive-pdf-qampa-a-retrieval-augmented-genera</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-line=&#34;2&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;In the information age, dealing with huge PDFs happens on a day-to-day basis. Most of the time, I have found myself drowning in a sea of text, struggling to find the information I wanted or needed reading page after page. But, what if I can ask questions about the PDF and recover not only the relevant information but also the page contents?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line=&#34;4&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;That&#39;s where the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-comparative-exploration-of-llm-and-rag&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; technique comes into play. By combining these cutting-edge technologies, I have created a locally hosted application that allows you to chat with your PDFs, ask questions, and receive all the necessary context.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-line=&#34;2&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;在信息时代，处理巨大的 PDF 是每天都会发生的事情。大多数时候，我发现自己淹没在文字的海洋中，努力寻找我想要或需要一页一页阅读的信息。但是，如果我可以提出有关 PDF 的问题，不仅可以恢复相关信息，还可以恢复页面内容，该怎么办？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line=&#34;4&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;这就是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-comparative-exploration-of-llm-and-rag&#34;&gt;&lt;strong &gt;检索增强生成（RAG）&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;技术开始发挥作用。通过结合这些尖端技术，我创建了一个本地托管的应用程序，允许您与 PDF 聊天、提出问题并接收所有必要的上下文。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Migration From GaussDB to GBase8a】GaussDB到GBase8a的数据迁移</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-migration-from-gaussdb-to-gbase8a</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Exporting Data From GaussDB&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Comparison of Export Methods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34; style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;table style=&#34;max-width: 100%; width: auto; table-layout: fixed; display: table;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Export Tool&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Export Steps&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Applicable Scenarios and Notes&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Using GDS Tool to Export Data to a Regular File System&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: The GDS tool must be installed on the server where the data files are exported&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Export Mode:&lt;/strong&gt; Export business data from the cluster to an external host.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      1. Plan the export path, create GDS operation users, and set write permissions for the GDS user on the export path.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. Install, configure, and start GDS on the server where data will be exported.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      3. Create an external table in the cluster, with the location path in the format &#34;gsfs://192.168.0.90:5000/&#34;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Local Export Mode:&lt;/strong&gt; Export business data from the cluster to the host where the cluster nodes are located. This strategy is tailored for numerous small files.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      1. Plan the export path and create directories to store exported data files on each DN in the cluster, such as &lt;code&gt;&#34;/output_data&#34;&lt;/code&gt;, and change the owner of this path to &lt;code&gt;omm&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. Install, configure, and start GDS on the server where data will be exported.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      3. Create an external table in the cluster, with the location path in the format &lt;code&gt;&#34;file:///output_data/&#34;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;GDS tools suitable for scenarios with high concurrency and large data exports. Utilizes multi-DN parallelism to export data from the database to data files, improving overall export performance. Does not support direct export to HDFS file system.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes on Remote Export:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      1. Supports concurrent export by multiple GDS services, but one GDS can only provide export services for one cluster at a time.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. Configure GDS services within the same intranet as the cluster nodes. Export speed is affected by network bandwidth. The recommended network configuration is 10GE.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      3. Supported data file formats: TEXT, CSV, and FIXED. Single-row data size must be &amp;lt;1GB.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes on Local Export:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      1. Data will be evenly split and generated in the specified folders on the cluster nodes, occupying disk space on the cluster nodes.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. Supports data file formats: TEXT, CSV, and FIXED. Single-row data size must be &amp;lt;1GB.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;gs_dump and gs_dumpall Tools&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;code&gt;gs_dump&lt;/code&gt; supports exporting a single database or its objects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;code&gt;gs_dumpall&lt;/code&gt; supports exporting all databases in the cluster or common global objects in each database.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      The tools support exporting content at the database level, schema level, and second level. Each level can be separately defined to export the entire content, only object definitions, or only data files.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 1:&lt;/strong&gt; The &lt;code&gt;omm&lt;/code&gt; operating system user logs into any host with MPPDB service installed and executes: &lt;code&gt;source $ {BIGDATA_HOME}/mppdb/.mppdb&lt;/code&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;code&gt;gs_profile&lt;/code&gt; command to start environment variables&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step 2:&lt;/strong&gt; Use &lt;code&gt;gs_dump&lt;/code&gt; to export the postgres database: &lt;code&gt;gs_dump -W Bigdata@123 -U jack -f /home/omm/backup/postgres_backup.tar -p 25308 postgres -F t&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;1. Export the entire database information, including data and all object definitions.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. Export the full information of all databases, including each database in the cluster and common global objects (including roles and tablespace information).&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      3. Export only all object definitions, including tablespace, database definitions, function definitions, schema definitions, table definitions, index definitions, and stored procedure definitions.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      4. Export only data, excluding all object definitions.&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA; &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GDS External Table Remote Export Example&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-wrapper&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeHeader&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div class=&#34;nameLanguage&#34;&gt;&#xA;    Shell&#xA;   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;icon-cancel-circled-1 cm-remove&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/i&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-code--wrapper&#34; data-code=&#34;mkdir -p /output_data &#xA;groupadd gdsgrp &#xA;useradd -g gdsgrp gds_user &#xA;chown -R gds_user:gdsgrp /output_data&#xA;/opt/bin/gds/gds -d /output_data -p 192.168.0.90:5000 -H 10.10.0.1/24 -D &#xA;CREATE FOREIGN TABLE foreign_tpcds_reasons &#xA;( &#xA;r_reason_sk integer not null, &#xA;r_reason_id char(16) not null, &#xA;r_reason_desc char(100) &#xA;) SERVER gsmpp_server OPTIONS (LOCATION &#39;gsfs://192.168.0.90:5000/&#39;, FORMAT &#39;CSV&#39;,ENCODING &#xA;&#39;utf8&#39;,DELIMITER E&#39;\x08&#39;, QUOTE E&#39;\x1b&#39;, NULL &#39;&#39;) WRITE ONLY; &#xA;INSERT INTO foreign_tpcds_reasons SELECT * FROM reasons; &#xA;ps -ef|grep gds &#xA;gds_user 128954 1 0 15:03 ? 00:00:00 gds -d /output_data -p 192.168.0.90:5000 -D &#xA;gds_user 129003 118723 0 15:04 pts/0 00:00:00 grep gds &#xA;kill -9 128954 &#34; data-lang=&#34;text/x-sh&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;text/x-sh&#34;&gt;mkdir -p /output_data &#xA;groupadd gdsgrp &#xA;useradd -g gdsgrp gds_user &#xA;chown -R gds_user:gdsgrp /output_data&#xA;/opt/bin/gds/gds -d /output_data -p 192.168.0.90:5000 -H 10.10.0.1/24 -D &#xA;CREATE FOREIGN TABLE foreign_tpcds_reasons &#xA;( &#xA;r_reason_sk integer not null, &#xA;r_reason_id char(16) not null, &#xA;r_reason_desc char(100) &#xA;) SERVER gsmpp_server OPTIONS (LOCATION &#39;gsfs://192.168.0.90:5000/&#39;, FORMAT &#39;CSV&#39;,ENCODING &#xA;&#39;utf8&#39;,DELIMITER E&#39;\x08&#39;, QUOTE E&#39;\x1b&#39;, NULL &#39;&#39;) WRITE ONLY; &#xA;INSERT INTO foreign_tpcds_reasons SELECT * FROM reasons; &#xA;ps -ef|grep gds &#xA;gds_user 128954 1 0 15:03 ? 00:00:00 gds -d /output_data -p 192.168.0.90:5000 -D &#xA;gds_user 129003 118723 0 15:04 pts/0 00:00:00 grep gds &#xA;kill -9 128954 &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;从GaussDB导出数据&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;导出方式比较&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34; style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;表格样式=“最大宽度：100％；宽度：自动；表格布局：固定；显示：表格；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;标题&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;导出工具&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;导出步骤&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;适用场景及注意事项&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/标题&gt;&#xA;  &lt;正文&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；&#34;宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;使用GDS工具导出数据到常规文件系统&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：导出数据文件的服务器上必须安装GDS工具&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td &gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;远程导出模式&lt;/strong&gt;：将业务数据从集群导出到外部主机。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      1.规划导出路径，创建GDS操作用户，并设置GDS用户对导出路径的写入权限。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. 在要导出数据的服务器上安装、配置并启动GDS。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      3、在集群中创建外部表，位置路径格式为“gsfs://192.168.0.90:5000/”。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;本地导出模式：&lt;/strong&gt;导出业务数据从集群到集群节点所在主机。此策略是为众多小文件量身定制的。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      1.规划导出路径，并在集群中每个DN上创建存放导出数据文件的目录，如&lt;code&gt;&#34;/output_data&#34;&lt;/code&gt;，并将该路径的所有者更改为&lt;code&gt;omm&lt;/code &gt;.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. 在要导出数据的服务器上安装、配置并启动GDS。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      3、在集群中创建外部表，位置路径格式为&lt;code&gt;“file:///output_data/”&lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;适合高并发、大数据导出场景的GDS工具。利用多DN并行性将数据从数据库导出到数据文件，提高整体导出性能。不支持直接导出到HDFS文件系统。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;远程导出注意事项：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      1. 支持多个GDS服务并发导出，但一个GDS一次只能为一个集群提供导出服务。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. 在与集群节点相同的内网中配置 GDS 服务。导出速度受网络带宽影响。推荐网络配置为10GE。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      3. 支持的数据文件格式：TEXT、CSV 和 FIXED。单行数据大小必须&lt;1GB。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;本地导出注意事项：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      1、数据会均匀拆分生成在集群节点上的指定文件夹中，占用集群节点上的磁盘空间。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2. 支持数据文件格式：TEXT、CSV、FIXED。单行数据大小必须&lt;1GB。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；&#34;宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;gs_dump 和 gs_dumpall 工具&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;code&gt;gs_dump&lt;/code&gt; 支持导出单个数据库或其对象。&lt;br&gt;&lt;code&gt;gs_dumpall&lt;/code&gt; 支持导出集群中的所有数据库或每个数据库中的公共全局对象。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      这些工具支持在数据库级别、架构级别和二级导出内容。每个级别都可以单独定义导出全部内容、仅导出对象定义或仅导出数据文件。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第1步：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;code&gt;omm&lt;/code&gt;操作系统用户登录任意安装了MPPDB服务的主机并执行：&lt;code&gt;source $ {BIGDATA_HOME}/mppdb/ .mppdb&lt;/code&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;code&gt;gs_profile&lt;/code&gt;命令启动环境变量&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;第2步：&lt;/strong&gt;使用&lt;code&gt;gs_dump&lt;/code&gt;导出 postgres 数据库： &lt;code&gt;gs_dump -W Bigdata@123 -U jack -f /home/omm/backup/postgres_backup.tar -p 25308 postgres -F t&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;1。导出整个数据库信息，包括数据和所有对象定义。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      2、导出所有数据库的完整信息，包括集群中的每个数据库和公共全局对象（包括角色和表空间信息）。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      3. 仅导出所有对象定义，包括表空间、数据库定义、函数定义、模式定义、表定义、索引定义和存储过程定义。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;      4. 仅导出数据，不包括所有对象定义。&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA; &lt;/表&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GDS 外部表远程导出示例&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-wrapper&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div 类=“codeHeader”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div class=&#34;nameLanguage&#34;&gt;&#xA;    壳&#xA;   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;icon-cancel-circled-1 cm-remove&#34;&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;codeMirror-code--wrapper&#34; data-code=&#34;mkdir -p /output_data &#xA;组添加 gdsgrp &#xA;useradd -g gdsgrp gds_user &#xA;chown -R gds_user:gdsgrp /output_data&#xA;/opt/bin/gds/gds -d /output_data -p 192.168.0.90:5000 -H 10.10.0.1/24 -D &#xA;创建外表foreign_tpcds_reasons &#xA;( &#xA;r_reason_sk 整数不为空， &#xA;r_reason_id char(16) 不为空， &#xA;r_reason_desc 字符(100) &#xA;）服务器 gsmpp_server 选项（位置“gsfs://192.168.0.90:5000/”，格式“CSV”，编码 &#xA;&#39;utf8&#39;,DELIMITER E&#39;\x08&#39;, QUOTE E&#39;\x1b&#39;, NULL &#39;&#39;) 只写； &#xA;INSERT INTOforeign_tpcds_reasons SELECT * FROM 原因； &#xA;ps -ef|grep gds &#xA;gds_user 128954 1 0 15:03 ？ 00:00:00 gds -d /输出数据 -p 192.168.0.90:5000 -D &#xA;gds_user 129003 118723 0 15:04 pts/0 00:00:00 grep gds &#xA;杀死-9 128954“data-lang =“text / x-sh”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;pre&gt;&lt;code lang=&#34;text/x-sh&#34;&gt;mkdir -p /output_data &#xA;组添加 gdsgrp &#xA;useradd -g gdsgrp gds_user &#xA;chown -R gds_user:gdsgrp /output_data&#xA;/opt/bin/gds/gds -d /output_data -p 192.168.0.90:5000 -H 10.10.0.1/24 -D &#xA;创建外表foreign_tpcds_reasons &#xA;( &#xA;r_reason_sk 整数不为空， &#xA;r_reason_id char(16) 不为空， &#xA;r_reason_desc 字符(100) &#xA;）服务器 gsmpp_server 选项（位置“gsfs://192.168.0.90:5000/”，格式“CSV”，编码 &#xA;&#39;utf8&#39;,DELIMITER E&#39;\x08&#39;, QUOTE E&#39;\x1b&#39;, NULL &#39;&#39;) 只写； &#xA;INSERT INTOforeign_tpcds_reasons SELECT * FROM 原因； &#xA;ps -ef|grep gds &#xA;gds_user 128954 1 0 15:03 ？ 00:00:00 gds -d /输出数据 -p 192.168.0.90:5000 -D &#xA;gds_user 129003 118723 0 15:04 pts/0 00:00:00 grep gds &#xA;杀死 -9 128954 &lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Viking Enterprise Solutions: Empowering Modern Data Infrastructure】Viking 企业解决方案：赋能现代数据基础设施</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/viking-enterprise-solutions-empowering-modern-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In today&#39;s rapidly evolving technological landscape, developers, engineers, and architects face unprecedented challenges in managing, processing, and deriving value from vast amounts of data. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.vikingenterprisesolutions.com/&#34;&gt;Viking Enterprise Solutions (VES)&lt;/a&gt;, a division of Sanmina Corporation, stands at the forefront of addressing these challenges with its innovative hardware and software solutions. This article explores how VES can help professionals in their roles, focusing on key areas of expertise and product offerings based on their recent presentation to the 56th &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.itpresstour.net&#34;&gt;IT Press Tour&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Bridging Hardware and Software for Optimal Performance&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;One of VES&#39;s core strengths lies in its ability to bridge the gap between hardware and software, creating solutions that maximize performance and efficiency. As a product division of Sanmina, a $9 billion public company, VES leverages decades of manufacturing expertise to deliver cutting-edge data center solutions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在当今快速发展的技术环境中，开发人员、工程师和架构师在管理、处理海量数据并从中获取价值方面面临着前所未有的挑战。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.vikingenterprisesolutions.com/&#34;&gt;Viking Enterprise Solutions (VES)&lt;/a&gt; 是 Sanmina Corporation 的一个部门，凭借其创新的硬件和软件解决方案站在应对这些挑战的最前沿。本文探讨了 VES 如何帮助专业人士履行其职责，根据他们最近在第 56 届 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.itpresstour.net&#34;&gt;IT 新闻发布会&lt;/上的演讲，重点关注专业知识和产品的关键领域。一个&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;桥接硬件和软件以获得最佳性能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;VES 的核心优势之一在于它能够弥合硬件和软件之间的差距，创建可最大限度提高性能和效率的解决方案。作为价值 90 亿美元的上市公司 Sanmina 的一个产品部门，VES 利用数十年的制造专业知识来提供尖端的数据中心解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Choose Between Node.js and Its Alternatives】如何在 Node.js 及其替代方案之间进行选择</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-choose-between-nodejs-and-its-alternatives</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have you ever chosen some technology without considering alternatives? How significant is conducting the research for selecting a reasonable tech stack? How would you approach the evaluation of suitable options? In this article, we’ll focus our attention on Node.js alternatives and core aspects for consideration when comparing other solutions with one of the most used web technologies like Node.js.&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The question of what technology to select for the project confronts every team starting software development. It’s clear that the tech choice would play a critical role in implementing the outlined product. The development team has to put considerable effort into finding tech solutions capable of meeting the set requirements.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;您是否曾经选择过某种技术而不考虑替代方案？进行研究以选择合理的技术堆栈有多重要？您将如何评估合适的选项？在本文中，我们将重点关注 Node.js 替代方案和核心方面，以便在将其他解决方案与 Node.js 等最常用的 Web 技术之一进行比较时考虑。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个开始软件开发的团队都面临着为项目选择什么技术的问题。显然，技术选择将在实施概述的产品中发挥关键作用。开发团队必须付出相当大的努力来寻找能够满足既定要求的技术解决方案。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>