<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【TIOBE Index for June 2025: Top 10 Most Popular Programming Languages】TIOBE索引2025年6月：十种最受欢迎​​的编程语言</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/tiobe-index-popular-programming-languages</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;SQL has dropped to its lowest position in the history of the TIOBE Programming Community Index, according to the June leaderboard.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Between May and June, SQL lost its place in the top 10, descending to 12th place. This created space for Fortran, the classic but still useful programming language that has moved in and out of the top 10 over the last year. Fortran took the opportunity to take 10th place.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】根据六月的排行榜，&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; SQL在Tiobe编程社区指数的历史上降至其最低位置。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在5月至6月之间，SQL在前十名中失去了位置，降至第12位。这为Fortran创造了空间，Fortran是一种经典但仍然有用的编程语言，在过去一年中已进入前十名。 Fortran借此机会排名第十。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Essential Cybersecurity Practices for Non-Profits】非营利组织的基本网络安全实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/essential-cybersecurity-practices-for-non-profits</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With an ever connected and globalized world, it is not surprising that cybersecurity attacks are on the rise. The repercussions of persistent &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/common-cybersecurity-threats-and-how-to-protect-yo&#34;&gt;cybersecurity attacks &lt;/a&gt;touch all types of organizations regardless of scale, from huge international companies to small local non-profits or charities. These organizations are heavily reliant on technology as forming the core backbone of their IT systems and infrastructure, as well as enabling the means of managing donations, communicating with supporters, tracking volunteer work. Cyber criminals have been pursuing infiltrating such institutions by utilizing both advanced and common techniques that might appear benign on the surface. Specifically, non-profit organizations that do not have adequate cybersecurity measures in place are at risk of attacks that expose private data, tarnish their image, and, in the long term, bring about legal and financial repercussions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start With Staff Awareness and Training&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;People are generally considered to be the weakest links in a cybersecurity attack. Non-profits are no different. In the digital world that is expanding very rapidly today, it is past time that people are aware of the looming cybersecurity risks affecting the organization. A traditional technique exploited by cybercriminals and hackers, for example, includes phishing emails, which may initially seem to be absolutely harmless, but can often be one of the primary ways through which a system gets infected. The objective of this kind of attack is to mislead users into disclosing their personal credentials.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着一个不断连接和全球化的世界，网络安全攻击正在上升并不奇怪。持续的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/common-cybersecurity-threats-and-and-how-to-protect-yo”&gt;网络安全攻击&lt;/a&gt;触摸所有类型的组织，无论规模不大，从大型国际公司转向小型非机构或慈善机构。这些组织在很大程度上依赖于技术，因为它构成了其IT系统和基础架构的核心骨干，并能够管理捐赠，与支持者进行交流，跟踪志愿者工作的手段。网络犯罪分子一直在利用可能在表面上看起来良性的高级技术和常见技术来追求此类机构。具体来说，没有足够网络安全措施的非营利组织面临暴露私人数据，损害其形象的攻击风险，并且从长远来看，会带来法律和财务影响。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;从员工意识和培训开始&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人们通常被认为是网络安全攻击中最弱的联系。非营利组织没有什么不同。在当今正在非常迅速的数字世界中，过去的时候，人们意识到了迫在眉睫的网络安全风险影响组织。例如，网络犯罪分子和黑客利用的传统技术包括网络钓鱼电子邮件，最初似乎绝对是无害的，但通常可以是系统感染的主要方式之一。这种攻击的目的是误导用户披露其个人证书。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Preventing Downtime in Public Safety Systems: DevOps Lessons from Production】预防公共安全系统中的停机时间：DevOps的生产课程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devops-public-safety-downtime-strategies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Public safety systems can’t afford to fail silently. An unnoticed &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/deploy-like-a-pro-mastering-the-best-practices-for&#34;&gt;deployment&lt;/a&gt; bug, delayed API response, or logging blind spot can derail operations across city agencies. In environments like these, DevOps isn’t a workflow; it’s operational survival.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With over two decades in software engineering and more than a decade leading municipal cloud platforms, I’ve built systems for cities that can&#39;t afford latency or silence. This article shares lessons we’ve gathered over years of working in high-stakes environments, where preparation, not luck, determines stability. The technical decisions described here emerged not from theory but from repeated trials, long nights, and the obligation to keep city services functional under load.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;公共安全系统无法静静地失败。一个未注意的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/deploy-like-a-pro-mastering-the-best-practices-for”&gt;部署&lt;/a&gt;错误，延迟的API响应或登录盲点可能会使整个城市代理商脱轨。在这样的环境中，DevOps不是工作流程。这是运营生存。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;拥有超过二十年的软件工程和十多年的领先市政云平台，我为无法负担潜伏期或沉默的城市建立了系统。本文分享了我们在高风险环境中工作多年来收集的课程，在这些环境中，准备工作而不是运气决定了稳定性。此处描述的技术决定不是从理论中出现的，而是来自重复的试验，漫长的夜晚以及保持城市服务在负载下运作的义务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Automation: How Artificial Intelligence Is Transforming Software Development】超越自动化：人工智能如何改变软件开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-ai-is-transforming-software-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Not too long ago, AI felt like something out of the future. Now, it’s everywhere. What once was a niche topic tucked away in academic circles has rapidly become a driving force reshaping how we live, work, and connect with the world. Today, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ai-ml&#34;&gt;AI&lt;/a&gt; touches nearly every part of daily life, from handling small, repetitive tasks to helping solve problems once thought out of reach. Think about how chatbots powered by AI now answer millions of customer service questions daily, doing the work that used to take large teams of people [1]. On a completely different front, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/pytorch-geometric-vs-deep-graph-library&#34;&gt;DeepMind’s AlphaFold&lt;/a&gt; cracked a challenge that puzzled scientists for decades: figuring out protein structures. This advance is now speeding up drug discovery and helping researchers understand diseases in new ways [2]. These examples show how broad and meaningful AI’s role has become, from everyday conveniences to huge scientific breakthroughs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI has moved well beyond being just an extra tool in the toolbox in software development. It’s become something that clears obstacles so developers can focus on what they do best. Whether automating repetitive chores, untangling complex workflows, or making it easier to build and test software, AI lets developers concentrate more on creativity and innovation. At this point, it doesn’t just offer assistance, it works side by side with developers to tackle challenges that once seemed too tough to crack.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;不久前，AI感觉就像未来一样。现在，无处不在。曾经藏在学术界的利基主题迅速成为一种驱动力，重塑了我们的生活，工作和与世界的联系。今天，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/ai-ml”&gt; ai &lt;/a&gt;几乎触及日常生活的每个部分，从处理小型，重复性的任务到一旦考虑到触手可及的解决问题。考虑一下AI提供动力的聊天机器人现在如何回答数百万客户服务问题，从事曾经吸引大型人员的工作[1]。在完全不同的方面，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/pytorch-geometric-ves-deep-graph-library”&gt; DeepMind的Alphafold &lt;/a&gt;遇到了一个困惑的科学家，几十年来困惑：弄清楚蛋白质结构。现在，这一进步正在加快毒品发现，并帮助研究人员以新的方式了解疾病[2]。这些示例表明，从日常便利到巨大的科学突破，AI的角色变得多么广泛和有意义。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; AI不仅仅是软件开发工具箱中的额外工具。这已经成为清除障碍的东西，因此开发人员可以专注于他们最擅长的事情。无论是自动化重复的琐事，弄清复杂的工作流程还是更容易构建和测试软件，AI都可以使开发人员更多地专注于创造力和创新。在这一点上，它不仅提供帮助，而且还与开发人员并肩作用，以应对曾经很难破解的挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating OpenAI/GPT Models Into Your Web and Mobile Apps】将OpenAI/GPT模型集成到您的网络和移动应用程序中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-openai-gpt-models-web-mobile-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The rapid growth of generative AI is shifting the user’s expectations for next-gen applications. In this context, OpenAI/GPT models are gaining prominence. Being one of the booming customer apps of the decade, OpenAI/GPT has crossed the 100 million mark of having weekly active users by the year 2024.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Behind the scenes, businesses are eager to integrate the same GPT functionalities into their own products by utilizing the OpenAI API. Improving business workflows through automation, transforming chatbots, and optimizing user interactions through human-like abilities.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;生成AI的快速增长正在改变用户对下一代应用程序的期望。在这种情况下，OpenAI/GPT模型正在获得突出。 OpenAI/GPT是十年来蓬勃发展的客户应用程序之一，到2024年就已经跨越了每周活跃用户的1亿分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在幕后，企业渴望通过使用OpenAI API将相同的GPT功能集成到自己的产品中。通过自动化，转换聊天机器人并通过类似人类的能力来改善业务工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Selenium With Amazon S3 for Test Artifact Management】将硒与亚马逊S3集成进行测试工件管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-selenium-amazon-test-artifact-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Test automation is a core part of the software testing life cycle today, and effective test artifact management is the most important aspect of maintaining a stable testing environment. For most software projects using Selenium for automated testing, integrating with Amazon S3 (Simple Storage Service) provides a scalable and secure solution for storing test data, reports, screenshots, videos, and logs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will explain how to improve your test automation framework by integrating &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/11-reasons-why-go-for-automation-testing-using-sel&#34;&gt;Selenium&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/scalable-secure-aws-data-lake-strategies&#34;&gt;Amazon S3&lt;/a&gt;. You&#39;ll be able to learn how to deploy a scalable solution to manage test artifacts that addresses your testing needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;测试自动化是当今软件测试生命周期的核心部分，有效的测试工件管理是维持稳定测试环境的最重要方面。对于使用Selenium进行自动测试的大多数软件项目，与Amazon S3集成（简单存储服务）为存储测试数据，报告，屏幕截图，视频和日志提供了可扩展且安全的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将通过集成&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/11-reasons-why-go-for-automation-testing-testing-using-sel-sel-sel”&gt; selenium &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a来解释如何改善测试自动化框架。 href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/scalable-secure-aws-data-lake-strategies”&gt; Amazon S3 &lt;/a&gt;。您将能够学习如何部署可扩展的解决方案来管理满足您的测试需求的测试工件。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 19:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Scrum Guide Expansion Pack】Scrum指南扩展包</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-scrum-guide-expansion-pack</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Is There a Need for the Scrum Guide Expansion Pack?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Scrum Guide Expansion Pack represents a fascinating contradiction in the agile world. While attempting to cure Scrum’s reputation crisis, it may actually amplify the very problems it seeks to solve. Let me explain what this means for practitioners dealing with the aftermath of failed Scrum implementations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Philosophical Shift: From Lightweight to Academic&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://scrumexpansion.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2020 Scrum Guide&lt;/a&gt; deliberately embraced minimalism. Ken Schwaber and Jeff Sutherland designed it as a “lightweight framework” that was “purposefully incomplete,” thus forcing teams to fill in the gaps with their intelligence and context. This approach was brilliant in its simplicity compared to competitors such as SAFe.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; TL; DR：是否需要Scrum指南扩展包？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Scrum Guide扩展包代表了敏捷世界中引人入胜的矛盾。在试图解决Scrum的声誉危机时，它实际上可能会扩大其寻求解决的问题。让我解释一下这对处理失败的Scrum实施后果的从业者意味着什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;哲学转变：从轻量级到学术&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://scrumexpansion.org/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; 2020 Scrum指南&lt;/a&gt;故意拥抱了简约。肯·施瓦伯（Ken Schwaber）和杰夫·萨瑟兰（Jeff Sutherland）将其设计为“轻量级框架”，该框架是“故意不完整”的，因此迫使团队在智能和背景下填补了空白。与Safe等竞争对手相比，这种方法的简单性非常简单。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Monitoring Server Health in Private Cloud Data Centers: A Scalable Approach】监视私有云数据中心中的服务器健康：可扩展的方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/monitoring-server-health-in-private-cloud-data-centers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With the increasing costs of public cloud services such as AWS, Azure, and GCP, many companies opt to establish their private cloud infrastructure. This transition necessitates the development of an adequate &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/saas-vs-paas-vs-iaas-which-cloud-service-is-suitable-for-you&#34;&gt;Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)&lt;/a&gt; team to manage and maintain the data center. A key challenge in this domain is monitoring the health of the bare metals (also called servers) to ensure high availability and reliability. This paper presents a comprehensive approach to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/bare-metal-vs-the-world-when-and-why-to-use-this-i&#34;&gt;bare metal&lt;/a&gt; health monitoring in private data centers. We will discuss the problem statement literature review, outline an industry-standard solution, propose a high-level system design to ensure real-time monitoring, fault detection, and automated remediation, and provide experimental results to show how our approach is better than existing industry solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the rise in operational expenses associated with public cloud providers, enterprises are increasingly shifting toward building their data centers. This shift necessitates a dedicated Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) team responsible for maintaining and managing these data centers. A fundamental aspect of infrastructure maintenance is ensuring all servers operate efficiently and reliably. Any failures or performance degradation in these bare metals can result in significant downtime and revenue loss. Therefore, an effective bare metal health monitoring system is crucial for maintaining operational continuity. This article will first define the problem statement and then propose the industry standard scalable solution to tackle the problem.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着AWS，Azure和GCP等公共云服务成本的不断增长，许多公司选择建立其私人云基础架构。这种过渡需要开发足够的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/saas-vs-paas-paas-vs-vs-iaas-aas-which-cloud-cloud-service-iservice-is-service-sutible-for-you”&gt;基础架构作为服务（IAAS）的团队（IAAS）&lt;/a&gt;来管理和维护数据中心。该领域的一个主要挑战是监视裸金属（也称为服务器）的健康，以确保高可用性和可靠性。本文提出了一种全面的方法，用于&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/bare-metal-vs-the-world-whorld-when-when-an--when-when-to-use-this-this-i”&gt;裸机&lt;/a&gt;私人数据中心的健康监控。我们将讨论问题声明文献综述，概述行业标准解决方案，提出高级系统设计，以确保实时监控，故障检测和自动补救，并提供实验结果以显示我们的方法比现有行业解决方案更好。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着与公共云提供商相关的运营费用的增加，企业越来越多地转向建立数据中心。这种转变需要一个专门的基础架构作为服务（IAAS）团队，负责维护和管理这些数据中心。基础设施维护的一个基本方面是确保所有服务器有效，可靠地运行。这些裸金属中的任何故障或性能降解都可能导致大幅停机和收入损失。因此，有效的裸金属健康监测系统对于维持操作连续性至关重要。本文将首先定义问题陈述，然后提出行业标准可扩展解决方案以解决问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Complete Guide: Managing Multiple GitHub Accounts on One System】完整指南：在一个系统上管理多个GitHub帐户</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/managing-multiple-github-accounts</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This comprehensive guide helps developers configure and manage multiple GitHub accounts on the same system, enabling seamless switching between personal, work, and client accounts without authentication conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Managing multiple GitHub accounts on a single development machine is a common requirement for modern developers. Whether you&#39;re maintaining separate personal and professional identities, working with multiple clients, or contributing to different organizations, proper account management ensures secure access control and maintains clear commit attribution.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本综合指南可帮助开发人员在同一系统上配置和管理多个GitHub帐户，从而在没有身份验证冲突的情况下无缝切换个人，工作和客户端帐户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;概述&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在单个开发机上管理多个GitHub帐户是现代开发人员的共同要求。无论您是维护独立的个人和专业身份，与多个客户合作还是为不同的组织做出贡献，都可以确保安全访问控制并维护明确的提交归因。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Docker Desktop Enhances Developer Workflows and Observability】Docker桌面如何增强开发人员的工作流程和可观察性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-desktop-improves-dev-workflows-observability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; made it easier to build, ship, and run applications consistently using lightweight containers. While Docker Engine handles the core functionality, Docker Desktop brings those capabilities into a more accessible environment for everyday development tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Though it may not attract as much attention as container orchestration tools or &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/microservices&#34;&gt;microservices&lt;/a&gt; frameworks, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-desktop-vs-rancher-desktop&#34;&gt;Docker Desktop&lt;/a&gt; serves a practical purpose in local development. It offers a straightforward interface for managing containers directly on a developer’s machine.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1”&gt; docker &lt;/a&gt;使使用轻量级容器始终如一地构建，运行和运行应用程序。 Docker Engine处理核心功能时，Docker桌面将这些功能带入了日常开发任务的更容易访问的环境。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;尽管它可能不像容器编排工具一样吸引注意力或&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/microservices”&gt; microservices &lt;/a&gt; frameworks，&lt;a href =“在地方发展方面有一个实际目的。它提供了一个直接在开发人员机器上直接管理容器的直接界面。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>