<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Build a Simple REST API Using Python Flask and SQLite (With Tests)】使用Python烧瓶和SQLITE构建一个简单的REST API（带有测试）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-simple-api-with-python-flask-and-sql</link>
      <description>【&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; You can find the complete project and test files for this tutorial on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tejachilled/flask-rest-api-starter&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; if you’d like to follow along or extend the code further.&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial we are going to build a REST API using Python Flask. We will create a simple Flask application that serves a single endpoint, &lt;strong&gt;GET /items&lt;/strong&gt;, which returns a list of items from a SQLite database.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide is written for beginners and will walk you through each step in a straightforward way. By the end, you will have a working API, a basic test file to verify the API, and a project structure that you can zip and upload to GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA; 您可以在&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/tejachilled/flask-rask-rask-api-starter“ rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; github &lt;/a&gt;如果您想沿着或进一步扩展彩色的情况下，您可以找到本教程的完整项目和测试文件。&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本教程中，我们将使用Python烧瓶构建REST API。我们将创建一个提供单个端点的简单烧瓶应用程序，&lt;strong&gt; get /item &lt; /strong&gt;，该应用程序从SQLITE数据库中返回项目列表。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南是为初学者编写的，将以直接的方式引导您浏览每个步骤。到最后，您将拥有一个工作的API，一个基本的测试文件来验证API，并且可以将其拉链和上传到GitHub。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Knowledge Graph Embeddings and NLP Innovations】知识图嵌入和NLP创新</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-knowledge-graph-embeddings-nlp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Knowledge Graph Question Answering (KGQA) systems facilitate the structuring of typical natural language queries and consequently retrieve specific, relevant information from knowledge graphs efficiently. Given new advances in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/supercharge-llms-with-knowledge-graphs&#34;&gt;Knowledge Graph&lt;/a&gt; Embeddings (KGEs) and the sophistication of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt;, significant strides are being made in understanding complex semantic relationships and multi-hop queries. This article provides a comprehensive examination of embedding methodologies, particularly emphasizing advanced negative sampling strategies, and discusses the deployment of cutting-edge NLP architectures, such as RoBERTa, to enhance query representation and retrieval accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem Synopsis and Importance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Current KGQA frameworks face substantial obstacles in accurately interpreting, extracting, and reasoning over intricate relational data patterns present in multi-hop queries. These questions are notoriously nuanced and call for the ability to draw complex distinctions and conclusions. Unfortunately, conventional embedding techniques can miss the nuances of these relationships across the entire knowledge graph space, limiting the reliability and performance of KGQA systems. Better continual refinement of knowledge graph embeddings using more sophisticated negative sampling methods and more detailed NLP models creates excellent opportunities for enhancing query interpretation and answer precision.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;知识图答案（KGQA）系统促进了典型的自然语言查询的结构，因此有效地从知识图中检索了特定的相关信息。给定在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/supercharge-with-with--wide-graphs”&gt;知识图&lt;/a&gt; embeddings（kges）和&lt;a href =“ （LLMS）&lt;/a&gt;，在理解复杂的语义关系和多跳查询方面正在取得显着步骤。本文提供了对嵌入方法的全面检查，特别是强调了先进的负面抽样策略，并讨论了尖端的NLP体系结构（例如罗伯塔）的部署，以提高查询代表和检索准确性。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;问题概要和重要性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当前的KGQA框架在多跳查询中精确解释，提取和推理的精确解释，提取和推理方面面临着重大障碍。这些问题是细微的，并要求提出复杂的区别和结论的能力。不幸的是，传统的嵌入技术可能会错过整个知识图空间中这些关系的细微差别，从而限制了KGQA系统的可靠性和性能。更好地使用更复杂的负面抽样方法和更详细的NLP模型对知识图嵌入进行更好的持续细化，为增强查询解释和答案精度创造了极好的机会。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Assessing Bias in AI Chatbot Responses】评估AI聊天机器人回复中的偏见</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/assessing-bias-in-ai-chatbot-responses</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;AI communication in the form of chatbots has brought about a new paradigm of communication and service delivery through the use of&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-large-language-models-and-how-they-work&#34;&gt;&lt;span lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;large language models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;(LLMs) like GPT. However, as these technologies are applied in daily life, questions about the bias of the answers given by chatbots also arise. In this paper, the focus will be on discussing the ethical considerations of AI chatbots, including the detection of bias, fairness, and transparency. Bias detection techniques described in the study include fairness metrics, sensitivity analysis, and bias correction algorithms. It also emphasizes the importance of diverse training data and the integration of ethical protocols to avoid radiating bias. The consequences of bias in AI chatbots are explored in a range of cases and actual-life scenarios in settings including healthcare, recruitment, and customer relations and service. The study draws attention to the fact that more work has to be done to make certain that AI chatbots are designed and utilized in a way that is ethical and not deceptive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;Keywords&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span lang=&#34;&#34;&gt;AI Chatbots, Bias Detection, Fairness Metrics, Transparency, Ethical AI, Bias Mitigation, Generative Pretrained Transformers (GPT), Chatbot Development, Ethical Guidelines, Artificial Intelligence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】在&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;span lang =“”&gt;以聊天机器人形式的ai通信通过使用&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https:///dzone.com/articles/articles/decoding-lange-lange-lange-lange-langue-models-models-and-how-how-how-they-works-模型&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span lang =“”&gt;（llms）像gpt一样。但是，由于这些技术是在日常生活中应用的，因此也出现了有关聊天机器人给出答案的偏见的问题。在本文中，重点将在于讨论AI聊天机器人的道德考虑，包括偏见，公平和透明度的检测。研究中描述的偏置检测技术包括公平度量，灵敏度分析和偏置校正算法。它还强调了各种培训数据的重要性以及道德协议的整合以避免散发偏见。在AI聊天机器人中偏见的后果将在包括医疗保健，招聘以及客户关系和服务在内的各种情况和实际生活场景中探索。该研究提请人们注意以下事实：必须做更多的工作以确保AI聊天机器人以道德而不是欺骗性的方式设计和利用。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;span lang =“”&gt; ai聊天机器人，偏见检测，公平指标，透明度，道德AI，偏见缓解，生成预处理的变形金刚（GPT），聊天机器人发展，道德准则，人工智能&lt;/pas&gt; &lt;/pas&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p &lt;/p &lt;/p &lt;/p &lt;/p &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p &lt;/p</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【System Coexistence: Bridging Legacy and Modern Architecture】系统共存：桥接遗产和现代建筑</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/system-coexcistence-legacy-modern-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Abstract&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Organizations are challenged with integrating &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-legacy-systems-through-scalable-architectures&#34;&gt;legacy systems&lt;/a&gt; and modern applications in a way that ensures operational harmony and business continuity. This article explores the concept of system coexistence, the ability of diverse software systems built across different eras and architectures to function together within shared environments. It delves into practical strategies for achieving coexistence, such as the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-the-strangler-fig-approach-can-revitalize-comp&#34;&gt;Strangler Fig Pattern&lt;/a&gt;, adapter-based decoupling, and event-driven communication models. The article also addresses critical supporting aspects like data coexistence, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/monitoring-and-observability&#34;&gt;observability&lt;/a&gt;, and performance monitoring, emphasizing that coexistence is not merely a transitional phase but a strategic imperative for sustainable growth and innovation. Drawing on real-world examples, such as Netflix’s cloud migration and the HealthCare.gov launch failure, this piece provides a roadmap for organizations to navigate coexistence successfully while preparing for scalable, future-ready systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;We live in a world where it&#39;s easy to assume that all our applications built at different times, using the &#34;best&#34; technologies of their era will seamlessly integrate and continue to function in harmony. Yet, time and again, we’re proven wrong.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;组织面对&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-legacy-systems-systems-through-scalable-architectures”&gt; legacy Systems &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;和现代应用程序，以确保运营和商业持续性。本文探讨了系统共存的概念，即跨不同时代和体系结构在共享环境中起作用的各种软件系统的能力。它研究了实现共存的实用策略，例如&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-the-the-strangler-fig-apphach-can-revitalize-can-revitalize-comp”&gt;“宿主无花果模式” &lt;/a&gt;，基于适配器的基于适配器的取消驱动式通信模型。本文还讨论了诸如数据共存之类的关键支持方面，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/monitoring-and-bobservility”&gt;可观察性&lt;/a&gt;和绩效监控，并强调同存不仅是过渡阶段，而且是对可持续增长和创新的战略性的。该作品借鉴了Netflix的Cloud Migration和Healthcare.gov发射失败等现实世界中的示例，为组织提供了一个路线图，可以在准备可扩展的，未来的准备就绪的系统时成功导航共存。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我们生活在一个很容易假设我们在不同时间构建的应用程序，使用其时代的“最佳”技术将无缝集成并继续和谐起作用。但是，一次又一次地被证明是错误的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SaaS in an Enterprise - An Implementation Roadmap】企业中的SaaS-实施路线图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/saas-in-an-enterprise-an-implementation-roadmap</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With business software changing daily, companies are adopting &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-cloud&#34;&gt;Software as a Service (SaaS)&lt;/a&gt; solutions due to their agility, expandability, and economical nature. Compared to conventional software that must be installed on a local computer, SaaS is more appealing because it makes accessing applications over the internet much simpler.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;That said, a successful SaaS implementation entails consideration of planning, proper training, engagement of relevant parties, and continuous improvement. In this article, we discuss several approaches that ensure the effectiveness of your SaaS implementation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;随着业务软件每天更改，公司正在采用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/getting-started-cloud”&gt;软件作为服务（SaaS）&lt;/a&gt;解决方案&lt;/a&gt;由于其敏捷性，可扩展性和经济性而引起的解决方案。与必须在本地计算机上安装的传统软件相比，SaaS更具吸引力，因为它使通过Internet访问应用程序变得更加简单。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;说，成功的SAAS实施需要考虑计划，适当的培训，相关各方的参与以及持续改进。在本文中，我们讨论了确保SaaS实施有效性的几种方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 3: Power BI Embedded Demo】Power BI嵌入式分析 - 第3部分：Power BI嵌入式演示</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/power-bi-embedded-demo</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: This article presents the details of a Power BI Embedded Demo application. This is a continuation of&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;the articles&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-power-bi-authoring-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/power-bi-embedded-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;, which discuss Power BI Authoring and Power BI Embedded. So, it is recommended that you go through the previous parts of the series&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Power BI Embedded Demo&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h3 dir=&#34;auto&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;Source Code&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/robinrizvi/bi-poc/tree/master?tab=readme-ov-file#source-code&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Github: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/robinrizvi/embedded-analytics-poc&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://github.com/robinrizvi/embedded-analytics-poc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;：本文介绍了Power BI嵌入式演示应用程序的详细信息。这是&lt;span style =“ margin：0px;填充：0px;”&gt;文章&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https：//dzone.com/articles/intredacles/introduction-power-power-bi-authoring-overview-- &lt;span&gt; &lt;span =” margin =“ margin：0px; 0px; parting：0px;” style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/power-bi-embedded-overview&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;“&gt;，讨论嵌入的Power BI创作和Power BI。因此，建议您通过系列的前面部分&lt;/span&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Power BI嵌入式演示&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div dir =“ auto”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h3 dir =“ auto” tabindex =“  -  1”&gt;源代码&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/robinrizvi/bi-poc/bi-poc/tree/master?tab=readme-readme-oveadme-ov-file#source-source-code-source-code”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ auto”&gt; github：&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/robinrizvi/embedded-analytics-poc” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _blank</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Role of AI in Identity and Access Management for Organizations】AI在组织身份和访问管理中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-artificial-intelligence-ai-in-identity</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/identity-and-access-management-2&#34;&gt;Identity and Access Management (IAM)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;is a key pillar of any organization. It plays a vital role in enterprise security—securing the resources and the data of an organization by making sure only authorized users have access. As the IT infrastructure of organizations is growing exponentially and increasing cyber threats, rule based IAM solutions are often insufficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;To enhance security, streamline processes, reduce operational costs, and adapt to evolving threats, organizations are integrating their IAM systems with Artificial Intelligence (AI). This article examines the technical aspects of how AI is driving a change in IAM for organizations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/indentity-and-yccess-management-2”&gt; IDECE and Access Management（iam）&lt;/a&gt;是任何组织的关键支柱。它在企业安全中起着至关重要的作用 - 通过确保只有授权用户才能访问组织的资源和数据。随着组织的IT基础设施呈指数增长和网络威胁的增加，基于规则的IAM解决方案通常不足。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;以增强安全性，简化流程，降低操作成本并适应不断发展的威胁，组织将其IAM系统与人工智能（AI）集成在一起。本文探讨了AI如何推动组织变更的技术方面。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 19:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Code Reviews: Building an AI-Powered GitHub Integration】代码评论：建立AI驱动的GitHub集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-code-reviews-github-integration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;One common issue with growing teams with an extensive codebase is maintaining the code quality. It requires tremendous effort to maintain the code base, and manual code reviews often create a bottleneck during the development process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One standard practice is to get the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/7-ways-to-manage-pull-requests&#34;&gt;pull request&lt;/a&gt; (PR) reviewed by a senior engineer before merging it into the code base. But developers often get overloaded with reviews as they continue to deliver their regular tasks and might overlook some of the minute details that end up in production. I personally had an experience where a simple missing null check created a cascading error during migration, ultimately leading to corrupted data in production. Human beings tend to make such mistakes, and it is a very common issue.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;拥有广泛代码库的成长团队的一个常见问题是保持代码质量。它需要巨大的努力来维持代码基础，并且在开发过程中，手动代码审查通常会产生瓶颈。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一种标准做法是获得&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/7-ways-to-manage-pull-requests”&gt;拉请请求&lt;/a&gt;（pr）高级工程师在将其合并到代码库之前对其进行了审查。但是，当开发人员继续执行常规任务时，他们通常会被评论超负荷，并且可能会忽略最终生产的一些细节。我个人有一个经验，即简单缺少的无效检查在迁移过程中造成了级联错误，最终导致生产中的数据损坏。人类倾向于犯这样的错误，这是一个非常普遍的问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.24+ Native FIPS Support for Easier Compliance】进行1.24+本机FIPS支持以更容易合规</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/go-1-24-fips-compliance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In February, Go released version 1.24, introducing significant enhancements to its cryptographic libraries, particularly in achieving &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/fips-security-standard-federal-data&#34;&gt;FIPS (Federal Information Processing Standards) compliance&lt;/a&gt;. This update positions Go as a superior choice for developers building applications for U.S. federal government use. By eliminating dependency on third-party libraries and integrating FIPS compliance directly into its core, Go 1.24 simplifies and streamlines development for government-regulated industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll explore what FIPS is, why it matters, and how Go 1.24 changes the game for FIPS compliance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; 2月，GO发布了1.24版，对其加密图书馆引入了重大增强功能，尤其是在实现&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/fips-security-andart-security-standard-federal-data”&gt; FIPS（联邦信息处理标准）的合规性&lt;/a&gt;。对于为美国联邦政府使用的开发人员而言，此更新位置是开发人员的卓越选择。通过消除对第三方图书馆的依赖并将FIPS直接纳入其核心，进行1.24简化并精简政府监管行业的发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨什么是FIP，为什么重要以及如何进行1.24更改FIPS合规性的游戏。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Create a Successful API Ecosystem】如何创建成功的API生态系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-create-a-successful-api-ecosystem</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Application programming interfaces (APIs) are essential to a developer’s daily work. They are the reasons why diverse hardware and the internet communicate seamlessly. Here is an accessible look into the world of API ecosystem creation for coders of all skill levels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Is an API Ecosystem and Its Role for Devs?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;An &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/10-threats-to-an-open-api-ecosystem&#34;&gt;API ecosystem&lt;/a&gt; is a collection of APIs working together. They function alongside many programs, documents, databases, scripts, and support to make digital spaces functional and easy to use. The network is like an open forum where various stakeholders can request services and information from other experts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;应用程序编程接口（API）对于开发人员的日常工作至关重要。这就是为什么多样化硬件和互联网无缝交流的原因。这是针对各个技能水平的编码人员的API生态系统创建世界的可访问外观。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;什么是API生态系统及其在开发人员中的作用？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; an &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/10-threats-to-to-to-an-apen-api-ecosystem”&gt; api生态系统&lt;/a&gt;是一个合作的API集合。它们与许多程序，文档，数据库，脚本和支持一起运行，以使数字空间功能易用且易于使用。该网络就像一个开放论坛，各种利益相关者可以向其他专家索取服务和信息。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>