<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How AI Agents Are Transforming Enterprise Automation Architecture】AI代理如何改变企业自动化体系结构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-ai-agents-transform-automation-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Imagine someone in the early 20s predicting that, in the future, intelligent autonomous systems would be capable of executing tasks and solving problems independently. Fast forward to today, and with the rise of machine learning and natural language processing, humans can now build intelligent agents that seamlessly blend both machine and human capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;With this exclusive guide, we will examine the nature of AI agents, how these AI Agents for enterprise automation function, and their revolutionary effects across various sectors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;想象一下20世纪初的某人预测，将来，智能自主系统将能够执行任务并独立解决问题。快进到今天，随着机器学习和自然语言处理的兴起，人类现在可以建立智能的代理，使机器和人类能力无缝融合。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在此独家指南中，我们将研究AI代理的性质，这些AI代理如何用于企业自动化功能以及它们在各个部门的革命性效应。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling DevOps With NGINX Caching: Reducing Latency and Backend Load】使用NGINX缓存缩放Devops：减少延迟和后端负载</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-devops-principles-for-reducing-web-latency</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;In large-scale companies with huge DevOps environments, caching isn’t just an optimization — it’s a survival strategy. Applications teams working with artifact repositories, container registries, and CI/CD pipelines often encounter performance issues that aren’t rooted in code inefficiencies, but rather in the overwhelming volume of metadata requests hammering artifact services or in short binary storage systems, which are key to the functioning of any application or batch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;&#34;A well-architected caching strategy can mitigate these challenges by reducing unnecessary backend load and improving request efficiency.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;在具有巨大DevOps环境的大型公司中，缓存不仅是一种优化，而且是一种生存策略。使用工件存储库，容器注册表和CI/CD管道工作的应用团队通常会遇到性能问题，这些问题不是植根于代码效率低下的性能，而是在限制元数据的压倒性元数据请求中，或者在短二进制存储系统中，这是任何应用程序或二进制存储系统的关键。&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;“良好的缓存策略可以通过降低不必要的后端负载并提高请求效率来减轻这些挑战。” &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fraud Detection Using Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning】使用人工智能和机器学习的欺诈检测</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fraud-detection-using-artificial-intelligence-ml</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Introduction&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;For industries such as e-commerce, finance, and insurance where transactional security is paramount, fraud detection is a pressing challenge. Until a decade ago, organizations were relying on predefined rules and thresholds which are often not sufficient to detect fraudulent activities. &amp;nbsp;With the advent of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ai-ml&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML)&lt;/a&gt;, organizations are enabling automated, adaptive, and real time anomaly detection techniques for fraud detection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In this article we will do a detailed review of AI and ML methodologies in fraud detection, including supervised, unsupervised, and deep learning techniques. Furthermore, this article also delves into the challenges of using AI in fraud detection.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;对于电子商务，金融和保险等行业，交易安全至关重要，欺诈检测是一个紧迫的挑战。直到十年前，组织一直依靠预定义的规则和阈值，这些规则和阈值通常不足以检测欺诈活动。  随着&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/ai-ml”&gt;人工智能（AI）和机器学习（ML）&lt;/a&gt;的出现，组织正在实现自动化，适应性和实时的欺诈检测技术。&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在本文中，我们将对欺诈检测中的AI和ML方法进行详细评论，包括受监督，无监督和深度学习技术。此外，本文还深入研究了在欺诈检测中使用AI的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ensuring Configuration Consistency Across Global Data Centers】确保整体数据中心的配置一致性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/configuration-consistency-data-centers</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today, nearly every large company operates several data centers distributed across the globe. Each of these data centers hosts a variety of infrastructure services such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/essential-mysql&#34;&gt;MySQL&lt;/a&gt;, Redis, Hive, and message queues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;For scalability and adherence to the&amp;nbsp;DRY (Don&#39;t Repeat Yourself)&amp;nbsp;principle in system design, it&#39;s crucial that the same codebase is used across all regions. However, engineers responsible for writing and maintaining this code are often spread across different geographies. As a result, teams may not always be aligned on system configurations—even within the same region. This misalignment leads to discrepancies in configuration across data centers.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;今天，几乎每个大型公司都经营着分布在全球范围内的几个数据中心。这些数据中心每个中心都有各种基础架构服务，例如&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/esential-mysql”&gt; mysql &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，redis，hive，hive和message queues。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;为系统设计中的干燥（不要重复自己）原理的可伸缩性和依从性，至关重要的是，在所有区域中使用相同的代码库。但是，负责编写和维护此代码的工程师通常会分布在不同的地理位置上。结果，甚至在同一区域内，团队可能并不总是在系统配置上对齐。这种未对准导致跨数据中心的配置差异。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unmasking Entity-Based Data Masking: Best Practices 2025】揭露基于实体的数据掩盖：最佳实践2025</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unmasking-entity-based-data-masking-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Masking data to protect confidentiality has become a mandate more than ever before. As enterprises attempt to mitigate their workloads to multi-tenant cloud environments and data lakes etc., it makes perfect sense to revisit the masking strategies and be prepared for the future. That, too, when compliance regulations have tightened their grip over potential defaulters.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;That&#39;s exactly why entity-based masking is gaining acceptance across industry facets. It moves sensitive data across the landscape without exposing it. This enables organizations to comply with privacy regulations such as the GDPR, CCPA, and HIPPA.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;掩盖数据以保护机密性已比以往任何时候都更加授权。当企业试图减轻其工作量到多租户云环境和数据湖等，重新审视掩盖策略并为未来做好准备是非常有意义的。当合规法规加强了对潜在违法者的控制时，这也是如此。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这就是为什么基于实体的掩饰正在跨行业方面获得接受的原因。它在不暴露的情况下将敏感数据移动到整个景观中。这使组织能够遵守GDPR，CCPA和HIPPA等隐私法规。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agentic AI for Automated Application Security and Vulnerability Management】用于自动化应用程序安全性和漏洞管理的代理AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-ai-security-vulnerability-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It was not so long ago that I was having a much closer look at how AI is becoming embedded in our everyday developer work. I have watched more intelligent code suggestions, automated testing routines, and those ubiquitous chatbots become a normal part of the everyday toolkit. They are useful, naturally, but at their core, they are still fundamentally reactive, they still wait for you to inquire of them before taking action.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What has really blown me away recently is the emergence of agentic AI. It is completely different, it does not just sit around and wait to be told what to do, but instead it takes charge itself. It can decide what should be done, strategize the steps, and even adjust if something unexpected happens. It&#39;s sort of like having a colleague who is always planning ahead, as opposed to merely carrying out orders.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;不久前，我正在仔细研究AI如何嵌入我们的日常开发人员工作中。我已经观看了更智能的代码建议，自动测试例程，而这些无处不在的聊天机器人成为日常工具包的正常部分。它们自然很有用，但是从根本上讲，它们仍然具有反应性，他们仍然在等待您在采取行动之前询问它们。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近真正炸毁了我的是Agesic AI的出现。它是完全不同的，它不仅坐在周围等待被告知该怎么做，而且还可以自行负责。它可以决定应采取的措施，制定步骤，甚至可以调整发生意外的事情。这就像有一个总是在提前计划的同事，而不是仅执行订单。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Role of Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) in Development of AI-Infused Enterprise Applications】检索增强发电（RAG）在AI注入企业应用程序开发中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rag-in-ai-enterprise-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is transforming enterprise applications, enabling businesses to enhance efficiency, improve decision-making, and unlock new opportunities. However, AI adoption is not a one-size-fits-all approach—organizations integrate AI at different levels depending on their needs, existing infrastructure, and strategic goals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores three categories of &lt;strong&gt;AI-infused applications&lt;/strong&gt;, their &lt;strong&gt;enterprise use cases&lt;/strong&gt;, and how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-retrieval-augmented-generation&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;is revolutionizing AI adoption by improving accuracy, relevance, and contextual understanding in AI-driven applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能（AI）正在改变企业应用程序，使企业能够提高效率，提高决策并解锁新的机会。但是，AI采用并不是一种千篇一律的方法 - 组织的组织会根据其需求，现有基础设施和战略目标而在不同层面上整合AI。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores three categories of &lt;strong&gt;AI-infused applications&lt;/strong&gt;, their &lt;strong&gt;enterprise use cases&lt;/strong&gt;, and how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-retrieval-augmented-generation&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;is revolutionizing AI adoption by improving accuracy,相关性，以及在AI驱动的应用程序中的上下文理解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【5 Subtle Indicators Your Development Environment Is Under Siege】5个微妙的指标您的开发环境正在围困</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/indicators-development-environment-under-siege</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Think your organization is too small to be a target for threat actors? Think again. In 2025, attackers no longer distinguish between size or sector. Whether you’re a flashy tech giant, a mid-sized auto dealership software provider, or a small startup, if you store data someone is trying to access it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As security measures around production environments strengthen, which they have, attackers are shifting left—straight into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-devops-in-enhancing-the-software-devel&#34;&gt;software development lifecycle (SDLC)&lt;/a&gt;. These less-protected and complex environments have become prime targets, where gaps in security can expose sensitive data and derail operations if exploited. That’s why recognizing the warning signs of nefarious behavior is critical. But identification alone isn’t enough—security and development teams must work together to address these risks before attackers exploit them. From suspicious clone activity to overlooked code review changes, subtle indicators can reveal when bad actors are lurking in your development environment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;认为您的组织太小，无法成为威胁参与者的目标？想一想。在2025年，攻击者不再区分大小或行业。无论您是一个浮华的技术巨头，中型汽车经销店软件提供商，还是小型初创公司，如果您存储了有人试图访问它的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着生产环境周围的安全措施的加强，攻击者正在向左移动，以至于&lt;a a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-devops-in-enhancing-the-software-the-software-devel-------这些受较少且复杂的环境已成为主要目标，如果利用了安全性差距可以暴露敏感数据并出轨操作。这就是为什么认识到邪恶行为的警告信号至关重要的原因。但是，仅识别是不够的 - 安全性和开发团队必须共同努力解决这些风险，然后才能利用攻击者。从可疑的克隆活动到被忽视的代码审查更改，微妙的指标可以揭示何时潜伏在您的开发环境中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Deep Dive Into Firmware Over the Air for IoT Devices】深入探究物联网设备的固件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deep-dive-into-fota-for-iot</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;An Overview of IoT Devices and FOTA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IoT devices are a combination of hardware and software which are programmed to collect and transmit the data over to the internet, other networks, or a variety of applications. There are various categories of IoT devices such as sensors, actuators, machines, gateways, and more. These IoT devices can be used independently, or can be attached to any other devices such as appliances, doors, industrial machinery, medical equipment, and other important assets. In today’s fast-paced environment, these devices offer the capability to provide all important sensory information without any manual intervention to their users via integrations with mobile apps or analytical platforms. These sensors solve various real-world problems such as asset tracking, infrastructure management, condition-based monitoring, industrial automation, and more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Companies that offer IoT solutions have to deploy and manage a large number of&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/iot-device-management-streamlining-connectivity-in&#34;&gt; IoT devices&lt;/a&gt; in globally-dispersed locations. To make sure that all the devices are working and transmitting the telemetry data as expected without any failure, it is very important to monitor these devices and keep them updated with the latest version of their firmware or software. These new versions of the firmware may contain bug fixes, patches for security vulnerabilities, or new functionalities throughout the device’s lifecycle. Since IoT devices are low powered, low memory constrained devices, and deployed at distributed locations, it is crucial to do &lt;strong&gt;firmware upgrades over the air (FOTA)&lt;/strong&gt; for these devices. FOTA happens remotely, and users do not need to be physically available at the same location. FOTA is an essential process for any IoT solution offerings as it enables IoT devices to provide uninterrupted flow of data to the users.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; IoT设备和FOTA &lt;/h2&gt;的概述&#xA;&lt;p&gt; IoT设备是硬件和软件的组合，这些硬件和软件被编程为以将数据收集和传输到Internet，其他网络或各种应用程序。有各种类型的物联网设备，例如传感器，执行器，机器，网关等。这些物联网设备可以独立使用，也可以连接到任何其他设备，例如设备，门，工业机械，医疗设备和其他重要资产。在当今快节奏的环境中，这些设备提供了通过与移动应用程序或分析平台的集成为其用户提供所有手动干预的所有重要感官信息的能力。这些传感器解决了各种现实世界中的问题，例如资产跟踪，基础架构管理，基于条件的监控，工业自动化等。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;提供IoT解决方案的公司必须部署和管理大量&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/iot-device-management-mmanagement-streamlining-connectivity-in&gt; IOT设备”&gt; IOT设备&lt;/a&gt;为了确保所有设备都可以按预期工作和传输遥测数据，而不会发生任何故障，因此监视这些设备并保持最新版本的固件或软件非常重要。这些新版本的固件可能包含错误修复程序，用于安全漏洞的补丁程序或整个设备生命周期中的新功能。由于物联网设备的功率低，内存限制的设备低，并且在分布式位置部署，因此对于这些设备进行&lt;strong&gt;固件升级（FOTA）&lt;/strong&gt;至关重要。 FOTA发生远程发生，用户不需要在同一位置进行物理上的可用。 FOTA是任何物联网解决方案产品的重要过程，因为它使IoT设备能够向用户提供不间断的数据流。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agile and Quality Engineering: A Holistic Perspective】敏捷和质量工程：整体观点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/holistic-approach-to-agile-and-quality-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Agile has emerged as a widely adopted and effective software development methodology, enabling teams to deliver high-quality products to end-users with increased speed and efficiency. Within &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/agile&#34;&gt;Agile frameworks&lt;/a&gt; such as Scrum, high-level software requirements or business needs are systematically decomposed into smaller, manageable units known as epics, which are further refined into user stories. Each user story is defined with specific acceptance criteria to ensure clarity in implementation and validation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Collaboration is a fundamental principle of Agile software development, emphasizing collective ownership and teamwork over individual contributions. Agile methodologies prioritize a &#34;we&#34; mindset, fostering a cohesive Scrum team that works iteratively to achieve project goals. Agile projects are executed in time-boxed iterations known as sprints, typically lasting two to four weeks. At the end of each sprint, the team produces a potentially shippable increment of the software. Various ceremonies, such as sprint planning, daily stand-ups, sprint reviews, and retrospectives, facilitate continuous improvement and alignment within the Scrum team.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;敏捷已成为一种广泛采用的有效的软件开发方法，使团队能够以提高速度和效率的最终用户提供高质量的产品。在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/agile”&gt;敏捷框架&lt;/a&gt;（例如Scrum，High-Level软件要求或业务需求）等敏捷框架被系统地分解为较小的，可管理的单位，这些单元被称为Epics，这些单元被进一步完善，这些单位被进一步精炼到用户故事中。每个用户故事都具有特定的接受标准，以确保实施和验证方面的清晰度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;协作是敏捷软件开发的基本原则，强调集体所有权和团队合作而不是个人贡献。敏捷的方法论优先考虑“我们”的心态，促进了一个迭代实现项目目标的凝聚力的Scrum团队。敏捷项目在被称为Sprints的时迭代迭代中执行，通常持续2到四个星期。在每次冲刺的结尾，团队会产生该软件的潜在易发性增量。各种仪式，例如冲刺计划，日常站立，冲刺评论和回顾展，促进了Scrum团队的持续改进和一致性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>