<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Tired of Reverse-Engineering Code? A Data-First Pattern for Legacy Modernization】厌倦了逆向工程代码？遗留现代化的数据优先模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-data-first-pattern-for-legacy-modernization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;379&#34; data-start=&#34;176&#34;&gt;We have all faced the &lt;strong data-end=&#34;220&#34; data-start=&#34;198&#34;&gt;Monolith from Hell&lt;/strong&gt;. It’s a 20-year-old system. The documentation is missing, the original architects retired a decade ago, and the codebase is a tangled mess of spaghetti logic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;580&#34; data-start=&#34;381&#34;&gt;When tasked with modernizing such a system, the instinct is a &lt;strong data-end=&#34;470&#34; data-start=&#34;443&#34;&gt;function-first approach&lt;/strong&gt;: read the source code, trace the logic, and try to replicate the existing functionality in a modern language.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;379&#34; data-start=&#34;176&#34;&gt;我们都曾面对过&lt;strong data-end=&#34;220&#34; data-start=&#34;198&#34;&gt;来自地狱的巨石&lt;/strong&gt;。这是一个已有20年历史的系统。文档丢失了，最初的架构师十年前就退休了，代码库是一团混乱的意大利面条逻辑。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;580&#34; data-start=&#34;381&#34;&gt;当承担对此类系统进行现代化改造的任务时，本能是一种&lt;strong data-end=&#34;470&#34; data-start=&#34;443&#34;&gt;功能优先的方法&lt;/strong&gt;：阅读源代码，跟踪逻辑，并尝试用现代语言复制现有功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AutoML vs. LLMs: A Developer’s Guide to Efficient ML Pipeline Generation】AutoML 与 LLM：高效 ML 管道生成的开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automl-vs-llms-a-guide-to-efficient-ml-pipeline-gen</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;568&#34; data-start=&#34;179&#34;&gt;In the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/taming-the-ai-wild-west&#34;&gt;current AI landscape&lt;/a&gt;, the hype cycle is undeniably focused on large language models (LLMs). From code generation to reasoning, models like GPT-4 and Llama 3 have transformed how we interact with data. However, for machine learning (ML) engineers tasked with building robust, production-grade pipelines for tabular data or predictive analytics, LLMs are not always the silver bullet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;767&#34; data-start=&#34;570&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-for-ai-systems-automation&#34;&gt;Automated Machine Learning (AutoML)&lt;/a&gt; has quietly matured into a powerhouse technology, automating the tedious aspects of data science — feature engineering, model selection, and hyperparameter tuning.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;568&#34; data-start=&#34;179&#34;&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/taming-the-ai-wild-west&#34;&gt;当前的 AI 格局&lt;/a&gt;中，炒作周期无疑集中在大型语言模型 (LLM) 上。从代码生成到推理，GPT-4 和 Llama 3 等模型改变了我们与数据交互的方式。然而，对于负责为表格数据或预测分析构建强大的生产级管道的机器学习 (ML) 工程师来说，法学硕士并不总是灵丹妙药。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;767&#34; data-start=&#34;570&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-for-ai-systems-automation&#34;&gt;自动化机器学习 (AutoML)&lt;/a&gt; 已悄然成熟为一项强大的技术，可实现数据科学中繁琐的工作（特征工程、模型选择和超参数调整）的自动化。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud to Local Copilots: A Hybrid Path to Privacy and Control】云到本地副驾驶：隐私和控制的混合路径</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-to-local-copilots-hybrid-path-to-privacy-and-control</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;852&#34; data-start=&#34;203&#34;&gt;Software usage patterns have always evolved alongside hardware capabilities. In recent years, with the rise of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/build-right-infrastructure-ai-private-cloud&#34;&gt;GPUs and cloud-based AI copilots&lt;/a&gt; such as GitHub Copilot, this evolution has accelerated — offering developers real-time code suggestions, documentation support, and automated testing at scale. However, concerns around personal data privacy, the cost of copilot usage, and the need for greater autonomy have given rise to local AI copilots. By hosting models on a local device, developers gain tighter control over sensitive data, reduce dependency on cloud providers, and unlock performance benefits tailored to their device’s capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Cloud Copilots vs. Local Copilots&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1194&#34; data-start=&#34;892&#34;&gt;Cloud-based copilots have become the default entry point for many developers, especially in workplace settings, offering seamless integration with cloud-hosted repositories and services. However, there are trade-offs — namely recurring subscription costs and potential exposure of sensitive code or data.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;852&#34; data-start=&#34;203&#34;&gt;软件使用模式始终与硬件功能一起发展。近年来，随着 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/build-right-infrastruct-ai-private-cloud&#34;&gt;GPU 和基于云的 AI copilot&lt;/a&gt;（例如 GitHub Copilot）的兴起，这种演变加速了——为开发人员提供实时代码建议、文档支持和大规模自动化测试。然而，对个人数据隐私、副驾驶使用成本以及更大自主权的需求的担忧引发了本地人工智能副驾驶的出现。通过在本地设备上托管模型，开发人员可以更严格地控制敏感数据，减少对云提供商的依赖，并释放适合其设备功能的性能优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;云副驾驶与本地副驾驶&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1194&#34; data-start=&#34;892&#34;&gt;基于云的 copilot 已成为许多开发人员的默认切入点，尤其是在工作场所环境中，提供与云托管存储库和服务的无缝集成。然而，也存在一些权衡——即经常性订阅成本和敏感代码或数据的潜在暴露。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【5 Challenges and Solutions in Mobile App Testing】移动应用测试的 5 个挑战和解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/5-challenges-in-mobile-app-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;552&#34; data-start=&#34;175&#34;&gt;Testing is one of the final stages of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mobile-app-development-process&#34;&gt;mobile app development&lt;/a&gt; before you’re ready for launch. The finish line may seem close, but it might not be. If you encounter mobile app testing challenges unprepared, you may have to push your launch window back by days or even weeks. Here’s why mobile app testing is essential, the challenges you might encounter, and how to resolve them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Importance of Mobile App Testing&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;977&#34; data-start=&#34;595&#34;&gt;The mobile app market is booming. By 2026, the Apple App Store is expected to see an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.statista.com/statistics/1010716/apple-app-store-google-play-app-downloads-forecast/?srsltid=AfmBOoqpDMibNFmFBaoSgiNgOFAeI4KMsLrXXGTO2nk-HobMVgfcQymn&#34;&gt;estimated 38 billion downloads&lt;/a&gt;, while projections indicate the Google Play Store will reach approximately &lt;strong data-end=&#34;815&#34; data-start=&#34;790&#34;&gt;143 billion downloads&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;— representing &lt;strong data-end=&#34;836&#34; data-start=&#34;829&#34;&gt;15%&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong data-end=&#34;848&#34; data-start=&#34;841&#34;&gt;30%&lt;/strong&gt; increases, respectively. Competition is intense, so you must prioritize comprehensive testing to attract and retain an audience.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;552&#34; data-start=&#34;175&#34;&gt;测试是准备发布之前&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mobile-app-development-process&#34;&gt;移动应用开发&lt;/a&gt;的最后阶段之一。终点线可能看起来很接近，但事实可能并非如此。如果您在毫无准备的情况下遇到移动应用程序测试挑战，您可能不得不将启动窗口推迟几天甚至几周。以下是移动应用测试至关重要的原因、您可能遇到的挑战以及解决这些挑战的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;移动应用测试的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;977&#34; data-start=&#34;595&#34;&gt;移动应用市场正在蓬勃发展。到 2026 年，Apple App Store 的下载量预计将达到 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.statista.com/statistics/1010716/apple-app-store-google-play-app-downloads-forecast/?srsltid=AfmBOoqpDMibNFmFBaoSgiNgOFAeI4KMsLrXXGTO2nk-HobMVgfcQymn&#34;&gt;估计 380 亿下载量&lt;/a&gt;，而预测表明 Google Play 商店的下载量将达到约 &lt;strong data-end=&#34;815&#34; data-start=&#34;790&#34;&gt;1430 亿次&lt;/strong&gt;，分别增加 &lt;strong data-end=&#34;836&#34; data-start=&#34;829&#34;&gt;15%&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong data-end=&#34;848&#34; data-start=&#34;841&#34;&gt;30%&lt;/strong&gt;。竞争非常激烈，因此您必须优先考虑全面测试才能吸引并留住受众。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is TOON a Boon for AI Communication, LLM Token Cost Economics?】TOON 是人工智能通信、LLM 代币成本经济学的福音吗？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/toon-ai-communication-llm-token-costs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern AI systems are hitting a new kind of bottleneck. It is not CPU, memory, or network bandwidth. It is &lt;strong&gt;tokens&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With large language models (LLMs), every character sent and received is tokenized, processed, and billed. At a small scale, this cost is easy to ignore. At enterprise scale, it becomes a first‑order architectural concern. This shift is driving interest in formats designed specifically for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a2a-mcp-agent-ai-communication-evolution&#34;&gt;AI communication&lt;/a&gt;, such as &lt;strong&gt;TOON (Token‑Oriented Object Notation)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代人工智能系统正在遇到一种新的瓶颈。它不是 CPU、内存或网络带宽。它是&lt;strong&gt;令牌&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借助大型语言模型 (LLM)，发送和接收的每个字符都会被标记化、处理和计费。在小规模下，这种成本很容易被忽视。在企业规模上，它成为首要的架构问题。这种转变引发了人们对专门为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a2a-mcp-agent-ai-communication-evolution&#34;&gt;人工智能通信&lt;/a&gt;设计的格式的兴趣，例如&lt;strong&gt;TOON（面向令牌的对象表示法）&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Monolith Migration for Resource-Constrained Edge Systems】资源受限边缘系统的自动化整体迁移</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-monolith-migration-for-resource-constra</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;323&#34; data-start=&#34;158&#34;&gt;We usually design &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservices-design-patterns-for-high-resiliency&#34;&gt;microservices&lt;/a&gt; with a &lt;em data-end=&#34;210&#34; data-start=&#34;197&#34;&gt;cloud-first&lt;/em&gt; mindset. If a container needs more RAM, we scale it up. If latency increases, we add a cache or a load balancer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;741&#34; data-start=&#34;325&#34;&gt;But the world is shifting toward &lt;strong data-end=&#34;394&#34; data-start=&#34;358&#34;&gt;Software-Defined Vehicles (SDVs)&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong data-end=&#34;417&#34; data-start=&#34;399&#34;&gt;edge computing&lt;/strong&gt;. In these environments, hardware is fixed, and latency can be a matter of life and death (e.g., autonomous braking systems). &lt;a href=&#34;https://launchdarkly.com/blog/migrating-legacy-monolithic-applications-microservices/&#34;&gt;Migrating a legacy C/C++ monolith to microservices&lt;/a&gt; in this context is dangerous. The overhead of containerization (Docker) and inter-process communication (IPC) can easily overwhelm an embedded CPU.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;323&#34; data-start=&#34;158&#34;&gt;我们通常以&lt;em data-end=&#34;210&#34; data-start=&#34;197&#34;&gt;云优先&lt;/em&gt;的心态来设计&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservices-design-patterns-for-high-resiliency&#34;&gt;微服务&lt;/a&gt;。如果容器需要更多 RAM，我们会对其进行扩展。如果延迟增加，我们会添加缓存或负载均衡器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;741&#34; data-start=&#34;325&#34;&gt;但世界正在转向&lt;strong data-end=&#34;394&#34; data-start=&#34;358&#34;&gt;软件定义车辆 (SDV)&lt;/strong&gt; 和&lt;strong data-end=&#34;417&#34; data-start=&#34;399&#34;&gt;边缘计算&lt;/strong&gt;。在这些环境中，硬件是固定的，延迟可能是生死攸关的问题（例如，自动制动系统）。在这种情况下，&lt;a href=&#34;https://launchdarkly.com/blog/migration-legacy-monolithic-applications-microservices/&#34;&gt;将旧版 C/C++ 整体迁移到微服务&lt;/a&gt;是危险的。容器化 (Docker) 和进程间通信 (IPC) 的开销很容易压垮嵌入式 CPU。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【LLMs in Data Engineering: How Generative AI is Changing ETL and Analytics】数据工程法学硕士：生成式 AI 如何改变 ETL 和分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llms-in-data-engineering-gen-ai-changing-etl-analytics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;670&#34; data-start=&#34;172&#34;&gt;For decades, data engineering has revolved around building reliable pipelines to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-elt-1&#34;&gt;extract, transform, and load (ETL) data&lt;/a&gt;, ensuring that business analysts and data scientists have access to trustworthy datasets. The role has always focused on &lt;strong&gt;scale&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;reliability&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;speed&lt;/strong&gt;. But with the rise of &lt;strong&gt;large language models (LLMs)&lt;/strong&gt;, the traditional definition of ETL and analytics is shifting. Generative AI is no longer just a research curiosity; it’s becoming a powerful co-pilot in modern data platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;986&#34; data-start=&#34;672&#34;&gt;This article explores how LLMs are impacting ETL and analytics, the opportunities and challenges they create, and what the near future may look like. To make things practical, we’ll refer to a &lt;strong&gt;real-world case&lt;/strong&gt; in which a global retailer used LLMs to automate parts of its data transformation and analytics pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;670&#34; data-start=&#34;172&#34;&gt;几十年来，数据工程一直围绕着构建可靠的管道来&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-elt-1&#34;&gt;提取、转换和加载 (ETL) 数据&lt;/a&gt;，确保业务分析师和数据科学家能够访问值得信赖的数据集。该角色始终关注&lt;strong&gt;规模&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;可靠性&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;速度&lt;/strong&gt;。但随着&lt;strong&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/strong&gt; 的兴起，ETL 和分析的传统定义正在发生变化。生成式人工智能不再只是一种研究好奇心；而是一种研究兴趣。它正在成为现代数据平台的强大副驾驶。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;986&#34; data-start=&#34;672&#34;&gt;本文探讨了 LLM 如何影响 ETL 和分析、它们带来的机遇和挑战，以及不久的将来会是什么样子。为了使事情变得实用，我们将参考一个&lt;strong&gt;现实案例&lt;/strong&gt;，其中一家全球零售商使用法学硕士来自动化其部分数据转换和分析管道。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Airflow vs. Dagster vs. Prefect: Which Scheduler Fits Your Data Team?】Airflow、Dagster 与 Prefect：哪个调度程序适合您的数据团队？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/airflow-vs-dagster-vs-prefect-which-scheduler-fits</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Workflow orchestration sits at the heart of modern &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-engineering-for-ai-native-architectures&#34;&gt;data engineering&lt;/a&gt;. Whether you’re running daily ETL jobs, streaming pipelines, or machine learning workflows, you need a scheduler to manage dependencies, retries, and monitoring. For years, Apache Airflow has been the default choice, but newer tools like Dagster and Prefect have emerged, each promising a more modern approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;871&#34; data-start=&#34;603&#34;&gt;The question is: &lt;strong data-end=&#34;665&#34; data-start=&#34;620&#34;&gt;Which scheduler best fits your data team?&lt;/strong&gt; In this article, we’ll explore the strengths and trade-offs of Airflow, Dagster, and Prefect through real-world lenses. We’ll focus less on abstract features and more on how these tools behave in practice.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;工作流编排是现代&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-engineering-for-ai-native-architectures&#34;&gt;数据工程&lt;/a&gt;的核心。无论您是运行日常 ETL 作业、流式传输管道还是机器学习工作流程，您都需要一个调度程序来管理依赖项、重试和监控。多年来，Apache Airflow 一直是默认选择，但 Dagster 和 Prefect 等更新的工具已经出现，每个工具都承诺提供更现代的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;871&#34; data-start=&#34;603&#34;&gt;问题是：&lt;strong data-end=&#34;665&#34; data-start=&#34;620&#34;&gt;哪种调度程序最适合您的数据团队？&lt;/strong&gt;在本文中，我们将通过现实世界的视角探讨 Airflow、Dagster 和 Prefect 的优势和权衡。我们将较少关注抽象功能，而更多地关注这些工具在实践中的行为方式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Turning Architectural Assumptions into Enforceable Code】将架构假设转化为可执行的代码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enforce-architectural-assumptions-with-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When Everything Works But Nothing Aligns&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;There is a moment in every large AI initiative when the system behaves correctly, the model behaves correctly, and yet the entire pipeline enters a state where nothing aligns with what was promised. The logs look fine. Dashboards look clean. Latency spikes are non-critical. But a design boundary that was agreed upon months earlier no longer maps to the reality the system is operating in. The failure does not originate in code. It originates in the assumptions underneath the code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The incident that pushed me to formalise this came from a simple requirement: the inference layer needed p95 latency under 180 ms during peak loads. Three teams signed off on it. Architecture captured it in diagrams, delivery scoped for it, and infra agreed to provision accordingly. But by the time the model reached production, none of those teams were working off the same interpretation. The latency budget existed. The system no longer matched it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;当一切正常但没有任何一致时&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在每一个大型人工智能项目中，都会有这样一个时刻：系统表现正确，模型表现正确，但整个流程却进入了一种与承诺不相符的状态。日志看起来不错。仪表板看起来很干净。延迟峰值并不重要。但几个月前商定的设计边界不再映射到系统运行的现实。故障并非源于代码。它源于代码下的假设。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;促使我正式确定这一点的事件来自一个简单的要求：推理层在峰值负载期间需要 180 毫秒以下的 p95 延迟。三支团队签署了该协议。架构在图表中捕获了它，交付范围针对它，基础设施同意相应地提供。但当模型投入生产时，这些团队都没有做出相同的解释。延迟预算是存在的。系统已不再匹配。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Generative AI Can Transform Cloud Support Operations: A Practical Framework】生成式人工智能如何改变云支持运营：实用框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-gen-ai-can-transform-cloud-support-operations</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;340&#34; data-start=&#34;326&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;578&#34; data-start=&#34;341&#34;&gt;Cloud support is no longer a staffing problem — it’s a cognition and scalability problem. As cloud platforms grow in complexity, support engineers are spending more time searching, routing, and rewriting than actually solving issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;830&#34; data-start=&#34;580&#34;&gt;This article introduces a &lt;strong data-end=&#34;631&#34; data-start=&#34;606&#34;&gt;three-layer framework&lt;/strong&gt; showing how generative AI can improve resolution speed, reduce escalations, and enhance communication quality in modern cloud support teams, using a vendor-neutral, implementation-focused approach.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;340&#34; data-start=&#34;326&#34;&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;578&#34; data-start=&#34;341&#34;&gt;云支持不再是人员配置问题，而是认知和可扩展性问题。随着云平台变得越来越复杂，支持工程师花在搜索、路由和重写上的时间比实际解决问题的时间还要多。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;830&#34; data-start=&#34;580&#34;&gt;本文介绍了一个&lt;strong data-end=&#34;631&#34; data-start=&#34;606&#34;&gt;三层框架&lt;/strong&gt;，展示了生成式 AI 如何使用供应商中立、以实施为中心的方法提高现代云支持团队的解决速度、减少升级并提高沟通质量。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>