<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Java Applications for Arm64 in the Cloud】在云中优化 Arm64 Java 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-java-arm64-cloud-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Java remains one of the most popular languages for enterprise applications running on the cloud. While languages like Go, Rust, JavaScript, and Python have a high profile for cloud application developers, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://redmonk.com/rstephens/2024/09/12/top20-jun2024/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RedMonk language rankings&lt;/a&gt; have ranked Java in the top three most popular languages throughout the history of the ranking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When deploying applications to the cloud, there are a few key differences between deployment environments and development environments. Whether you’re spinning up a microservice application on Kubernetes or launching virtual machine instances, it is important to tune your &lt;a href=&#34;https://amperecomputing.com/glossary/java-virtual-machine&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Java Virtual Machine (JVM)&lt;/a&gt; to ensure that you are getting your money’s worth from your cloud spend. It pays to know how the JVM allocates resources and to ensure you use them efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Java 仍然是在云上运行的企业应用程序最流行的语言之一。虽然 Go、Rust、JavaScript 和 Python 等语言在云应用程序开发人员中享有很高的知名度，但 &lt;a href=&#34;https://redmonk.com/rstephens/2024/09/12/top20-jun2024/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RedMonk 语言排名&lt;/a&gt;在整个排名历史上将 Java 列为最受欢迎的三种语言。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;将应用程序部署到云时，部署环境和开发环境之间存在一些关键差异。无论您是在 Kubernetes 上启动微服务应用程序还是启动虚拟机实例，调整 &lt;a href=&#34;https://amperecomputing.com/glossary/java-virtual-machine&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Java 虚拟机 (JVM)&lt;/a&gt; 都非常重要，以确保您从云支出中获得物有所值。了解 JVM 如何分配资源并确保有效地使用它们是值得的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Architecture of Prompts: Designing Reliable, Deterministic AI Systems】提示的架构：设计可靠、确定性的人工智能系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/architecture-of-prompts-ai-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If 2025 was the year organizations discovered prompt engineering as a discipline, 2026 will be when we establish it as standard practice. Prompts aren&#39;t clever text tricks—they&#39;re software components with architectures, failure modes, and lifecycle requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As production LLM deployments multiply, consequences escalate from &#34;weird response&#34; to &#34;compliance violation&#34; or &#34;incorrect customer data.&#34; This demands a fundamental shift: we must think about prompts like APIs or microservices. A prompt isn&#39;t a sentence—it&#39;s an engineered system designed for consistent outputs under varying conditions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果说 2025 年是组织发现即时工程作为一门学科的一年，那么 2026 年我们将把它确立为标准实践。提示并不是聪明的文本技巧——它们是具有架构、故障模式和生命周期要求的软件组件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着生产 LLM 部署的增加，后果会从“奇怪的响应”升级为“违反合规性”或“不正确的客户数据”。这需要根本性的转变：我们必须考虑 API 或微服务等提示。提示不是一个句子，它是一个工程系统，旨在在不同条件下提供一致的输出。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Inside a Large Retailer’s Web Architecture: Data Extraction and Analytical Insights】大型零售商的 Web 架构内部：数据提取和分析见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/inside-a-large-retailers-web-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Recently, I was trying to identify and understand my daily sugar and other nutrient intake. So, I was trying to find ways to get my bills sorted and identify specific product items. Whether shopping at Whole Foods, QFC, or Costco, I wanted to access my information in an accessible way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; To solve this problem, I probably need an app that will read my bills and categorize accordingly. There must be an existing some app for that, or we can now use AI to automate most of it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;最近，我试图确定并了解我每天的糖和其他营养摄入量。因此，我试图找到方法来整理我的账单并识别特定的产品项目。无论是在 Whole Foods、QFC 还是 Costco 购物，我都希望以便捷的方式访问我的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; 为了解决这个问题，我可能需要一个应用程序来读取我的账单并进行相应的分类。必须有一个现有的应用程序可以实现这一点，或者我们现在可以使用人工智能来自动化大部分操作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shift-Left Strategies for Cloud-Native and Serverless Architectures】云原生和无服务器架构的左移策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/shift-left-cloud-serverless-strategies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The growth observed in modern-day cloud applications is staggering to say the least. Applications are being built faster and deployed at a faster pace. However, there can be several obstacles on this journey toward proactive security, as security and compliance often lag behind rapid development cycles. Traditional, end-of-cycle security checks simply haven’t kept up. Shift-left security has become a true game-changer in this regard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The whole architectural framework of shift-left security depends on moving critical security practices earlier in the development lifecycle. Incorporating security in the development lifecycle should not be an afterthought. Within this context, teams are empowered to identify and eliminate risks at design time, build time, and during CI/CD — not after. These modern workloads are highly dynamic and interconnected, and a single mishap can trickle down across the entire environment. And as cloud-native and serverless architectures grow more prominent by the day, it becomes imperative to adopt this proactive approach. In this article, we will take a look at some of the ways in which shift left security strategy can be incorporated into cloud native and serverless architecture from day one.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;至少可以说，现代云应用程序的增长令人震惊。应用程序的构建和部署速度越来越快。然而，在实现主动安全的过程中可能会遇到一些障碍，因为安全性和合规性往往落后于快速的开发周期。传统的周期结束安全检查根本跟不上。在这方面，左移安全性已成为真正的游戏规则改变者。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;左移安全性的整个架构框架取决于在开发生命周期的早期移动关键安全实践。将安全性纳入开发生命周期不应该是事后才想到的。在此背景下，团队有权在设计时、构建时以及 CI/CD 期间（而不是之后）识别并消除风险。这些现代工作负载是高度动态且相互关联的，单个事故可能会蔓延到整个环境。随着云原生和无服务器架构日益突出，采用这种主动方法变得势在必行。在本文中，我们将探讨从第一天起将左移安全策略纳入云原生和无服务器架构的一些方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Custom Attributes in Relational Databases】关系数据库中的自定义属性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/custom-attributes-in-relational-databases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Learn five proven approaches to handle &lt;em&gt;custom attributes&lt;/em&gt; in relational databases (RDBMS) — from EAV and JSON columns to dynamic schema automation. Understand their pros, cons, and when to use each.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every modern product needs flexibility — users want to add their own fields, labels, or attributes without waiting for a database migration. The problem? &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/choose-a-sql-database&#34;&gt;Relational databases&lt;/a&gt; weren’t built for change.&lt;br&gt;&#xA; This article explores five ways to bring flexibility to RDBMS, from JSON and metadata-driven models to fully automated schema evolution, so you can support dynamic attributes without sacrificing performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;学习五种经过验证的方法来处理关系数据库 (RDBMS) 中的自定义属性 - 从 EAV 和 JSON 列到动态架构自动化。了解它们的优点、缺点以及何时使用它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个现代产品都需要灵活性 - 用户希望添加自己的字段、标签或属性，而无需等待数据库迁移。问题？ &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/choose-a-sql-database&#34;&gt;关系数据库&lt;/a&gt;并不是为了改变而构建的。&lt;br&gt;&#xA; 本文探讨了为 RDBMS 带来灵活性的五种方法，从 JSON 和元数据驱动模型到完全自动化的架构演变，以便您可以在不牺牲性能的情况下支持动态属性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Architect&#39;s Guide to Logging】架构师日志记录指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/architects-guide-to-logging</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Every developer and architect thinks they understand logging until they’re staring at a production issue at 3:00 a.m. Realizing that their logs lack context, have no defined structure, and they’re sifting through a wall of text, desperately looking for that needle in a haystack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;If this sounds familiar, it’s time to upgrade your logging strategy. Good logging is the black box recorder of your system. Here are the best tips to ensure your logs are an asset, not an obstacle.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;每个开发人员和架构师都认为自己了解日志记录，直到他们在凌晨 3:00 盯着生产问题时才意识到他们的日志缺乏上下文，没有定义的结构，并且他们正在筛选一堵文本墙，拼命地大海捞针。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;如果这听起来很熟悉，那么是时候升级您的日志记录策略了。良好的日志记录是系统的黑匣子记录器。以下是确保您的日志成为资产而不是障碍的最佳提示。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Decoupling Azure Releases With GitHub Actions】将 Azure 版本与 GitHub Actions 解耦</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/decoupling-azure-releases-github-actions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Cloud deployments often fail because environment configurations are hardcoded into the build process. Here is a pattern to decouple your Build Artifacts from your Deployment Logic using GitHub Actions and a flexible JSON Configuration map.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the world of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;, we are used to the separation of concerns: Docker builds the image, and Helm/Kustomize handles the environment configuration. However, when working with serverless (Azure Functions) or PaaS (App Service), developers often fall into the trap of monolithic pipelines. They build a package that only works in DEV, and then rebuild it for PROD.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;云部署经常失败，因为环境配置被硬编码到构建过程中。以下是使用 GitHub Actions 和灵活的 JSON 配置映射将构建工件与部署逻辑解耦的模式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; 的世界中，我们习惯于关注点分离：Docker 构建镜像，Helm/Kustomize 处理环境配置。然而，在使用无服务器（Azure Functions）或PaaS（应用服务）时，开发人员经常陷入单一管道的陷阱。他们构建了一个仅在 DEV 中工作的包，然后为 PROD 重新构建它。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Principled Framework for Scalable Experimentation and Reliable A/B Testing】可扩展实验和可靠 A/B 测试的原则框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scalable-ab-testing-framework</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If you’ve ever shipped a feature and thought, “Did we actually make things better?”, you’re not alone. A/B testing is supposed to be our scientific answer to that question, but running good experiments takes more than sprinkling some feature flags and plotting a graph.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In practice, many teams learn &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-reliable-experimentation-systems&#34;&gt;experimentation&lt;/a&gt; the hard way. They launch tests with unclear hypotheses, biased assignments, or underpowered sample sizes, only to discover weeks later that their results are inconclusive or misleading. This means going back to the drawing board, restarting experiments, and losing valuable time, a hit to both product velocity and team morale.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果您曾经发布过一项功能并想：“我们真的让事情变得更好了吗？”，您并不孤单。 A/B 测试应该是我们对这个问题的科学答案，但进行良好的实验需要的不仅仅是撒一些功能标志和绘制图表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在实践中，许多团队通过艰难的方式学习&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-reliable-experimentation-systems&#34;&gt;实验&lt;/a&gt;。他们发起了假设不明确、任务有偏见或样本量不足的测试，结果几周后才发现他们的结果是不确定的或具有误导性。这意味着回到绘图板，重新开始实验，并浪费宝贵的时间，这对产品速度和团队士气都造成了打击。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Extracting Clean Excel Tables From PDFs Using Python + Docling】使用 Python + Dobling 从 PDF 中提取干净的 Excel 表格</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/pdf-to-excel-python-docling</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;1040&#34; data-start=&#34;706&#34;&gt;PDFs remain the most widely used format for distributing structured reports — financial statements, regulatory filings, research documents, fund fact sheets, and more. Yet despite their structured appearance, PDFs are &lt;em data-end=&#34;927&#34; data-start=&#34;922&#34;&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; machine-readable. Extracting tables reliably is famously error-prone and often requires hours of manual cleanup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1161&#34; data-start=&#34;1042&#34;&gt;This is especially true in finance and enterprise environments where analysts rely on Excel for modeling and reporting.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;1040&#34; data-start=&#34;706&#34;&gt;PDF 仍然是分发结构化报告（财务报表、监管文件、研究文件、基金概况介绍等）最广泛使用的格式。然而，尽管 PDF 具有结构化外观，但它&lt;em data-end=&#34;927&#34; data-start=&#34;922&#34;&gt;不是&lt;/em&gt;机器可读的。众所周知，可靠地提取表很容易出错，并且通常需要数小时的手动清理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1161&#34; data-start=&#34;1042&#34;&gt;在分析师依赖 Excel 进行建模和报告的金融和企业环境中尤其如此。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Driven Schema Evolution and Adaptive Pipelines】人工智能驱动的模式演化和自适应管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-driven-schema-evolution-adaptive-pipelines</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;The Modern Challenge of Schema Drift&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In dynamic enterprise ecosystems, schemas rarely stay static. APIs evolve, microservices introduce new fields, IoT devices emit data in new formats, and third-party providers alter payloads overnight. The result: &lt;strong&gt;schema drift&lt;/strong&gt; — the silent killer of data reliability.&lt;br&gt;&#xA; A single schema mismatch can cascade through hundreds of tables, breaking joins, corrupting aggregates, and halting analytics pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional ETL frameworks rely on static definitions or manual version control to handle schema changes. But at today’s scale — millions of daily events, hundreds of interconnected datasets, dozens of teams — manual remediation simply doesn’t scale.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;模式漂移的现代挑战&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在动态的企业生态系统中，架构很少保持静态。 API 不断发展，微服务引入了新领域，物联网设备以新格式发出数据，第三方提供商在一夜之间改变了有效负载。结果：&lt;strong&gt;架构漂移&lt;/strong&gt;——数据可靠性的无声杀手。&lt;br&gt;&#xA; 单个架构不匹配可能会级联数百个表，从而破坏连接、破坏聚合并停止分析管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统的 ETL 框架依赖静态定义或手动版本控制来处理架构更改。但在当今的规模下——数百万个日常事件、数百个互连数据集、数十个团队——手动修复根本无法扩展。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>