<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Llama 3.2 AI With Amazon SageMaker】将 Llama 3.2 AI 与 Amazon SageMaker 集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-llama-32-ai-with-amazon-sagemaker</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Generative AI encompasses algorithms capable of producing novel content, such as text, images, and audio, based on learned patterns from training data. Llama 3.2, the latest iteration in the Llama series developed by Meta, is designed for versatility and enhanced performance across various tasks, including conversational agents, content creation, and personalized recommendations. The efficient implementation and deployment of such complex models necessitate robust frameworks like Amazon SageMaker, which provides a suite of tools for building, training, and deploying machine learning models at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s explore the implementation and deployment of Llama 3.2, a state-of-the-art generative AI model, using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-comprehensive-guide-to-amazon-sagemaker&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Amazon SageMaker&lt;/a&gt;. With its advanced capabilities in natural language understanding and generation, Llama 3.2 has emerged as a powerful tool for various applications, including content creation, conversation agents, and more. This article will provide a step-by-step guide on setting up the environment, training the model, deploying it, and making predictions using Amazon SageMaker, along with practical code examples.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;生成式人工智能包含能够根据从训练数据中学习到的模式生成新颖内容（例如文本、图像和音频）的算法。 Llama 3.2 是 Meta 开发的 Llama 系列的最新版本，旨在实现各种任务的多功能性和增强性能，包括对话代理、内容创建和个性化推荐。此类复杂模型的高效实施和部署需要 Amazon SageMaker 等强大的框架，它提供了一套用于大规模构建、训练和部署机器学习模型的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-compressive-guide-to-amazon 来探索最先进的生成式 AI 模型 Llama 3.2 的实施和部署-sagemaker&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Amazon SageMaker&lt;/a&gt;。凭借其在自然语言理解和生成方面的先进功能，Llama 3.2 已成为各种应用程序的强大工具，包括内容创建、对话代理等。本文将提供有关设置环境、训练模型、部署模型以及使用 Amazon SageMaker 进行预测的分步指南，以及实际的代码示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Security in Kubernetes: A Comparative Analysis of Cosign and Connaisseur】增强 Kubernetes 的安全性：Cosign 和 Connaisseur 的比较分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-comparative-analysis-of-cosign-and-connaisseur</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As Kubernetes continues to gain traction in the realm of container orchestration, ensuring the security of container images has become paramount. Two prominent tools that focus on securing the software supply chain in Kubernetes environments are &lt;strong&gt;Cosign&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Connaisseur&lt;/strong&gt;. While both tools aim to enhance the integrity and authenticity of container images, they serve distinct purposes and functionalities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This article provides an in-depth analysis of these tools, highlighting their definitions, key differences, learning approaches, management strategies, and overall usability and maintenance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;随着 Kubernetes 在容器编排领域不断获得关注，确保容器映像的安全性已变得至关重要。 &lt;strong&gt;Cosign&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;Connaisseur&lt;/strong&gt; 是专注于保护 Kubernetes 环境中软件供应链安全的两个著名工具。虽然这两种工具都旨在增强容器映像的完整性和真实性，但它们具有不同的目的和功能。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;本文对这些工具进行了深入分析，重点介绍了它们的定义、主要差异、学习方法、管理策略以及整体可用性和维护。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mainframe to Serverless Migration on AWS: Challenges and Solutions】AWS 上的大型机到无服务器迁移：挑战和解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mainframe-to-serverless-migration-on-aws-challenge</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Companies across the globe spend more than $65 billion each year to maintain their legacy mainframe systems. Moving from mainframes to serverless systems on AWS gives businesses a great chance to cut operating costs. They can also benefit from cloud-native architecture. This fundamental change lets companies replace their rigid, monolithic systems with adaptable ones that meet market needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS serverless technologies offer modern alternatives to traditional mainframe parts. Amazon EventBridge and Amazon API Gateway stand out as prime examples. These services make infrastructure management simple. They also deliver better scaling options and lower operating costs. This piece gets into the technical hurdles, strategies, and best practices you need for a successful mainframe-to-AWS serverless move. Your organization can direct this complex transition with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;全球各地的公司每年花费超过 650 亿美元来维护其遗留大型机系统。从大型机迁移到 AWS 上的无服务器系统为企业提供了削减运营成本的绝佳机会。他们还可以从云原生架构中受益。这一根本性的变化使公司能够用适应市场需求的适应性系统取代僵化的整体系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS 无服务器技术为传统大型机部件提供了现代替代品。 Amazon EventBridge 和 Amazon API Gateway 就是典型的例子。这些服务使基础设施管理变得简单。它们还提供更好的扩展选项和更低的运营成本。本文探讨成功从大型机到 AWS 无服务器迁移所需的技术障碍、策略和最佳实践。您的组织可以充满信心地指导这一复杂的过渡。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dropwizard vs. Micronaut: Unpacking the Best Framework for Microservices】Dropwizard 与 Micronaut：揭开微服务的最佳框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dropwizard-vs-micronaut</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservice-architecture-2&#34;&gt;Microservices architecture&lt;/a&gt; has reshaped the way we design and build software, emphasizing scalability, maintainability, and agility. Two frameworks, Dropwizard and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-quick-guide-to-microservices-with-the-micronaut&#34;&gt;Micronaut&lt;/a&gt;, have gained prominence in the microservices ecosystem, each offering unique features to simplify and optimize development. In this article, we delve into a detailed comparison to help you determine which framework best suits your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Comparison Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Dropwizard and Micronaut differ significantly in their design philosophies and capabilities:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservice-architecture-2&#34;&gt;微服务架构&lt;/a&gt;重塑了我们设计和构建软件的方式，强调可扩展性、可维护性和敏捷性。 Dropwizard 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-quick-guide-to-microservices-with-the-micronaut&#34;&gt;Micronaut&lt;/a&gt; 这两个框架在微服务生态系统中占据了重要地位，每个都提供独特的功能来简化和优化开发。在本文中，我们将进行详细的比较，以帮助您确定哪个框架最适合您的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;比较概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Dropwizard 和 Micronaut 在设计理念和功能上存在显着差异：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a New Public API】构建新的公共 API</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-new-publicapi</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This year, I embarked on an exciting journey to build a new public API system for one of my clients. The goal was to create a system allowing them to sell access to their valuable dataset to external parties. This project wasn&#39;t just about opening up new revenue streams; it was about innovation and expanding the value we could offer to the clients sector.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-should-know-about-apis&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;APIs&lt;/a&gt; play a crucial role in modern software systems, facilitating the flow of essential data across various components and platforms. By enabling third parties to build products on top of our infrastructure, we were set to significantly increase the platform&#39;s value and reach.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;今年，我踏上了一段激动人心的旅程，为我的一个客户构建一个新的公共 API 系统。目标是创建一个系统，允许他们向外部各方出售对其有价值的数据集的访问权限。该项目不仅仅是为了开辟新的收入来源；这是关于创新和扩大我们可以为客户部门提供的价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-should-know-about-apis&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;API&lt;/a&gt; 发挥着至关重要的作用在现代软件系统中发挥着重要作用，促进重要数据在各种组件和平台之间的流动。通过允许第三方在我们的基础设施之上构建产品，我们将显着提高平台的价值和覆盖范围。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Step-By-Step Guide to Integrating Python With RPA (Blue Prism)】将 Python 与 RPA 集成的分步指南 (Blue Prism)</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-python-with-rpa-blue-prism</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Most automation companies leverage the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/coredotnet&#34;&gt;.NET&lt;/a&gt; Framework as a core language, particularly in the top three &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-robotic-process-automation&#34;&gt;RPA&lt;/a&gt; platforms: Blue Prism, UiPath, and Power Automate. However, Automation Anywhere uses &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;, and Power Automate utilizes Azure Functions and AI-enhanced capabilities along with the .NET Framework.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34; style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;table border=&#34;1&#34; cellpadding=&#34;0&#34; cellspacing=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;max-width: 100%; width: auto; table-layout: fixed; display: table;&#34; summary=&#34;&#34; title=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RPA Platform&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main Languages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reasons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style=&#34;overflow-wrap: break-word; width: auto;&#34; valign=&#34;top&#34; width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;     &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blue Prism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大多数自动化公司都利用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/coredotnet&#34;&gt;.NET&lt;/a&gt; 框架作为核心语言，尤其是前三名&lt;a href=&#34;https: //dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-robotic-process-automation&#34;&gt;RPA&lt;/a&gt; 平台：Blue Prism、UiPath 和 Power Automate。但是，Automation Anywhere 使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;，而 Power Automate 使用 Azure Functions 和 AI 增强功能以​​及 .NET Framework。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34; style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;table border=&#34;1&#34; cellpadding=&#34;0&#34; cellspacing=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;max-width: 100%; width: auto; table-layout:fixed; display: table;&#34;摘要=“”标题=“”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;标题&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RPA 平台&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;主要语言&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th style=“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” width=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;原因&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/标题&gt;&#xA;  &lt;正文&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td style =“overflow-wrap：break-word；宽度：自动；” valign=“顶部”宽度=“自动”&gt;&#xA;     &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;蓝色棱镜&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating a Web Project: Four Questions to Ask Before You Start】创建 Web 项目：开始之前要问的四个问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-a-web-project-questions-before-you-start</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;History knows a lot of examples when brilliant ideas were conceived in a garage and started in a somewhat chaotic manner. But it also knows just as many examples of equally brilliant ventures failing because of simple mistakes and a general lack of a systematic approach. I suggest you have a look at four basic steps that can get you some decent insurance against chaos. Get yourself and your team through them &amp;nbsp;— and build your project’s foundation layer by layer. And remember: Amat Victoria Curam, Victory Loves Preparation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Question 1: Who Needs Your Project?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Identifying your target audience is a critical step that should never be skipped. Without this, your project is at risk of failure even before it starts. You may ask why defining a target audience is of any matter for a developer. The answer is simple and straightforward. Your audience is the fundamental factor that defines everything else, from technology stack to product features. When you know who is going to use your product and how they will use it, you can optimize it accordingly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;历史上有很多这样的例子：绝妙的想法是在车库里构思出来并以某种混乱的方式开始的。但它也知道同样出色的企业因简单错误和普遍缺乏系统方法而失败的例子。我建议您看一下四个基本步骤，它们可以帮助您避免混乱。让您自己和您的团队完成这些任务，并逐层构建项目的基础。请记住：Amat Victoria Curam，胜利热爱准备。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;问题 1：谁需要您的项目？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;确定目标受众是不容忽视的关键步骤。如果没有这一点，您的项目甚至在开始之前就面临失败的风险。您可能会问为什么定义目标受众对于开发人员来说很重要。答案简单明了。您的受众是定义其他一切（从技术堆栈到产品功能）的基本因素。当您知道谁将使用您的产品以及他们将如何使用它时，您可以相应地对其进行优化。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Strengthening IAM Security for Cloud IaaS Accounts】加强云 IaaS 账户的 IAM 安全</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/strengthening-iam-security-for-cloud-iaas-accounts</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Cloud IaaS providers like AWS, Azure, OCI, and GCP operate on a shared responsibility model. While they secure the underlying infrastructure, You, as a customer, are responsible for protecting data, applications, and access management. The rapid adoption of cloud services has made IaaS a prime target for cybercriminals. According to a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/reports/data-breach&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;recent study by IBM&lt;/a&gt;, misconfigurations in cloud services are responsible for billions of exposed records annually.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;The article covers important&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisecurity.org/benchmark/oracle_cloud&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CIS hardening strategies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;for securing OCI cloud accounts and focusing on identity and access management.&lt;/span&gt; Effective IAM is the cornerstone of cloud security as it ensures that only authorized users can access your cloud resources and that they have only the permissions necessary to perform their tasks. Neglecting this responsibility can lead to data breaches, financial losses, and reputational damage.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;AWS、Azure、OCI 和 GCP 等云 IaaS 提供商采用责任共担模式运营。虽然他们保护底层基础设施，但作为客户，您有责任保护数据、应用程序和访问管理。云服务的快速采用使 IaaS 成为网络犯罪分子的主要目标。根据 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/reports/data-breach&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IBM 最近的研究&lt;/a&gt;，云服务中的错误配置每年要对数十亿条暴露的记录负责。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;本文涵盖重要内容&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cisecurity.org/benchmark/oracle_cloud&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CIS强化策略&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;用于保护 OCI 云帐户并专注于身份和访问管理。&lt;/span&gt;有效的 IAM 是云安全的基石，因为它确保只有经过授权的用户才能访问用户可以访问您的云资源，并且他们仅具有执行其任务所需的权限。忽视这一责任可能会导致数据泄露、财务损失和声誉受损。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting Sh!t Done Without Doing It Yourself: Part 1】不自己动手就能完成任务：第 1 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/getting-sht-done-without-doing-it-yourself-part-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;There’s a common &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/elevate-your-it-career-three-step-strategy&#34;&gt;career progression&lt;/a&gt; in this technical industry. You come in wet behind the ears as a junior developer, whether front-end, back-end, infrastructure, or even security. After a few years, you lose the “junior” from your title, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-stay-happy-and-relevant-as-a-java-developer&#34;&gt;after a few more years&lt;/a&gt;, you gain a “senior.” You might become a team lead after that with some light duties around oversight and overall team delivery. But then you’re promoted into some role with &#34;manager&#34; in the title — &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/engineering-manager-thoughts&#34;&gt;engineering manager&lt;/a&gt; or software development manager or something similar. Suddenly, you’re in a position where it’s pretty easy to prove out the Peter principle. Wikipedia summaries this principle, coined in a 1969 book, as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;“The Peter principle is a concept in management developed by Laurence J. Peter which observes that people in a hierarchy tend to rise to &#39;a level of respective incompetence&#39;: Employees are promoted based on their success in previous jobs until they reach a level at which they are no longer competent, as skills in one job do not necessarily translate to another.”&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这个技术行业有一个常见的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/elevate-your-it-career- Three-step-strategy&#34;&gt;职业发展&lt;/a&gt;。作为一名初级开发人员，无论是前端、后端、基础设施，甚至安全性，你都一无所知。几年后，您失去了头衔中的“初级”，并且 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-stay-happy-and-relevant-as-a-java-developer ”再过几年&lt;/a&gt;，你就获得了“高级”。之后，您可能会成为团队领导，承担一些有关监督和整体团队交付的轻微职责。但随后您会被晋升到头衔中带有“经理”的职位 - &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/engineering-manager-thoughts&#34;&gt;工程经理&lt;/a&gt;或软件开发经理或类似的东西。突然之间，你就很容易证明彼得原理了。维基百科在 1969 年的一本书中总结了这一原则，如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;“彼得原则是劳伦斯·J·彼得提出的一个管理概念，它观察到，处于等级制度中的人往往会上升到“各自无能的水平”：员工根据他们在以前工作中的成功获得晋升，直到他们达到他们不再胜任的水平，因为一项工作的技能不一定能转化为另一项工作。”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing APIs in Modern Web Applications】保护现代 Web 应用程序中的 API 安全</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/securing-apis-in-modern-web-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;APIs play a critical role in web applications in the modern digital world. They are the means by which diverse components of the software talk to each other and effectively communicate. Thus, with the growing use of APIs, new kinds of vulnerabilities come into play. The developers who want their applications to be secure should study the principles of API security. It is about security related to APIs, which would fall within an all-inclusive approach to cybersecurity in which sensitive data needs protection, and application interactions should be secure.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API Security and Why It Matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;APIs facilitate data between clouds, mobile applications, and web applications. This means they act like a perfect target for any form of attack. If there is no proper security measure in place, sensitive data can be easily exposed, and unauthorized access can be increased. Let the case be worse, wherein a poorly secured API could let hackers take advantage of API vulnerabilities through which large data could be breached or manipulated unethically. API security is, therefore, important in preventing leakages, ensuring the privacy of user information, and protecting the infrastructures of applications from adversarial threats.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;API 在现代数字世界的 Web 应用程序中发挥着至关重要的作用。它们是软件不同组件相互对话和有效通信的手段。因此，随着 API 使用的不断增加，新型漏洞开始发挥作用。希望应用程序安全的开发人员应该研究 API 安全原理。它涉及与 API 相关的安全性，属于包罗万象的网络安全方法，其中敏感数据需要保护，并且应用程序交互应该是安全的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API 安全性及其重要性&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;API 促进云、移动应用程序和 Web 应用程序之间的数据传输。这意味着它们就像任何形式攻击的完美目标。如果没有适当的安全措施，敏感数据很容易暴露，并且未经授权的访问可能会增加。更糟糕的是，安全性较差的 API 可能会让黑客利用 API 漏洞，从而破坏或不道德地操纵大数据。因此，API 安全对于防止泄漏、确保用户信息的隐私以及保护应用程序的基础设施免受敌对威胁非常重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>