<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【React Performance Optimization: Tricks Every Dev Should Know】反应性能优化：每个开发人员都应该知道的技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/react-performance-optimization-tricks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Let’s face it: we’ve all been there. You build a sleek React app, only to watch it slow to a crawl as it grows. Buttons lag, pages take forever to load, and users start bouncing. Sound familiar? I’ve been in that exact spot — debugging performance issues at 2 AM, fueled by coffee and frustration.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this guide, I’ll share battle-tested strategies to optimize &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-react-a-complete-guide&#34;&gt;React apps&lt;/a&gt;, sprinkled with real-world war stories and practical examples. No jargon, no fluff — just actionable advice.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;让我们面对现实吧：我们都去过那里。您构建了一个光滑的React应用程序，只是看着它在生长时慢慢到爬行。按钮滞后，页面永远需要加载，用户开始弹跳。听起来很熟悉吗？我一直处于那个确切的位置 - 在咖啡和沮丧的推动下，在凌晨2点调试表演问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在本指南中，我将分享经过战斗的策略，以优化&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-react-a-complete-guide”&gt; React Apps &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;用现实世界中的战争和实践示例撒上。没有行话，没有绒毛 - 只是可行的建议。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Critical Role of CISOs in Managing IAM, Including NHIs】CISO在管理IAM中的关键作用，包括NHIS</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/critical-role-cisos-managing-iam-including-nhis</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Who Should Own IAM in the Enterprise?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Identity and access management (IAM) started as an IT function, with the entire focus on giving human users the right access to the right systems. But today, identity has become the primary attack surface, with at least 80% of all modern breaches involving compromised or stolen identities from adversaries who exploit poor identity. This reality has moved the responsibility for risk onto the shoulders of the team tasked with protecting the organization from attacks, namely security. Which ultimately means the CISO.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, there’s a major blind spot in this conversation: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-non-human-identities-governance&#34;&gt;non-human identities&lt;/a&gt; (NHIs). This is a critical oversight. We are witnessing non-human identities (NHIs) &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.gitguardian.com/non-human-identity-security-zero-trust-architecture/#:~:text=NHIs%20outnumbered%20human%20identities%20at%20an%20enterprise%20by%20a%20factor%20of%2045%20to%201.&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;outnumber humans&lt;/a&gt; by a factor of at least 45-to-one in the enterprise, with some estimates as high as 100 to 1. As organizations accelerate to deliver more code and products faster than ever, the number of these machine identities, such as service accounts, APIs, and automated workloads, will continually increase this imbalance. LLMs and the rapid adoption of new coding assistants and AI productivity tools will only rapidly accelerate this trend.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;谁应该在企业中拥有IAM？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;身份和访问管理（IAM）始于IT函数，整个关注的重点是让人类用户正确访问正确的系统。但是今天，身份已成为主要的攻击表面，至少有80％的现代违规行为涉及利用糟糕身份的对手的受损或被盗的身份。这一现实将风险的责任转移到了为保护组织免受攻击（即安全性）侵害的团队肩膀上。最终意味着CISO。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，这次对话中有一个主要的盲点：&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-non-human-indistities-governance”&gt; non-human Identities &lt;/a&gt;（NHIS）。这是一个关键的监督。我们目睹了非人类身份（NHIS）&lt;a href =“ https://blog.gitguardian.com/non-human-indentity-security-secerity-zero-zero-trust-architector/#:~: text=nhis%20OUTNUMBERDMEDNUMBERED%20HUMAN%20HUMAN%20HUMAN%20AT； rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;超过人类的&lt;/a&gt;在企业中至少要有45倍至一倍，估计有些估计高达100比1。随着组织加速以比以往任何时候都更快地提供代码和产品，这些机器标识的数量（例如服务帐户，Apis，APIS，APIS，APIS，APIS和AUTAPTALE）会逐步增加，并将其升级为综述，并将其逐步升高。 LLM和新的编码助手和AI生产力工具的迅速采用只会迅速加速这一趋势。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Essential Python Libraries: Introduction to NumPy and Pandas】基本Python图书馆：Numpy和Pandas简介</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-libraries-introduction-numpy-pandas</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In Python programming, NumPy and Pandas stand out as two of the most powerful libraries for numerical computing and data manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NumPy: The Foundation of Numerical Computing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-numpy&#34;&gt;NumPy&lt;/a&gt; (Numerical Python) provides support for multi-dimensional arrays and a wide range of mathematical functions, making it essential for scientific computing.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在Python编程中，Numpy和Pandas是数值计算和数据操作的两个最强大的库。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; numpy：数值计算的基础&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-numpy”&gt; numpy &lt;/a&gt;（数值python）为多维数组和广泛的数学功能提供了支持，使其对于科学计算至关重要。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Redis With Message Brokers】将Redis与消息经纪人集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-redis-with-message-brokers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s look at how to integrate Redis with different message brokers. In this article, we will point out the benefits of this integration. We will talk about which message brokers work well with Redis.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will also show how to set up Redis as a message broker with practical code examples, and discuss how to handle message persistence and how to monitor Redis when it is used as a message broker.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;让我们看一下如何将Redis与不同的消息经纪人集成在一起。在本文中，我们将指出这种整合的好处。我们将讨论哪个消息经纪人与Redis效果很好。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还将展示如何将Redis设置为具有实际代码示例的消息经纪，并讨论如何处理消息持久性以及如何在将REDIS用作消息经纪时监视REDIS。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Feather Wand: Your AI-Powered Companion for JMeter】羽毛魔杖：您的AI驱动伴侣Jmeter</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/introducing-feather-wand-your-ai-powered-companion</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Imagine having an intelligent assistant right inside JMeter, ready to help you craft, optimize, and troubleshoot your test plans with ease. That’s exactly what &lt;strong&gt;Feather Wand&lt;/strong&gt;, a new JMeter plugin, brings to the table — a sprinkle of AI magic to transform your performance testing experience. Let’s dive into what makes this tool special, how it works, and why it might just become your go-to JMeter sidekick — especially for performance test engineers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class=&#34;wp-block-heading&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The Story Behind the Name&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Before we get technical, a quick nod to the whimsical origin of &#34;Feather Wand.&#34; The name comes from my kids, who were inspired by an episode of &lt;em&gt;Bluey&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; the charming animated show. In that episode, a simple feather turns into a magical wand, making ordinary things extraordinary (and hilariously heavy).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;想象一下在Jmeter内有一个智能助手，可以轻松帮助您制作，优化和对测试计划进行解决。这正是&lt;strong&gt;羽毛魔杖&lt;/strong&gt;是一个新的Jmeter插件，它带到了桌子上 - 撒上AI魔术来改变您的性能测试体验。让我们深入了解使此工具与众不同的原因，以及为什么它可能会成为您的Jmeter Sidekick（尤其是对于性能测试工程师）。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 class =“ wp-block-heading” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;名称背后的故事&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在我们获得技术之前，快速点头“羽毛魔杖”的异想天开。这个名字来自我的孩子，他们受到&lt;em&gt; bluey &lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style =“ margin：0px; padding：0px;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;，&lt;em&gt;，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt;迷人的动画节目的启发。在那集中，一个简单的羽毛变成了一个神奇的魔杖，使普通的东西变得非凡（而且很重）。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Weather Service With Genkit and AI】使用Genkit和AI建立气象服务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-weather-service-genkit-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This project demonstrates how to build an AI-enhanced weather service using Genkit, TypeScript, OpenWeatherAPI, and GitHub models. The application showcases modern Node.js patterns and AI integration techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before you begin, ensure you have the following:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt;概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个项目演示了如何使用GenKit，TypeScript，OpenWeatherapi和Github模型来构建AI增强气象服务。应用程序展示了现代节点。JS模式和AI集成技术。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;先决条件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在开始之前，请确保您有以下内容：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automated Bug Fixing: From Templates to AI Agents】自动错误修复：从模板到AI代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automated-bug-fixing-from-templates-to-ai-agents</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;ve spent any time in software development, you know that debugging is often the most time-consuming and frustrating part of the job. What if AI could handle those pesky bugs for you?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recent advances in automated program repair (APR) are making this increasingly realistic. Let&#39;s explore how this technology has evolved and where it&#39;s headed.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您花了任何时间在软件开发领域，您知道调试通常是工作中最耗时和令人沮丧的部分。如果AI可以为您处理那些讨厌的错误怎么办？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自动化计划维修（APR）的最新进展正在使这一越来越现实。让我们探索这项技术的发展以及它的发展方向。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Database Query Service With OpenAI and PostgreSQL in .NET】带有openai和postgresql的数据库查询服务。</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/database-query-service-openai-postgresql-dotnet</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Generate SQL queries based on natural language input&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, we&#39;ll explore how to build a service that interacts with a PostgreSQL database and uses OpenAI&#39;s GPT-4 model to generate SQL queries based on natural language input. This service called &lt;code&gt;NorthwindServicefromDB&lt;/code&gt; is designed to make it easier for users to query a database without needing to write SQL themselves.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ll walk through the code step by step, explaining each component and how it fits into the overall architecture.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;基于自然语言输入生成SQL查询&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此博客文章中，我们将探讨如何构建与PostgreSQL数据库交互的服务，并使用OpenAI的GPT-4模型来基于自然语言输入来生成SQL查询。此服务称为&lt;code&gt; NorthwindServiceFromDB &lt;/code&gt;旨在使用户更容易查询数据库而无需编写SQL自己。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将逐步浏览代码，解释每个组件及其如何适合整体体系结构。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Agents for Data Warehousing】数据仓库的AI代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agents-for-data-warehousing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;436&#34; data-start=&#34;140&#34;&gt;The term &#34;data warehousing&#34; was first introduced in the 1980s, referring to the practice of storing data from various sources within an organization. The collected data is then utilized for reporting, decision-making, accurate analytics, better customer insights, and handling ad hoc queries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;753&#34; data-start=&#34;438&#34;&gt;However, traditional data warehousing techniques come with significant challenges, including high setup and maintenance costs, slow processing speeds, and scalability limitations. However, with the rise of artificial intelligence, the introduction of DW Agent AI is revolutionizing data management, making processes more automated, efficient, and scalable.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 436” data-start =“ 140”&gt;术语“数据仓库”是在1980年代首次引入的，指的是从组织内的各种来源存储数据的做法。然后，将收集的数据用于报告，决策，准确的分析，更好的客户见解和处理临时查询。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 753” data-start =“ 438”&gt;但是，传统数据仓库技术面临着巨大的挑战，包括高设置和维护成本，缓慢的处理速度和可扩展性限制。但是，随着人工智能的兴起，DW代理AI的引入正在彻底改变数据管理，使过程更加自动化，高效和可扩展。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Agents For Automated Claims Processing】自动索赔处理的AI代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agents-for-automated-claims-processing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Agent-grounded models live for quite some time. They are generally enforced as computer simulations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;An AI agent is a software operation that engages with its surroundings, collects information, and utilizes that data to negotiate predefined objectives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;AI agents:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul type=&#34;disc&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Are software programs that accomplish jobs autonomously or semi-autonomously&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Run independently to design, implement, and optimize workflows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Have proper boundaries to help execute tasks properly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Help in driving better decision-making and functional effectiveness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Can enable personalization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Help in performing tasks accurately and consistently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Manage and optimize complex systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Monitor and analyze security pitfalls in real time, delivering proactive measures to prevent breaches and guarantee data protection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Increase productivity by reasoning, planning, and self-checking, releasing users from certain tasks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Business Case for AI Agents Usage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Today, CXOs see the IT budget as an area of overspending and are continuously looking for ways to reduce costs and time [1].&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;代理型模型已有一段时间。通常将它们作为计算机模拟执行。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; AI代理是一种软件操作，可与周围环境进行互动，收集信息并利用该数据来协商预定义的目标。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; AI代理：&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul type =“ disc”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;是可以自主或半自治完成作业的软件程序&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;独立运行以设计，实现和优化工作流&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;具有适当的边界，可以帮助正确执行任务&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;有助于推动更好的决策和功能有效性&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;可以启用个性化&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;有助于准确，始终如一地执行任务&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;管理和优化复杂系统&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;实时监视和分析安全陷阱，提供积极的措施以防止违规并保证数据保护&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;通过推理，计划和自我检查提高生产率，从某些任务中释放用户&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;span&gt; AI代理使用的业务案例&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;今天，CXO将IT预算视为超支的领域，并一直在寻找减少成本和时间的方法[1]。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>