<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Compliance Automated Standard Solution (COMPASS), Part 9: Taking OSCAL-Compass to Industry Complexity Level】合规性自动化标准解决方案（Compass），第9部分：将持续款项带到行业复杂性水平</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/compliance-automated-standard-solution-compass-par</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; A list of links for all articles in this series can be found at the conclusion of this article.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;566&#34; data-start=&#34;77&#34;&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/compliance-automated-standard-solution-compass-part-2-trestle-sdk&#34;&gt;parts 2&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/compliance-automated-standard-solution-compass-part-3-artifacts-and-personas&#34;&gt;part 3&lt;/a&gt; of this blog series, we introduced the open-source &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/oscal-compass/compliance-trestle&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Trestle&lt;/a&gt; SDK, which implements the &lt;a href=&#34;https://pages.nist.gov/OSCAL/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;NIST Open Security Control Assessment Language (OSCAL) standard&lt;/a&gt; framework. We also covered Trestle’s agile authoring capabilities, allowing users to create and edit compliance artifacts as Markdown content and convert them to OSCAL format. Additionally, we explained how the Agile Authoring GitOps workflow automation tool supports the various personas involved throughout the compliance process.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;em&gt;（&lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;：&lt;/strong&gt;在本文的结论中可以找到本系列中所有文章的链接列表。）&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 566” data-start =“ 77”&gt; in &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/compliance-automated-automated-automated-andomated-andomast-solutian-solution-compass-compass-part-part-part-part-2-trestle-sdk”&gt; parts 2 &lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/compliance-automated-antod-solution-solution-solution-compass-part-3-artifacts-and-personas-&gt; part 3 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;我们介绍了开放式&lt;a a href = a href =“ target =“ _ blank”&gt;栈桥&lt;/a&gt; SDK，它实现了&lt;a href =“ https://pages.nist.gov/oscal/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” noopener noreferrer“ target =“ _ blank”&gt; nist black“ _”&gt; nist开放安全控制评估语言（OSCAL）标准&lt;/a&gt;框架。我们还涵盖了Trestle的敏捷创作能力，使用户可以创建和编辑合规性工件作为Markdown内容，并将其转换为振荡格式。此外，我们解释了敏捷的Gitops Workflow Automation工具如何支持整个合规过程所涉及的各个角色。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring C++23: Multidimensional Subscript Operator】探索C ++ 23：多维下标操作员</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/c23-multidimensional-subscript-operator</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;C++23, the latest iteration of the C++ programming language standard, brings a plethora of exciting features and improvements to the table. Among these is the multidimensional subscript operator, a long-awaited addition that promises to simplify and enhance the way we interact with multidimensional arrays and containers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll delve into the world of multidimensional subscript operators, exploring their syntax, usage, and benefits. We&#39;ll also examine how this feature integrates with existing C++ constructs and what implications it has for our coding practices.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; c ++ 23，C ++编程语言标准的最新迭代，为表带来了很多令人兴奋的功能和改进。其中包括多维下标运算符，这是一个期待已久的补充，有望简化和增强我们与多维阵列和容器相互作用的方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将深入研究多维下标操作员的世界，探索他们的语法，用法和福利。我们还将研究此功能如何与现有的C ++结构集成在一起，以及它对我们的编码实践的含义。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Configure a Jenkins Job for a Maven Project】如何为Maven项目配置Jenkins作业</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-configure-a-jenkins-job-for-a-maven-project</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;66f6&#34;&gt;Jenkins is a widely used automation server that plays a big role in modern software development. It helps teams streamline their continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) processes by automating tasks like building, testing, and deploying applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;8b37&#34;&gt;One of the key strengths of Jenkins is its flexibility. It easily integrates with a wide range of tools and technologies, making it adaptable to different project needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name =“ 66f6”&gt; Jenkins是一家广泛使用的自动化服务器，在现代软件开发中起着重要作用。它通过自动化构建，测试和部署应用程序等任务来帮助团队简化他们的持续集成和连续交付（CI/CD）流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name =“ 8B37”&gt;詹金斯的关键优势之一是其灵活性。它很容易与广泛的工具和技术集成，使其适应不同的项目需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What the AI Coding Experience Senior Software Engineers Want】AI编码体验高级软件工程师想要什么</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-coding-experience-senior-software-engineers-want</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;3641&#34;&gt;AI coding assistants or editors, such as Cursor, Windsurf, Lovable, and GitHub Copilot, are transforming how developers write code. You can now turn an idea into a working app in minutes just by typing a few prompts. That’s exciting but also risky. Many new developers can now build features without really understanding how the code works. Can you trust what the AI writes? Will you or your team understand it later? In some cases, the AI is making big decisions about how the software architecture is built, not the developer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;25b1&#34;&gt;Usually, senior engineers do not jump straight into coding without considering domain knowledge, architecture, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-ultimate-code-quality-checklist&#34;&gt;code reusability&lt;/a&gt;. They know when a piece of code fits and when it doesn’t. To be useful for real projects, AI tools need to provide developers with more structure, control, and ways to test and trust what gets built.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name =“ 3641”&gt; AI编码助手或编辑器，例如光标，Windsurf，Lobable和Github Copilot，正在改变开发人员编写代码的方式。现在，您可以通过输入一些提示来几分钟将一个想法变成工作应用程序。这很令人兴奋，但也有冒险。现在，许多新开发人员可以构建功能，而无需真正了解代码的工作原理。您能相信AI的写作吗？您或您的团队以后会理解吗？在某些情况下，AI对软件体系结构的构建方式而不是开发人员做出了重大决定。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name =“ 25b1”&gt;通常，高级工程师不会在不考虑域知识，体系结构或&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-yultimate-code-quality-quality-checklist”&gt;代码可重用性&lt;/a&gt;的情况下直接跳入编码。他们知道一块代码何时适合，何时不适合。为了对实际项目有用，AI工具需要为开发人员提供更多的结构，控制和测试和信任构建的方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Agentic AI: From Simple Chatbots to Autonomous Decision-Making Systems】了解代理AI：从简单的聊天机器人到自主决策系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-ai-chatbots-to-autonomous-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This comprehensive guide breaks down the concept using real-world examples and practical code implementations to help you understand the evolution from basic chatbots to sophisticated autonomous AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Evolution: From RAG to Agentic AI&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Stage 1: RAG-Based AI Systems&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consider a company with 75+ employees needing an HR assistant to answer policy questions like &#34;How many vacation days do I have per year?&#34; or &#34;What is the policy on sick leave?&#34; The traditional approach involves building a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag&#34;&gt;retrieval-augmented generation&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) chatbot that pulls information from PDF policy documents and provides answers.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;该综合指南使用现实世界中的示例和实用代码实现分解了概念，以帮助您了解从基本聊天机器人到复杂自主AI系统的演变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;演变：从抹布到代理AI &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3&gt;阶段1：基于抹布的AI系统&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;考虑一家拥有75名员工的公司，需要人力资源助理来回答政策问题，例如“我每年有多少个假期？”或“病假政策是什么？”传统方法涉及构建a &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-to-to--retrieval-augment-generation-generation-generation-rag”&gt; reterieval-aughted Generation &lt;/a&gt;（rag）chatbot，从PDF政策文档中获取信息</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introduction to Data-Driven Testing With JUnit 5: A Guide to Efficient and Scalable Testing】使用JUNIT 5的数据驱动测试简介：有效且可扩展的测试指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-data-driven-testing-with-junit</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;When discussing the history of software development, we can observe an increase in software complexity, characterized by&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;rules and conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;When it comes to modern applications that rely heavily on databases, testing how the application interacts with its data becomes equally important. It is where&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;data-driven testing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;plays a crucial role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-power-of-data-driven-testing-a-deep-dive-into&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Data-driven testing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;helps increase software quality by enabling tests with multiple data sets, which means the same test runs multiple times with different data inputs.&lt;/span&gt; Automating these tests also ensures scalability and repeatability across your test suite, reducing human error, boosting productivity, saving time, and guaranteeing that the same mistake doesn&#39;t happen twice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-proserver空间=“ true”&gt;在讨论软件开发的历史记录时，我们可以观察到软件复杂性的增加，其特征是&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span data-parserver spaces =“ true”&gt;更多&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;“ true”&gt;“ true”&gt;“ true”&gt;规则和条件。该应用程序如何与数据相互作用变得同样重要。这是&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;数据驱动的测试&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span data-parserver spaces =“ true”&gt;扮演至关重要的角色。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-power-of-data-driven-testing-a-deep-dive-into&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Data-driven testing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt; helps increase software quality by enabling tests with多个数据集，这意味着相同的测试通过不同的数据输入进行多次运行。&lt;/span&gt;自动化这些测试还确保了整个测试套件的可伸缩性和可重复性，降低了人为错误，提高生产力，节省了时间，并确保同一错误不会发生两次。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/pas&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【JWT Policy Enforcement, Rate Limiting, IP White Listing: Using Mulesoft, API Security, Cloudhub 2.0】JWT策略执行，费率限制，IP白色列表：使用mulesoft，API安全性，CloudHub 2.0</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/jwt-policy-enforcement-raml-anypoint-platform</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;506&#34; data-start=&#34;180&#34;&gt;This tutorial is all about implementing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/enforcing-mulesoft-jwt-validation-policy-using-api&#34;&gt;JWT Policy Enforcement&lt;/a&gt; in API Manager using a sample RAML-based project. It&#39;s especially helpful when applying policies through the API Manager in the Anypoint Platform. Along the way, you’ll also learn how to secure a specific API endpoint using a third-party Auth Provider like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/auth0-okta-vs-cognito&#34;&gt;Auth0&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;610&#34; data-start=&#34;508&#34;&gt;In this project, the following policies have been applied to enhance API security and traffic control:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 506” data-start =“ 180”&gt;本教程是关于实现&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/enforcing-mulesoft-mulesoft-jwt-validation-policy-policy-usis-policy-usis--usis--usis-api-使用api manager in a api manager in a样用板的项目。通过Anypoint平台在API经理应用策略时，这特别有用。在此过程中，您还将学习如何使用第三方Auth提供商来保护特定的API端点，例如&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/auth0-okta-okta-vs-cognito”&gt; auth0&gt; auth0 &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 610” data-start =“ 508”&gt;在此项目中，已应用以下策略来增强API安全和流量控制：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Boost Your Coding Agent and Understand Its Reasoning with 3 Simple Prompts】增强您的编码代理，并使用3个简单的提示理解其推理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/boost-coding-agent-understand-reasoning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left: 20px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Use the custom prompts from this article and the linked repository to have the agent (1) plan, (2) implement, and (3) review any code before considering it complete.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;margin-left: 20px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;These are straightforward, proven client-side prompt engineering techniques. This approach consistently improves results, regardless of the LLM used.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“保证金左：20px;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;使用本文中的自定义提示和链接的存储库来具有代理（1）计划，（2）实施，（3）在考虑完成之前查看任何代码。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“保证金左：20px;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;这些都是直接的，已证实的客户端及时工程技术。无论使用什么LLM，这种方法都一致地改善结果。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Impact of Artificial Intelligence on Network Routers and Switches】人工智能对网络路由器和开关的影响</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/impact-of-ai-on-network-routers-switches</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: Readers should not infer that Google is using or planning to use any of these technologies in its products or services.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The ever-increasing demand for data-driven applications and services has placed pressure on networking infrastructures. As the primary source for data flow, network routers and switches play an important role in ensuring seamless communication, data management, and network reliability. Traditionally, these devices relied on static configurations and manual management, which often led to challenges in scalability, efficiency, and security. However, Artificial Intelligence (AI) is changing the domain of networking by introducing intelligent, autonomous, and adaptive capabilities to routers and switches.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;免责声明：读者不应推断Google正在使用或计划在其产品或服务中使用这些技术中的任何一种。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;对数据驱动的应用程序和服务的需求不断增加，这给网络基础架构带来了压力。作为数据流的主要来源，网络路由器和交换机在确保无缝通信，数据管理和网络可靠性方面起着重要作用。传统上，这些设备依赖于静态配置和手动管理，这通常会导致可扩展性，效率和安全性挑战。但是，人工智能（AI）正在通过向路由器和开关引入智能，自主和自适应功能来改变网络的领域。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Availability to Accountability: Running AI Workloads Responsibly in the Cloud】问责制的可用性：在云中负责任地运行AI工作负载</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-cloud-availability-to-accountability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI exists everywhere, from personal assistants to autonomous systems, while the cloud serves as its fundamental foundation. The great power creates actual operational difficulties. The cloud enables the rapid growth of AI workloads because it serves as the main platform for hosting and training these systems at a large scale. The management of AI systems within cloud environments requires specific operational challenges. Engineers, together with architects, need to solve essential problems regarding system availability, reliability, observability, and responsibility. The following discussion examines these operational challenges and provides effective solutions to address them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Availability: More Than Just Compute Power&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The compute-intensive nature of AI workloads necessitates dedicated cluster groups (DCGs) to ensure performance. The clusters need to stay within the same proximity group to reduce latency, thus preventing multi-region distribution. The financial limitations often determine cluster dimensions, which leads to reduced scalability when demand increases. The process of cluster provisioning and updates becomes difficult because of worldwide hardware shortages. The process of identifying availability problems remains difficult to accomplish. The absence of built-in diagnostic tools and dependence on outside vendors leads to extended service disruptions. Cloud providers provide buffer capacity for demand increases, yet this capability requires additional expenses.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; AI到处都是，从个人助理到自主系统，而云则是其基本基础。强大的力量会带来实际的操作困难。云使AI工作负载的快速增长，因为它是大规模托管和训练这些系统的主要平台。云环境中AI系统的管理需要具体的操作挑战。工程师与建筑师一起需要解决有关系统可用性，可靠性，可观察性和责任的基本问题。以下讨论研究了这些操作挑战，并提供了有效的解决方案来解决这些挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可用性：不仅仅是计算功率&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; AI工作负载的计算密集型性质需要专门的集群组（DCG）来确保性能。群集需要保持在同一接近组内，以减少潜伏期，从而防止多区域分布。财务限制通常决定集群维度，这会导致需求增加时可伸缩性降低。由于全球硬件短缺，集群供应和更新的过程变得困难。识别可用性问题的过程仍然很难完成。没有内置的诊断工具和对外部供应商的依赖会导致扩展服务中断。云提供商为需求增加提供了缓冲能力，但此功能需要额外的费用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>