<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Supercharging IaC With AI for Next-Gen Infrastructure Efficiency】利用 AI 增强 IaC 性能，提高下一代基础设施效率</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/supercharging-iac-with-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today’s technology landscape, it’s hard to overlook the impact AI is having across nearly every domain. As &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-infrastructure-as-code&#34;&gt;Infrastructure as Code (IaC)&lt;/a&gt; enthusiasts, we’ve been exploring how AI can drive the next evolution of the IaC ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we have already seen, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-devops-with-ai-a-strategy-for-optimized&#34;&gt;AI is playing a significant role in enhancing DevOps&lt;/a&gt; and platform capabilities, and it has become clear that AI will be central to the future of IaC practices. Below, we’ll explore some important areas where AI is reshaping IaC operations and discuss what the future may hold.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的技术领域，很难忽视人工智能对几乎每个领域的影响。作为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-infrastruct-as-code&#34;&gt;基础设施即代码 (IaC)&lt;/a&gt; 爱好者，我们一直在探索人工智能如何推动下一代IaC 生态系统的演变。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正如我们已经看到的，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-devops-with-ai-a-strategy-for-optimized&#34;&gt;人工智能在增强 DevOps 方面发挥着重要作用&lt;/a&gt; 和平台功能，并且很明显，人工智能将成为未来 IaC 实践的核心。下面，我们将探讨人工智能正在重塑 IaC 运营的一些重要领域，并讨论未来的前景。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Order in Chaos: Python Configuration Management for Enterprise Applications】混乱中的秩序：企业应用程序的 Python 配置管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/order-in-chaos-python-configuration-management-for</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Importance of Configuration Management&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In enterprise applications, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/software-configuration&#34;&gt;configuration management&lt;/a&gt; is the most underrated operator that keeps everything integrated and running smoothly. It acts as a backstage manager ensuring all lights are in place, theatrical queues are ready, and the show can go on without a hiccup. Especially, while dealing with multi-environment deployments, with tight-knit &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-ci-cd&#34;&gt;CI/CD&lt;/a&gt; processes, one wrong configuration can pose an application-wide shutdown risk.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Multi-environment enterprise applications carry their own set of challenges and managing configs is no exception. We all have heard the famous “But, it was working on my machine!” excuse more times than daily salutations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;配置管理的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在企业应用程序中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/software-configuration&#34;&gt;配置管理&lt;/a&gt;是最被低估的操作者，它可以保持一切集成并顺利运行。它充当后台经理，确保所有灯光都就位、剧院队列准备就绪、演出可以顺利进行。特别是，在处理多环境部署时，使用紧密的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-ci-cd&#34;&gt;CI/CD&lt;/a&gt; 流程，一个错误的配置可能会造成应用程序范围内的关闭风险。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;多环境企业应用程序面临着自己的一系列挑战，管理配置也不例外。我们都听过著名的“但是，它在我的机器上运行！”原谅的次数比每日问候的次数还要多。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【My Journey With AWS CDK and Java: What You Need To Know】我的 AWS CDK 和 Java 之旅：您需要了解的内容</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/my-journey-with-aws-cdk-and-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;One of the first decisions you’ll need to make when working with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/cdk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)&lt;/a&gt; is choosing the language for writing your Infrastructure as Code (IaC). The CDK currently supports TypeScript, JavaScript, Python, Java, C#, and Go. Over the past few years, I’ve worked with the CDK in TypeScript, Python, and Java. While there is ample information available online for TypeScript and Python, this post aims to share my experience using Java as the language of choice for the AWS CDK.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Wait…What? Use Java With the AWS CDK?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some may say that TypeScript is the most obvious language to use while working with the AWS CDK. The CDK itself is written in TypeScript and it’s also the most used language &lt;a href=&#34;https://matthewbonig.com/posts/community-survey-2023/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;according to the 2023 CDK Community Survey&lt;/a&gt;. Java is coming in 3rd place with a small percentage of use.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/cdk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AWS 云开发套件 (CDK)&lt; 时需要做出的首要决定之一&lt; /a&gt; 正在选择用于编写基础架构即代码 (IaC) 的语言。 CDK 目前支持 TypeScript、JavaScript、Python、Java、C# 和 Go。在过去的几年里，我使用了 TypeScript、Python 和 Java 中的 CDK。虽然网上有大量有关 TypeScript 和 Python 的信息，但本文旨在分享我使用 Java 作为 AWS CDK 的首选语言的经验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;等等……什么？将 Java 与 AWS CDK 结合使用？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有人可能会说，TypeScript 是使用 AWS CDK 时最明显的语言。 CDK 本身是用 TypeScript 编写的，它也是最常用的语言&lt;a href=&#34;https://matthewbonig.com/posts/community-survey-2023/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;根据 2023 年 CDK 社区调查&lt; /a&gt;. Java 排在第三位，使用比例很小。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cutting the High Cost of Testing Microservices】降低微服务测试的高成本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cutting-the-high-cost-of-testing-microservices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A specter is haunting modern development: as our architecture has grown more mature, developer velocity has slowed. A primary cause of lost developer velocity is a decline in testing: in testing speed, accuracy, and reliability. Duplicating environments for microservices has become a common practice in the quest for consistent testing and production setups. However, this approach often incurs significant infrastructure costs that can affect both budget and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;fr-inner&#34; contenteditable=&#34;true&#34; spellcheck=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p contenteditable=&#34;true&#34; style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Testing services in isolation isn’t usually effective; we want to test these components together.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;一个幽灵困扰着现代开发：随着我们的架构变得更加成熟，开发人员的速度已经放缓。开发人员速度下降的主要原因是测试的下降：测试速度、准确性和可靠性。复制微服务环境已成为寻求一致的测试和生产设置的常见做法。然而，这种方法通常会产生大量基础设施成本，从而影响预算和效率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class =“fr-inner”contenteditable =“true”spellcheck =“false”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p contenteditable=&#34;true&#34; style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;单独测试服务通常效果不佳；我们想一起测试这些组件。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The AI Security Gap: Protecting Systems in the Age of Generative AI】人工智能安全差距：保护生成式人工智能时代的系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/protecting-systems-in-the-age-of-genai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The rapid adoption of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;Generative AI (GenAI)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; is transforming industries at an unprecedented pace. Nearly 90% of organizations are actively implementing or exploring LLM use cases, eager to harness the power of these revolutionary technologies. However, this enthusiasm is juxtaposed with a concerning lack of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guarding-the-gates-of-genai-security-challenges-in&#34;&gt;security preparedness&lt;/a&gt;. A recent GenAI Readiness report by Lakera reveals that only about 5% of organizations are confident in their GenAI security frameworks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This glaring disparity between adoption and security readiness raises a critical question: Is the market prepared for GenAI&#39;s potential security risks?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;生成式人工智能 (GenAI)&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/a&gt; 正在以前所未有的速度改变行业。近 90% 的组织正在积极实施或探索 LLM 用例，渴望利用这些革命性技术的力量。然而，这种热情与令人担忧的缺乏&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guarding-the-gates-of-genai-security-challenges-in&#34;&gt;安全准备&lt;/a&gt;并存。 Lakera 最近的一份 GenAI 准备情况报告显示，只有约 5% 的组织对其 GenAI 安全框架充满信心。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;采用和安全准备之间的这种明显差异引发了一个关键问题：市场是否为 GenAI 的潜在安全风险做好了准备？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Lead a Successful Agile Transformation With the VICTORY Framework】利用 VICTORY 框架引领成功的敏捷转型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/successful-agile-transformation-with-victory-framework</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/resistance-to-agile-transformations&#34;&gt;Agile transformations can be tough&lt;/a&gt;. They’re messy, time-consuming, and more often than not, they fail to deliver the promises that got everyone excited in the first place. That’s why it’s so important to approach an Agile transformation as a full-scale organizational change rather than just a shift in how our development teams work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my years as a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/adaptive-change-management&#34;&gt;change management&lt;/a&gt; consultant, I have studied and applied various change management models, from John Kotter’s 8-Step Change Model to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-the-adkar-model-with-it-change&#34;&gt;ADKAR&lt;/a&gt; and Lean Change Management by Jason Little. I have learned through these experiences and countless transformations that there isn’t a one-size-fits-all approach.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/resistance-to-agile-transformations&#34;&gt;敏捷转型可能很困难&lt;/a&gt;。它们很混乱、耗时，而且往往无法兑现最初让每个人都兴奋的承诺。这就是为什么将敏捷转型作为全面的组织变革而不仅仅是我们开发团队工作方式的转变如此重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在担任&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/adaptive-change-management&#34;&gt;变革管理&lt;/a&gt;顾问的这些年里，我研究并应用了 John 的各种变革管理模型Kotter 的 8 步变革模型到 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-the-adkar-model-with-it-change&#34;&gt;ADKAR&lt;/a&gt; 和 Jason Little 的精益变革管理。通过这些经验和无数的转变，我了解到没有一种放之四海而皆准的方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 19:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Set Up Multiple JMS Pods With a Single jmsstore File per Queue in Maximo Application Suites (MAS8)】如何在 Maximo 应用程序套件 (MAS8) 中的每个队列使用单个 jmsstore 文件设置多个 JMS Pod</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/jms-pods-with-single-jmsstore-file-per-queue-in-mas8</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem Statement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, the IBM Manage JMS setup creates a single JMS store file for all queues, which effectively places all queues in one repository. This approach poses a risk: if one queue becomes corrupt and a message is affected, you would have to delete the store file for all queues to resolve the issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;How To Overcome the Problem&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We developed a solution to configure the MAS 8 application with a distinct JMS store file for each queue.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;问题陈述&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认情况下，IBM Manage JMS 设置会为所有队列创建一个 JMS 存储文件，这实际上将所有队列放在一个存储库中。这种方法存在风险：如果一个队列损坏并且一条消息受到影响，您将必须删除所有队列的存储文件才能解决该问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;如何克服问题&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们开发了一种解决方案，为每个队列配置具有不同 JMS 存储文件的 MAS 8 应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ember.js vs React.js: Comparing JavaScript Technologies】Ember.js 与 React.js：比较 JavaScript 技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/comparing-ember-js-vs-react-js</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Frontend technologies are integral to web development as they determine how users interact with a website or app. For this reason, picking the right front-end technology is essential for optimal user engagement and subsequent project success. React.js and Ember.js are among the most popular front-end technologies used in modern web development. Although both fall under the JavaScript umbrella, these technologies differ significantly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will compare React.js vs Ember.js and explore their strengths and weaknesses to help you choose the most suitable one for your needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;前端技术是网络开发不可或缺的一部分，因为它们决定用户如何与网站或应用程序交互。因此，选择正确的前端技术对于最佳用户参与和后续项目成功至关重要。 React.js 和 Ember.js 是现代 Web 开发中最流行的前端技术。尽管两者都属于 JavaScript，但这些技术存在显着差异。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将比较 React.js 与 Ember.js，并探讨它们的优缺点，以帮助您选择最适合您需求的一个。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Keeping Two Multi-Master Databases Aligned With a Vector Clock】保持两个多主数据库与矢量时钟对齐</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/keeping-two-multi-master-dbs-aligned-with-vector-clock</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s tech environment, there is a frequent requirement to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-why-we-need-and-how-to-do-data-synchroniza&#34;&gt;synchronize&lt;/a&gt; applications. This need often arises during technology upgrades, where the goal is to transition a database and its processes from an outdated legacy system to a newer technology. In such scenarios, it&#39;s typically required to allow both applications to coexist for a period of time. Sometimes both applications, together with their own databases, must be maintained as masters because dismantling the processes dependent on the legacy one is not viable. Consequently, specific solutions for keeping the two master databases aligned are essential, ensuring that operations on one database are mirrored on the other one, and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we discuss a real case we dealt with by abstracting away from several technical details, but focusing on those decisions that shape the structure of our solution.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的技术环境中，经常需要&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-why-we-need-and-how-to-do-data-synchroniza &#34;&gt;同步&lt;/a&gt;应用程序。这种需求通常在技术升级期间出现，其目标是将数据库及其流程从过时的遗留系统过渡到更新的技术。在这种情况下，通常需要允许两个应用程序共存一段时间。有时，两个应用程序及其自己的数据库都必须作为主应用程序进行维护，因为拆除依赖于旧应用程序的进程是不可行的。因此，保持两个主数据库一致的特定解决方案至关重要，确保一个数据库上的操作镜像到另一个数据库上，反之亦然。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们通过抽象一些技术细节来讨论我们处理过的一个真实案例，但重点关注那些塑造我们解决方案结构的决策。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 14:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Setting Up a Data Warehouse for Starlight: A Comprehensive Guide】为 Starlight 设置数据仓库：综合指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-set-up-a-data-warehouse</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the rapidly evolving fintech industry, data is a cornerstone for driving innovation, ensuring compliance, and making informed decisions. For Starlight, a burgeoning fintech company, harnessing the power of data is crucial for maintaining a competitive edge. A data warehouse serves as the backbone for such data-driven initiatives, providing a centralized repository where data from various sources is consolidated, analyzed, and made accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A data warehouse is a specialized type of database optimized for analysis and reporting. Unlike traditional databases designed for transactional processing, data warehouses are tailored for query performance and complex analytics. They enable businesses to store vast amounts of historical data, query it efficiently, and derive actionable insights.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在快速发展的金融科技行业，数据是推动创新、确保合规性和做出明智决策的基石。对于星光这样一家新兴的金融科技公司来说，利用数据的力量对于保持竞争优势至关重要。数据仓库是此类数据驱动计划的支柱，提供一个集中存储库，可对来自不同来源的数据进行整合、分析和访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据仓库是一种专门类型的数据库，针对分析和报告进行了优化。与专为事务处理而设计的传统数据库不同，数据仓库是针对查询性能和复杂分析而定制的。它们使企业能够存储大量历史数据、高效查询数据并得出可行的见解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>