<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Seamless RDS to DynamoDB Migration: Unlocking Scalability With the Dual Write Strategy】RDS 到 DynamoDB 的无缝迁移：通过双写入策略解锁可扩展性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/migration-from-rds-to-dynamodb-with-the-dual-write-strategy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Migrating from Amazon RDS to DynamoDB can be a significant challenge, especially when transitioning from a relational database like RDS (PostgreSQL, MySQL, etc.) to DynamoDB, a NoSQL, key-value store. One of the most effective strategies for migrating data incrementally is the Dual Write approach. This allows you to keep both databases in sync during the transition, minimizing downtime and reducing the risk of data inconsistency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article provides a detailed overview of the&amp;nbsp;Incremental Migration with the Dual Write&amp;nbsp;strategy, including the necessary steps, considerations, and best practices.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;从 Amazon RDS 迁移到 DynamoDB 可能是一项重大挑战，尤其是从 RDS（PostgreSQL、MySQL 等）等关系数据库迁移到 DynamoDB（一种 NoSQL 键值存储）时。增量迁移数据的最有效策略之一是双写入方法。这使您可以在过渡期间保持两个数据库同步，从而最大限度地减少停机时间并降低数据不一致的风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文详细概述了使用双写入策略进行增量迁移，包括必要的步骤、注意事项和最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS Performance Tuning: Why EC2 Autoscaling Isn’t a Silver Bullet】AWS 性能调优：为什么 EC2 自动扩展不是灵丹妙药</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-ec2-autoscaling-isnt-a-silver-bullet</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AWS EC2 Autoscaling is frequently regarded as the ideal solution for managing fluctuating workloads. It offers automatic adjustments of computing resources in response to demand, theoretically removing the necessity for manual involvement. Nevertheless, depending exclusively on &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/autoscaling/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;EC2 Autoscaling&lt;/a&gt; can result in inefficiencies, overspending, and performance issues. Although Autoscaling is an effective tool, it does not serve as a one-size-fits-all remedy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a comprehensive exploration of why Autoscaling isn’t a guaranteed fix and suggestions for engineers to improve its performance and cost-effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;AWS EC2 Autoscaling 通常被认为是管理波动工作负载的理想解决方案。它可以根据需求自动调整计算资源，理论上消除了手动参与的必要性。然而，完全依赖 &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/autoscaling/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;EC2 Autoscaling&lt;/a&gt; 可能会导致效率低下、超支、和性能问题。尽管自动缩放​​是一种有效的工具，但它并不是万能的补救措施。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这里全面探讨了为什么自动缩放不能保证修复，并为工程师提供了提高其性能和成本效益的建议。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 22:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Seamless CI/CD Integration: Playwright and GitHub Actions】无缝 CI/CD 集成：Playwright 和 GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/seamless-ci-cd-integration-playwright-and-github-actions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Action integration with Playwright&lt;/strong&gt; enables seamless automated testing and deployment workflows for web applications. GitHub Actions, the platform’s automation tool, allows these tests to be triggered automatically upon code changes, ensuring rapid feedback and efficient bug detection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;This integration empowers teams to build, test, and deploy with confidence, automating repetitive tasks and enhancing overall development productivity. By combining the versatility of Playwright with the automation capabilities of GitHub Actions, developers can streamline their workflows, delivering high-quality web applications with speed and precision.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub Action 与 Playwright 集成&lt;/strong&gt;支持 Web 应用程序的无缝自动化测试和部署工作流程。该平台的自动化工具 GitHub Actions 允许在代码更改时自动触发这些测试，确保快速反馈和高效的错误检测。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;这种集成使团队能够充满信心地构建、测试和部署，自动执行重复任务并提高整体开发效率。通过将 Playwright 的多功能性与 GitHub Actions 的自动化功能相结合，开发人员可以简化工作流程，快速、精确地交付高质量的 Web 应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Python Multi-Version Testing With Tox and Nox】使用 Tox 和 Nox 自动化 Python 多版本测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-python-testing-across-versions-with-tox-and-nox</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In modern Python development, maintaining compatibility across multiple Python versions is super critical, especially for libraries and tools that target a diverse user base. Here, we explore how to use &lt;strong&gt;Tox&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Nox&lt;/strong&gt;, two powerful tools for Python test automation, to validate projects across multiple Python versions. Using a concrete project as an example, we’ll walk through setting up multi-version testing, managing dependencies with &lt;strong&gt;Poetry&lt;/strong&gt;, and using &lt;strong&gt;Pytest&lt;/strong&gt; for unit testing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Automate Multi-Version Testing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Automating tests across &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-tutorial-for-beginners-a-comprehensive-guid&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; versions ensures your project remains robust and reliable in diverse environments. Multi-version testing can:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在现代 Python 开发中，保持多个 Python 版本之间的兼容性非常重要，特别是对于面向不同用户群的库和工具。在这里，我们探讨如何使用 &lt;strong&gt;Tox&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;Nox&lt;/strong&gt; 这两个强大的 Python 测试自动化工具跨多个 Python 版本验证项目。以一个具体项目为例，我们将逐步介绍如何设置多版本测试、使用 &lt;strong&gt;Poetry&lt;/strong&gt; 管理依赖关系，以及使用 &lt;strong&gt;Pytest&lt;/strong&gt; 进行单元测试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么要自动化多版本测试？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;跨 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-tutorial-for-beginners-a-compressive-guid&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; 版本进行自动化测试可确保您的项目在多样化的环境。多版本测试可以：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bitmaps in Dragonfly: Compact Data With Powerful Analytics】Dragonfly 中的位图：具有强大分析功能的紧凑数据</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/bitmaps-in-dragonfly-compact-data-with-powerful-analytics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Do you know that you can represent huge amounts of binary data super compactly by using just a few commands? That&#39;s where the &lt;strong&gt;Bitmap&lt;/strong&gt; data type in Dragonfly comes in. Under the hood, bitmaps are stored as &lt;strong&gt;String&lt;/strong&gt; values, but what makes them special is the ability to perform powerful bit-level operations. Whether you&#39;re counting active users across millions of entries or performing complex bitwise calculations, bitmaps offer a super-efficient way to handle binary data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s dive in and explore the related commands and use cases in this post.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您知道只需使用几个命令就可以超级紧凑地表示大量二进制数据吗？这就是 Dragonfly 中的&lt;strong&gt;位图&lt;/strong&gt;数据类型的用武之地。在幕后，位图存储为&lt;strong&gt;字符串&lt;/strong&gt;值，但它们的特别之处在于能够执行强大的位级操作运营。无论您是计算数百万个条目中的活跃用户数，还是执行复杂的按位计算，位图都提供了一种处理二进制数据的超高效方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们深入探讨本文中的相关命令和用例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Spring Boot WebClient: Performance Optimization and Resilience】Spring Boot WebClient：性能优化和弹性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-webclient-optimizing-performance-and-resilience</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Spring WebClient is a reactive, non-blocking HTTP (HyperText Transfer Protocol) client designed for making requests to external services. It belongs to the Spring WebFlux framework and provides advanced, scalable handling of HTTP requests more efficiently than the RestTemplate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-webclient-and-java-date-time-fields&#34;&gt;WebClient&lt;/a&gt; also supports parallel and reactive programming, making it suitable to perform a large volume of operations without blocking requests. It is ideal when you want to build high-performance applications, either by making external API calls or having thousands of concurrent requests.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Spring WebClient 是一个反应式、非阻塞 HTTP（超文本传输​​协议）客户端，设计用于向外部服务发出请求。它属于 Spring WebFlux 框架，比 RestTemplate 更有效地提供高级、可扩展的 HTTP 请求处理。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-webclient-and-java-date-time-fields&#34;&gt;WebClient&lt;/a&gt; 还支持并行和反应式编程，使其适合在不阻塞请求的情况下执行大量操作。当您想要通过进行外部 API 调用或处理数千个并发请求来构建高性能应用程序时，它是理想的选择。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Level Up Your Code With Formal Methods】使用正式方法升级您的代码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/level-up-your-code-with-formal-methods</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nobody likes bugs in their code&lt;/strong&gt;. They hide in there and cause problems later. Sure, we test our code, but even with things like unit tests, you can&#39;t catch everything. But imagine if you could actually prove your code is totally right, like a math problem. That&#39;s what formal methods let you do. It&#39;s a powerful way to make sure your software really works the way it should.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Formal methods are mathematical techniques used to specify, design, and verify software. They offer a way to guarantee that your code behaves exactly as intended under all possible circumstances. This isn&#39;t just for life-or-death systems like aerospace software; the benefits of formal methods apply to any software project aiming for rock-solid reliability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;没有人喜欢代码中出现错误&lt;/strong&gt;。他们躲在那里并在以后造成问题。当然，我们测试了我们的代码，但即使使用单元测试之类的东西，您也无法捕获所有内容。但想象一下，如果您真的可以证明您的代码完全正确，就像数学问题一样。这就是正式方法可以让你做的事情。这是确保您的软件真正按其应有的方式运行的有效方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;形式化方法是用于指定、设计和验证软件的数学技术。它们提供了一种方法来保证您的代码在所有可能的情况下都完全按照预期运行。这不仅适用于航空软件等生死攸关的系统；也适用于航空航天软件等生死攸关的系统。形式化方法的好处适用于任何旨在实现坚如磐石可靠性的软件项目。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Platforms for End-to-End Testing in 2024】2024 年端到端测试的顶级平台</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-platforms-for-end-to-end-testing-in-2024</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With the app production rate matching the huge user demand, we see millions of apps released every year. Statista states that the total revenue from the app market may reach a projected market volume of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.statista.com/outlook/amo/app/worldwide&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;US$673.80 billion by 2027&lt;/a&gt;. As users expect the best experience in every app, each new software is being released with more innovative features and benefits for added convenience. This makes it crucial for the different app components, including UI and API layers, networks, and external databases, to perform well together.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Malfunctions in even a single component can have a cascading effect, leading to the app crashing. App developers realize that the only way to ensure the smooth functioning of their applications is to perform comprehensive testing with an end-to-end testing tool. The technique called &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-end-to-end-testing-3&#34;&gt;end-to-end testing&lt;/a&gt; verifies an application’s functionality from the users’ perspective, ensuring that all its components work as intended.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着应用程序的生产率与巨大的用户需求相匹配，我们每年都会看到数以百万计的应用程序发布。 Statista 表示，应用程序市场的总收入可能达到预计的市场规模 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.statista.com/outlook/amo/app/worldwide&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank &#34;&gt;到 2027 年将达到 6,738 亿美元&lt;/a&gt;。由于用户期望每个应用程序都能获得最佳体验，因此每个新软件的发布都具有更多创新功能和优势，以增加便利性。这使得不同的应用程序组件（包括 UI 和 API 层、网络和外部数据库）能够良好地协同工作至关重要。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使是单个组件的故障也会产生连锁效应，导致应用程序崩溃。应用程序开发人员意识到，确保应用程序顺利运行的唯一方法是使用端到端测试工具执行全面测试。称为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-end-to-end-testing-3&#34;&gt;端到端测试&lt;/a&gt;的技术可验证用户的应用程序功能&#39; 的角度，确保其所有组件按预期工作。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Intelligent Multi-Agent Conversational Systems Using the AutoGen Framework】使用 AutoGen 框架构建智能多代理对话系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-multi-agent-systems-with-autogen-framework</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Multi-agent conversational systems are multi-layered AI solutions that implement multiple intelligent agents working toward a common objective. Unlike single-agent chatbots, these systems are composed of different agents who perform various roles, such as answering questions or performing certain tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The essential elements that constitute such systems encompass dialogue management (so that the conversation is threaded together), &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-natural-language-interaction&#34;&gt;natural language understanding&lt;/a&gt; (NLU) (to make sense of the user’s utterances), and response generation (to provide suitable context for the replies).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;多代理对话系统是多层人工智能解决方案，可实现多个智能代理以实现共同目标。与单代理聊天机器人不同，这些系统由执行各种角色的不同代理组成，例如回答问题或执行某些任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;构成此类系统的基本要素包括对话管理（以便将对话串联在一起）、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-natural-language -交互&#34;&gt;自然语言理解&lt;/a&gt; (NLU)（理解用户的话语）和响应生成（为回复提供合适的上下文）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ulyp: Recording Java Execution Flow for Faster Debugging】Ulyp：记录 Java 执行流程以加快调试速度</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ulyp-recording-java-execution-flow-for-faster-debugging</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The article presents &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/0xaa4eb/ulyp&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ulyp&lt;/a&gt;, which is an open-source instrumentation agent that records method calls (including arguments and return values) of all third-party libraries of JVM apps. Software engineers can later upload a recording file to the UI desktop app in order to better understand the internals of libraries and even all the applications. The tool can help developers understand the internals of frameworks faster, gain deeper insights, find inefficiencies in software, and debug more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In a few words, Ulyp allows to run this code, which sets up a database source, a cache over the source, and then queries the cache:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本文介绍了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/0xaa4eb/ulyp&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ulyp&lt;/a&gt;，它是一个开源检测代理记录JVM应用程序的所有第三方库的方法调用（包括参数和返回值）。软件工程师稍后可以将录制文件上传到 UI 桌面应用程序，以便更好地了解库甚至所有应用程序的内部结构。该工具可以帮助开发人员更快地了解框架的内部结构，获得更深入的见解，发现软件中的低效问题并更有效地进行调试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;简而言之，Ulyp 允许运行此代码，该代码设置数据库源、源上的缓存，然后查询缓存：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>