<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Reasoning Models Explained: What They Are, How They Work, and When to Use Them Over Traditional LLMs】推理模型解释了：它们是什么，它们的工作方式以及何时在传统LLM上使用它们</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/reasoning-models-vs-llms-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’ve been closely following the evolution of AI in recent years, you are probably aware of the various significant leaps that have advanced the capabilities of the technology. From the development of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLMs&lt;/a&gt; to the generative pre-trained transformer (GPT) that delivered the generative AI offerings that have taken the world by storm, innovation in the field has ramped up significantly in a relatively short space of time. It is an incredible journey that has precipitated the fast realization of AI-led value and potential across industries—and that journey continues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The latest and most significant advancement comes in the form of reasoning models, which are, quite literally, bringing a more considerate element to the technology. Here’s how.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您近年来一直在密切关注AI的演变，那么您可能会意识到已经提高了该技术能力的各种重要飞跃。从&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-with-with-large-language-models”&gt; llms &lt;/a&gt;到生成的预培训的变压器（GPT），这些变压器（gpt）为世界所吸引了世界上的创新空间，使世界相对地占据了现场的空间。这是一段令人难以置信的旅程，它促使AI领导的价值和潜力的快速实现，而这一旅程仍在继续。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最新和最重要的进步以推理模型的形式出现，从字面上看，这为技术带来了更体贴的元素。这是如何。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ArchUnit, Unit Testing The Architecture】Archunit，单位测试架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/archunit-unit-testing-the-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Enforcing a specific package structure or architecture is very important. Especially in Java, where some things must be public to work correctly or actually be available outside their package. ArchUnit is an open-source library that will help you whenever the compiler is not enough.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of the code examples from this article are available in my &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Pask423/articles-misc/tree/master/archunit&#34;&gt;GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;执行特定的软件包结构或体系结构非常重要。尤其是在Java，其中有些事情必须公开工作正确，或者实际上可以在包装外面使用。 Archunit是一个开源库，每当编译器还不够时，都会为您提供帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文中的所有代码示例均可在我的&lt;a a href =“ https://github.com/pask423/articles-misc/tree/master/master/archunit”&gt; github repo &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing and Operating Single-Tenant Architectures at Scale】大规模设计和操作单租户建筑</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/designing-and-operating-single-tenant-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/single-tenant-vs-multi-tenant-architecture-breakin&#34;&gt;Single-tenant architecture&lt;/a&gt; plays a very important role when driven by regulatory/compliance needs, workload isolation to improve security posture and improved performance with dedicated resources. At the same time, these architectures are highly complex and hard to manage, specifically at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll explore common deployment patterns for single-tenant resources, walk through architecture examples, and share automation and observability best practices to run such environments at scale. This post is platform-agnostic and applicable across off-premise or on-premise setups.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/single-tenant-vs-multi-tenant-architecture-arkitecture-breakin-”&gt;单端体系结构&lt;/a&gt;在受监管/合规需求的驱动时，由监管/合规需求，工作负载隔离，以提高安全性和提高专用资源的工作量时起着非常重要的作用。同时，这些体系结构非常复杂且难以管理，特别是规模。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将探讨单租资源的常见部署模式，浏览架构示例，并共享自动化和可观察性的最佳实践，以规模运行此类环境。这篇文章是平台不可静止的，适用于非本地或本地设置。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software Supply Chain Security Regulations From a DevSecOps Perspective】从DEVSECOPS角度来看，软件供应链安全法规</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-supply-chain-security-regulations-devsecops</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-security-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Software Supply Chain Security: Enhancing Trust and Resilience Across the Software Development Lifecycle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;High-profile software supply chain attacks like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.npr.org/2021/04/16/985439655/a-worst-nightmare-cyberattack-the-untold-story-of-the-solarwinds-hack&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SolarWinds&lt;/a&gt;, Log4j, and MOVEit highlight the urgent need to address the vulnerabilities caused by insecure software supply chains, prompting a decisive regulatory response. In the United States, entities like the Federal Trade Commission (FTC), the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.justice.gov/jm/jm-9-48000-computer-fraud&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Computer Fraud and Abuse Act&lt;/a&gt;, and emerging state laws are already being used to penalize companies that contain or distribute vulnerable or malicious code. Meanwhile, Europe&#39;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://digital-strategy.ec.europa.eu/en/policies/cyber-resilience-act&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cyber Resilience Act&lt;/a&gt; and new &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.darkreading.com/cybersecurity-operations/eus-new-product-liability-directive-cybersecurity-impact&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Product Liability Directive&lt;/a&gt; impose stricter cybersecurity obligations, heavy fines, and even personal accountability for software-related harm.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ font-size：17px;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;编辑注：以下是为Dzone的2025年2025年趋势报告编写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/link/link/link/link/2025-security-contribity-contributor-contributor-artilecutor-article- sepusence”增强软件开发生命周期的信任和韧性&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.npr.org/2021/04/16/16/985439655/a-16/985439655/a-worst-nightmare-cyberattack-cy-cyberattack-the-the--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Log4j和Moveit强调了迫切需要解决由不安全的软件供应链引起的漏洞，从而促使其决定性的监管响应。 In the United States, entities like the Federal Trade Commission (FTC), the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.justice.gov/jm/jm-9-48000-computer-fraud&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Computer Fraud and Abuse Act&lt;/a&gt;, and emerging state laws are already being used to penalize companies that contain or distribute vulnerable or恶意代码。同时，欧洲的&lt;a href =“ https://digital-strategy.ec.europa.eu/en/policies/cyber-risilience-act-act- href=&#34;https://www.darkreading.com/cybersecurity-operations/eus-new-product-liability-directive-cybersecurity-impact&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Product Liability Directive&lt;/a&gt; impose stricter cybersecurity obligations, heavy fines, and even personal accountability for software-related harm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Expose IBM FS Cloud Container App to Public】如何将IBM FS Cloud Container应用程序展示到公共</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-expose-ibm-fs-cloud-container-app-to-public</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;352&#34; data-start=&#34;198&#34;&gt;Are you looking for a way to expose your containerized applications to the internet without breaking compliance with IBM Cloud for Financial Services?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;660&#34; data-start=&#34;354&#34;&gt;This guide walks through how to do just that. It shows how to securely expose your apps using the IBM Cloud Framework for Financial Services, with a focus on the IBM Cloud Private Path Service. This service helps you route external traffic to private clusters over secure, compliant VPC-to-VPC connections.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 352” data-start =“ 198”&gt;您是否正在寻找一种将您的容器化应用程序曝光到Internet而不破坏IBM Cloud的金融服务的方法？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 660” data-start =“ 354”&gt;本指南将介绍如何做到这一点。它显示了如何使用IBM云框架为金融服务安全地曝光您的应用程序，重点是IBM Cloud私人路径服务。此服务可帮助您通过安全的，符合安全的VPC-to-VPC连接将外部流量与私人群集路由。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Data Analytics in Healthcare: A Hands-On Approach】实施医疗保健中的数据分析：一种动手方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/healthcare-data-analytics-challenges</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When I first started working with healthcare businesses, one thing struck me right away: there is tons of data, but most of it is a mess. It’s usually stored in separate systems, in different formats, and is hard to aggregate and analyze.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Getting this kind of data into shape takes more than just loading it into a database and writing a few queries. In this article, I’ll walk through some of the real challenges in building healthcare data analytics solutions based on my experience and suggest ways to overcome them.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;当我刚开始与医疗保健业务合作时，一件事就会让我感到震惊：有很多数据，但其中大部分都是一团糟。它通常以不同的格式存储在单独的系统中，并且很难汇总和分析。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;将这种数据变成形状不仅需要将其加载到数据库中并编写一些查询。在本文中，我将根据我的经验来介绍建立医疗保健数据分析解决方案的一些真正挑战，并提出克服它们的方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Today’s Platform Engineer Needs to Build AI-Ready Infrastructure】当今的平台工程师需要建立AI-Ready基础架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/platform-engineering-ai-infrastructure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The demands on today’s platform engineers are evolving at breakneck speed. What began as a natural evolution from DevOps has transformed into a distinct discipline with expanding responsibilities. Today’s platform engineers find themselves at an inflection point: they must not only manage increasingly complex cloud-native environments but also architect the foundation for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence&lt;/a&gt; (AI) across the enterprise. This mandate requires rethinking infrastructure from the ground up to support the unique demands of AI workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;It’s undeniable, however, that this role and shift are both necessary. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/infrastructure-and-it-operations-leaders/topics/platform-engineering&#34;&gt;Gartner states&lt;/a&gt; that by 2026, 80% of large software engineering organizations will establish &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/revealing-the-core-of-platform-engineering&#34;&gt;platform engineering&lt;/a&gt; teams as internal providers of reusable services, components and tools for application delivery — up from 45% in 2022. By 2027, its adoption is expected to significantly impact how infrastructure and operations teams make technology choices, influencing more than half of their decisions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;当今平台工程师的需求正在以惊人的速度发展。从Devops开始的自然演变开始，已转变为一门独特的学科，并扩大了责任。当今的平台工程师发现自己处于一个拐点：他们不仅必须管理越来越复杂的云本地环境，而且还必须为&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-to--antroduction-to-to--artodercorce-interligence”构建基础。该任务要求从头开始重新思考基础架构，以支持AI工作负载的独特要求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;不可否认的是，这种角色和转移都是必要的。 &lt;a href =“ https://www.gartner.com/en/in/infrastructure-and-it-coerations-leaders/topics/pplatform-eendering”&gt; Gartner States &lt;/a&gt;到2026年，到2026年，80％的大型软件工程组织将建立&lt;a &lt;a &lt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/revealing-the-core-of-platform-weadmineering”&gt;平台工程&lt;/a&gt;作为可重用服务，申请服务的内部提供商，用于申请交付的内部提供商，增加了45％的范围，从2022年有45％的影响。决策。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【6 Ways AI-Enhanced Phishing Can Hijack Developer Workflows (and What to Do About It)】A-增强网络钓鱼的6种方式可以劫持开发人员的工作流（以及该怎么做）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-phishing-attacks-developer-workflows</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Phishing is no longer just an inbox problem – it’s a full-fledged software development supply chain risk.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.verizon.com/business/resources/Tea/reports/2025-dbir-data-breach-investigations-report.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;60% of breaches&lt;/a&gt; studied in the 2025 Verizon Data Breach Investigations Report involved the “human element,” with phishing and credential abuse topping the list. Phishing volume overall has &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/slashnext-mid-year-state-of-phishing-report-shows-341-increase-in-bec-and-advanced-phishing-attacks-302152148.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;increased by 4,151%&lt;/a&gt; since ChatGPT’s debut, according to SlashNext’s mid-2024 report.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;网络钓鱼不再只是收件箱问题 - 它是一个成熟的软件开发供应链风险。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一些&lt;a href =“ https://www.verizon.com/business/resources/tea/reports/2025-dbir-data-data-breach-breach-investigations-report.pdf”元素，“网络钓鱼和凭证滥用都在列表中。整体网络钓鱼量&lt;根据Slashnext的2024年中期报告，自Chatgpt首次亮相以来，为4,151％&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Log Spikes? No Sweat: How Top DevOps Teams Tame Bursty Workloads】登录尖峰？没有汗水：顶级DevOps团队如何驯服爆发工作负载</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devops-taming-bursty-workloads</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Taylor Swift ticket sales brought the entire platform to its knees… a crypto exchange saw 10x its regular traffic during a price swing… holiday deals dropped at midnight, and retail sites scrambled to keep up. These weren’t just high-traffic moments. They were log storms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;For DevOps teams in bursty verticals like media, fintech, gaming, and retail, moments like these are make-or-break. Whether the spike is planned (like a product drop) or unpredictable (like an influencer mention), what happens behind the scenes is intense: logging pipelines can flood, ingestion costs can surge, and dashboards often freeze when you need them the most.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;泰勒·斯威夫特（Taylor Swift）的门票销售将整个平台置于膝盖上……加密交易所在价格下跌期间的正常交通量为10倍……假期交易在午夜下降，零售网站争先恐后地跟上。这些不仅仅是流量的时刻。他们是原木风暴。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;对于媒体，金融科技，游戏和零售等爆发的垂直行业的DevOps团队，类似的时刻都是零钱。无论是计划的（例如产品掉落）还是不可预测的（如有影响力的人提到），幕后发生的事情是激烈的：伐木管道可能会洪水泛滥，摄入成本可能会增加，而仪表板通常会在需要时冻结。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【1-Line IO in Java】1线I在Java</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/1-line-io-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Here is a quick coding challenge for all Java developers: How many lines of code do you need to implement the following tasks, using the JDK and any library of your choice?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Rules of the game: Lines of code are counted using standard formatting, you need to close any opened resources, the code may throw IOExceptions, except if stated otherwise):&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这是所有Java开发人员的快速编码挑战：使用JDK和您选择的任何库需要多少行代码来实现以下任务？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;（游戏规则：代码行使用标准格式计数，您需要关闭任何打开的资源，代码可能会抛出IOExceptions，除非另有说明）：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>