<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Supercharging LLMs With Knowledge Graphs for Smarter, Fairer AI】使用知识图增压LLM，以智能，更公平的AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/supercharge-llms-with-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Hey, folks. I’m an AI geek who’s spent years wrestling with large language models (LLMs) like GPT-4. They’re incredible — chatting, coding, reasoning like champs — but they’ve got a flaw: they’re trained on the wild web, soaking up biases like gender stereotypes or racial skews.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Picture an LLM skipping a top-notch female data scientist because it’s hung up on “tech = male.” That’s a real danger in hiring or healthcare apps, and it’s why I’ve poured my energy into Knowledge Graph-Augmented Training (KGAT).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;嘿，伙计们。我是一个AI极客，他花了多年的时间与GPT-4这样的大型语言模型（LLM）搏斗。他们令人难以置信 - 聊天，编码，像冠军一样的推理 - 但他们有一个缺陷：他们在野外的网络上接受了训练，吸收了性别刻板印象或种族偏斜之类的偏见。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;图片llm跳过一流的女性数据科学家，因为它挂在“ Tech = Male”上。这是招聘或医疗保健应用程序的真正危险，这就是为什么我将精力投入到知识的图形培训（KGAT）的原因中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Zero to Meme Hero: How I Built an AI-Powered Meme Generator in React】从零到模因英雄：我如何在React中构建AI驱动的模因发生器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-i-built-ai-powered-meme-generator-react</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Would One Even Construct an AI Meme Generator?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Memes are literally the one thing on the internet that anyone can understand. Whether you want to take a jab at your friend or want to show how coding sometimes gives you brain freezes, memes will always come to your rescue. The issue? Manually doing everything takes ages. You need to source the right picture, come up with snarky lines, and then figure out how to stick everything together without making it look like something a 5-year-old put together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;But now, there are tools such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-openai-reasoning-models-mean-for-gpt-and-ai&#34;&gt;OpenAI&lt;/a&gt; and DeepSeek. With these, you don’t just automate comedy; you also automate currently trending formats and allow users to create memes in a matter of seconds. Here is how we approached our tasks:&lt;/p&gt;】在&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; Memes实际上是任何人都能理解的Internet上的一件事。无论您是想对朋友戳戳还是想展示编码有时会如何使您的大脑冻结，模因总是会救出。问题？手动做所有事情都花了很长时间。您需要采购正确的图片，提出尖锐的线条，然后弄清楚如何将所有东西粘在一起而不使其看起来像一个5岁的东西一起放在一起。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;，但是现在，有一些工具，例如&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-what--what-----reasoning-models-models-mean-for-gpt-and-and-and-and-and-and-and-and-and-and-and-and------------------pt-ind-and-ai一下”&gt; openai &lt;/a&gt;和deepseek。有了这些，您不仅会自动喜剧；您还可以自动化当前趋势格式，并允许用户在几秒钟内创建模因。这是我们处理任务的方式：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding ldd: The Linux Dynamic Dependency Explorer】了解LDD：Linux动态依赖性资源管理器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/linux-ldd-command-dynamic-dependencies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the world of Linux system administration and software development, understanding how executables interact with shared libraries is crucial. Enter &lt;code&gt;ldd&lt;/code&gt; (List Dynamic Dependencies), a powerful command-line utility that helps you peer into the complex web of library dependencies that make your applications run.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this comprehensive guide, we&#39;ll explore &lt;code&gt;ldd&lt;/code&gt;, its usage, security considerations, and how it can help you solve common problems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在Linux系统管理和软件开发的世界中，了解可执行文件如何与共享库进行交互至关重要。输入&lt;code&gt; ldd &lt;/code&gt;（列表动态依赖项），这是一个强大的命令行实用程序，可帮助您浏览使您的应用程序运行的复杂库依赖性网络。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本综合指南中，我们将探索&lt;code&gt; ldd &lt;/code&gt;，其用法，安全注意事项以及如何帮助您解决常见问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Injecting Implementations With Jakarta CDI Using Polymorphism】使用多态性向雅加达CDI注射实施</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/injecting-implementations-jakarta-cdi-polymorphism</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;622&#34; data-start=&#34;363&#34;&gt;When building extensible and maintainable Java applications, a key challenge is &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;choosing the right implementation of an interface without violating the &lt;strong&gt;Open/Closed Principle&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;—&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;that is, without modifying existing code whenever a new behavior is added.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;938&#34; data-start=&#34;624&#34;&gt;In this tutorial, you’ll learn how &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;to &lt;strong&gt;inject implementations&lt;/strong&gt; using Jakarta CDI dynamically&lt;/span&gt;. We’ll use a simple and relatable sample (inspired by musical instruments) to illustrate polymorphism, custom qualifiers, and dynamic resolution with &lt;code data-end=&#34;884&#34; data-start=&#34;871&#34;&gt;Instance&amp;lt;T&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, enabling your code to be both flexible and robust.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;622&#34; data-start=&#34;363&#34;&gt;When building extensible and maintainable Java applications, a key challenge is &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;choosing the right implementation of an interface without violating the &lt;strong&gt;Open/Closed Principle &lt;/strong&gt;— &lt;/span&gt;that is, without modifying existing code whenever a new behavior is added.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 938” data-start =“ 624”&gt;在本教程中，您将了解&lt;span style =“ margin：0px; padding：0px;”&gt; to &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;使用jakarta cdi cdi &lt;/strong&gt;动态&lt;/span&gt;。我们将使用一个简单且相关的样本（受乐器的启发）来说明多态性，定制预选赛和动态分辨率，并使用&lt;code data-end =“ 884” data-start =“ 871”&gt;实例&lt;t&gt; &lt;/code&gt;，使您的代码既灵活又有强大。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Monitor a Folder Using Event-Driven Ansible】如何使用事件驱动的Ansible监视文件夹</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/folder-monitoring-with-event-driven-ansible</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Real-time data processing, security compliance, and automation are crucial for keeping systems running smoothly and efficiently. &lt;strong&gt;Folder monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; plays a big role in this, allowing systems to detect changes — like new files being added, modified, or deleted — and take action right away.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Event-Driven Ansible provides an automated way to monitor and manage folders, instantly reacting to changes, detecting them quickly, and taking automated actions while integrating smoothly with your existing tools and systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;实时数据处理，安全性合规性和自动化对于保持系统的运行平稳有效至关重要。 &lt;strong&gt;文件夹监视&lt;/strong&gt;在此中起着重要作用，允许系统检测更改（例如被添加，修改或删除的新文件）并立即采取行动。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;事件驱动的Ansible提供了一种自动化方法来监视和管理文件夹，立即对更改做出反应，快速检测它们并采取自动操作，同时与现有的工具和系统平稳集成。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When Doris Learns to &#34;Speak Dialects&#34;】当多丽丝学会“说话”</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/when-doris-learns-to-speak-dialects</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Data migration is like moving house — every data engineer has faced this headache: a pile of SQL statements that need rewriting, as if you have to disassemble and reassemble all the furniture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Different systems&#39; SQL syntax is like different dialects. Although they all speak the SQL language, each has its own &#34;accent&#34; and habits. &lt;em style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&#34;If only there were a &#39;translator&#39;!&#34;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;This is probably the wish of every engineer who has experienced system migration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据迁移就像搬家一样 - 每个数据工程师都面临着这种头痛：一堆需要重写的SQL语句，就好像您必须拆卸和重新组装所有家具一样。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不同的系统的SQL语法就像不同的方言。尽管他们都说SQL语言，但每种语言都有自己的“口音”和习惯。 &lt;em style =“背景色：透明;”&gt;“如果只有&#39;translator&#39;！“！” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style =“ backend-color：transparent;”&gt;这可能是每个经历系统迁移的工程师的愿望。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Create Dialog Boxes in Java】如何在Java中创建对话框</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/create-dialogue-boxes-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Dialog boxes are graphical components that are usually used to display errors or give some other information (e.g., request input) to the user. They are commonly part of the three top-level containers that each Java graphical user interface (GUI) application must have as a root. Dialogs are typically associated with a parent frame. Their dependence on frames means that when you close a frame, all its associated dialog boxes also close. However, note that minimizing (iconifying) a frame does not automatically minimize its dialogs in modern Java implementations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Java programming tutorial introduces developers to creating and working with dialog boxes in Java GUI applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;对话框是图形组件，通常用于显示错误或向用户提供其他信息（例如，请求输入）。它们通常是每个Java图形用户界面（GUI）应用程序必须将其作为根的三个顶级容器的一部分。 Dialogs are typically associated with a parent frame.它们对帧的依赖意味着，当您关闭框架时，其所有相关的对话框也关闭。但是，请注意，将框架最小化（Iconify）并不能自动最大程度地减少其在现代Java实现中的对话框。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此Java编程教程介绍了开发人员在Java GUI应用程序中创建和使用对话框。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Apache Doris and Hudi for Data Querying and Migration】集成Apache Doris和Hudi进行数据查询和迁移</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrate-apache-doris-hudi-data-querying-migration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;In the field of big data analytics, real-time data availability, query performance, and flexibility are crucial. With the rise of the Lakehouse architecture as a new paradigm in big data, integrating Apache Doris, a high-performance real-time analytical database, with Apache Hudi, a data lake management framework focused on incremental data processing, provides powerful federated query and data migration capabilities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;This integration enables seamless collaboration while accelerating enterprise data architecture upgrades. In this article, we will explore how to integrate Apache Doris with Hudi to achieve efficient federated querying and data migration, along with best practices and optimization techniques.&lt;/p&gt;】在大数据分析，实时数据可用性，查询性能和灵活性的领域中，&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;至关重要。随着Lakehouse体系结构作为大数据的新范式的兴起，Apache Doris是一个高性能实时分析数据库，而Apache Hudi则是一个集中在增量数据处理的数据湖管理框架Apache Hudi，提供了强大的联合疑问和数据迁移功能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;此集成在加速企业数据体系结构升级的同时可以实现无缝协作。在本文中，我们将探讨如何将Apache Doris与Hudi集成，以实现有效的联合查询和数据迁移以及最佳实践和优化技术。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Implement Linked Lists in Go】如何在GO中实现链接列表</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/go-linked-lists</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Linked lists are one of the most common data structures used for dynamic memory allocation. Here, a list of a finite set of elements is created, which contains at least two memory locations: one for the data element and another for the pointer that links the next set of elements. This tutorial explains how different linked lists can be implemented using pointers and structure types in Go.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Data Structures in Go&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The random access memory (RAM) can be visualized as a table, a matrix, or a grid of addressable locations. In order to store values in the table, Go programmers need to designate it into &lt;em&gt;locatable structures&lt;/em&gt;. These locatable structures are given a convenient name called &lt;em&gt;variable name&lt;/em&gt;. Understand that a name given to a variable is only for the convenience of the programmer; once the program is compiled, the variable name is replaced with a &lt;em&gt;reference&lt;/em&gt; (or memory address, such as &lt;strong&gt;0x78BAC&lt;/strong&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;链接列表是用于动态内存分配的最常见数据结构之一。在这里，创建了一组有限元素的列表，其中包含至少两个内存位置：一个用于数据元素，另一个用于链接下一组元素的指针。本教程解释了如何使用指针和结构类型在GO中实现不同的链接列表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; GO &lt;/h2&gt;中的数据结构&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随机访问存储器（RAM）可以可视化为表，矩阵或可寻址位置的网格。为了将值存储在表格中，GO程序员需要将其指定为可置处的结构&lt;/em&gt;。这些可定点的结构被给出了一个方便的名称，称为&lt;em&gt;变量名称&lt;/em&gt;。理解给变量的名称仅是为了方便程序员；一旦编译了程序，变量名称将替换为A &lt;em&gt;参考&lt;/em&gt;（或内存地址，例如&lt;strong&gt; 0x78bac &lt;/strong&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Problem Analysis in Apache Doris StreamLoad Scenarios】Apache Doris流中心方案中的问题分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/problem-analysis-of-apache-doris-streamload</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Apache Doris provides multiple ways to import data,&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;including StreamLoad, HdfsLoad (gradually replacing BrokerLoad), RoutineLoad, MySQLLoad, and others. StreamLoad is the most commonly used method, as many data synchronization tools like Flink, Spark, and DataX use it&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;under the hood.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since &lt;a href=&#34;https://doris.apache.org/docs/dev/data-operate/import/import-way/stream-load-manual?_highlight=stream&amp;amp;_highlight=load&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;StreamLoad&lt;/a&gt; is the underlying mechanism for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/auto-synchronization-of-a-whole-mysql-database-for&#34;&gt;Flink Doris Connector&lt;/a&gt;, Spark Doris Connector, and DataX, most data import issues tend to occur with StreamLoad. This article will discuss common import errors and their solutions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; apache doris提供了多种导入数据的方法，&lt;span style =“ margin：0px; padding：0px;”&gt;包括流载荷，hdfsload，hdfsload（逐渐替换了BROKERLOAD），ROFURINELOLOAD，MYSQLLOAD和其他。流载是最常用的方法，因为许多数据同步工具（例如Flink，Spark和Datax）在引擎盖下使用&lt;/span&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以来&lt;a href =“ https://doris.apache.org/docs/dev/data-operation/import/import-port/import-way/stream-load-load-manual?_highlight = stream＆_highlight＆_highlight＆highlight = lightlight = llight = light = light = lighlight = llight =“ href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/auto-synchronization-of-a-whole-mysql-database-for”&gt; Flink Doris Connector &lt;/a&gt; Spark Doris Connector和Datax，大多数数据导入问题往往会随着流载荷而发生。本文将讨论常见的导入错误及其解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>