<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Greenplum vs Apache Doris: Features, Performance, and Advantages Compared】GreenPlum vs Apache Doris：比较功能，性能和优势</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/greenplum-vs-apache-doris-mpp-analytics-comparison</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;257&#34; data-start=&#34;226&#34;&gt;As organizations increasingly rely on data for real-time decision-making, the demand for scalable, high-performance analytical databases has never been higher. Among the contenders in the modern analytics space, Greenplum and Apache Doris stand out for their MPP (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-greenplum-database-intro-to-the-big-data-d&#34;&gt;Massively Parallel Processing&lt;/a&gt;) architectures and ability to handle large-scale data workloads. While both are designed for analytics, they differ significantly in architecture, performance, and ease of management. This article provides a side-by-side comparison to help data teams evaluate which solution better aligns with their technical and business needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;257&#34; data-start=&#34;226&#34;&gt;1. Overview and Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-end=&#34;272&#34; data-start=&#34;259&#34;&gt;Greenplum&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;523&#34; data-start=&#34;274&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-ensure-fast-join-queries-for-self-service-b&#34;&gt;Greenplum&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;is an open-source distributed relational database based on PostgreSQL. It adopts an MPP (Massively Parallel Processing) architecture, designed specifically for large-scale data analytics. Its architecture consists of three main components:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 257” data-start =“ 226”&gt;，随着组织越来越依赖数据进行实时决策，对可扩展，高性能分析数据库的需求从未如此高。在现代分析领域的竞争者中，GreenPlum和Apache Doris脱颖而出（&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what what-is-is-greenplum-database-intro-database-intro-the-the-the-the-the-big-data----------------&gt;大量平行处理&lt;/a&gt;）架构和能力的架构数据工作。尽管两者都是为分析设计的，但它们在体系结构，性能和易于管理方面都有很大差异。本文提供了并排的比较，以帮助数据团队评估哪些解决方案更好地与其技术和业务需求保持一致。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end =“ 257” data-start =“ 226”&gt; 1。概述和体系结构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-end =“ 272” data-start =“ 259”&gt; greenplum &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 523” data-start =“ 274”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-xe--gene-fast-join-quin-join-quin-----------------------self-service-b&gt; greenplum &lt;/a&gt;是一个基于PostGresql的开放式源数据库。它采用了专门为大规模数据分析设计的MPP（大规模并行处理）体系结构。它的架构由三个主要组成部分组成：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero-Touch Patch Management With PowerShell and Intune: How We Automated Compliance at Scale】使用PowerShell和Intune的零接触补丁管理：我们如何规模自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automated-patch-management-intune-powershell</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Keeping hundreds of endpoints patched and compliant sounds easy on paper until you’re juggling different departments, conflicting maintenance windows, and manual tracking spreadsheets. We knew our approach had to change when a missed update led to a critical zero-day vulnerability exposure in one of our branch office servers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article walks through how we transitioned from inconsistent, manual patching to a fully automated, audit-friendly system using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/endpoint-security-controls&#34;&gt;Microsoft Intune&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/windows-powershell&#34;&gt;PowerShell&lt;/a&gt;, and scheduled compliance logic. No third-party tools. No more guesswork.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在纸上保持数百个端点和兼容的声音，直到您兼顾不同的部门，维护窗口冲突和手动跟踪电子表格。我们知道，当错过的更新导致我们的分支机构服务器之一的关键零日漏洞暴露时，我们的方法必须改变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/endpoint-security-controls”&gt; Microsoft Intune &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a&gt;，&lt;a&gt; Microsoft Intune &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/windows-powershell”&gt; PowerShell &lt;/a&gt;，并计划合规性逻辑。没有第三方工具。没有更多的猜测。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Comparing Cassandra and DynamoDB: A Side-By-Side Guide】比较Cassandra和DynamoDB：并排指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cassandra-vs-dynamodb-database-comparison</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;654&#34; data-start=&#34;104&#34;&gt;Database technologies have gone through revolutions in the last decade. With just a handful of databases before, there are now multiple options — selecting the right one for a new project is often a challenge. The last decade saw the rise in popularity of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-nosql-database-1&#34;&gt;NoSQL databases&lt;/a&gt;, which remove some of the complexities of relational databases for use cases that don’t require structured queries. This article attempts to compare two popular NoSQL databases: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-dynamodb-a-developers-guide&#34;&gt;DynamoDB&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/apache-cassandra&#34;&gt;Cassandra&lt;/a&gt;. It highlights their features and compares database operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Evolution&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;943&#34; data-start=&#34;661&#34;&gt;Cassandra is an open-source database released under the Apache License. It was originally built by Facebook for internal use and open-sourced in 2008. Ongoing development and stewardship of Cassandra is handled by the Apache Software Foundation. The latest version available at the time of writing is 5.0.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 654” data-start =“ 104”&gt;数据库技术在过去十年中经历了旋转。以前只有少数数据库，现在有多个选项 - 为新项目选择合适的选项通常是一个挑战。在过去的十年中，&lt;a a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-nosql-database-1”&gt; nosql数据库的受欢迎程度的上升&lt;/a&gt;，这些数据库&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，它消除了不需要结构质量的用例的一些复杂的关系数据库。本文尝试比较两个流行的NOSQL数据库：&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-dynamodb-a-developers-guide”&gt; dynamyodb &lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href =“它突出了他们的功能并比较数据库操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Evolution &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 943” data-start =“ 661”&gt; Cassandra是根据Apache许可证发布的开源数据库。它最初是由Facebook建造的，用于内部用途，并于2008年开源。卡桑德拉（Cassandra）正在进行的开发和管理由Apache Software Foundation处理。写作时可用的最新版本为5.0。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python Async/Sync: Understanding and Solving Blocking (Part 1)】python async/sync：理解和解决阻塞（第1部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-async-vs-sync-blocking</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: This blog post is divided into two parts to provide a comprehensive guide to mastering asynchronous and synchronous code coexistence in Python. This first part focuses on understanding the core problems and initial solutions. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/async-sync-advanced-blocking-detection&#34;&gt;second part&lt;/a&gt; will&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;focus on detecting blocking code and best practices&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern Python applications increasingly leverage asyncio to build highly concurrent systems, from responsive APIs and intelligent bots to efficient data pipelines. However, a common challenge arises when integrating new asynchronous code with existing synchronous components. This fusion often leads to frustrating performance bottlenecks, including mysterious timeouts, blocked event loops, and unexpected slowdowns. The complexity can escalate further when multithreading enters the equation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;：此博客文章分为两个部分，以提供综合指南，以掌握Python中的异步和同步代码共存。第一部分专注于理解核心问题和初始解决方案。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/async-sync-advanced-blocking-detection”&gt;第二部分&lt;/a&gt; Will &lt;span style =“ backgly-color：throckfact-color：parterparent;&gt; &lt;/sparent;&gt; &lt;/sparent;“&gt; &lt;/spar&gt;专注于检测块代码和最佳实践&lt;span style &lt;span style &lt;span style =“背景=” croppent collor =“ contercolor：cransparent：crantparent：&gt; &lt;/preparent;&gt; &lt;/prepparent;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代Python应用程序越来越多利用Asyncio来构建高度并发系统，从响应式API和智能机器人到有效的数据管道。但是，将新的异步代码与现有同步组件集成在一起时会出现一个普遍的挑战。这种融合通常会导致令人沮丧的性能瓶颈，包括神秘的超时，堵塞的事件循环和意外的放缓。当多线程进入方程式时，复杂性可以进一步升级。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Ultimate Guide to OCR Transcription Services】OCR转录服务的最终指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-ultimate-guide-to-ocr-transcription-services</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Transcribing handwriting to text is standard among businesses that need to scan handwritten documents or convert old records into something accessible and editable online or in searchable databases. Not only can transcribing handwritten documents make data extraction easy, but it is also a way to go paperless.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With OCR’s expanding role across industries, from healthcare and finance to logistics and legal, the global market reached a valuation of USD 12.56 billion in 2023 and is projected to grow at a CAGR of 14.8% through 2030 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.grandviewresearch.com/industry-analysis/optical-character-recognition-market&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Grand View Research&lt;/a&gt;). This surge is largely fueled by advancements in transcription services that enhance OCR accuracy and usability, ensuring high-quality text extraction from diverse sources.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;将笔迹转录为文本是需要扫描手写文档或将旧记录转换为在线或可搜索数据库中可访问且可编辑的事物的企业中的标准标准。抄录手写文档不仅可以使数据提取变得容易，而且还可以使数据提取无纸化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;随着OCR在整个行业的不断扩展，从医疗保健和财务到物流和法律，全球市场在2023年达到125.6亿美元，预计将以14.8％的复合年增长href =“ https://www.grandviewresearch.com/industry-analysis/optical-character-character-rcognition-market” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt;大视图研究&lt;/a&gt;）。这种激增在很大程度上是由提高OCR准确性和可用性的转录服务的进步所推动的，从而确保了从各种来源中提取高质量的文本。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing Cloud Applications: Best Practices for Developers】确保云应用程序：开发人员的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-security-best-practices-for-developers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;402&#34; data-start=&#34;171&#34;&gt;Cloud computing offers unmatched scalability and flexibility, but it also introduces new security challenges. Developers must take proactive steps to secure applications, infrastructure, and sensitive data from cyber threats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;805&#34; data-start=&#34;404&#34;&gt;In this tutorial, we will explore essential cloud security best practices covering:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 402” data-start =“ 171”&gt;云计算提供了无与伦比的可扩展性和灵活性，但它也引入了新的安全挑战。开发人员必须采取积极的步骤来保护应用程序，基础架构和敏感数据，从网络威胁中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 805” data-start =“ 404”&gt;在本教程中，我们将探索基本的云安全性最佳实践：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Yet Another Servers in Go: Understanding epoll, kqueue, and netpoll】GO中的另一个服务器：了解Epoll，Kqueue和NetPoll</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/go-servers-understanding-epoll-kqueue-netpoll</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Hi there!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article demystifies how Go’s standard &lt;code&gt;net&lt;/code&gt; package handles thousands of connections under high load by leveraging non-blocking I/O through&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;嗨！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文通过利用非块I/O到&lt;/p&gt;来揭示GO的标准&lt;/code&gt; net &lt;/code&gt;软件包在高负载下处理数千个连接</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Root Cause Analysis: Introducing the Incident Investigator】AI驱动的根本原因分析：介绍事件研究者</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/introducing-the-incident-investigator</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Debugging cloud infrastructure problems can be time-consuming and stressful. Incidents rarely come with an obvious explanation. It usually takes digging through logs, comparing deployments, and searching through dashboards just to understand what changed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With Microtica’s AI Incident Investigator, that changes. This AI-powered agent helps &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sre-vs-devopssre-is-to-devops-what-scrum-is-to-agi&#34;&gt;DevOps and SRE teams&lt;/a&gt; find the root cause of incidents faster by providing natural language insights based on deployment context, change history, and system telemetry.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;调试云基础架构问题可能耗时且压力很大。事件很少有明显的解释。通常需要挖掘日志，比较部署和通过仪表板进行搜索，以了解发生了什么变化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;与Microtota的AI事件调查员发生了变化。 This AI-powered agent helps &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sre-vs-devopssre-is-to-devops-what-scrum-is-to-agi&#34;&gt;DevOps and SRE teams&lt;/a&gt; find the root cause of incidents faster by providing natural language insights based on deployment context, change history, and system telemetry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build an AI-Powered Chatbot With Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) Using LangGraph】如何使用langgraph构建具有检索型发电（RAG）的AI驱动聊天机器人</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-chatbot-with-rag-langgraph</link>
      <description>【&lt;h3 data-end=&#34;511&#34; data-start=&#34;497&#34;&gt;Why RAG?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1923&#34; data-start=&#34;1582&#34;&gt;Large language models (LLMs) like GPT-4 can produce fluent, grammatically accurate text; however, without access to external, updated knowledge, they frequently hallucinate or fabricate facts. This turns into a prime issue in high-stakes environments — like legal, medical, or business enterprise contexts — in which accuracy and accept as true with are non-negotiable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;2261&#34; data-start=&#34;1925&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag&#34;&gt;Retrieval-augmented generation&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) resolves this problem by fetching relevant, trusted information from your own knowledge base (e.g., documents, PDFs, internal databases) and injecting it into the LLM prompt. This method grounds the model`s outputs, dramatically lowering hallucinations whilst tailoring responses to your domain.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h3 data-end =“ 511” data-start =“ 497”&gt;为什么抹布？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1923” data-start =“ 1582”&gt;大型语言模型（LLMS）（例如GPT-4）可以产生流利的，语法准确的文本；但是，如果没有访问外部，更新的知识，他们经常幻觉或捏造事实。在高风险环境（例如法律，医疗或商业企业环境）中，这变成了一个主要问题，在该环境中，准确性并接受为真实的是不可谈判的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 2261” data-start =“ 1925”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/Articles/introduction-tocult-to-to-to-to-to-to-to-to--retrieval-aig--generation-generation-generation-generation-rag”&gt; reteliectal-aignieval-aignieval-aightenagment-aight agient &lt;/a&gt;（rag）（rag）通过从您的知识群体中找到该问题来解决此问题，从您自己的知识群体中（E.并将其注入LLM提示。这种方法将模型的输出理由，大大降低了幻觉，同时调整对您的域的响应。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Design Automation in Closure Engineering: Building Parametric Assemblies With CATIA and VB Scripting】封闭工程中的设计自动化：使用CATIA和VB脚本的构建参数组件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/design-automation-closure-engineering-catia-vb</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern closure systems in EVs and advanced vehicles demand more than just clean geometry; they require embedded logic, constraint-driven structures, and validation-aware modeling. While CATIA V5/V6 offers robust 3D capabilities, its true power emerges when engineers start treating CAD like code. With VB scripting, it is possible to encode design intelligence directly into the CAD model, enabling parametric automation across complex mechanical assemblies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article breaks down how parametric automation can reduce review-cycle fatigue, enforce design intent, and enable a traceable, simulation-ready closure workflow.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;电动汽车和高级车辆中的现代封闭系统不仅仅是干净的几何形状，还需要更多。他们需要嵌入式逻辑，约束驱动的结构和验证感知建模。尽管Catia V5/V6具有强大的3D功能，但当工程师开始像代码一样将CAD处理时，它的真实功能就会出现。通过VB脚本，可以将设计智能直接编码到CAD模型中，从而在复杂的机械组件上实现参数自动化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文分解了参数自动化如何减少审核周期疲劳，强制设计意图，并启用可追溯的，可进行模拟的闭合工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>