<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Foundational Building Blocks for AI Applications】人工智能应用的基础构建模块</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/foundational-building-blocks-for-ai-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Startups are revolutionizing their growth trajectory by harnessing AI technologies. From intelligent chatbots handling customer inquiries to sophisticated recommendation systems personalizing user experiences, AI tools are enabling small teams to achieve outsized impact. Modern startups can now automate complex operations, derive actionable insights from data, and scale their services efficiently - capabilities once reserved for large enterprises. Let&#39;s explore the practical implementation of AI in startups, examining both the essential technology stack and real-world applications through the lens of system architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the following article, we will dive deep into two ways you can leverage AI models in your organization&#39;s solution stack:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;初创公司正在利用人工智能技术彻底改变其增长轨迹。从处理客户询问的智能聊天机器人到提供个性化用户体验的复杂推荐系统，人工智能工具使小型团队能够发挥巨大的影响力。现代初创公司现在可以自动化复杂的操作，从数据中获取可行的见解，并有效地扩展其服务——这些能力曾经是大型企业保留的。让我们探索人工智能在初创企业中的实际实施，通过系统架构的视角来审视基本技术堆栈和实际应用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在下一篇文章中，我们将深入探讨您在组织的解决方案堆栈中利用 AI 模型的两种方法：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java Application Containerization and Deployment】Java应用程序容器化和部署</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/refcardz/java-application-containerization-and-deployment</link>
      <description>【Application containerization provides a way to combine all required app resources into a single, standardized, easily manageable package. And for Java applications, containerization helps solve the majority of challenges related to portability and consistency. This Refcard walks readers step by step through Dockerfile creation for Java apps, container image builds, deployment strategies, and more.】应用程序容器化提供了一种将所有必需的应用程序资源组合到单个、标准化、易于管理的包中的方法。对于 Java 应用程序来说，容器化有助于解决与可移植性和一致性相关的大多数挑战。此参考卡将逐步引导读者了解 Java 应用程序的 Dockerfile 创建、容器映像构建、部署策略等。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Redefining Ethical Web Scraping in the Wake of the Generative AI Boom】在生成式人工智能热潮中重新定义道德网络抓取</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ethical-web-scraping-in-the-wake-of-generative-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Public web data is being used for various purposes, from impactful research to creating and improving products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;One of the most common ways to acquire such data is through web scraping. Because it involves gathering large amounts of data published by businesses or individuals online, it raises questions such as &#34;Is it ethical?&#34; The short answer is yes if you&#39;re following certain practices, but we need to lay the groundwork before diving head-first into it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;公共网络数据被用于各种目的，从有影响力的研究到创建和改进产品。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;获取此类数据的最常见方法之一是通过网络抓取。由于它涉及收集企业或个人在线发布的大量数据，因此引发了诸如“这是否道德？”等问题。如果您遵循某些做法，简短的答案是肯定的，但我们需要在深入研究之前奠定基础。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitOps Software Development Principles – And the Benefits for the Entire Organization】GitOps 软件开发原则 – 以及对整个组织的好处</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gitops-software-development-principles</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The GitOps model for software development is a boon to productivity and software security. Companies that aren’t embracing it are missing a huge opportunity to release better software faster and with lower risk. This benefits the entire organization by reducing the possibility of everything from buggy software to cyberattacks. Here’s a bit of history to explain what GitOps is, how it has evolved, why developers love it, and why businesses should too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;History of DevOps&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DevOps was created about a decade ago to bridge the longstanding gap between software development and IT operations. Traditionally, these two groups worked in silos: developers focused on writing code and adding new features, while the operations team was responsible for deploying and maintaining the software in production environments. This separation often led to miscommunication, conflicting objectives, and delays. Developers aimed for rapid innovation, sometimes introducing changes that could destabilize the system, whereas operations prioritized system stability and uptime, often resisting frequent changes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;软件开发的 GitOps 模型有助于提高生产力和软件安全性。不接受它的公司会错失一个以更低的风险更快地发布更好的软件的巨大机会。这可以降低从有缺陷的软件到网络攻击等各种情况的可能性，从而使整个组织受益。这里有一些历史来解释 GitOps 是什么、它是如何演变的、为什么开发人员喜欢它以及为什么企业也应该喜欢它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DevOps 的历史&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DevOps 大约十年前创建，旨在弥合软件开发和 IT 运营之间长期存在的差距。传统上，这两个团队各自为政：开发人员专注于编写代码和添加新功能，而运营团队负责在生产环境中部署和维护软件。这种分离常常导致沟通不畅、目标冲突和延误。开发人员的目标是快速创新，有时会引入可能破坏系统稳定性的更改，而运营人员则优先考虑系统稳定性和正常运行时间，通常会抵制频繁的更改。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Write for DZone Publications: Trend Reports and Refcards】如何为 DZone 出版物写作：趋势报告和参考卡</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-write-for-dzone-publications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The DZone team is thrilled that you&#39;re interested in writing for DZone Publications! We are always seeking new authors to build up our author database. However, DZone Publications operate a bit differently from DZone site articles. Keep reading to learn more about writing for DZone Publications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;How to Stand Out on DZone&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;We handpick authors to write for DZone Publications. There are many things we look for when selecting authors, but it all boils down to one thing: &lt;strong&gt;Your DZone profile is your best tool for recognition&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DZone 团队很高兴您有兴趣为 DZone Publications 撰写文章！我们一直在寻找新的作者来建立我们的作者数据库。然而，DZone 出版物的运作方式与 DZone 网站文章略有不同。继续阅读以了解有关为 DZone Publications 撰写文章的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如何在 DZone 上脱颖而出&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我们精心挑选作者为 DZone Publications 撰稿。在选择作者时，我们会考虑很多因素，但这一切都归结为一件事：&lt;strong&gt;您的 DZone 个人资料是您获得认可的最佳工具&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 12:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker Security Best Practices for Enterprise Applications: From Development to Production】企业应用程序的 Docker 安全最佳实践：从开发到生产</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-security-best-practices-for-enterprise-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s enterprise landscape, containerization has become almost synonymous with modern application deployment. However, with containers handling sensitive data and critical business operations, security should be carefully considered and implemented. I&#39;ve spent years securing containerized applications in the financial sector, and today I&#39;m going to share some battle-tested Docker security practices that have helped protect sensitive data for millions of customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Enterprise Container Security Landscape&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we dive into the technical stuff, let&#39;s talk about why &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-explained-an-introductory-guide-to-docker&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; security matters more than ever. With containers handling everything from payment processing to personal data, a single vulnerability can expose your entire infrastructure. Here&#39;s what keeps enterprise security teams up at night:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的企业环境中，容器化几乎已成为现代应用程序部署的代名词。然而，对于处理敏感数据和关键业务操作的容器，应仔细考虑和实施安全性。我花了数年时间保护金融领域的容器化应用程序，今天我将分享一些经过实战检验的 Docker 安全实践，这些实践帮助保护了数百万客户的敏感数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;企业容器安全格局&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在深入讨论技术内容之前，我们先来谈谈为什么&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-explained-an-introductory-guide-to-docker&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt;安全比以往任何时候都更加重要。由于容器处理从支付处理到个人数据的所有事务，一个漏洞就可能暴露您的整个基础设施。以下是让企业安全团队彻夜难眠的原因：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring the New Boolean Data Type in Oracle 23c AI】探索 Oracle 23c AI 中的新布尔数据类型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-the-new-boolean-data-type-in-oracle-23c-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This exciting release of Boolean Data Type Lab for Oracle Database 23c AI introduces native support for the boolean data type, a game-changer for database developers. With this enhancement, you can &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;natively represent &lt;strong&gt;true&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;false&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;null&lt;/strong&gt; values&lt;/span&gt;, simplifying data modeling and making SQL and PL/SQL development more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate, let’s recreate a scenario involving a &lt;strong&gt;Student Information System&lt;/strong&gt;, where we’ll track whether students are currently enrolled in courses using the new boolean data type.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这个激动人心的 Oracle Database 23c AI 布尔数据类型实验室版本引入了对布尔数据类型的本机支持，这为数据库开发人员带来了游戏规则的改变。通过此增强功能，您可以&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;本机表示 &lt;strong&gt;true&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;false&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;null&lt;/strong&gt;值&lt;/span&gt;，简化数据建模并使 SQL 和 PL/SQL 开发更加高效。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了说明这一点，让我们重新创建一个涉及&lt;strong&gt;学生信息系统&lt;/strong&gt;的场景，我们将在其中使用新的布尔数据类型跟踪学生当前是否注册了课程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Java Class Extension Library for Data-Oriented Programming - Part 2】使用 Java 类扩展库进行面向数据的编程 - 第 2 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/using-java-class-extension-library-part-2</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This is the second article that presents an object-oriented programming (OOP) approach to effectively separate data from domain-specific logic in data-oriented programming, utilizing the dynamic class extensions using the Java Class Extension Library. You can read the &lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-java-class-extension-library&#34; target=&#34;_self&#34;&gt;first article there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Let us reconsider the same scenario where we are building a warehouse application designed to handle the shipping of various items. We have established a hierarchy of classes to represent the goods we have:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;这是介绍面向对象编程 (OOP) 方法的第二篇文章，该方法利用动态类扩展，在面向数据的编程中有效地将数据与特定于域的逻辑分离Java 类扩展库。您可以在那里阅读&lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-java-class-extension-library&#34; target=&#34;_self&#34;&gt;第一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;让我们重新考虑同样的场景，我们正在构建一个旨在处理各种物品运输的仓库应用程序。我们建立了一个类层次结构来表示我们拥有的商品：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero Trust for AI: Building Security from the Ground Up】人工智能零信任：从头开始构建安全</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-for-ai-building-security-from-the-ground-up</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;As artificial intelligence (AI) continues to revolutionize industries, its role in critical applications continues to grow exponentially. With all this innovation comes a growing concern — how do we keep AI systems secure? Unlike traditional applications, AI deals with highly sensitive data, intricate models, and sprawling networks that don’t fit neatly within the walls of traditional security measures. Traditional security models, built on the assumption of trust within a defined network perimeter, are proving inadequate in protecting the highly distributed, dynamic, and sensitive nature of AI workflows. In the context of AI, where sensitive data, complex models, and distributed systems intersect, Zero Trust offers a proactive and holistic approach to security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This article explores the need for Zero Trust in AI, the fundamental principles that direct its application, and practical methods to safeguard AI systems from the outset.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;随着人工智能 (AI) 不断给行业带来变革，其在关键应用中的作用继续呈指数级增长。随着所有这些创新，人们越来越关注——我们如何保证人工智能系统的安全？与传统应用程序不同，人工智能处理高度敏感的数据、复杂的模型和庞大的网络，这些数据无法完全适应传统安全措施的范围。传统的安全模型建立在定义的网络边界内的信任假设之上，事实证明，它不足以保护人工智能工作流程的高度分布式、动态和敏感的性质。在敏感数据、复杂模型和分布式系统交叉的人工智能背景下，零信任提供了一种主动且全面的安全方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;本文探讨了人工智能零信任的必要性、指导其应用的基本原则，以及从一开始就保护人工智能系统的实用方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Atlassian Data Center Application Upgrades】自动化 Atlassian 数据中心应用程序升级</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-atlassian-data-center-application-upgrades</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Atlassian applications like Jira, Jira Service Management (JSM), Confluence, and Bitbucket are indispensable business tools worldwide. However, maintaining their security, stability, and performance requires regular updates to patch vulnerabilities, enhance features, and improve overall efficiency. With frequent security releases from Atlassian, managing upgrades in multi-node environments can become challenging. This is where tools like Ansible, Chef, and Terraform become essential for simplifying and streamlining the upgrade process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article demonstrates how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/automation-ansible-ai&#34;&gt;Ansible&lt;/a&gt; facilitates upgrading Jira Data Center, ensuring security and operational efficiency while minimizing downtime.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Jira、Jira Service Management (JSM)、Confluence 和 Bitbucket 等 Atlassian 应用程序是全球不可或缺的业务工具。然而，保持其安全性、稳定性和性能需要定期更新以修补漏洞、增强功能并提高整体效率。随着 Atlassian 频繁发布安全版本，管理多节点环境中的升级可能变得具有挑战性。这就是 Ansible、Chef 和 Terraform 等工具对于简化升级过程至关重要的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文演示了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/automation-ansible-ai&#34;&gt;Ansible&lt;/a&gt; 如何促进 Jira Data Center 升级，确保安全性和运营效率，同时最大限度地减少停机时间。&lt; /p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>