<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Zero Trust API With ASP.NET Core: A Developer’s Guide】使用 ASP.NET Core 构建零信任 API：开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-zero-trust-api-with-aspnet-core-a-devel</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In a world where cyber threats are just one click away (or just one QR code scan away), the old-school “castle and moat” security approach isn’t enough. Enter Zero Trust — a security model that flips the script, requiring every request to be verified, authenticated, and monitored, no matter where it comes from. For developers working with ASP.NET Core APIs that handle sensitive data, this isn’t just a trend; it’s a necessity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s dive into the why, what, and how of implementing Zero Trust in your ASP.NET Core API.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在网络威胁只需点击一下（或只需扫描一次二维码）的世界中，老式的“城堡和护城河”安全方法是不够的。输入零信任——一种翻转脚本的安全模型，要求每个请求都经过验证、认证和监控，无论它来自哪里。对于使用处理敏感数据的 ASP.NET Core API 的开发人员来说，这不仅仅是一种趋势；这是必需的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们深入了解在 ASP.NET Core API 中实现零信任的原因、内容和方式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 23:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Backpressure in Distributed Systems】分布式系统中的背压</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/backpressure-in-distributed-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An unchecked flood will sweep away even the strongest dam.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;–&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Ancient Proverb&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;不受控制的洪水甚至会冲走最坚固的水坝。 &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;–&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;古代谚语&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Augmenting the Client With Vue.js】使用 Vue.js 增强客户端</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/augmenting-the-client-with-vuejs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/server-side-rendering-with-spring-boot&#34;&gt;previous post&lt;/a&gt;, I laid the ground to build upon. Now is the time to start &#34;for real&#34;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I heard a lot of &lt;a href=&#34;https://vuejs.org/&#34;&gt;Vue.js&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, a friend who transitioned from developer to manager told me good things about Vue, which further piqued my interest. I decided to take a look at it. It will be the first &#34;lightweight&#34; JavaScript framework I&#39;ll study — from the point of view of a newbie, which I am.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/server-side-rendering-with-spring-boot&#34;&gt;上一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;中，我奠定了基础。现在是开始“真正”的时候了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我听过很多&lt;a href=&#34;https://vuejs.org/&#34;&gt;Vue.js&lt;/a&gt;。此外，一位从开发人员转型为经理的朋友告诉我有关 Vue 的好消息，这进一步激起了我的兴趣。我决定看一下。它将是我要研究的第一个“轻量级”JavaScript 框架——从我这个新手的角度来看。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Data Engineering Into Artificial Intelligence】将数据工程融入人工智能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-data-engineering-into-machine-learning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Data is often referred to as the lifeblood of artificial intelligence and machine learning (ML). We know the value of data: it fuels insights, provides input for predictions, and is foundational for data engineers&#39; and data scientists&#39; decisions. The journey from raw data to meaningful information is lengthy which is where data engineering fits into play. Incorporating data engineering and dealing with the messiness of the dataset is crucial to having a smooth flow of data through the ML pipeline, leading us to better models and consistent results. In this article, I’ll take a deep dive into how data engineering and Machine Learning intersect and why it is important in this era of modern data-driven applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Importance of Data Engineering in Artificial Intelligence&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Machine learning relies on data and its accuracy. Raw data transformation involves landing data, cleaning, transformation as per requirements, and loading to the target to make it meaningful. These activities take from extracting the source systems up to a point where you analyze using some tool/configuration. The ML lifecycle has these stages, and data engineering is the focus of each step.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;数据通常被称为人工智能和机器学习 (ML) 的命脉。我们知道数据的价值：它可以激发洞察力，为预测提供输入，并且是数据工程师和数据科学家决策的基础。从原始数据到有意义的信息的过程是漫长的，这正是数据工程发挥作用的地方。结合数据工程并处理数据集的混乱程度对于使数据顺利通过机器学习管道至关重要，从而使我们获得更好的模型和一致的结果。在本文中，我将深入探讨数据工程和机器学习如何交叉，以及为什么它在现代数据驱动应用程序的时代如此重要。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;数据工程在人工智能中的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;机器学习依赖于数据及其准确性。原始数据转换涉及数据落地、清理、根据需求进行转换，并加载到目标以使其有意义。这些活动从提取源系统到使用某种工具/配置进行分析。机器学习生命周期有这些阶段，数据工程是每个步骤的重点。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 20:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java for AI】用于人工智能的 Java</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-for-artificial-intelligence</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is modernizing industries by enabling machines to perform tasks that typically require no human intervention; tasks such as problem-solving, natural language understanding, and image processing. For AI-related software development, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/machine-learning-with-python-data-preprocessing&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; is often used. However, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; is also a powerful option, as many organizations are using it in enterprise applications due to its robustness and scalability. In this article, we explore how the Java programming language can be used for AI development, along with supporting libraries and tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Java Programming Language for AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java offers several features that make Java suitable for AI-related task development:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能 (AI) 使机器能够执行通常不需要人工干预的任务，从而实现工业现代化；解决问题、自然语言理解和图像处理等任务。对于AI相关的软件开发，经常使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/machine-learning-with-python-data-preprocessing&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt;。然而，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 也是一个强大的选择，因为许多组织由于其稳健性和可扩展性而在企业应用程序中使用它。在本文中，我们将探讨如何使用 Java 编程语言以及支持库和工具进行 AI 开发。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;人工智能 Java 编程语言&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java 提供了多种功能，使 Java 适合人工智能相关任务的开发：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 18:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maturing an Engineering Organization From DevOps to Platform Team】使工程组织从 DevOps 到平台团队走向成熟</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/maturing-an-organization-from-devops-to-platform</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The DevOps model broke down the wall between development and production by assigning deployment and production management responsibilities to the application engineers and providing them with infrastructure management tools. This approach expanded engineers&#39; competencies beyond their initial skill sets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This model helped companies gain velocity as applications weren&#39;t passed around from team to team, and owners became responsible from ideation to production. It shortened the development lifecycle and time to deployment, making companies more agile and responsive.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DevOps 模型通过将部署和生产管理职责分配给应用工程师并为他们提供基础设施管理工具，打破了开发和生产之间的壁垒。这种方法扩展了工程师的能力，超出了他们最初的技能范围。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;该模型帮助公司提高了速度，因为应用程序不再在团队之间传递，并且所有者负责从构思到生产的整个过程。它缩短了开发生命周期和部署时间，使公司更加敏捷和响应迅速。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 19:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Concurrency Issues in SQL and Distributed Systems】SQL 和分布式系统中的并发问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/concurrency-issues-in-sql-and-distributed-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;An SQL database must handle multiple incoming connections simultaneously to maintain optimal system performance. The expectation is that the database can accept and process numerous requests in parallel. It&#39;s straightforward when different requests target separate data, such as one request reading from &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and another from &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Table 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. However, complications arise when multiple requests involve reading from and writing to the same table. How do we keep the performance high and yet avoid consistency issues? Let’s read on to understand how things work in SQL databases and distributed systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Transactions and Issues&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An SQL transaction is a collection of queries (such as &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SELECT&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;INSERT&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;UPDATE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;DELETE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;) sent to the database to be executed as a single unit of work. This means that either all queries in the transaction must be executed, or none should be. Executing transactions is not atomic and takes time. For example, a single &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;UPDATE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; statement might modify multiple rows, and the database system needs time to update each row. During this update process, another transaction might start and attempt to read the modified rows. This raises the question: should the other transaction read the new values of the rows (even if not all rows are updated yet), the old values of the rows (even if some rows have been updated), or should it wait? What happens if the first transaction must be canceled later for any reason? How should this affect the other transaction?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;SQL 数据库必须同时处理多个传入连接以保持最佳系统性能。期望数据库能够并行接受和处理大量请求。当不同的请求针对不同的数据时，这很简单，例如一个请求读取&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;表 1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;，另一个请求读取&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;表 2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; 。然而，当多个请求涉及读取和写入同一个表时，就会出现复杂情况。我们如何保持高性能并避免一致性问题？让我们继续阅读以了解 SQL 数据库和分布式系统中的工作原理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;交易和问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SQL 事务是查询的集合（例如 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;SELECT&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;INSERT&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;&lt; em&gt;UPDATE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;DELETE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;）发送到数据库以作为单个工作单元执行。这意味着要么必须执行事务中的所有查询，要么不执行任何查询。执行事务不是原子的并且需要时间。例如，单个&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;UPDATE&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;语句可能会修改多行，而数据库系统需要时间来更新每行。在此更新过程中，另一个事务可能会启动并尝试读取已修改的行。这就提出了一个问题：另一个事务应该读取行的新值（即使尚未更新所有行）、行的旧值（即使某些行已更新），还是应该等待？如果由于任何原因必须稍后取消第一笔交易，会发生什么情况？这将如何影响其他交易？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advanced Strategies for Building Modern Data Pipelines】构建现代数据管道的高级策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-strategies-for-building-modern-data-pipel</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In today&#39;s data-driven world, organizations increasingly rely on sophisticated data pipelines to manage vast volumes of data generated daily. A &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-data-pipeline&#34;&gt;data pipeline&lt;/a&gt; is more than just a conduit for data — it is a complex system that involves the extraction, transformation, and loading (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-elt-1&#34;&gt;ETL&lt;/a&gt;) of data from various sources to ensure that it is clean, consistent, and ready for analysis. This article explores advanced strategies, the process of building data pipelines, and the pillars of a successful modern data strategy, with a focus on both real-time and batch data processing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Steps for Building Data Pipelines&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Building modern data pipelines that are efficient, scalable, and resilient requires advanced strategies and a deep understanding of the underlying technologies. Let’s dive into the key steps to building out your data pipelines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在当今数据驱动的世界中，组织越来越依赖复杂的数据管道来管理每天生成的大量数据。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-data-pipeline&#34;&gt;数据管道&lt;/a&gt;不仅仅是数据的管道 - 它是一个复杂的系统，涉及从各种来源提取、转换和加载 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-elt-1&#34;&gt;ETL&lt;/a&gt;) 数据，以确保数据干净、一致，并准备好进行分析。本文探讨了高级策略、构建数据管道的过程以及成功的现代数据策略的支柱，重点关注实时和批量数据处理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;构建数据管道的步骤&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;构建高效、可扩展且具有弹性的现代数据管道需要先进的策略和对底层技术的深入了解。让我们深入探讨构建数据管道的关键步骤。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 21:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Angular RxJS Unleashed: Supercharge Your App With Reactive Operators】Angular RxJS 释放：使用响应式运算符为您的应用程序增强功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/angular-rxjs-reactive-operators</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/angularjs-essentials&#34;&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most popular frameworks for building dynamic web applications, and at its core lies &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/rxjs-streams&#34;&gt;RxJS&lt;/a&gt;, is a library designed for composing asynchronous and event-based programs by using observable sequences. RxJS operators are powerful tools that allow developers to manipulate and transform data streams efficiently. But how exactly do you use them in Angular? This article will provide a detailed, step-by-step guide on how to leverage RxJS operators in Angular, complete with examples to help you master this essential skill.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 527px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;37.5 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/jpeg&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1726296106728&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/14/2024 06:41 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17918475-a-new-design-made-with-postermywall-4.jpg&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;37517&#34; data-name=&#34;a-new-design-made-with-postermywall-4.jpg&#34; data-id=&#34;17918475&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17918475-a-new-design-made-with-postermywall-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Angular and RxJS logos&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Are RxJS Operators?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In Angular, RxJS operators play a key role in managing HTTP requests, user actions, and other asynchronous tasks, making it easier to chain operations and work with data streams. These operators are essentially functions that take an Observable as input and produce a new Observable as output. This allows developers to efficiently handle asynchronous workflows, event handling, and state management. RxJS operators are grouped into categories like creation, transformation, filtering, and combination, offering a powerful toolkit for composing and managing complex operations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/angularjs-essentials&#34;&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt; 是构建动态 Web 应用程序最流行的框架之一，其核心是位于&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/rxjs-streams&#34;&gt;RxJS&lt;/a&gt;，是一个设计用于通过使用可观察序列来编写异步和基于事件的程序的库。 RxJS 运算符是强大的工具，允许开发人员有效地操作和转换数据流。但在 Angular 中到底如何使用它们呢？本文将提供有关如何在 Angular 中利用 RxJS 运算符的详细分步指南，并提供示例来帮助您掌握这项基本技能。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 527px;&#34; class =“fr-fic fr-dib lazyload”data-image =“true”data-new =“false”data-sizeformatted =“37.5 kB”data-mimetype =“image/jpeg”data-creationdate =“1726296106728”数据-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/14/2024 06:41 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17918475-a-new-design-made- with-postermywall-4.jpg&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;37517&#34; data-name=&#34;a-new-design-made-with-postermywall-4.jpg&#34; data-id=&#34;17918475&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17918475-a-new-design-made-with-postermywall-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Angular 和 RxJS 徽标&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;什么是 RxJS 运算符？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在 Angular 中，RxJS 运算符在管理 HTTP 请求、用户操作和其他异步任务方面发挥着关键作用，使链接操作和处理数据流变得更加容易。这些运算符本质上是采用 Observable 作为输入并生成新的 Observable 作为输出的函数。这使得开发人员能够有效地处理异步工作流程、事件处理和状态管理。 RxJS 运算符分为创建、转换、过滤和组合等类别，为编写和管理复杂操作提供了强大的工具包。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 17:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Flink, Kafka, and NiFi for Real-Time Airport Arrivals and Departures】使用 Flink、Kafka 和 NiFi 实现实时机场到达和出发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/flink-kafka-and-nifi-for-real-time-airport-arrivals</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In this stage of development of our real-time data pipeline, we are starting to build up all of the feeds we need to be able to make smart decisions quickly and provide all the necessary data to AI and ML models to things like answer LLM/NLP chat questions on how should I go somewhere if I am leaving tomorrow, now, or soon. This will incorporate weather, air quality, roads, buses, light rail, rail, planes, social media, travel advisories, and more. As part of this, we will provide real-time notifications to users via Slack, Discord, Email, Web socket front-ends, and other dashboards. I am open to working with collaborators in open source or suggestions for end-user applications and other data processors like my friends at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.risingwave.dev/docs/current/intro/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RisingWave&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.timeplus.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Timeplus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://startree.ai/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;StarTree Pinot,&lt;/a&gt; LLM/Vector Database collaborators like &lt;a href=&#34;https://zilliz.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Zilliz Milvus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/products/watsonx-ai&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IBM watsonx.ai&lt;/a&gt;, and others.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;source srcset=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 640w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 720w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 750w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 786w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 828w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 1100w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 1400w&#34; sizes=&#34;(min-resolution: 4dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (min-resolution: 3dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 67vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 3) and (max-width: 700px) 65vw, (min-resolution: 2.5dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2.5) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (min-resolution: 2dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px&#34; type=&#34;image/webp&#34;&gt; &lt;source data-testid=&#34;og&#34; srcset=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 640w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 720w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 750w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 786w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 828w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 1100w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 1400w&#34; sizes=&#34;(min-resolution: 4dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (min-resolution: 3dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 67vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 3) and (max-width: 700px) 65vw, (min-resolution: 2.5dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2.5) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (min-resolution: 2dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px&#34;&gt; &lt;img data-fr-image-pasted=&#34;true&#34; alt=&#34;openskyairport — nifi — kafka — flink SQL&#34; width=&#34;700&#34; height=&#34;310&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;openskyairport — nifi — kafka — flink SQL&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;source srcset=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 640w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 720w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 750w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 786w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 828w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 1100w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 1400w&#34; sizes=&#34;(min-resolution: 4dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (min-resolution: 3dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 67vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 3) and (max-width: 700px) 65vw, (min-resolution: 2.5dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2.5) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (min-resolution: 2dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px&#34; type=&#34;image/webp&#34;&gt; &lt;source data-testid=&#34;og&#34; srcset=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 640w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 720w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 750w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 786w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 828w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 1100w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 1400w&#34; sizes=&#34;(min-resolution: 4dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (min-resolution: 3dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 67vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 3) and (max-width: 700px) 65vw, (min-resolution: 2.5dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2.5) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (min-resolution: 2dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;img data-fr-image-pasted=&#34;true&#34; alt=&#34;Airport terminal&#34; width=&#34;700&#34; height=&#34;1050&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-src=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;br&gt;&#xA; &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/ko/@klalive&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Jue Huang&lt;/a&gt; on&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unsplash&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;REST API To Obtain Airport Information&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;https://opensky-network.org/api/flights/arrival?airport=${airport}&#xA;&amp;amp;begin=${now():toNumber():divide(1000):minus(604800)}&#xA;&amp;amp;end=${now():toNumber():divide(1000)}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;在实时数据管道的现阶段开发中，我们开始构建我们需要的所有源，以便能够快速做出明智的决策并提供所有必要的数据人工智能和机器学习模型，比如回答 LLM/NLP 聊天问题，如果我明天、现在或很快就要离开，我应该去哪里。这将包括天气、空气质量、道路、公共汽车、轻轨、铁路、飞机、社交媒体、旅行建议等。作为其中的一部分，我们将通过 Slack、Discord、电子邮件、Web 套接字前端和其他仪表板向用户提供实时通知。我愿意与开源合作者合作，也愿意为最终用户应用程序和其他数据处理器提供建议，例如我的朋友 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.risingwave.dev/docs/current/intro/&#34; rel=&#34; noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RisingWave&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.timeplus.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Timeplus&lt;/a&gt; 、&lt;a href=&#34;https://startree.ai/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;StarTree Pinot、&lt;/a&gt; 法学硕士/矢量数据库合作者，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https:// zilliz.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Zilliz Milvus&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/products/watsonx-ai&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IBM watsonx.ai&lt;/a&gt; 等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;源srcset =“https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 640w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit： 720/格式：webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 720w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 750w，https://miro.medium。 com/v2/resize:fit:786/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 786w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 828w， https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/format:webp/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 1100w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/format:webp /1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 1400w&#34; 尺寸=&#34;(最小分辨率: 4dppx) 和 (最大宽度: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4) 和 (最大宽度: 700px) 50vw，（最小分辨率：3dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）67vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：3）和（最大宽度：700px）65vw，（最小分辨率：2.5dppx） ）和（最大宽度：700px）80vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：2.5）和（最大宽度：700px）80vw，（最小分辨率：2dppx）和（最大宽度：700px） 100vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：2）和（最大宽度：700px）100vw，700px“type =“image / webp”&gt; &lt;源data-testid =“og”srcset =“https： //miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 640w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 720w，https: //miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 750w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 786w，https: //miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 828w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 1100w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png 1400w&#34; 尺寸=&#34;（最小分辨率：4dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）50vw， （-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：4）和（最大宽度：700px）50vw，（最小分辨率：3dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）67vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel -ratio：3）和（最大宽度：700px）65vw，（最小分辨率：2.5dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）80vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：2.5）和（最大-宽度：700px）80vw，（最小分辨率：2dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）100vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：2）和（最大宽度：700px）100vw，700px“ &gt; &lt;img data-fr-image-pasted=&#34;true&#34; alt=&#34;openskyairport — nifi — kafka — flink SQL&#34; width=&#34;700&#34; height=&#34;310&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-diblazyload&#34; data-src =&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/1*8HGyMyGp4pWf9fz6vnlz8g.png&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;openskyairport — nifi — kafka — flink SQL&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/图标题&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;源srcset =“https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 640w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 720w ，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 750w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 786w，https:// /miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 828w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 1100w，https://miro.medium .com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 1400w&#34; 尺寸=&#34;(最小分辨率: 4dppx) 和 (最大宽度: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4)和（最大宽度：700px）50vw，（最小分辨率：3dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）67vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：3）和（最大宽度：700px）65vw ，（最小分辨率：2.5dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）80vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：2.5）和（最大宽度：700px）80vw，（最小分辨率：2dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）100vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：2）和（最大宽度：700px）100vw，700px“type =“image / webp”&gt; &lt;源数据testid = “og” srcset =“https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 640w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 720w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 750w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 786w，https： //miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 828w，https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 1100w，https://miro。 medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ 1400w&#34; 尺寸=&#34;(最小分辨率: 4dppx) 和 (最大宽度: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4 ）和（最大宽度：700px）50vw，（最小分辨率：3dppx）和（最大宽度：700px）67vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：3）和（最大宽度：700px） 65vw，（最小分辨率：2.5dppx）和（最大宽度：700px） 80vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：2.5）和（最大宽度：700px）80vw，（最小分辨率：2dppx ）和（最大宽度：700px）100vw，（-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio：2）和（最大宽度：700px）100vw，700像素&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;img data-fr-image-pasted=&#34;true&#34; alt=&#34;机场航站楼&#34; width=&#34;700&#34; height=&#34;1050&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-src=&#34;https: //miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:700/0*SVjyNPDBr6VnxtQJ&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;br&gt;&#xA; &lt;/图标题&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;照片由 &lt;a href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/ko/@klalive&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Jue Huang&lt;/a&gt; 拍摄，在 Unsplash 上&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/图标题&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;REST API 获取机场信息&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;https://opensky-network.org/api/flights/arrival?airport=${airport}&#xA;&amp;begin=${now():toNumber():除(1000):减(604800)}&#xA;&amp;end=${now():toNumber():divide(1000)}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>