<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Spring Data Neo4j: How to Update an Entity】春季数据NEO4J：如何更新实体</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spring-data-neo4j-how-to-update-an-entity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;After working on a new online Spring Data Neo4j course, I learned a couple more things about updating an entity. The course required a different set of scenarios than outlined in my previous SDN update blog post, so I wanted to cover those scenarios, as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Spring save() Method&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First up is the out-of-the-box &lt;code&gt;save()&lt;/code&gt; method that is provided by &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-guide-to-spring-framework-annotations&#34;&gt;Spring&lt;/a&gt; as a default. This method takes an input of the entity object you want to save to the database.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在进行新的在线春季数据NEO4J课程后，我学到了更多有关更新实体的知识。该课程与我以前的SDN更新博客文章中概述的课程相比需要不同的方案，因此我也想介绍这些方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; Spring Save（）方法&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先是由&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a-guide-to-to-to-提供的开箱即用&lt;/code&gt; save（）&lt;/code&gt;方法Spring-Framework-Notations“&gt; Spring &lt;/a&gt;默认情况下。此方法将要保存到数据库的实体对象输入。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing Kubernetes in Production With Wiz】与Wiz一起确保Kubernetes的生产</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-security-platform-wiz</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Today&#39;s cloud environments use Kubernetes to orchestrate their containers. The Kubernetes system minimizes operational burdens associated with provisioning and scaling, yet it brings forth advanced security difficulties because of its complex nature. The adoption of Kubernetes by businesses leads organizations to use dedicated security platforms to protect their Kubernetes deployments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wiz functions as a commercial &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-kubernetes-security&#34;&gt;Kubernetes security&lt;/a&gt; solution that delivers threat detection, policy enforcement, and continuous monitoring capabilities to users. Organizations must evaluate Wiz against direct competitors both inside and outside the open-source landscape to confirm it satisfies their requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;今天的云环境使用Kubernetes来编排其容器。 Kubernetes系统最大程度地减少了与配置和扩展相关的运营负担，但由于其复杂的性质，它带来了先进的安全困难。企业对Kubernetes的采用使组织使用专用的安全平台来保护其Kubernetes部署。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; wiz用作商业&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-kubernetes-security”&gt; kubernetes安全连续向用户监视功能。组织必须对开源环境内外的直接竞争对手进行评估，以确认其满足其要求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Security Controls in the Android Operating System (OS)】Android操作系统（OS）中的安全控制</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/security-controls-in-the-android-operating-system</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As part of the Android Application Security series, we are going to understand the security controls provided by Android OS (operating system) to protect the applications that are running on the device. Without these security controls in place, the data on the devices or transmitted by apps could be easily accessed by other apps or devices in the network.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before getting started, if you haven&#39;t read the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/andriod-application-architecture&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;first part of this series&lt;/a&gt;, I highly recommend reading it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为Android应用程序安全系列的一部分，我们将了解Android OS（操作系统）提供的安全控件，以保护设备上运行的应用程序。如果没有这些安全控件，则可以由网络中的其他应用程序或设备轻松访问设备上的数据或应用程序传输的数据。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在开始之前，如果您还没有阅读&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/andriod-application-architection-architecture” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ _ blank”&gt;这个系列&lt;/a&gt;，我强烈建议阅读它。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing API Integration Efficiency With a Mock Client】通过模拟客户提高API集成效率</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-api-integration-efficiency-mock-client</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Due to the rapid growth of the API industry, client-server interaction must be seamless for everyone. Dependence on live APIs during development, however, may cause delays, particularly if the APIs are currently being built or undergoing frequent changes. A mock client can be&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;helpful for developers aiming for efficiency and reliability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, we focus on the concept of mock clients, their significance, and how to use them for development.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;span data-proserver空间=“ true”&gt;由于API行业的快速增长，客户服务器的交互对于每个人来说都必须无缝。但是，在开发过程中对实时API的依赖可能会导致延迟，特别是如果当前正在构建API或经常进行更改时。模拟客户端可以是&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;对旨在提高效率和可靠性的开发人员有帮助。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在本文中，我们关注模拟客户的概念，其意义以及如何将其用于开发。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Drupal as a Headless CMS for Static Sites】Drupal作为静态站点的无头CM</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/drupal-headless-cms-for-static-sites</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The use of digital platforms has made it crucial for people and companies to build their brands online. Although traditional CMS solutions are versatile, they involve the burden of taking care of databases and server-side rendering.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article examines the possibility of using Drupal as a headless CMS coupled with static site generators. In this way, Drupal can act as a powerful backend for handling the content while allowing for the development of fast, secure, and lightweight static websites. This approach is to get the best of both platforms: on the one hand, Drupal’s flexibility in content modeling and, on the other hand, the efficiency and scalability of static sites.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;数字平台的使用使人们和公司在线建立自己的品牌至关重要。尽管传统的CMS解决方案具有通用性，但它们涉及照顾数据库和服务器端渲染的负担。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;本文研究了将Drupal用作无头CMS与静态位点发生器的可能性。这样，Drupal可以充当处理内容的强大后端，同时允许开发快速，安全和轻质静态网站。这种方法是为了获得两个平台的最好：一方面，Drupal在内容建模方面的灵活性以及另一方面的静态站点的效率和可扩展性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【An In-Depth Guide to Threads in OpenAI Assistants API】Openai Assistants API中线程的深入指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/openai-assistants-api-threads-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this blog, we will explore what chat completion models can and cannot do and then see how Assistance API addresses those limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;section name=&#34;6073&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;6178&#34;&gt;We will also focus on threads and messages  —  how to create them, list them, retrieve them, modify them, and delete them. Additionally, we will add some Python code snippets and show possible outputs based on the script language.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在此博客中，我们将探讨哪些聊天完成模型可以和不能执行的操作，然后查看帮助API如何解决这些限制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;部分名称=“ 6073”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name =“ 6178”&gt;我们还将专注于线程和消息 - 如何创建它们，列出它们，检索它们，修改它们并删除它们。此外，我们将添加一些Python代码片段，并根据脚本语言显示可能的输出。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Improving Cloud Infrastructure for Achieving AGI】改善实现AGI的云基础架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/improving-cloud-infrastructure-for-agi</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Artificial general intelligence (AGI) represents the most ambitious goal in the field of artificial intelligence. AGI seeks to emulate human-like cognitive abilities, including reasoning, understanding, and learning across diverse domains.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The current state of cloud infrastructure is not sufficient to support the computational and learning requirements necessary for AGI systems. To realize AGI, significant improvements to cloud infrastructure are essential.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p Style =“ Text-Align：左;”&gt;人工通用智能（AGI）代表了人工智能领域中最雄心勃勃的目标。 AGI试图效仿类似人类的认知能力，包括跨不同领域的推理，理解和学习。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;云基础架构的当前状态不足以支持AGI系统所需的计算和学习要求。要实现AGI，对云基础架构的重大改进是必不可少的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Explore Open WebUI: Your Offline AI Interface】探索打开的webui：您的离线AI接口</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/explore-open-webui-your-offline-ai-interface</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for a user-friendly, self-hosted AI interface designed to operate entirely offline? Look no further; Open WebUI might be what you are looking for. In this blog, you will dive into some nice features of Open WebUI. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quite some inference engines exist which can run locally, for example, Ollama, LMStudio, LocalAI, Jan, and many others. Some of them also come with a Graphical User Interface (GUI). However, these run locally on the same machine as the inference engine. What if you would like to offer a ChatGPT-like user interface within your company that runs entirely offline? The inference engine runs on dedicated machines with GPUs (on-premise or in a private cloud), and the GUI is a web application available to your users. The advantage of this setup is that all your data does not leave your company and is not shared with any cloud vendor. The privacy of your data is secured with this setup.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否正在寻找旨在完全离线操作的用户友好，自托管的AI接口？别无所求；打开webui可能是您想要的。在此博客中，您将研究开放WebUI的一些不错的功能。享受！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;存在一些可以在本地运行的推理引擎，例如Ollama，Lmstudio，Localai，Jan等。其中一些还带有图形用户界面（GUI）。但是，这些与推理引擎在同一机器上本地运行。如果您想在公司内完全离线运行的类似ChatGpt的用户界面，该怎么办？推理引擎可在带有GPU（本地或私有云中）的专用机器上运行，而GUI是可用于用户的Web应用程序。此设置的优点是，您的所有数据都不会离开您的公司，也不会与任何云供应商共享。使用此设置可以确保您的数据的隐私。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Indexed View for Aggregating Metrics】汇总指标的索引视图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/indexed-view-for-aggregating-metrics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Azure SQL is a robust, fully managed database platform designed for high-performance querying, relational data storage, and analytics. For a typical web application with a backend, it is a good choice when we want to consider a managed database that can scale both vertically and horizontally.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An application software generates user metrics on a daily basis, which can be used for reports or analytics. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/loading-data-into-azure-sql-data-warehouse-1&#34;&gt;Azure SQL&lt;/a&gt; is a great choice to consider for storing and querying this data under certain conditions:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Microsoft Azure SQL是一个可靠的，完全管理的数据库平台，旨在高性能查询，关系数据存储和分析。对于具有后端的典型Web应用程序，当我们想考虑一个可以垂直和水平扩展的托管数据库时，这是一个不错的选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;应用程序软件每天生成用户指标，可用于报告或分析。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/loading-data-into-azure-sql-data-warehouse-1”&gt; azure sql &lt;/a&gt;是考虑存储和查询此数据的绝佳选择在某些条件下：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing AI Multi-Agent Systems in Java】在Java设计AI多代理系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/designing-ai-multi-agent-systems-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The year 2025 is the year of AI agents. For the purposes of this article, an AI agent is a system that can leverage AI to achieve a goal by following a series of steps, possibly reasoning on its results and making corrections. In practice, the steps that an agent follows can constitute a graph.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will build a reactive agent (meaning that it reacts to a stimulus, in our case, the input from a user) to help people find their perfect vacation. Our agent will find the best city in the specified country, considering the food, sea, and activity specified by the user.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; 2025年是AI代理年。出于本文的目的，AI代理是一个可以通过遵循一系列步骤来利用AI实现目标的系统，可能会推理其结果并进行更正。实际上，代理遵循的步骤可以构成图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将建立一个反应剂（这意味着它对刺激的反应，在我们的情况下是用户的输入），以帮助人们找到理想的假期。考虑到用户指定的食物，海洋和活动，我们的经纪人将找到特定国家/地区最好的城市。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>