<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Migrating Java Microservices to Go: A Comprehensive Guide】迁移Java微服务要去：综合指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/migrating-java-microservices-to-go-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;With the rising demand for high-performance, scalable, and resource-efficient microservices, many organizations are exploring the transition from Java to Go (Golang). Java, a long-standing enterprise favorite, offers robustness and a vast ecosystem, but Go’s lightweight concurrency model, fast execution speed, and lower memory footprint make it an attractive alternative.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This guide explores why and how to migrate Java microservices to Go effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;随着对高性能，可扩展和资源有效的微服务的需求不断上升，许多组织正在探索从Java到GO（Golang）的过渡。长期存在的企业最喜欢的Java提供了鲁棒性和庞大的生态系统，但是Go的轻巧并发模型，快速执行速度和较低的内存足迹使其成为有吸引力的选择。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;本指南探讨了为什么以及如何有效地迁移Java微服务。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Import Order in React: A Deep Dive Into Best Practices and Tools】React进口订单：深入研究最佳实践和工具</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/import-order-react-best-practices-tools</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Have you ever spent hours debugging a seemingly simple React application, only to realize the culprit was a misplaced import? Incorrect import order can lead to a host of issues, from unexpected behavior to significant performance degradation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll delve into the intricacies of import order in React, exploring best practices and powerful tools to optimize your code. By the end, you&#39;ll be equipped to write cleaner, more efficient, and maintainable React applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否曾经花了几个小时来调试看似简单的React应用程序，只是意识到罪魁祸首是放错了位置的进口？不正确的进口顺序可能导致许多问题，从意外行为到重大绩效降级。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将深入探讨进口订单在React中的复杂性，探索最佳实践和强大的工具以优化您的代码。到最后，您将有能力编写清洁，更高效和可维护的反应应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Deploy Karpenter on AWS Kubernetes With kOps】如何用kops在AWS Kubernetes上部署karpenter</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deploy-karpenter-aws-kubernetes-kops</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;kOps&lt;/strong&gt; is a widely used tool for deploying and managing Kubernetes clusters in multi-cloud or hybrid cloud environments. It provides a unified configuration system (YAML or JSON), which lets you easily set up clusters across AWS, GCP, Azure, and on-premises environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With flexible customization options, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubernetes/kops&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;kOps&lt;/a&gt; lets you adjust everything from control plane and worker node operating systems to network plugins (like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tigera.io/tigera-products/calico/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Calico&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://cilium.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cilium&lt;/a&gt;) and storage solutions, which makes it an excellent fit for complex setups.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; kops &lt;/strong&gt;是一种广泛使用的工具，用于在多云或混合云环境中部署和管理Kubernetes群集。它提供了一个统一的配置系统（YAML或JSON），该系统使您可以轻松地在AWS，GCP，Azure和本地环境中设置簇。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;具有灵活的自定义选项，&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/kubernetes/kops” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; kops &lt;/a&gt;让您从控制平面和工作节点插件中调整所有内容（例如href =“ https://www.tigera.io/tigera-products/calico/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; calico &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ href =”解决方案，使其非常适合复杂的设置。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Use GPU Nodes in Amazon EKS】如何在Amazon EKS中使用GPU节点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-gpu-nodes-in-amazon-eks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Running GPU workloads on Amazon EKS requires configuring GPU-enabled nodes, installing necessary drivers, and ensuring proper scheduling. Follow these steps to set up GPU nodes in your EKS cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;1. Create an Amazon EKS Cluster&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;First, create an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/deploying-a-kubernetes-cluster-with-amazon-eks&#34;&gt;EKS cluster&lt;/a&gt; without worker nodes&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;using &lt;code&gt;eksctl&lt;/code&gt; (for simplicity, we don’t use Terraform/OpenTofu.):&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p数​​据选择可选 -  paragraph =“”&gt;在Amazon EKS上运行GPU工作负载需要配置启用GPU的节点，安装必要的驱动程序并确保适当的安排。请按照以下步骤在EKS群集中设置GPU节点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2数据选择 - 段落=“”&gt; 1。创建一个Amazon EKS群集&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph =“”&gt;首先，创建一个&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/deploying-a-kubernetes-cluster-cluster-with-amazon-eks-eks&gt; eks cluster &lt;/a&gt;没有工人节点&lt;/ Terraform/opentofu。）：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Your Tech Startup: 4 Key Traps and Ways to Tackle Them】建立您的技术创业公司：4个关键陷阱和解决方案的方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/tech-startup-traps-and-solutions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The tech sector is based on human rather than physical assets: not on machinery or warehouses but on talented specialists and innovations. Competition is fierce, and success often hinges on adaptability in an ever-changing environment. Speed takes precedence, where the ability to launch a product swiftly can outweigh even its quality. If you have any experience in software development, all these issues definitely sound like a daily routine.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But what if you are about to launch your own startup? What if your project’s ambitions go all the way to Unicorn heights? In this case, you are going to face additional and (most probably) unfamiliar obstacles. These include workforce challenges, management issues, insufficient investment in innovation, and neglect of technical branding.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;技术领域是基于人类的，而不是物理资产：不是在机械或仓库上，而是基于才华横溢的专家和创新。竞争是激烈的，成功通常取决于不断变化的环境中的适应性。速度需要优先，在这种情况下，迅速推出产品的能力甚至超过了其质量。如果您在软件开发方面有任何经验，那么所有这些问题肯定听起来像是日常工作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;，但是如果您要启动自己的创业公司怎么办？如果您的项目的野心一直到独角兽高度怎么办？在这种情况下，您将面临额外的（很可能）陌生的障碍。其中包括劳动力挑战，管理问题，对创新的投资不足以及对技术品牌的忽视。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Disaster Recovery Plan for DevOps】DevOps的灾难恢复计划</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/disaster-recovery-plan-for-devops</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A well-designed disaster recovery plan is critical to mitigate risks, recover swiftly from failures, and ensure your data and infrastructure integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Are There Any Myths Related to DR in DevOps?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some organizations still mistakenly assume that DevOps tools, like GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket, Azure DevOps, or Jira, come with built-in, all-encompassing disaster recovery. However, we shouldn’t forget about the shared responsibility models, which explicitly clarify that while providers secure their infrastructure and smoothly run their services, users must safeguard their own account data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;精心设计的灾难恢复计划对于减轻风险，迅速从失败中恢复并确保您的数据和基础架构完整性至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;在DevOps中有与DR的神话吗？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一些组织仍然错误地假设DevOps工具，例如GitHub，Gitlab，Bitbucket，Azure DevOps或Jira，都具有内置的，无所不包的灾难恢复。但是，我们不应该忘记共同的责任模型，该模型明确澄清说，尽管提供商确保其基础架构并顺利运行其服务，但用户必须维护自己的帐户数据。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【8 Java GUI Frameworks for Modern Applications】8个用于现代应用的Java GUI框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/8-best-java-gui-frameworks-for-modern-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Java has become one of the world’s most versatile programming languages, chosen for its adaptability, stability, and platform independence. Its extensive ecosystem encompasses virtually every application type, from web development to enterprise solutions, game design, Internet of Things (IoT), and beyond.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With an estimated &lt;a href=&#34;https://stratoflow.com/why-is-java-so-popular/&#34;&gt;51 billion active Java virtual machines&lt;/a&gt; (JVMs) globally, it goes without question that Java powers a substantial portion of modern software infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Java已成为世界上用途最广泛的编程语言之一，该语言以其适应性，稳定性和平台独立性而选择。它的广泛生态系统几乎包含从Web开发到企业解决方案，游戏设计，物联网（IoT）及以后的每种应用程序类型。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用估计&lt;a href =“ https://stratoflow.com/why-is-java-sopopular/”&gt; 51亿个活动的Java虚拟机&lt;/a&gt;（JVMS）在全球范围内，毫无疑问，Java可以实现现代软件基础结构的大量部分。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The LLM Advantage: Smarter Time Series Predictions With Less Effort】LLM优势：更智能的时间序列预测，努力更少</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llm-advantage-smarter-time-series-predictions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered why predicting next month&#39;s sales is so hard? Or why forecasting the weather seems like a coin flip sometimes? Time series data is everywhere, but making sense of it has always been a headache — until now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Large language models (LLMs) are shaking things up in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-time-series-analysis-techniques-models-a&#34;&gt;time series&lt;/a&gt; world. Seriously, it&#39;s like someone finally handed us a decent flashlight after we&#39;ve been stumbling around in the dark for years.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否曾经想过为什么要预测下个月的销售如此艰难？还是为什么预测天气似乎有时会翻转？时间序列数据无处不在，但是要理解它一直是头痛 - 直到现在。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大语言模型（LLM）正在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mastering time-series-series-series-analysis-techniques-models-a”&gt;时间序列&lt;/a&gt;世界。认真地说，这就像有人在黑暗中绊倒了多年后终于递给我们一个不错的手电筒一样。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhanced Monitoring Pipeline With Advanced RAG Optimizations】通过高级抹布优化增强的监视管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhanced-monitoring-pipeline-rag-optimizations</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observability Integration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Observability is the cornerstone of reliability and trust in any production-grade retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) pipeline. As these systems become more complex — handling sensitive data, supporting real-time queries, and interfacing with multiple services — being able to trace and measure each step of the data flow and inference process becomes critical. From retrieving logs in vector databases to generating final responses with large language models, every interaction must be visible and auditable to scale confidently in production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address these needs, our enhanced &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-generative-ai-with-retrieval-augmented&#34;&gt;RAG pipeline&lt;/a&gt; integrates Literal AI for end-to-end tracing of both retrieval and generation steps. Literal AI provides robust observability mechanisms, allowing teams to pinpoint performance bottlenecks, detect anomalies, and seamlessly incorporate human-in-the-loop feedback.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;可观察性集成&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可观察性是对任何生产级检索生成（RAG）管道的可靠性和信任的基石。随着这些系统变得越来越复杂 - 处理敏感数据，支持实时查询以及与多个服务的接口 - 能够追踪和测量数据流和推理过程的每个步骤变得至关重要。从在矢量数据库中检索日志到使用大语言模型生成最终响应，每个互动都必须可见且可审核才能在生产中自信地扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了满足这些需求，我们的增强&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-with-retreval-augmented”&gt; rag Pipeline &lt;/a&gt;集成了文字AI，以进行端到端的检索和发电步骤。字面的AI提供了强大的可观察性机制，使团队能够查明性能瓶颈，检测异常，并无缝地融合了人类的反馈。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Time Data Series: It’s Not What You Said; It’s How You Said It】时间数据系列：这不是您所说的；这就是你说的</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/time-data-series-how-you-said-it</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/time-data-series-the-rest-of-the-story&#34;&gt;last post on PHP Zmanim&lt;/a&gt;, I said the next thing I’d write about was astronomy calculations. I still plan to do that, but something came up recently that caught my attention, so I’m going to talk about that instead. I still plan to get to the astronomy stuff.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Sephardi vs. Ashkenazi&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No, not kitniyot. No, not how to hang your mezuzzah. No, not whether you have to use water challah or if egg challah is ok. I’m talking about the “T” sound in certain words.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/time-data-series-the-rest-of-the-story”&gt; php zmanim上的最后一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;，我说下一个我写的是天文学计算。我仍然打算这样做，但是最近出现了一些引起我注意的事情，所以我将谈论这一点。我仍然打算去天文学的东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Sephardi vs. Ashkenazi &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不，不是Kitniyot。不，不是如何吊死您的Mezuzzah。不，不是您必须使用水鸡蛋面包还是鸡蛋鸡蛋面包还可以。我说的是某些话的“ t”声音。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>