<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Alignment Tools】对齐工具</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/alignment-tools</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Understanding and implementing the right alignment tools in Agile product development can significantly enhance the effectiveness of your team and organization. Fostering better relationships between stakeholders and teams can ensure strategic clarity, improve adaptability, and maintain a user-centric focus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article provides actionable insights on leveraging these tools to build trust, enhance collaboration, navigate risks, and maximize value creation. This will ultimately lead to more successful product outcomes aligned with organizational goals.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在敏捷产品开发中了解并实施正确的调整工具可以显着提高团队和组织的效率。在利益相关者和团队之间培养更好的关系可以确保战略清晰度、提高适应性并保持以用户为中心的焦点。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文提供了有关利用这些工具建立信任、加强协作、规避风险和最大限度地创造价值的可行见解。这最终将带来与组织目标相一致的更成功的产品成果。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Use Guardrails To Prevent Hallucinations in Generative AI Applications】使用护栏防止生成人工智能应用中的幻觉</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/use-guardrails-to-prevent-hallucinations</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/guardrails.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock&lt;/a&gt; enables you to implement safeguards for your generative AI applications based on your use cases and responsible AI policies. You can create multiple guardrails tailored to different use cases and apply them across multiple foundation models (FM), providing a consistent user experience and standardizing safety and privacy controls across generative AI applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Until now, Guardrails supported four policies — denied topics, content filters, sensitive information filters, and word filters. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/guardrails-ctxgrd-filters.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Contextual grounding check policy&lt;/a&gt; (the latest one added at the time of writing) can detect and filter hallucination in model responses that are &lt;em&gt;not grounded&lt;/em&gt; in enterprise data or are &lt;em&gt;irrelevant&lt;/em&gt; to the users’ query.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/guardrails.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; &gt;Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock&lt;/a&gt; 使您能够根据您的用例和负责任的 AI 策略为生成式 AI 应用程序实施保护措施。您可以根据不同的用例创建多个护栏，并将它们应用于多个基础模型 (FM)，从而提供一致的用户体验并标准化生成型 AI 应用程序的安全和隐私控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;到目前为止，Guardrails 支持四种策略 - 拒绝主题、内容过滤器、敏感信息过滤器和单词过滤器。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/guardrails-ctxgrd-filters.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;上下文接地检查策略&lt; /a&gt;（撰写本文时最新添加的）可以检测和过滤模型响应中的幻觉，这些幻觉&lt;em&gt;不基于企业数据&lt;/em&gt;或与用户的&lt;em&gt;无关&lt;/em&gt;查询。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Ultimate 5-Step Guide for Mobile App Testing Automation】移动应用测试自动化终极 5 步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/five-step-guide-for-mobile-app-testing-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The global mobile app market has been growing at more than 11.5% per year and is now worth more than $154.06 billion after the COVID-19 shift toward remote work has increased and time spent online has gone up. With over 10.97 billion mobile connections worldwide, the demand for sophisticated, high-performance B2B and B2C mobile apps is increasing. The main reason for app abandonment is poor user experience. This includes a perplexing UI/UX and an excessive number of bugs. Loading times are slow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Continuous testing for mobile applications is required to ensure that a mobile app functions properly on both iOS and Android. In addition, mobile app testing can be difficult, involving numerous platforms, operating systems, and network connections.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着 COVID-19 疫情导致远程工作转向以及上网时间增加，全球移动应用市场每年以超过 11.5% 的速度增长，目前价值超过 1,540.6 亿美元。全球移动连接数超过 109.7 亿，对复杂、高性能 B2B 和 B2C 移动应用程序的需求不断增长。应用程序被放弃的主要原因是用户体验不佳。这包括令人困惑的 UI/UX 和过多的错误。加载时间很慢。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需要对移动应用程序进行持续测试，以确保移动应用程序在 iOS 和 Android 上都能正常运行。此外，移动应用测试可能很困难，涉及众多平台、操作系统和网络连接。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Empowering Developers in Code Security】增强开发人员的代码安全能力</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/empowering-developers-in-code-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Effective security requires a shared responsibility model. Developers are already overburdened with their primary tasks of writing code and delivering features, and we think it is not realistic to expect them to know everything about security, be responsible for triaging and handling incidents on their own, or consider all the implications of security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adding security responsibilities without proper support and integration can lead to frustration, resistance, and, ultimately, a less secure environment. Yet, their involvement in fixing code security issues is crucial and cannot be replaced by security work.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;有效的安全性需要共同的责任模型。开发人员编写代码和交付功能的主要任务已经负担过重，我们认为期望他们了解有关安全的所有知识、负责自行分类和处理事件或考虑安全的所有影响是不现实的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在没有适当支持和集成的情况下增加安全责任可能会导致挫败感、阻力，并最终导致环境安全性降低。然而，他们对修复代码安全问题的参与至关重要，是安全工作无法替代的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Practical Guide To Implementing Adaptive Software Development】实施自适应软件开发的实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-practical-guide-to-implementing-software</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As a tech leader in the custom software development industry for over a decade, I’ve seen methodologies evolve and change. One that has particularly caught my attention in recent years is Adaptive Software Development (ASD). This approach is designed to help teams thrive in uncertain and rapidly changing environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this guide, I’ll walk you through the principles, benefits, and practical steps for implementing ASD in your projects.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为定制软件开发行业十多年来的技术领导者，我见证了方法论的发展和变化。近年来特别引起我注意的是自适应软件开发（ASD）。这种方法旨在帮助团队在不确定和快速变化的环境中蓬勃发展。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本指南中，我将引导您了解在项目中实施 ASD 的原则、好处和实际步骤。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advanced Deployment Strategies】高级部署策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-deployment-strategies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In today&#39;s software development and deployment, maintaining agility, stability, and security is crucial. &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/architecture/cloud-native/centralized-configuration&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Centralized configuration management&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://launchdarkly.com/blog/what-are-feature-flags/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;feature flags&lt;/a&gt; are tools that help in achieving these goals. Integrating these into an organization’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devsecops-the-broken-or-blurred-lines-of-defense&#34;&gt;DevSecOps&lt;/a&gt; process provides the flexibility needed to respond to changes quickly and effectively.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Feature Flag Driven Development (FFDD)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Feature Flag Driven Development (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/feature-flag-driven-development&#34;&gt;FFDD&lt;/a&gt;) is a software development approach that uses feature flags or toggles. These flags help to control the new feature deployments. The main goal of FFDD is to separate the development and release of new features. This provides flexibility to development teams and allows them to roll out features gradually and choose specific user groups to test them.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在当今的软件开发和部署中，保持敏捷性、稳定性和安全性至关重要。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/dotnet/architecture/cloud-native/centralized-configuration&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;集中配置管理&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://launchdarkly.com/blog/what-are-feature-flags/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;功能标志&lt;/a&gt;是帮助实现这些目标的工具目标。将这些集成到组织的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devsecops-the-broken-or-blurred-lines-of-defense&#34;&gt;DevSecOps&lt;/a&gt; 流程中，可以提供响应所需的灵活性改变迅速而有效。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;功能标记驱动开发 (FFDD)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;功能标记驱动开发 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/feature-flag-driven-development&#34;&gt;FFDD&lt;/a&gt;) 是一个使用功能标志或切换的软件开发方法。这些标志有助于控制新功能的部署。 FFDD 的主要目标是将新功能的开发和发布分开。这为开发团队提供了灵活性，允许他们逐步推出功能并选择特定的用户组来测试它们。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Hands-On Guide to OpenTelemetry: Using Automatic Instrumentation】OpenTelemetry 实践指南：使用自动仪器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-opentelemetry-automatic-instrumentation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiB0g9TENTSo1x2JqkGeWaKklzNjNuCmOC1whPrX1fhNqPi2Ia87bEBSYZFy2PDzxrstIcvKlzBO4UEEnfq320n80kn3wvmkrdfgWzNtW0kxEYL-MskPtVUqP5LeZxSW__G3mwpdmTqxEgtX8v_gKFD2VWk1smGnKktmQ4x5ZiRlLz-5uk_3cGK3W1McfA/s1710/otel-collector.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Are you ready to start your journey on the road to collecting telemetry data from your applications? Great observability begins with great instrumentation!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiB0g9TENTSo1x2JqkGeWaKklzNjNuCmOC1whPrX1fhNqPi2Ia87bEBSYZFy2PDzxrstIcvKlzBO4UEEnfq320n80kn3wvmkrdfgWzNtW0kxEYL-MskPtVUqP5LeZxSW__G3mwpdmTqxEgtX8v_gKFD2VWk1smGnKktmQ4x5ZiRlLz-5uk_3cGK3W1McfA/s1710/otel-collector.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;30.5 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1721053356517&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;07/15/2024 02:22 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17796576-1721053356905.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;30536&#34; data-name=&#34;1721053356905.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17796576&#34; style=&#34;width: 575px;&#34; alt=&#34;OTel Collector&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17796576-1721053356905.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; In this series, you&#39;ll explore how to adopt &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; and how to instrument an application to collect tracing telemetry. You&#39;ll learn how to leverage out-of-the-box automatic instrumentation tools and understand when it&#39;s necessary to explore more advanced manual instrumentation for your applications. By the end of this series, you&#39;ll have an understanding of how telemetry travels from your applications to the OpenTelemetry Collector, and be ready to bring OpenTelemetry to your future projects. Everything discussed here is supported by &lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a hands-on, self-paced workshop&lt;/a&gt; authored &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;by Paige Cruze&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiB0g9TENTSo1x2JqkGeWaKklzNjNuCmOC1whPrX1fhNqPi2Ia87bEBSYZFy2PDzxrstIcvKlzBO4UEEnfq320n80kn3wvmkrdfgWz NtW0kxEYL-MskPtVUqP5LeZxSW__G3mwpdmTqxEgtX8v_gKFD2VWk1smGnKktmQ4x5ZiRlLz-5uk_3cGK3W1McfA/s1710/otel-collector.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;您准备好开始您的旅程了吗正在从您的应用程序收集遥测数据吗？出色的可观测性始于出色的仪器！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiB0g9TENTSo1x2JqkGeWaKklzNjNuCmOC1whPrX1fhNqPi2Ia87bEBSYZFy2PDzxrstIcvKlzBO4UEEnfq320n80kn3wvmkrdfgWz NtW0kxEYL-MskPtVUqP5LeZxSW__G3mwpdmTqxEgtX8v_gKFD2VWk1smGnKktmQ4x5ZiRlLz-5uk_3cGK3W1McfA/s1710/otel-collector.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib延迟加载” data-image =“ true” data-new =“ false” data-sizeformatted =“ 30.5 kB” data-mimetype =“ image / png” data-creationdate =“ 1721053356517” data-creationdateformatted =“ 07/15/2024 02:22 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17796576-1721053356905.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;30536 “数据名称=“1721053356905.png”数据id=“17796576”样式=“宽度：575px;” alt=&#34;OTel Collector&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17796576-1721053356905.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 在本系列中，您将探索如何采用&lt;a href =&#34;https://opentelemetry.io&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; 以及如何检测应用程序以收集跟踪遥测数据。您将学习如何利用开箱即用的自动仪表工具，并了解何时需要为您的应用探索更高级的手动仪表。在本系列结束时，您将了解遥测如何从应用程序传输到 OpenTelemetry Collector，并准备好将 OpenTelemetry 引入您未来的项目。这里讨论的所有内容均由&lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;动手、自定进度的研讨会支持&lt; /a&gt; 作者：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;作者：Paige Cruze&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Task-Specific Large Language Models Using Distillation】使用蒸馏的特定于任务的大型语言模型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/task-specific-large-language-models</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Large Language Models&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Large language models (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-llm-technology&#34;&gt;LLMs&lt;/a&gt;) represent a significant advancement in Artificial Intelligence, particularly in the field of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/4-business-applications-for-natural-language-proce&#34;&gt;Natural Language Processing&lt;/a&gt;. These models are designed to understand, generate, and interact with natural language in a way that closely mimics human communication. Trained on vast datasets comprising text from diverse sources, LLMs learn to recognize patterns, contexts, and nuances within language, enabling them to perform tasks such as translation, summarization, question-answering, and creative writing. Their ability to generate coherent and contextually relevant text makes them valuable tools in various applications, including customer service, content creation, and educational assistance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;General-purpose LLMs are powerful and impressive but come with issues like non-determinism in outputs and formatting, and high resource and financial costs. Smaller, task-specific LLMs distilled from larger, general-purpose LLMs can be an attractive option for many tasks.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;大型语言模型&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-llm-technology&#34;&gt;LLM&lt;/a&gt;) 代表了人工智能领域的重大进步，特别是在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/4-business-applications-for-natural-language-proce&#34;&gt;自然语言处理&lt;/a&gt;领域。这些模型旨在以密切模仿人类交流的方式理解、生成自然语言并与之交互。法学硕士接受来自不同来源的文本的庞大数据集的训练，学会识别语言中的模式、上下文和细微差别，使他们能够执行翻译、摘要、问答和创意写作等任务。它们生成连贯且上下文相关文本的能力使它们成为各种应用中的宝贵工具，包括客户服务、内容创建和教育帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;通用法学硕士非常强大且令人印象深刻，但也存在诸如输出和格式的不确定性以及高昂的资源和财务成本等问题。从大型通用法学硕士中提炼出来的小型、特定任务的法学硕士对于许多任务来说可能是一个有吸引力的选择。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Your Own IoT Project: A Step-By-Step Guide】构建您自己的物联网项目：分步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-your-own-iot-project-a-step-by-step-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/iot-security-strategies-challenges-and-essential-t&#34;&gt;IoT&lt;/a&gt;) is revolutionizing the way we interact with technology, enabling everyday objects to connect, collect data, and communicate with each other. Whether you’re a tech enthusiast or a beginner, diving into your own IoT project can be both exciting and rewarding.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide will walk you through the essential steps to build your first IoT project, ensuring you have a solid foundation to explore this fascinating field.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;物联网 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/iot-security-strategies-challenges-and-essential-t&#34;&gt;IoT&lt;/a&gt;) 正在彻底改变我们的互动方式通过技术，使日常物体能够连接、收集数据并相互通信。无论您是技术爱好者还是初学者，深入研究自己的物联网项目都既令人兴奋又有益。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南将引导您完成构建第一个物联网项目的基本步骤，确保您拥有探索这个迷人领域的坚实基础。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Foundation of AI and Analytics Success: Why Architecture Matters】人工智能和分析成功的基础：为什么架构很重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-foundation-of-ai-and-analytics-success</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the rapidly evolving landscape of AI and analytics, the importance of a robust architecture cannot be overstated. As businesses increasingly rely on data-driven insights and AI-powered solutions, the underlying infrastructure that supports these technologies becomes a critical factor in their success. Recently, a panel of experts gathered to discuss architecture&#39;s pivotal role in AI and analytics, sharing insights on business drivers, common pitfalls, and innovative solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Business Drivers Shaping AI and Analytics Architectures&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Several essential business requirements are driving the need for advanced AI and analytics architectures:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在快速发展的人工智能和分析领域，强大的架构的重要性怎么强调都不为过。随着企业越来越依赖数据驱动的洞察和人工智能驱动的解决方案，支持这些技术的底层基础设施成为其成功的关键因素。最近，专家小组聚集在一起讨论架构在人工智能和分析中的关键作用，分享对业务驱动因素、常见陷阱和创新解决方案的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;塑造人工智能和分析架构的业务驱动因素&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;几个基本业务需求正在推动对高级人工智能和分析架构的需求：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>