<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Snowflake Cortex for GenAI】使用雪花皮质进行 GenAI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-cortex-for-genai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Snowflake Cortex enables seamless integration of Generative AI&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;(GenAI) capabilities within the Snowflake Data Cloud. It allows organizations to use pre-trained large language models (LLMs) and create applications for tasks like content generation, text summarization, sentiment analysis, and conversational AI — all without managing external ML infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prerequisites for Snowflake Cortex Setup&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Snowflake Environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enterprise Edition or higher is required as a baseline for using advanced features like External Functions and Snowpark.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Snowflake Cortex 支持在 Snowflake 数据云中无缝集成生成式 AI&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;(GenAI) 功能。它允许组织使用预先训练的大型语言模型 (LLM) 并为内容生成、文本摘要、情感分析和对话式 AI 等任务创建应用程序 - 所有这些都无需管理外部 ML 基础设施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;雪花皮质设置的先决条件&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;雪花环境&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需要企业版或更高版本作为使用外部功能和 Snowpark 等高级功能的基准。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Copy SQL Execution Plan from One Database to Another in Oracle 19c】在 Oracle 19c 中将 SQL 执行计划从一个数据库复制到另一个数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/copy-sql-plans-oracle</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Performance tuning is a critical responsibility for Oracle database administrators, ensuring that SQL queries run efficiently across various environments. This guide details how to copy an SQL execution plan from one Oracle 19c database to another, a practical solution when a query performs inconsistently across environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, if a query runs efficiently in a staging environment but poorly in production, transferring the execution plan can resolve performance issues without modifying the SQL code. Below are the steps to copying SQL execution plans.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;性能调优是 Oracle 数据库管理员的一项重要职责，确保 SQL 查询在各种环境中高效运行。本指南详细介绍了如何将 SQL 执行计划从一个 Oracle 19c 数据库复制到另一个数据库，这是当查询在不同环境中执行不一致时的实用解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，如果查询在临时环境中运行高效，但在生产环境中运行不佳，则传输执行计划可以解决性能问题，而无需修改 SQL 代码。以下是复制 SQL 执行计划的步骤。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Process Mining Key Elements】流程挖掘关键要素</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/process-mining-key-elements</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Process mining is a technique that helps organizations understand, analyze, and improve their processes. This article tries to break it down into simple terms. It explains how process mining can benefit users looking to extract process-level metrics from their applications or tools with minimal data mining background.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Questions About Process Mining&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following questions help get a high-level idea of process mining and whether it’s a good fit for your analytics use case:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;流程挖掘是一种帮助组织理解、分析和改进其流程的技术。本文试图将其分解为简单的术语。它解释了流程挖掘如何使那些希望从具有最少数据挖掘背景的应用程序或工具中提取流程级指标的用户受益。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;有关流程挖掘的关键问题&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下问题有助于深入了解流程挖掘以及它是否适合您的分析用例：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Security in the Age of AI: Challenges and Best Practices】人工智能时代的安全：挑战和最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-security-challenges-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence (AI) has transformed industries by driving innovation and efficiency across sectors. However, its rapid adoption has also exposed vulnerabilities that bad actors can exploit, making security a paramount concern. This article talks about the challenges and strategies to ensure robust security in AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Key Security Challenges in AI&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Data Breaches and Privacy Violations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI systems rely heavily on vast amounts of data, often including sensitive personal information. A breach in the data pipeline can result in significant privacy violations and financial losses.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能 (AI) 通过推动各行业的创新和效率，改变了各行各业。然而，它的快速采用也暴露了不良行为者可以利用的漏洞，使安全性成为首要问题。本文讨论了确保人工智能系统稳健安全的挑战和策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;人工智能的主要安全挑战&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;1。 &lt;strong&gt;数据泄露和侵犯隐私&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能系统严重依赖大量数据，通常包括敏感的个人信息。数据管道的泄露可能会导致严重的隐私侵犯和财务损失。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 10:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Custom SCD2 Implementation Using PySpark】使用 PySpark 的自定义 SCD2 实现</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/custom-scd2-using-pyspark</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A Slowly Changing Dimension (SCD) is a dimension that stores and manages both current and historical data over time in a data warehouse. It is considered and implemented as one of the most critical ETL tasks in tracking the history of dimension records.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-slowly-changing-dimensions-in-data-wareh&#34;&gt;SCD2&lt;/a&gt; is a dimension that stores and manages current and historical data over time in a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-warehouses-the-undying-titans-of-information&#34;&gt;data warehouse&lt;/a&gt;. The purpose of an SCD2 is to preserve the history of changes. If a customer changes their address, for example, or any other attribute, an SCD2 allows analysts to link facts back to the customer and their attributes in the state they were at the time of the fact event.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;缓慢变化维度 (SCD) 是在数据仓库中随着时间的推移存储和管理当前数据和历史数据的维度。它被视为跟踪维度记录历史中最关键的 ETL 任务之一并实施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-slowly-having-dimensions-in-data-wareh&#34;&gt;SCD2&lt;/a&gt; 是一个维度，在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-warehouses-the-undying-titans-of-information&#34;&gt;数据仓库&lt;/a&gt;中存储和管理当前和历史数据。 SCD2 的目的是保存更改的历史记录。例如，如果客户更改了他们的地址或任何其他属性，SCD2 允许分析师将事实链接回客户及其属性（处于事实事件发生时的状态）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enterprise RAG in Amazon Bedrock: Introduction to KnowledgeBases】Amazon Bedrock 中的企业 RAG：知识库简介</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rag-in-amazon-bedrock-intro-to-knowledgebases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Amazon Bedrock&#39;s KnowledgeBases is truly a serverless way to build a RAG pipeline rapidly, which allows the developer to connect almost all types of enterprise data sources including Jira or Confluence pages. This capability simplifies the process for developers looking to integrate document storage, chunking, retrieval, and analysis into their generative AI applications without spending much time writing code for document ingestion or deciding the chunking strategies, etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;For instance, if a developer has a large set of customer support documents stored in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/confused-by-aws-storage-options-s3-ebs-amp-efs-explained&#34;&gt;Amazon S3&lt;/a&gt;, they can designate this storage location as the source for Bedrock. From there, Bedrock automatically manages the entire ingestion and retrieval workflow: it fetches documents from S3, splits them into manageable chunks, creates &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-guide-to-vector-embeddings-for-product-and-softw&#34;&gt;vector embeddings&lt;/a&gt;, and stores these in a chosen vector database. This architecture orchestrates the efficient retrieval of relevant information when a user query is submitted and the whole process is serverless.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Amazon Bedrock 的知识库确实是一种快速构建 RAG 管道的无服务器方式，它允许开发人员连接几乎所有类型的企业数据源，包括 Jira 或 Confluence 页面。对于希望将文档存储、分块、检索和分析集成到生成式 AI 应用程序中的开发人员来说，此功能简化了流程，而无需花费大量时间编写文档摄取代码或决定分块策略等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;例如，如果开发人员在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/confused-by-aws-storage-options-s3 中存储了大量客户支持文档-ebs-amp-efs-explained&#34;&gt;Amazon S3&lt;/a&gt;，他们可以指定此存储位置作为 Bedrock 的源。从那里，Bedrock 自动管理整个摄取和检索工作流程：它从 S3 获取文档，将它们分割成可管理的块，创建 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-guide-to-vector-embeddings -for-product-and-softw&#34;&gt;矢量嵌入&lt;/a&gt;，并将其存储在选定的矢量数据库中。该架构在提交用户查询时协调相关信息的高效检索，并且整个过程是无服务器的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Spreadsheet Application in JavaScript: A Step-by-Step Guide】使用 JavaScript 构建电子表格应用程序：分步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spreadsheet-application-javascript-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Spreadsheets have become an integral part of modern-day computing. They allow users to organize, manipulate, and analyze data in a tabular format. Applications like Google Sheets have set the standard for powerful, interactive spreadsheets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, we will walk you through the process of building a spreadsheet application using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-javascript-in-front-end-and-back-end-d&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt;. We&#39;ll focus on key programming concepts, explore JavaScript features, and include detailed code snippets with explanations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;电子表格已成为现代计算不可或缺的一部分。它们允许用户以表格格式组织、操作和分析数据。 Google 表格等应用程序为功能强大的交互式电子表格设定了标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇博文中，我们将引导您完成使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-javascript-in-front-end- 构建电子表格应用程序的过程和-back-end-d&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt;。我们将重点关注关键编程概念，探索 JavaScript 功能，并提供详细的代码片段和解释。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Buildpacks: An Open-Source Alternative to Chainguard】Buildpacks：Chainguard 的开源替代品</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/buildpacks-open-source-alternative-to-chainguard</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The industry&#39;s increasing focus on secure container images is undeniable. Companies like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.chainguard.dev/&#34;&gt;Chainguard&lt;/a&gt; — specializing in delivering container images free of CVEs — have demonstrated the demand by recently &lt;a href=&#34;https://siliconangle.com/2024/07/25/chainguard-nabs-140m-secure-enterprise-applications-open-source-components/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;raising&lt;/a&gt; an impressive $140 million at a $1.1 billion valuation. In the open-source ecosystem, &lt;a href=&#34;https://buildpacks.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Buildpacks&lt;/a&gt;, an &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/buildpacks/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;incubating CNCF project&lt;/a&gt;, and their vibrant communities deliver a comparable value proposition by automating the creation of optimized and secure container images.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, I&#39;ll explore Buildpack&#39;s core concepts, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-you-should-use-buildpacks-over-docker&#34;&gt;comparing them with Docker&lt;/a&gt; to illustrate their functionality and highlight how they provide a community-driven alternative to the value Chainguard brings to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/container-security-guide&#34;&gt;container security&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;不可否认的是，业界对安全容器映像的日益关注。像 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.chainguard.dev/&#34;&gt;Chainguard&lt;/a&gt; 这样的公司（专门提供不含 CVE 的容器镜像）最近已经证明了这一需求 &lt;a href=&#34;https://siliconangle .com/2024/07/25/chainguard-nabs-140m-secure-enterprise-applications-open-source-components/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;筹集&lt;/a&gt;令人印象深刻1.4 亿美元，估值 11 亿美元。在开源生态系统中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://buildpacks.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Buildpacks&lt;/a&gt;，一个&lt;a href=&#34;https:// /www.cncf.io/projects/buildpacks/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;孵化 CNCF 项目&lt;/a&gt;，其充满活力的社区通过自动创建优化且安全的容器来提供可比较的价值主张图片。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我将探讨 Buildpack 的核心概念，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-you-should-use-buildpacks-over-docker&#34;&gt;将它们与 Docker 进行比较，以说明它们的功能，并强调它们如何提供社区驱动的替代方案来替代 Chainguard 为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/container-security-guide&#34;&gt; 带来的价值容器安全&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering SSR and CSR in Next.js: Building High-Performance Data Visualizations】掌握 Next.js 中的 SSR 和 CSR：构建高性能数据可视化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-ssr-and-csr-in-nextjs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern web and mobile applications require showing information from large and changing datasets in an actionable manner to end users. As an example, for a trading application, it is of paramount importance to show changing stock prices for several stocks in a single instance with high performance and accuracy. Slow load times and sluggishness can cause users to become frustrated or even incur financial losses as in the case of the trading application example — which breaks user trust. Therefore, performance in the web application becomes a &#34;must have&#34; and not just a &#34;nice to have.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-server-side-rendering-and-why-do-you-need&#34;&gt;Next.js&lt;/a&gt; is tailormade for such scenarios. It is built on top of React — incorporating all performance gains &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-web-standards-shadow-dom-and-custom&#34;&gt;techniques such as shadow DOM&lt;/a&gt; and one-way data from it. Moreover, it supports advanced features such as Server-Side Rendering (SSR) and static site generation (SSG), which reduce page load times significantly compared to traditional rendering techniques. Moreover, Next.js is a full-stack application development framework and has integrated routing, API endpoints, and support for fetching data from other servers.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代网络和移动应用程序需要以可操作的方式向最终用户显示来自大型且不断变化的数据集的信息。例如，对于交易应用程序来说，在单个实例中以高性能和准确性显示多只股票的股票价格变化至关重要。缓慢的加载时间和迟缓可能会导致用户感到沮丧，甚至造成经济损失，就像交易应用程序示例一样，这会破坏用户的信任。因此，Web 应用程序的性能成为“必须具备”，而不仅仅是“最好具备”。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-server-side-rendering-and-why-do-you-need&#34;&gt;Next.js&lt;/a&gt; 是为此类量身定制的场景。它构建在 React 之上 - 融合了所有性能提升&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-web-standards-shadow-dom-and-custom&#34;&gt;技术，例如影子 DOM&lt;/a &gt; 以及来自它的单向数据。此外，它还支持服务器端渲染（SSR）和静态站点生成（SSG）等高级功能，与传统渲染技术相比，可显着减少页面加载时间。此外，Next.js 是一个全栈应用程序开发框架，集成了路由、API 端点，并支持从其他服务器获取数据。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OpenTelemetry vs Dynatrace: Key Differences Explained】OpenTelemetry 与 Dynatrace：主要差异解释</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/opentelemetry-vs-dynatrace</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s fast-paced software world, keeping track of how applications are performing is very important. Two major tools that help with this are OpenTelemetry and Dynatrace. But how do you know which one is best for you? In this article, we&#39;ll break down the key differences, strengths, and ideal situations for using each. Whether you&#39;re a developer, DevOps engineer, or IT manager, this will help you make a smart choice for your monitoring needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Are OpenTelemetry and Dynatrace?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-opentelemetry-intro-to-observability&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; is a free, open-source framework that helps collect and send out data on how your applications are running. It combines two earlier projects, OpenCensus and OpenTracing, and gives you a unified, vendor-neutral way to monitor systems. Think of OpenTelemetry as giving each delivery truck in a fleet a GPS tracker. You decide what data to collect — such as speed, routes, or delivery times — and you can use this data with any tracking system. It’s highly flexible and free, but if something goes wrong, like a delay or detour, you’ll need to look through the data and figure out the solution yourself.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今快节奏的软件世界中，跟踪应用程序的执行情况非常重要。 OpenTelemetry 和 Dynatrace 是有助于实现这一目标的两个主要工具。但你怎么知道哪一个最适合你呢？在本文中，我们将详细分析它们的主要区别、优点以及使用它们的理想情况。无论您是开发人员、DevOps 工程师还是 IT 经理，这都将帮助您针对监控需求做出明智的选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是 OpenTelemetry 和 Dynatrace？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-opentelemetry-intro-to-observability&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt;是一个免费的开源框架，可帮助收集和发送有关应用程序运行情况的数据。它结合了两个早期项目 OpenCensus 和 OpenTracing，为您提供了一种统一的、供应商中立的方式来监控系统。将 OpenTelemetry 视为为车队中的每辆送货卡车配备 GPS 跟踪器。您可以决定收集哪些数据（例如速度、路线或交货时间），并且可以将这些数据用于任何跟踪系统。它非常灵活且免费，但如果出现问题，例如延误或绕行，您需要查看数据并自行找出解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>