<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing and Testing Cryptographic Primitives With Go】使用GO实施和测试加密原语</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-testing-cryptographic-primitives-go</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Implementing cryptographic primitives securely is crucial for maintaining the integrity, confidentiality, and authenticity of data in Go applications. This guide will walk you through the process of implementing and testing various cryptographic primitives using Go’s standard library and best practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding Cryptographic Primitives&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cryptographic primitives are the building blocks of cryptographic protocols and systems. They include:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;牢固地实现加密原语对于维持GO应用程序中数据的完整性，机密性和真实性至关重要。本指南将带您完成使用GO标准库和最佳实践实施和测试各种加密原始的过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解加密原始图&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;加密原始图是加密协议和系统的基础。它们包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Soft Skills Are as Important as Hard Skills for Developers】软技能和开发人员的硬技能一样重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/soft-skills-important-as-hard-skills-for-developers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;At the beginning of my career as a backend developer, I focused almost exclusively on hard skills. I believed that becoming a technically strong specialist was the key to success, and once I mastered that, job security would be guaranteed. After all, employers care about your ability to solve real problems, not how well you can articulate your thoughts, right? But over time, as my experience grew, I came to realize that technical skills alone aren&#39;t enough if you want to progress further in your career.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Without soft skills, reaching a high level in your profession becomes a challenge. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/software-developers-need-these-soft-skills&#34;&gt;Soft skills&lt;/a&gt; open doors to exciting projects, enable you to take on responsibility for important decisions, and ultimately help you take top technical roles in reputable companies. Even brilliant code means little if you can&#39;t explain its value to your team, align changes with your colleagues, or understand what the business truly needs. Let&#39;s explore why soft skills are crucial for developers and how they can help you advance in your profession.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在我作为后端开发人员职业生涯的开始时，我几乎专注于硬技能。我认为成为一名技术上有力的专家是成功的关键，一旦我掌握了这一点，就可以保证工作安全。毕竟，雇主关心您解决真正问题的能力，而不是您能表达自己的想法，对吗？但是随着时间的流逝，随着我的经验的增长，我开始意识到，如果您想在职业生涯中进步，那么仅仅是技术技能就不够。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;没有软技能，在您的职业中达到高水平就成为一个挑战。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/software-developers-need-these-soft-skills”&gt;软技能最终帮助您在知名公司中扮演最佳技术角色。即使您无法向您的团队解释其价值，与同事的变化或了解业务真正需要的内容，即使您也没有意义。让我们探讨为什么软技能对开发人员以及他们如何帮助您的职业发展至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Stop Shipping Waste: Fix Your Product Backlog】停止运输废物：修复您的产品积压</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/stop-shipping-waste-fix-your-product-backlog</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Stop Shipping Waste&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When product teams fail to establish stakeholder alignment and implement rigorous Product Backlog management, they get caught in an endless cycle of competing priorities, reactive delivery, and shipping waste.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The result? Wasted resources, frustrated teams, and missed business opportunities. Success in 2025 requires turning your Product Backlog from a chaotic wish list into a strategic tool that connects vision to value delivery. Learn how to do so.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; TL; DR：停止运输废物&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当产品团队未能建立利益相关者对齐并实施严格的产品积压管理时，他们会被无休止的竞争优先级，反应性交付和运输浪费的循环。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结果？浪费资源，沮丧的团队并错过了商机。 2025年的成功要求将您的产品积压从混乱的愿望清单转变为将视觉连接到价值交付的战略工具。学习如何做。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implement a Geographic Distance Calculator Using TypeScript】使用打字稿实现地理距离计算器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/geographic-distance-calculator-using-typescript</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When developing educational games, providing accurate and meaningful feedback is crucial for user engagement. In this article, I&#39;ll share how we implemented a geographic calculation system for Flagle Explorer, a flag-guessing game that helps users learn world geography through interactive feedback.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a name=&#34;the-technical-challenge&#34; href=&#34;https://dev.to/new#the-technical-challenge&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The Technical Challenge&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our main requirements were:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;开发教育游戏时，提供准确而有意义的反馈对于用户参与至关重要。在本文中，我将分享我们如何为Flagle Explorer实施一个地理计算系统，这是一款旗帜猜测游戏，可帮助用户通过交互式反馈来学习世界地理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;a name =“ the-technical-challenge” href =“ https://dev.to/new#the-technical-challenge”&gt; &lt;/a&gt;技术挑战&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的主要要求是：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Vector Storage, Indexing, and Search With MariaDB】使用Mariadb的矢量存储，索引和搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vector-storage-indexing-and-search-with-mariadb</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When you develop generative AI applications, you typically introduce three additional components to your infrastructure: an embedder, an LLM, and a vector database.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, if you are using MariaDB, you don&#39;t need to introduce an additional database along with its own SQL dialect — or even worse — its own proprietary API. Since MariaDB version 11.7 (and &lt;a href=&#34;https://mariadb.com/resources/blog/introducing-vector-search-with-the-latest-version-of-mariadb-enterprise-platform/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MariaDB Enterprise Server 11.4&lt;/a&gt;) you can simply store your embeddings (or vectors) in any column of any table—no need to make your applications database polyglots.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;开发生成AI应用程序时，通常会将三个其他组件引入基础架构：嵌入式，LLM和矢量数据库。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，如果您使用的是Mariadb，则无需引入其他数据库以及其自己的SQL方言（甚至更糟）其自己的专有API。由于Mariadb版本11.7（and &lt;a href =“ https://mariadb.com/resources/blog/introducing-vector-vector-search-with-with-the-latest-the-latest-version-of-mariadb-enterprise-platform/ noreferrer“ target =” _ black“&gt; mariadb企业服务器11.4 &lt;/a&gt;）您只需将您的embeddings（或向量）存储在任何表的任何列中 - 无需使您的应用程序数据库Polyglots。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implement RAG With PGVector, LangChain4j, and Ollama】使用PGVECTOR，Langchain4J和Ollama实施抹布</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implement-rag-with-pgvector-langchain4j-ollama</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this blog, you will learn how to implement retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) using PGVector, LangChain4j, and Ollama. This implementation allows you to ask questions about your documents using natural language. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href=&#34;https://mydeveloperplanet.com/2024/03/06/implement-rag-using-weaviate-langchain4j-and-localai/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;previous blog&lt;/a&gt;, RAG was implemented using Weaviate, LangChain4j, and LocalAI. Now, one year later, it is interesting to find out how this has evolved. E.g.:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在此博客中，您将学习如何使用PGVECTOR，LANGCHAIN4J和OLLAMA实施检索型生成（RAG）。此实现使您可以使用自然语言询问有关文档的问题。享受！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a a &lt;a href =“ https://mydeveloperplanet.com/2024/03/06/implement-rag-usish-weaviate-langchain4j-and4j-and-localai/” rel =“ noreferrer noopener” &gt;上一个博客&lt;/a&gt;，使用Weaviate，Langchain4j和Localai实施了RAG。现在，一年后，发现这是如何发展的有趣的。例如：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Inference Time Compute】了解推理时间计算</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-inference-time-compute</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In the field of machine learning and artificial intelligence, inference is the phase where a trained model is applied to real world data to generate predictions or decisions. After a model undergoes training, which can be computationally intensive and time consuming, the inference process allows the model to make predictions with the goal of providing actionable results.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Inference Time Compute&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Inference time compute refers to the amount of computational power required to make such predictions using a trained model. While training a model involves processing large datasets to learn patterns and relationships, inference is the process where the model is used to make predictions on new, unseen data. This phase is critical in real world applications such as image recognition, natural language processing, autonomous vehicles, and more.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在机器学习和人工智能领域，推断是将训练有素的模型应用于现实世界数据以生成预测或决策的阶段。在模型接受培训之后，可以在计算上进行密集且耗时，推理过程允许模型进行预测，以提供可行的结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;推理时间计算&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;推理时间计算是指使用训练有素的模型进行此类预测所需的计算能力量。训练模型涉及处理大型数据集以学习模式和关系，但推断是该模型用于对新的，看不见的数据进行预测的过程。在现实世界中，此阶段至关重要，例如图像识别，自然语言处理，自动驾驶汽车等。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Spring AI to Generate Images With OpenAI&#39;s DALL-E 3】使用Spring AI使用Openai的Dall-E生成图像3</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spring-ai-generate-images-openai-dalle</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Hi, community!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This is my first article in a series of introductions to Spring AI. Today, we will see how we can easily generate pictures using text prompts. To achieve this, we will leverage the OpenAI API and the DALL-E 3 model.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;嗨，社区！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这是我在Spring AI的一系列介绍中的第一篇文章。今天，我们将看到如何使用文本提示轻松地生成图片。为了实现这一目标，我们将利用OpenAI API和DALL-E 3模型。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Apache Flink and Apache Paimon Influence Data Streaming】Apache Flink和Apache Paimon如何影响数据流</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/apache-flink-apache-paimon-transform-data-streaming</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apache Paimon is made to function well with constantly flowing data, which is typical of contemporary systems like financial markets, e-commerce sites, and Internet of Things devices. It is a data storage system made to effectively manage massive volumes of data, particularly for systems that deal to analyze data continuously such as streaming data or with changes over time like database updates or deletions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To put it briefly, Apache Paimon functions similarly to a sophisticated librarian for our data. Whether we are operating a large online business or a little website, it keeps everything organized, updates it as necessary, and ensures that it is always available for use. An essential component of Apache Paimon&#39;s ecosystem, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/apache-flink-101-a-guide-for-developers?fromrel=true&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apache Flink&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is a real-time stream processing framework that significantly expands its capabilities. Let&#39;s investigate how well Apache Paimon and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Apache Flink&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; work with each other so effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt; Apache Paimon可以通过不断流动的数据来很好地发挥作用，这是当代系统，例如金融市场，电子商务网站和物联网设备的典型代表。它是一个数据存储系统，旨在有效地管理大量数据，特别是对于处理数据连续分析数据的系统，例如流媒体数据或随着时间的变化（例如数据库更新或删除）。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;简而言之，Apache Paimon的功能与我们的数据相似。无论我们是经营大型在线业务还是小网站，它都可以使所有内容都井井有条，必要时进行更新，并确保它始终可用。 Apache Paimon的生态系统的重要组成部分，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/apache-flink-101-a-guide-for-for-developers？fromrel = true”&gt; &lt;span&gt; apache Flink &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;是一个实时流处理框架，可显着扩展其功能。让我们研究Apache Paimon和&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; Apache Flink &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;彼此之间的工作状况。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Next Generation Observability: An Architectural Introduction】下一代可观察性：建筑介绍</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/next-generation-observability-introduction</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In my past life, I spent many hours researching, creating, explaining, and publishing portfolio architectures across a collection of application development, domain verticals, infrastructure solutions, and hybrid cloud domains. Most of these concentrated on the application layers and their usage of the infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, I transitioned into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/observations-on-cloud-native-observability&#34;&gt;cloud native observability&lt;/a&gt; space, and observability became the guiding light on my learning path. This quickly led to the realization that the same solution mapping that the previous portfolio architectures brought to organizations struggling with solving hard problems also applied to the observability world. It&#39;s just a matter of a different angle from which we look at those solutions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我的前世中，我花了很多时间研究，在应用程序开发，域垂直，基础架构解决方案和混合云领域的集合中进行研究，解释和发布投资组合体系结构。其中大多数集中在应用层及其对基础设施的使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，我过渡到&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/observations-on-cloud-native-bobservility”&gt;云本机可观察性&lt;/a&gt;空间，可观察性成为指导光在我的学习道路上。这很快导致了这样一个意识到，以前的投资组合架构带来了为解决难题而努力的组织所带来的解决方案映射也适用于观察性世界。这只是一个不同的角度的问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>