<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Iceberg Catalogs: A Guide for Data Engineers】冰山目录：数据工程师指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/iceberg-catalogs-a-guide-for-data-engineers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Apache Iceberg has become a popular choice for managing large datasets with flexibility and scalability. Catalogs are central to Iceberg’s functionality, which is vital in table organization, consistency, and metadata management. This article will explore what Iceberg catalogs are, their various implementations, use cases, and configurations, providing an understanding of the best-fit catalog solutions for different use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;What Is an Iceberg Catalog?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-iceberg&#34;&gt;Iceberg&lt;/a&gt;, a catalog is responsible for managing table paths, pointing to the current metadata files that represent a table’s state. This architecture is essential because it enables atomicity, consistency, and efficient querying by ensuring that all readers and writers access the same state of the table. Different catalog implementations store this metadata in various ways, from file systems to specialized metastore services.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Apache Iceberg 已成为管理具有灵活性和可扩展性的大型数据集的流行选择。目录是 Iceberg 功能的核心，这对于表组织、一致性和元数据管理至关重要。本文将探讨 Iceberg 目录是什么、它们的各种实现、用例和配置，让您了解最适合不同用例的目录解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;什么是冰山目录？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-iceberg&#34;&gt;Iceberg&lt;/a&gt; 中，目录负责管理表路径，指向表示表状态的当前元数据文件。这种架构至关重要，因为它通过确保所有读取器和写入器访问表的相同状态来实现原子性、一致性和高效查询。不同的目录实现以不同的方式存储此元数据，从文件系统到专门的元存储服务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Receipt Scanner App With OCR, OpenAI, and PostgreSQL】使用 OCR、OpenAI 和 PostgreSQL 构建收据扫描仪应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-receipt-scanner-app-with-ocr-openai-postgresql</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Managing expenses and keeping track of receipts can be cumbersome. Digitalizing receipts and extracting product information automatically can greatly enhance efficiency. In this blog, we’ll build a &lt;strong&gt;Receipt Scanner App&lt;/strong&gt; where users can scan receipts using their phone, extract data from them using OCR (Optical Character Recognition), process the extracted data with OpenAI to identify products and prices, store the data in PostgreSQL, and analyze product prices across different stores.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Does the Receipt Scanner App do?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This app allows users to:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;管理费用和跟踪收据可能很麻烦。收据数字化、自动提取产品信息可以大大提高效率。在本博客中，我们将构建一个&lt;strong&gt;收据扫描仪应用&lt;/strong&gt;，用户可以使用手机扫描收据，使用 OCR（光学字符识别）从中提取数据，使用 OpenAI 处理提取的数据以识别产品和价格，将数据存储在 PostgreSQL 中，并分析不同商店的产品价格。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;收据扫描仪应用程序有什么作用？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此应用程序允许用户：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamlining Database Management: Running PostgreSQL in Docker Containers】简化数据库管理：在 Docker 容器中运行 PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/running-postgresql-in-docker-containers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Docker containers offer a lightweight, portable, and consistent way to deploy databases across different environments. This article will guide you through the process of running a PostgreSQL database in a Docker container, providing you with a flexible and scalable solution for your database needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why Docker for PostgreSQL?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before diving into the how-to, let&#39;s briefly discuss why running &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-everywhere-and-for-everything&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt; in a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-explained-an-introductory-guide-to-docker&#34;&gt;Docker container&lt;/a&gt; is beneficial:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Docker 容器提供了一种轻量级、可移植且一致的方式来跨不同环境部署数据库。本文将指导您完成在 Docker 容器中运行 PostgreSQL 数据库的过程，为您提供满足您的数据库需求的灵活且可扩展的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么选择 Docker for PostgreSQL？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在深入了解操作方法之前，我们先简要讨论一下为什么在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-everywhere-and-for-everything&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt; 中运行 &lt; href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-explained-an-introductory-guide-to-docker&#34;&gt;Docker 容器&lt;/a&gt; 是有益的：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing DevOps in the Cloud With AI Innovation】通过 AI 创新增强云中的 DevOps</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-devops-in-the-cloud-with-ai-innovation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Since the introduction of simple applications to the market, DevOps teams have faced increasing demands in terms of speed, efficiency, and application reliability. To meet these needs, some are embracing artificial intelligence (AI) to introduce more automation, business intelligence, and intelligent decision-making to cloud DevOps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Role of AI in DevOps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;AI brings new features that enable&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devops-culture-2&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;DevOps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;to improve the efficiency of processes, ensure better security, and reduce the need for interventions that can be both lengthy and inaccurate. AI&#39;s capacity to manipulate data and make instantaneous, intelligent decisions is beneficial for operations that necessitate analysis, irregular event monitoring, and maintenance forecasting, all of which are highly pertinent in today&#39;s cloud environments. The integration of AI with DevOps enhances the level of automation as well as the overall adaptability of the new value stream to deliver an ideal response to meeting new needs as well as managing new risks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;自从将简单应用程序引入市场以来，DevOps 团队在速度、效率和应用程序可靠性方面面临着日益增长的需求。为了满足这些需求，一些企业正在拥抱人工智能 (AI)，为云 DevOps 引入更多自动化、商业智能和智能决策。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;人工智能在 DevOps 中的作用&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;人工智能带来了新功能，可实现&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devops-culture-2&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;DevOps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt; 提高流程效率、确保更好的安全性并减少冗长且不准确的干预需求。人工智能操纵数据并做出即时智能决策的能力有利于需要分析、不规则事件监控和维护预测的操作，所有这些都与当今的云环境高度相关。人工智能与DevOps的集成提高了自动化水平以及新价值流的整体适应性，从而为满足新需求和管理新风险提供理想的响应。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Power of Docker and Cucumber in Automation Testing】Docker 和 Cucumber 在自动化测试中的强大功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-power-of-docker-and-cucumber-in-automation-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Automation testing is a must for almost every software development team. But when the automation suite consists of many scenarios, the running time of automation suites tends to increase a lot, and sometimes, rather than helping a team to reduce the turnaround time of testing, it doesn’t help in a much-expected way. Thus, there is a need for parallelization of the automation suite. With parallelization comes another difficult thing. Running the automation suite parallelly is not much cheaper. It requires a bigger infrastructure to run the suite.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With all these things, we still have one solution that comes to mind: to reduce the cost and the running time of the automation suite, i.e., utilizing the docker technology, which will act as a different architecture but comes with a much cheaper or almost no cost. So, in today’s article, we will discuss how to achieve our goal of reducing the total turnaround time of the testing team with the help of automation testing utilizing technologies like Docker and Cucumber.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;自动化测试几乎是每个软件开发团队都必须做的。但是，当自动化套件由许多场景组成时，自动化套件的运行时间往往会增加很多，有时，它不但不能帮助团队减少测试的周转时间，反而不会以预期的方式提供帮助。因此，需要自动化套件的并行化。并行化带来了另一件困难。并行运行自动化套件并不便宜。它需要更大的基础设施来运行该套件。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;尽管如此，我们仍然想到一个解决方案：降低自动化套件的成本和运行时间，即利用 docker 技术，它将充当不同的架构但价格便宜得多或几乎没有成本。因此，在今天的文章中，我们将讨论如何借助 Docker 和 Cucumber 等技术的自动化测试来实现减少测试团队总周转时间的目标。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KubeVirt Implementation: Who Needs It and Why?】KubeVirt 实施：谁需要它以及为什么？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubevirt-implementation-who-needs-it-and-why</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The adoption of cloud-native architectures and containerization is transforming the way we develop, deploy, and manage applications. Containers offer speed, agility, and scalability, fueling a significant shift in IT strategies. However, the reality for many organizations is that virtual machines (VMs) continue to play a critical role, especially when it comes to legacy or stateful applications. Even leading financial institutions like Goldman Sachs recognize &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.computerweekly.com/news/366575472/Goldman-Sachs-discusses-virtues-of-Kubernetes-for-VM-management&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;the value of VMs alongside containerized workloads&lt;/a&gt; and are exploring ways to manage them efficiently.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This creates a potential divide: the benefits of containerization on one side and the enduring need for VMs on the other. KubeVirt bridges this gap by extending the power of Kubernetes to virtual machine management, giving you the ability to unify your infrastructure while enabling a smoother transition to cloud-native technologies.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;云原生架构和容器化的采用正在改变我们开发、部署和管理应用程序的方式。容器提供速度、敏捷性和可扩展性，推动 IT 战略的重大转变。然而，对于许多组织来说，现实是虚拟机 (VM) 继续发挥着关键作用，尤其是在涉及遗留或有状态应用程序时。即使像高盛这样的领先金融机构也认识到 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.computerweekly.com/news/366575472/Goldman-Sachs-discusses-virtues-of-Kubernetes-for-VM-management&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer “ target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;虚拟机与容器化工作负载的价值&lt;/a&gt;，并正在探索有效管理它们的方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;这造成了潜在的鸿沟：一方面是容器化的好处，另一方面是对虚拟机的持久需求。 KubeVirt 通过将 Kubernetes 的功能扩展到虚拟机管理来弥补这一差距，使您能够统一基础架构，同时能够更顺利地过渡到云原生技术。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agile Failure Has Strengthened, Not Weakened, Software】敏捷失败增强了而不是削弱了软件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agile-failure-has-strengthened-not-weakened-software</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;2024 is promised to be the year of generative AI. Instead, it has been the year of catastrophic software outages. Earlier this year, we saw outages affecting high-street shops, banks, and cloud vendors, whilst those of us in the UK saw the Post Office Horizon IT scandal reach new levels of public outrage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;Having made a living working to investigate and resolve such scandals in recent times, I found myself amid furor after leading a study that found that&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.20696&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Agile wasn’t all that it was cracked up to be&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;After the international crises following the Crowdstrike outage helped underscore the point, I spoke to The Register about how &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theregister.com/2024/08/07/agile_catastrophes_risk_undermining_the/&#34;&gt;catastrophic takes on Agile feed into failure&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;2024 年有望成为生成式人工智能年。相反，今年是灾难性软件中断的一年。今年早些时候，我们看到商业街商店、银行和云供应商受到影响，而我们英国人则目睹了 Post Office Horizo​​n IT 丑闻激起了公众的愤怒。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt; span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.20696&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;敏捷并不像人们所吹捧的那样&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;。&lt;/span&gt; Crowdstrike 中断之后的国际危机凸显了这一点，我向 The Register 讲述了&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.theregister.com/2024/08/07/ Agile_catastrophes_risk_undermining_the/&#34;&gt;敏捷的灾难性后果会导致失败&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Effective Exception Handling in Microservices Integration】微服务集成中的有效异常处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/effective-exception-handling-in-microservices-integration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Microservices architecture offers benefits such as scalability, agility, and maintainability, making it ideal for building robust applications. Spring Boot, as the preferred framework for developing microservices, provides various mechanisms to simplify integration with different systems. The modules offered by the Spring framework abstract much of the complexity, allowing developers to integrate seamlessly with external systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Integration types may vary depending on the system, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-an-api-integration-example&#34;&gt;API integration&lt;/a&gt;, messaging system integration, or database connectivity. Each system requires specific error-handling mechanisms. Regardless of the integration type, the API layer should not directly expose errors returned by the integrated systems to ensure a consistent and user-friendly response.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;微服务架构具有可扩展性、敏捷性和可维护性等优势，使其成为构建健壮应用程序的理想选择。 Spring Boot作为开发微服务的首选框架，提供了各种机制来简化与不同系统的集成。 Spring框架提供的模块抽象了大部分复杂性，允许开发人员与外部系统无缝集成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;集成类型可能因系统而异，包括&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-an-api-integration-example&#34; &gt;API 集成&lt;/a&gt;、消息系统集成或数据库连接。每个系统都需要特定的错误处理机制。无论集成类型如何，API 层都不应该直接暴露集成系统返回的错误，以确保一致且用户友好的响应。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Importance of Kubernetes in MLOps and Its Influence on Modern Businesses】Kubernetes 在 MLOps 中的重要性及其对现代业务的影响</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-importance-of-kubernetes-in-mlops</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;MLOps, or Machine Learning Operations, is a set of practices that combine machine learning (ML), data engineering, and DevOps to streamline and automate the end-to-end ML model lifecycle. MLOps is an essential aspect of the current data science workflows. It is a foundational component of the contemporary information technology landscape, and its influence is expected to increase significantly in the coming years. It encompasses everything from data processing and model development to deployment, monitoring, and continuous improvement, making it a crucial discipline in integrating machine learning into production environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, a significant challenge in MLOps lies in the demand for scalable and flexible infrastructure capable of handling the distinct requirements of machine learning workloads. While the development cycle is often experimental, typically using interactive tools like Jupyter notebooks, production deployment requires automation and scalability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;MLOps（即机器学习操作）是一组结合了机器学习 (ML)、数据工程和 DevOps 的实践，旨在简化和自动化端到端 ML 模型生命周期。 MLOps 是当前数据科学工作流程的一个重要方面。它是当代信息技术领域的基本组成部分，预计其影响力在未来几年将显着增加。它涵盖了从数据处理和模型开发到部署、监控和持续改进的所有内容，使其成为将机器学习集成到生产环境中的关键学科。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，MLOps 的一个重大挑战在于需要能够处理机器学习工作负载的不同要求的可扩展且灵活的基础架构。虽然开发周期通常是实验性的，通常使用 Jupyter Notebook 等交互式工具，但生产部署需要自动化和可扩展性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Lake vs. Data Warehouse vs. Data Lakehouse】数据湖、数据仓库、数据湖屋</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-lake-vs-data-warehouse-vs-data-lakehouse</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Let us look into the strengths and weaknesses of leading data storage solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data is central to modern business and society. Depending on what sort of leaky analogy you prefer, data can be the new oil, gold, or even electricity. Of course, even the biggest data sets are worthless and might even be a liability if they aren’t organized properly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;让我们研究一下领先的数据存储解决方案的优点和缺点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据是现代商业和社会的核心。根据您喜欢哪种泄漏类比，数据可以是新的石油、黄金，甚至电力。当然，即使是最大的数据集也毫无价值，如果组织不当，甚至可能成为一种负担。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>