<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Brilliant Ideas, Bad Pitch? How to Communicate Tech Proposals That Win Support】出色的想法，糟糕的投球？如何交流赢得支持的技术建议</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/communicating-technical-ideas-to-non-technical-stakeholders</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;5:1-5:511&#34;&gt;We all know the drill: refactoring makes our code easier to understand, static analysis points out complex areas and code smells, tests help us track and improve our code&#39;s coverage, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-domain-driven&#34;&gt;Domain-Driven Design&lt;/a&gt; lets us build code that directly reflects the business rules. Sounds logical, right? Yet, we often find it tough to convince managers, product owners, and other stakeholders of the value in these practices. What&#39;s even more puzzling is that we usually have no problem getting fellow developers on board.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;7:1-7:899&#34;&gt;You might wonder, &#34;What&#39;s going on here?&#34; We use the same language, list the same problems and solutions, and back up our points with the same arguments. So, where&#39;s the disconnect? Well, it&#39;s right in how we&#39;re presenting it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 5：1-5：511”&gt;我们都知道练习：重构使我们的代码更易于理解，静态分析指出了复杂的区域和代码气味，测试有助于我们跟踪和改善代码的覆盖范围，&lt;a href =”反映业务规则。听起来合乎逻辑，对吧？但是，我们经常发现很难说服经理，产品所有者和其他利益相关者在这些实践中的价值。更令人困惑的是，我们通常没有问题让其他开发人员加入船。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 7：1-7：899”&gt;您可能想知道，“这里发生了什么？”我们使用相同的语言，列出相同的问题和解决方案，并使用相同的论点备份我们的观点。那么，断开连接在哪里？好吧，我们如何展示它是正确的。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Modern IT Incident Management: Tools, Trends, and Faster Recovery】现代IT事件管理：工具，趋势和更快的恢复</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-incident-management-tools</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Modern IT systems are built on interconnected, cloud-native architectures with complex service dependencies and distributed components. In such an environment, unplanned incidents can severely impact your software service availability and revenue streams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Well-defined &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/insights-from-incident-management&#34;&gt;IT incident management&lt;/a&gt; helps tech teams manage disruptions to IT services to restore normal service operations. These could be anything from server crashes, cybersecurity threats, hardware failures, or even natural disasters.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;现代IT系统建立在具有复杂服务依赖性和分布式组件的互连的云本地体系结构上。在这样的环境中，计划外事件可能会严重影响您的软件服务可用性和收入流。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;良好定义&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/insights-from-incident-management”&gt; IT事件管理&lt;/a&gt;帮助技术团队管理干扰IT服务以恢复正常服务操作。这些可能是服务器崩溃，网络安全威胁，硬件故障甚至自然灾害的任何东西。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cybersecurity Innovations in Software Development: How Developers Are Tackling Security Threats】软件开发中的网络安全创新：开发人员如何应对安全威胁</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cybersecurity-innovations-in-software-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Cybersecurity is more critical than ever as technology becomes more integrated into our daily lives and business operations. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/common-cybersecurity-threats-and-how-to-protect-yo&#34;&gt;Cyber threats&lt;/a&gt; change quickly, so software developers need to make sure that apps, data, and users are safe by putting strong security measures in place. New developments in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/iot-cybersecurity-privacy-security-challenges&#34;&gt;cybersecurity&lt;/a&gt;, like post-quantum cryptography and AI-driven threat detection, are changing the way software are developed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I will discuss the advanced cybersecurity innovations in software development and how software developers are dealing with security problems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;网络安全比以往任何时候都更为重要，因为技术变得更加融入了我们的日常生活和业务运营。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/common-cybersecurity-threats-and-how-to-protect-yo”&gt;网络威胁&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;快速变化，因此软件开发人员需要确保应用程序，数据和用户通过在适当的位置采取强大的安全措施来安全。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/iot-cybersecurity-privacy-security-challenges”中的新发展&gt; cybersecurity &lt;/a&gt;，例如后Quantum Cryptography和Ai-drian驱动的威胁检测，都在改变软件的开发方式。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇博客文章中，我将讨论软件开发中的高级网络安全创新以及软件开发人员如何处理安全问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Object Detection at the Edge: AWS IoT Greengrass and YOLOv5】边缘的实体检测：AWS IoT Greengrass和Yolov5</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-object-detection-edge-aws-iot-greengrass-yolo</link>
      <description>【&lt;p lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Edge computing has transformed how we process and respond to data. By taking compute capability to the point of data, such as cameras, sensors, and machines, businesses can make decisions faster, reduce latency, save on bandwidth, and enhance privacy. AWS empowers this revolution with a set of edge-capable services, most notably AWS IoT Greengrass.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll give an example of how to run a machine learning model (YOLOv5) on an&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/managing-iot-edge-devices-at-scale-device-lifecycl&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;edge device&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;via&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;AWS IoT Greengrass v2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;to identify objects in real-time within a retail setting. This is a fault-tolerant and scalable solution appropriate for an intermittently cloud-connected environment. Let&#39;s look at a Retail Store Video Analytics on the Edge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p lang =“ en-us”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ en-us”&gt; edge Computing已改变了我们处理和响应数据的方式。通过将计算能力符合数据点，例如相机，传感器和机器，企业可以更快地做出决策，减少延迟，节省带宽并增强隐私。 AWS通过一组可竞争能力的服务赋予了这项革命，最著名的是AWS IOT Greengrass。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll give an example of how to run a machine learning model (YOLOv5) on an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/managing-iot-edge-devices-at-scale-device-lifecycl&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;edge device&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt; via &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;AWS IoT Greengrass v2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt; to identify objects in real-time within a retail setting.这是一种适合间歇性云连接环境的耐断层且可扩展的解决方案。让我们看一下边缘的零售商店视频分析。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building an SQL to DataFrame Converter With ANTLR】使用ANTLR构建向数据框转换器的SQL</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-sql-to-dataframe-converter-with-antlr</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The modern data engineering landscape frequently demands seamless transitions and interoperability between established SQL-based systems and the popular ecosystem of Dataframe-centric frameworks like Pandas, Apache Spark and Polars. Migrating legacy applications or building hybrid systems often requires translating SQL queries into their DataFrame API equivalents. While manual rewriting is feasible for small-scale projects, it quickly becomes a bottleneck, prone to errors and challenging to maintain as complexity grows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article delves into leveraging &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.antlr.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ANTLR&lt;/a&gt; (ANother Tool for Language Recognition), a powerful parser generator, to construct a robust and extensible SQL to DataFrame converter. We will explore the core principle, implementation steps and challenges involved in building such system.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代数据工程格局经常需要基于SQL的系统与以数据框架为中心的框架（如Pandas，Apache Spark和Porars）的流行生态系统之间的无缝过渡和互操作性。迁移的旧应用程序或建筑混合系统通常需要将SQL查询转换为其数据框架API等效物。尽管手动重写对于小型项目是可行的，但它很快就变成了瓶颈，容易出现错误，并且随着复杂性的增长而保持挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article delves into leveraging &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.antlr.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ANTLR&lt;/a&gt; (ANother Tool for Language Recognition), a powerful parser generator, to construct a robust and extensible SQL to DataFrame converter.我们将探讨构建此类系统的核心原则，实施步骤和挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Is NLP Essential in Speech Recognition Systems?】为什么NLP在语音识别系统中至关重要？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-is-nlp-essential-in-speech-recognition-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Audio annotation services are pivotal in training machine learning models to accurately comprehend and interpret auditory data. These services utilize human annotators to label, transcribe, and classify audio recording that spans speech recognition, sound classification, sentiment analysis, and training AI models. It is a necessity applicable across industries that rely on annotated audio data for model development and refinement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Complemented by developments in Natural Language Processing (NLP) and speech synthesis, Automated Speech Recognition models show more seamless communication between humans and machines. In the coming sections, we shall discuss the critical role of NLP in ASR.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;音频注释服务在训练机学习模型中至关重要，可以准确理解和解释听觉数据。这些服务利用人类注释者标记，转录和分类音频录制，以跨越语音识别，声音分类，情感分析和培训AI模型。这是依靠注释的音频数据进行模型开发和改进的行业的必要性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;与自然语言处理（NLP）和语音合成的发展相辅相成，自动语音识别模型显示了人类与机器之间的更多无缝通信。在即将到来的部分中，我们将讨论NLP在ASR中的关键作用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Snowflake Cortex for Developers: How Generative AI and SaaS Enable Self-Serve Data Analytics】开发人员的雪花皮层：生成AI和SaaS如何启用自助数据分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-cortex-generative-ai-self-serve-analytics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;878&#34; data-start=&#34;179&#34;&gt;In the era of low-code, no-code platforms, SaaS solutions, and the new trend called Agentic AI, the industry is focused on optimizing software development for greater efficiency. Text-to-SQL is one such area in software engineering where organizations aim to enable self-serve analytics and democratize SQL using AI. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-cortex-for-genai&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-cortex-for-genai&#34;&gt;Snowflake Cortex AI&lt;/a&gt;, a generative AI offering from Snowflake, bundles this capability into a SaaS product that eliminates the complexity of building custom text-to-SQL solutions. The benefits go beyond reduced development effort. Cortex AI also delivers significantly higher accuracy in SQL query generation compared to custom-built solutions, thanks to its use of a semantic model.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;911&#34; data-start=&#34;880&#34;&gt;Cortex AI comes in two versions:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 878” data-start =“ 179”&gt;在低代码，无代码平台，SaaS解决方案和称为AgentIC AI的新趋势的时代，该行业专注于优化软件开发以提高效率。文本到SQL是软件工程中的这样一个领域的领域之一，组织旨在使用AI实现自我服务分析并民主化SQL。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-cortex-for-genai”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href =“ https:/ https：//dzone.com/articles/snowflake-cortex-for-cortex-for-genai--构建自定义文本到SQL解决方案的复杂性。好处超出了减少的开发工作。与定制的解决方案相比，Cortex AI在SQL查询生成中的准确性也明显更高，这要归功于其使用语义模型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 911” data-start =“ 880”&gt; Cortex AI有两个版本：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Future Is Now: Top Generative AI Services You Can’t Ignore】现在的未来是：您不能忽略的最佳生成AI服务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-generative-ai-services</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI continues to transform various sectors, with generative AI leading a new wave of innovation. Unlike traditional AI that focuses on processing and interpreting data, generative AI creates entirely new content, including text, visuals, audio, and video, offering fresh possibilities for how we build and interact with technology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of Generative AI Services and Solutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;How Does Generative AI Work?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Generative AI works by taking a large dataset. It learns patterns from the data. Then it learns and creates new and unique content.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; AI继续改变各个部门，生成的AI引导了新的创新浪潮。与专注于处理和解释数据的传统AI不同，生成AI创建了全新的内容，包括文本，视觉效果，音频和视频，为我们如何构建和与技术互动提供了新的可能性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;生成AI服务和解决方案的概述&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;生成AI如何工作？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;生成的AI可以使用大数据集来起作用。它从数据中学习模式。然后它学习并创建新的独特内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Java 8 to Java 21: How the Evolution Changed My Developer Workflow】从Java 8到Java 21：演变如何改变我的开发人员工作流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-evolution-changed-developer-workflow</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;As a Java developer who spent years working with Java 8, I was comfortable with the stability and functionality it provided — lambda expressions, Streams and the java.time API felt like revolutionary improvements when they first arrived. But like many others, I stuck with Java 8 for years, not seeing the need to move on. That was, until I had the chance to work with Java 17 and eventually Java 21. In this post, I reflect on the features that truly changed the way I code and why it’s worth upgrading from Java 8 to Java 21.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why I Stuck With Java 8 for So Long&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I stuck with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/j%CE%BBv%CE%BB-8-a-comprehensive-look&#34;&gt;Java 8&lt;/a&gt; for a long time because it just worked. It was stable, widely adopted and most importantly, it met the needs of enterprise projects. Newer versions came out, but transitioning wasn&#39;t always worth the effort — until my personal project pushed me to try something different. As I joined a team using Java 17+ and started working with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-21-features-a-detailed-look&#34;&gt;Java 21&lt;/a&gt; in real-world projects, I began to see just how much had changed.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;作为Java开发人员，他与Java 8一起工作了多年，我对所提供的稳定性和功能感到满意 -  Lambda表达式，流和Java。但是像许多其他人一样，我一直坚持使用Java 8多年来，没有看到继续前进的必要性。那就是，直到我有机会与Java 17和Java 21合作。在这篇文章中，我反思了真正改变了我编码方式的功能，以及为什么值得从Java 8升级到Java 21。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么我坚持使用java 8这么长&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;我坚持&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/j%Ce%BBV%CE%BB-8-A- comprehensive-look-look”&gt; java 8 &lt;/a&gt;很长一段时间以来，因为它刚刚起作用。它是稳定的，广泛采用的，最重要的是，它满足了企业项目的需求。较新的版本出现了，但是过渡并不总是值得付出的努力 - 直到我的个人项目促使我尝试不同的东西。当我加入一个使用Java 17+的团队并开始使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/java-21-features-a-detailed-look-look”&gt; java 21 &lt;/a&gt;在现实世界中，我开始看到多少变化了。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Architects of Ambient Intelligence With IoT and AI Personal Assistants】与物联网和AI个人助理的环境智能建筑师</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ambient-intelligence-iot-ai-personal-assistants</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-sourcepos=&#34;9:1-9:85&#34;&gt;Introduction: The Moment It Clicked — From Convenience to Contextual Intelligence&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;11:1-11:761&#34;&gt;I still vividly recall a particular brainstorming session at Amazon, the hum of whiteboard markers and the scent of lukewarm coffee filling the room. My team and I were neck-deep in the intricate challenge of weaving Alexa into a sprawling home automation system. We weren&#39;t just integrating devices; we were grappling with the nuances of creating a truly &lt;em&gt;responsive&lt;/em&gt; environment. It was in that moment, as we debated the finer points of event-driven architectures and state synchronization across disparate protocols, that it truly clicked for me: this wasn&#39;t merely about convenience anymore. This was about reshaping the very fabric of how we live, how we interact with our digital and physical worlds, and how technology can genuinely anticipate our needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;13:1-13:637&#34;&gt;As a software development manager with a longstanding affinity for distributed systems, I&#39;ve witnessed countless technological shifts. Yet, few have captivated me as much as the potent convergence of the Internet of Things (IoT) and artificial intelligence (AI), especially when it comes to personal assistants. The sheer potential for these technologies to deliver hyper-personalized, almost clairvoyant experiences and fundamentally enhance our daily lives is immense. But let&#39;s be honest, getting there is a tightrope walk, fraught with complex technical challenges that demand not just dexterity, but deep, insightful engineering.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-sourcepos =“ 9：1-9：85”&gt;简介：单击的那一刻 - 从便利到上下文智能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 11：1-11：761”&gt;我仍然生动地回想起亚马逊的特定集思广益会议，白板标记的嗡嗡声和充满了房间的不透水咖啡的气味。我和我的团队在将Alexa编织到庞大的家庭自动化系统中的复杂挑战中很艰巨。我们不仅仅是整合设备；我们正在努力创建真正&lt;em&gt;响应式&lt;/em&gt;环境的细微差别。正是在那一刻，当我们讨论了跨不同协议的事件驱动架构和状态同步的更好点时，它确实对我来说是真正的点击：这不仅仅是便利性。这是关于重塑我们的生活方式，与数字和物理世界的互动以及技术如何真正预期我们的需求的结构。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 13：1-13：637”&gt;作为一名软件开发经理，对分布式系统具有长期亲和力，我目睹了无数的技术转变。然而，很少有人能像物联网（IoT）和人工智能（AI）的有效融合一样吸引我，尤其是在个人助理方面。这些技术提供超为个性化的，几乎千里眼的经历并从根本上改善我们的日常生活的巨大潜力是巨大的。但是，老实说，到达那里是一条绳索步行，充满了复杂的技术挑战，不仅需要灵巧，而且需要深刻而有见地的工程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>