<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Writing (Slightly) Cleaner Code With Collections and Optionals】使用集合和选项编写（稍微）更干净的代码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cleaner-code-with-collections-and-optionals</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/HTTP-RPC/Kilo&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kilo&lt;/a&gt; is an open-source project for creating and consuming RESTful and REST-like web services in Java. Among other things, it includes the &lt;code&gt;Collections&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;Optionals&lt;/code&gt; classes, which are designed to help simplify code that depends on collection types and optional values, respectively. Both are discussed in more detail below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Collections&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kilo’s &lt;code&gt;Collections&lt;/code&gt; class provides a set of static utility methods for declaratively instantiating list, map, and set values:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/HTTP-RPC/Kilo&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kilo&lt;/a&gt; 是一个开源项目，用于在 Java 中创建和使用 RESTful 和类似 REST 的 Web 服务。除此之外，它还包括 &lt;code&gt;Collections&lt;/code&gt; 和 &lt;code&gt;Optionals&lt;/code&gt; 类，它们旨在帮助简化分别依赖于集合类型和可选值的代码。下面将更详细地讨论两者。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;集合&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kilo 的 &lt;code&gt;Collections&lt;/code&gt; 类提供了一组静态实用方法，用于以声明方式实例化列表、映射和设置值：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Fluent Bit: Top Tip Using Telemetry Pipeline Parsers for Developers (Part 8)】掌握 Fluent Bit：为开发人员使用遥测管道解析器的重要提示（第 8 部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/telemetry-pipeline-parsers-for-developers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This series is a general-purpose getting-started guide for those of us wanting to learn about the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) project Fluent Bit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div itemprop=&#34;articleBody&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;Each article in this series addresses a single topic by providing insights into &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; the topic is, &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; we are interested in exploring that topic, &lt;em&gt;where&lt;/em&gt; to get started with the topic, and &lt;em&gt;how&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;to get hands-on with learning about the topic as it relates to the Fluent Bit project.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本系列是为我们这些想要了解云原生计算基金会 (CNCF) 项目 Fluent Bit 的人提供的通用入门指南。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div itemprop=&#34;articleBody&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;本系列中的每篇文章都针对一个主题，深入介绍该主题是什么、我们为何对探索该主题感兴趣、从何处开始了解该主题，以及如何实际操作了解与 Fluent Bit 项目相关的主题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Set Up Spring Data Elasticsearch With Basic Authentication】使用基本身份验证设置 Spring Data Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/setup-spring-data-elasticsearch-54-with-basic-auth</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Recently, I wrote the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-spring-data-elasticsearch-upgrade&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Introduction to Spring Data Elasticsearch 5.5&lt;/a&gt; article about Spring Data Elasticsearch usage as a NoSQL database. The article covered just the setup of the unsecured Elasticsearch. However, we need to be able to connect to the secured Elasticsearch as well. Let&#39;s follow the previous article and see the needed changes to run and connect to the secured Elasticsearch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;In This Article, You Will Learn&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;How to create a secure Elasticsearch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;How to connect to the secured Elasticsearch with Spring Data Elasticsearch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;How to change the password in Elasticsearch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Set Up Secured Elasticsearch&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The setup for creating a secure Elasticsearch is pretty similar to the steps in the already-mentioned &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-spring-data-elasticsearch-upgrade&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;. The technologies used in this article, compliant with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.spring.io/spring-data/elasticsearch/reference/elasticsearch/versions.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;compatibility matrix&lt;/a&gt;, are:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;最近，我撰写了关于 Spring Data Elasticsearch 作为 NoSQL 数据库使用的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-spring-data-elasticsearch-upgrade&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Spring Data Elasticsearch 5.5 简介&lt;/a&gt;文章。本文仅介绍了不安全的 Elasticsearch 的设置。然而，我们还需要能够连接到安全的 Elasticsearch。让我们按照上一篇文章的内容，了解运行和连接到安全 Elasticsearch 所需的更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;在本文中，您将学到&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;如何创建安全的 Elasticsearch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;如何使用 Spring Data Elasticsearch 连接到安全的 Elasticsearch&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;如何更改 Elasticsearch 中的密码&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;设置安全的 Elasticsearch&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建安全 Elasticsearch 的设置与已经提到的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-spring-data-elasticsearch-upgrade&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;文章&lt;/a&gt;中的步骤非常相似。本文中使用的符合&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.spring.io/spring-data/elasticsearch/reference/elasticsearch/versions.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;兼容性矩阵&lt;/a&gt;的技术是：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Schema Registry to Manage Real-Time Data Streams in AI Pipelines】使用架构注册表管理 AI 管道中的实时数据流</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/schema-registry-real-time-ai-pipelines</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today’s AI-powered systems, real-time data is essential rather than optional. Real-time data streaming has started having an important impact on modern AI models for applications that need quick decisions. However, as data streams increase in complexity and speed, ensuring data consistency is a significant engineering challenge. As we know, AI models are heavily dependent on the input data used to train them. The quality of this input data is very important and should not be corrupted or contain errors. The accuracy, reliability, and fairness of the model’s predictions can be significantly affected if the quality of the input data is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The above statement is concrete, while AI models are being developed and subsequently made ready to identify patterns, make predictions based on input data. If we integrate these developed and tested trained AI models with real-time data stream processing pipelines, the&amp;nbsp;predictions can be achieved on the fly. Because the real-time data streaming plays a key role for AI models as it allows them to handle and respond to data as it comes in, instead of just using old fixed datasets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;You could read here my previous article, “&lt;a href=&#34;https://dataview.in/ai-on-the-fly-real-time-data-streaming-from-apache-kafka-to-live-dashboards&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI on the Fly: Real-Time Data Streaming from Apache Kafka to Live Dashboards&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/span&gt; But the big question is how we can ensure real-time data that comes as a stream from various sources is free from errors and not at all bad data. By spotting patterns and trained data, AI systems decide. If this data has mistakes, doesn’t add up, or is messy, the model might pick up wrong patterns. This can lead to outputs that are biased, off the mark, or even risky.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今人工智能驱动的系统中，实时数据是必不可少的，而不是可选的。实时数据流已开始对需要快速决策的应用程序的现代人工智能模型产生重要影响。然而，随着数据流的复杂性和速度的增加，确保数据一致性是一项重大的工程挑战。众所周知，人工智能模型严重依赖于用于训练它们的输入数据。输入数据的质量非常重要，不应损坏或包含错误。如果输入数据的质量受到影响，模型预测的准确性、可靠性和公平性可能会受到显着影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上述说法是具体的，而人工智能模型正在开发中，随后准备好识别模式，根据输入数据进行预测。如果我们将这些开发和测试的训练有素的人工智能模型与实时数据流处理管道集成，则可以即时实现预测。因为实时数据流对于人工智能模型起着关键作用，因为它允许它们处理和响应传入的数据，而不仅仅是使用旧的固定数据集。 &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;您可以在这里阅读我之前的文章，“&lt;a href=&#34;https://dataview.in/ai-on-the-fly-real-time-data-streaming-from-apache-kafka-to-live-dashboards&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI on the Fly：从 Apache Kafka 到 Live 的实时数据流 仪表板&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;但最大的问题是我们如何确保来自各种来源的实时数据没有错误，而且完全没有坏数据。通过发现模式和训练数据，人工智能系统做出决定。如果这些数据有错误、不相加或混乱，模型可能会选择错误的模式。这可能会导致产出有偏差、偏离目标，甚至存在风险。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Anthropic’s Model Context Protocol (MCP): A Developer’s Guide to Long-Context LLM Integration】Anthropic 的模型上下文协议 (MCP)：长上下文 LLM 集成开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/anthropics-model-context-protocol-mcp-a-developers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Large language models (LLMs) like Anthropic’s Claude have unlocked massive context windows (up to 100k tokens in Claude 2) that let them consider entire documents or codebases in a single go. However, effectively providing relevant context to these models remains a challenge. Traditionally, developers have resorted to complex prompt engineering or retrieval pipelines to feed external information into an LLM’s prompt. Anthropic’s Model Context Protocol (MCP) is a new open standard designed to simplify and standardize this process. Think of MCP as the &lt;em&gt;“USB-C for AI applications”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;— a universal connector that lets your LLM seamlessly access external data, tools, and systems. In this article, we’ll explain what MCP is, why it’s important for long-context LLMs, how it compares to traditional prompt engineering, and walk through building a simple MCP-compatible context server in Python. We’ll also discuss practical use cases (like retrieval-augmented generation and agent tools) and provide code examples, diagrams, and references to get you started with MCP and Claude.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What is MCP and why does it matter?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MCP (Model Context Protocol) is an open protocol introduced by Anthropic in late 2024 to standardize how AI applications provide context to LLMs. In essence, MCP defines a common client–server architecture for connecting AI assistants to the places where your data lives — whether that’s local files, databases, cloud services, or business applications. Before MCP, integrating an LLM with each new data source or API meant writing a custom connector or prompt logic for that specific case. This led to a combinatorial explosion of integrations: &lt;em&gt;M&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;AI applications times &lt;em&gt;N&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;data sources could require &lt;em&gt;M×N&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;bespoke implementations. &amp;nbsp;MCP addresses this by providing a universal interface so that any compliant AI client can communicate with any compliant data/service server, reducing the problem to &lt;em&gt;M + N&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;integration points.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;像 Anthropic 的 Claude 这样的大型语言模型 (LLM) 已经解锁了巨大的上下文窗口（Claude 2 中多达 100k 个标记），让他们可以一次性考虑整个文档或代码库。然而，有效地为这些模型提供相关背景仍然是一个挑战。传统上，开发人员采用复杂的提示工程或检索管道将外部信息输入到法学硕士的提示中。 Anthropic 的模型上下文协议 (MCP) 是一个新的开放标准，旨在简化和标准化此过程。将 MCP 视为“用于 AI 应用的 USB-C”&lt;/em&gt;——一种通用连接器，可让您的法学硕士无缝访问外部数据、工具和系统。在本文中，我们将解释 MCP 是什么、为什么它对于长上下文 LLM 很重要、它与传统提示工程的比较，并逐步介绍如何使用 Python 构建一个简单的 MCP 兼容上下文服务器。我们还将讨论实际用例（例如检索增强生成和代理工具）并提供代码示例、图表和参考，以帮助您开始使用 MCP 和 Claude。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是 MCP？它为什么重要？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MCP（模型上下文协议）是 Anthropic 于 2024 年末推出的开放协议，旨在标准化人工智能应用程序向法学硕士提供上下文的方式。本质上，MCP 定义了一个通用的客户端-服务器架构，用于将 AI 助手连接到数据所在的位置 - 无论是本地文件、数据库、云服务还是业务应用程序。在 MCP 之前，将 LLM 与每个新数据源或 API 集成意味着为该特定案例编写自定义连接器或提示逻辑。这导致了集成的组合爆炸：&lt;em&gt;M 个&lt;/em&gt;人工智能应用程序乘以&lt;em&gt;N&lt;/em&gt;个数据源可能需要&lt;em&gt;M×N&lt;/em&gt;定制实现。  MCP 通过提供通用接口来解决这个问题，以便任何合规的 AI 客户端都可以与任何合规的数据/服务服务器进行通信，从而将问题减少到 &lt;em&gt;M + N&lt;/em&gt; 个集成点。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Series: Toward a Shared Language Between Humans and Machines Part 1/4: Why Machines Still Struggle to Understand Us】系列：迈向人与机器之间的共享语言第 1/4 部分：为什么机器仍然难以理解我们</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-machines-still-struggle-to-understand-us</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Language models give the impression of conversing with us as if they really understood. But behind this fluency lies an illusion: machines share neither our experiences nor our intentions. This article explores the fundamental barriers that prevent any genuine mutual understanding: the absence of lived experience, the absence of a world, and the radical difference in how reasoning works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Anyone who has ever translated between two human languages can’t help but notice that the task is quite complex, even when mastering both languages perfectly. Language holds many subtleties and ambiguities, unspoken meanings, and things that are simply untranslatable from one language to another. These difficulties often have their roots in cultural grounding as well as in lived experience, frames of thought that shape languages.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;语言模型给人的印象是与我们交谈，就好像它们真的理解一样。但这种流畅性的背后隐藏着一种幻觉：机器既不分享我们的经验，也不分享我们的意图。本文探讨了阻碍任何真正相互理解的根本障碍：缺乏生活经验、缺乏世界以及推理方式的根本差异。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;任何曾经在两种人类语言之间进行翻译的人都会不禁注意到，即使完美掌握两种语言，这项任务也相当复杂。语言包含许多微妙之处和歧义、未言明的含义以及无法从一种语言翻译成另一种语言的东西。这些困难往往根源于文化基础、生活经验以及塑造语言的思维框架。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enterprise-Grade Document Intelligence: Cloud Big Data AI With YOLOv9 and Spark on AWS】企业级文档智能：AWS 上使用 YOLOv9 和 Spark 的云大数据 AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/document-intelligence-yolov9-spark-aws</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Document analysis, a modern way:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Managing considerable volumes of documents, including&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;checks, ID cards, and tax forms, etc,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;is an error-prone, tedious, and time-consuming endeavor for financial institutions and enterprises.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;The standard approach usually employs people and/or older, often less accurate, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-perform-ocr-on-a-photograph-of-a-receipt-us&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Optical Character Recognition (OCR)&lt;/a&gt; technology to try to manage the variable layouts in documents, the variability in handwriting, and issues with image quality.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;文档分析，一种现代方式：&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;管理大量文档，包括&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt; 支票、身份证和纳税申报表等，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;对于金融机构和企业来说是一项容易出错、繁琐且耗时的工作。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;标准方法通常雇用人员和/或老年人，通常不太准确，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-perform-ocr-on-a-photograph-of-a-receipt-us&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;光学字符识别 (OCR)&lt;/a&gt; 技术尝试管理文档中的可变布局、手写变化以及图像质量问题。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Engineering Performance: Technical Analysis of telecom-mas-agent vs Google Cloud Pub/Sub in High-Throughput Telecom Automation】工程性能：高吞吐量电信自动化中 Telecom-mas-agent 与 Google Cloud Pub/Sub 的技术分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/telecom-mas-agent-vs-google-pubsub-performance-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When building telecom automation systems that process millions of messages daily, every millisecond and megabyte matters. After eighteen months of running production workloads and experiencing recurring performance bottlenecks with Google&#39;s enterprise-grade solutions, I embarked on a systematic engineering analysis to quantify the true performance characteristics of telecom automation tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This investigation compares &lt;strong&gt;telecom-mas-agent&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;code&gt;@npm-telecom-mas-agent&lt;/code&gt;)against &lt;strong&gt;Google Cloud Pub/Sub&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;code&gt;@google-cloud/pubsub&lt;/code&gt;) across multiple dimensions: memory management, network optimization, error handling resilience, and computational efficiency. The findings reveal fundamental architectural differences that create measurable performance gaps when competing directly with Google&#39;s flagship messaging infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在构建每天处理数百万条消息的电信自动化系统时，每一毫秒和每一兆字节都很重要。在运行生产工作负载十八个月并经历了 Google 企业级解决方案反复出现的性能瓶颈之后，我开始进行系统工程分析，以量化电信自动化工具的真实性能特征。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这项调查从多个维度对 &lt;strong&gt;telecom-mas-agent&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;code&gt;@npm-telecom-mas-agent&lt;/code&gt;) 与 &lt;strong&gt;Google Cloud Pub/Sub&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;code&gt;@google-cloud/pubsub&lt;/code&gt;) 进行了比较：内存管理、网络优化、错误处理弹性和计算效率。研究结果揭示了根本性的架构差异，这些差异在与 Google 的旗舰消息传递基础架构直接竞争时造成了可衡量的性能差距。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Renaming Columns in PySpark: withColumnRenamed vs toDF】在 PySpark 中重命名列：withColumnRenamed 与 toDF</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/pyspark-rename-columns-withcolumnrenamed-vs-todf</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’ve worked with PySpark DataFrames, you’ve probably had to rename columns. Either using &lt;code&gt;withColumnRenamed&lt;/code&gt; repeatedly or &lt;code&gt;toDF()&lt;/code&gt;. At first glance, both approaches work the same; you get the renamed columns you wanted. But under the hood, they interact with Spark’s Directed Acyclic Graph (DAG) in very different ways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;withColumnRenamed&lt;/code&gt; creates a new projection layer for each rename, gradually stacking transformations in the logical plan.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;toDF()&lt;/code&gt;, on the other hand, applies all renames in a single step.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While both are optimized to the same physical execution, their impact on the DAG size, planning overhead, and code readability can make a real difference in larger pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您使用过 PySpark DataFrames，您可能必须重命名列。重复使用 &lt;code&gt;withColumnRenamed&lt;/code&gt; 或 &lt;code&gt;toDF()&lt;/code&gt;。乍一看，这两种方法的工作原理是相同的。您将获得所需的重命名列。但在幕后，它们以非常不同的方式与 Spark 的有向无环图 (DAG) 交互。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;withColumnRenamed&lt;/code&gt; 为每个重命名创建一个新的投影层，逐渐在逻辑计划中堆叠转换。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; 另一方面，&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;toDF()&lt;/code&gt; 在一个步骤中应用所有重命名。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然两者都针对相同的物理执行进行了优化，但它们对 DAG 大小、规划开销和代码可读性的影响可以在较大的管道​​中产生真正的差异。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes Debugging Recipe: Practical Steps to Diagnose Pods Like a Pro】Kubernetes 调试秘诀：像专业人士一样诊断 Pod 的实用步骤</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/debugging-kubernetes-pods-like-a-pro</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Automation isn’t optional at enterprise scale. It’s resilient by design. Kubernetes provides remarkable scalability and resilience , but when pods crash, even seasoned engineers struggle to translate complex and cryptic logs and events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide walks you through the spectrum of AI-powered root cause analysis and manual debugging, combining command-line reproducibility and predictive observability approaches.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;自动化在企业规模上不是可选的。它的设计具有弹性。 Kubernetes 提供了卓越的可扩展性和弹性，但是当 Pod 崩溃时，即使是经验丰富的工程师也很难翻译复杂且神秘的日志和事件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南将引导您完成人工智能驱动的根本原因分析和手动调试，结合命令行再现性和预测可观察性方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>