<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Rust vs Python: Differences and Ideal Use Cases】Rust vs Python：差异和理想用例</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rust-vs-python-differences-and-use-cases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Rust and Python are widely used programming languages in software development and data science. Rust’s adoption has grown significantly in recent years, leaving many wondering if it will eventually replace Python as a top programming language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Compared to Python, Rust is a newbie but is making its mark among developers. According to the StackOverflow Developer Survey, Python is preferred over Rust, but in some cases, Rust is better. To better understand which one to choose, this article walks you through both languages&#39; features, what makes them different, and how they fit into specific projects.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Rust和Python是软件开发和数据科学中广泛使用的编程语言。近年来，Rust的采用已经大大增长，许多人想知道它是否最终将取代Python作为顶级编程语言。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;与Python相比，Rust是一个新手，但在开发人员中却留下了自己的印记。根据Stackoverflow开发人员的调查，Python比Rust更喜欢，但在某些情况下，Rust更好。为了更好地了解要选择哪种内容，本文会引导您介绍两种语言的功能，什么使它们与众不同以及它们如何适应特定项目。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Quarantine a Malicious File in Java】如何在Java隔离恶意文件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-quarantine-a-malicious-file-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Scanning file uploads for viruses, malware, and other threats is standard practice in any application that processes files from an external source. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;No matter which antimalware we use, the goal is always the same: to prevent malicious executables from reaching a downstream user (directly, via database storage, etc.) or automated workflow that might inadvertently execute the malicious content.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;扫描文件上传病毒，恶意软件和其他威胁都是从外部源处理文件的任何应用程序中的标准实践。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;无论我们使用哪种反疑问软件，目标始终是相同的：防止恶意可执行文件到达下游用户（直接通过数据库存储等）或自动化工作流程或自动化工作流程可能无意中执行恶意内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Codify Your Cloud and Kubernetes With Crossplane and IaC】用交叉平面和IAC将云和kubernetes编纂</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/codify-cloud-kubernetes-crossplane-iac</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;As organizations embrace Kubernetes for cloud-native applications, managing infrastructure efficiently becomes challenging. Traditional Infrastructure as Code (IaC) tools like Terraform, Pulumi, and others provide declarative configurations but lack seamless integration into the Kubernetes-native workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crossplane.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Crossplane&lt;/a&gt; effectively bridges the gap between Kubernetes and cloud infrastructure in this situation. In this blog, we’ll explore how Crossplane enables IaC for Kubernetes and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;随着组织拥抱云的应用程序，有效地管理基础架构变得具有挑战性。传统的基础架构作为Terraform，Pulumi和其他工具等代码（IAC）工具提供声明性配置，但缺乏无缝集成到Kubernetes-native Workflows中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.crossplane.io/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; crossplane &lt;/a&gt;有效地弥合了缝隙在这种情况下，在Kubernetes和云基础架构之间。在此博客中，我们将探讨跨平面如何启用kubernetes及以后的IAC。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Redirects With Cloudflare Bulk Redirects】用Cloudflare散装重定向重定向重定向</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-redirects-with-cloudflare-bulk-redirects</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem Statement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Controlling numerous URL redirects in IIS Manager operating on Windows Server systems proves difficult because it requires extended work time. When redirect rules within the IIS interface and web.config file require manual configuration, their management becomes more complicated due to the growing number of redirects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Website migrations and site restructurings lead to this particular challenge since teams need to maintain multiple redirects numbering in the dozens and potentially even hundreds. The end result of manual processing methods creates slower operations followed by elevated possibilities of long-term configuration mistakes and human errors. Multiple team members working with the &lt;code&gt;web.config&lt;/code&gt; file for editing encounters complicated backup and version control challenges because of repeated edits.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;问题语句&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Windows Server系统上操作的IIS管理器中控制大量URL重定向很难，因为它需要延长工作时间。当IIS接口和Web.config文件中的重定向规则需要手动配置时，由于重定向的数量越来越多，它们的管理变得更加复杂。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;网站迁移和网站重组导致了这一特殊挑战，因为团队需要维持数十个甚至数百个可能的重定向编号。手动处理方法的最终结果创造了较慢的操作，然后是长期配置错误和人体错误的可能性升高。使用&lt;code&gt; web.config &lt;/code&gt;用于编辑遇到复杂备份和版本控制挑战的多个团队成员。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【API Mesh: The Next Big Leap in Distributed Backend Systems】API网格：分布式后端系统的下一个大飞跃</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/api-mesh-the-next-big-leap-in-distributed-backend</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;API Mesh simplifies API management across distributed systems by providing a unified layer for orchestration, security, and observability. In this article, we’ll explore the intricacies of API Mesh, its unique capabilities, and how it is set to redefine how businesses manage their APIs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-teams=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding API Mesh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-teams=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-teams=&#34;true&#34;&gt;To understand the value of an API Mesh, we first need to distinguish it from other tools like API gateways and service meshes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; api网格通过提供统一的层面层，用于编排，安全性和可观察性来简化分布式系统的API管理。在本文中，我们将探讨API网格的复杂性，其独特的功能以及如何重新定义企业如何管理其API。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;span data-teams =“ true”&gt; &lt;span data-teams =“ true”&gt;以了解API网格的值，我们首先需要将其与其他区分开API网关和服务网格等工具：&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Integrate Platform Engineering Into Your Business】如何将平台工程整合到您的业务中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-integrate-platform-engineering-into-your-bu</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-devex-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Experience: The Coalescence of Developer Productivity, Process Satisfaction, and Platform Engineering&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How do we even start approaching platform engineering? The good news is that major organizations that have successfully adopted platform engineering have contributed their insights, best practices, and lessons learned to frameworks like the Cloud Native Computing Foundation&#39;s (CNCF)&lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-app-delivery.cncf.io/whitepapers/platform-eng-maturity-model/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;Platform Maturity Model&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/platform-engineering/platform-engineering-capability-model&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Microsoft&#39;s Platform Engineering Capability Model&lt;/a&gt;. These models provide a structured pathway for organizations to evaluate their current state and identify gaps and actionable steps toward building an effective internal developer platform (IDP).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;编辑注：以下是为Dzone的2025趋势报告编写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/link.com/link/2025-tr-tr-devex-contributor -article“ rel =” noopener noreferrer“ target =“ _ blank”&gt; &lt;em&gt;开发人员体验：开发人员生产率，过程满意度的合并，和平台工程&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们甚至如何开始接触平台工程？好消息是，成功采用平台工程的主要组织为他们的见解，最佳实践和经验教训贡献了诸如Cloud Native Computing Foundation（CNCF）的框架（CNCF）&lt;a HREF =“ https：//ttps：//tag-app-delivery。 cncf.io/whitepapers/platform-eng-maturity-model/“ rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;平台成熟模型&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/platform-egneering/platform-egneering/platform-egneering-capibility-capibility-capibility-capibaliety-capibility-model” rel =“ noopener noreferrer “ target =“ _ blank”&gt; Microsoft的平台工程能力模型&lt;/a&gt;。这些模型为组织提供了一个结构化的途径，以评估其当前状态，并确定构建有效的内部开发人员平台（IDP）的差距和可行的步骤。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tips to Choose the Right SQL Database】选择正确的SQL数据库的提示</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/choose-a-sql-database</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It’s the same in the world of data, where choosing the right SQL database can make or break your organization’s success. With several options available, database selection is a crucial decision that can shape the performance, scalability and efficiency of your data platform. Finding the perfect fit for your specific needs requires careful consideration of various factors and taking time to understand different database types.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article guides you through the process of selecting a SQL database. We&#39;ll explore the main types of SQL databases, discuss key factors to consider when making your choice, and take a look at some popular options in the market. By the end, you&#39;ll have a clearer picture of how to pick a database that aligns with your project requirements and business goals — setting you up for better data management and analysis.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在数据世界中，选择正确的SQL数据库可以创造或破坏组织的成功。有了几种可用的选项，数据库选择是一个至关重要的决定，可以塑造数据平台的性能，可扩展性和效率。找到适合您特定需求的最适合的需要仔细考虑各种因素，并花时间了解不同的数据库类型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文指导您选择SQL数据库的过程。我们将探索SQL数据库的主要类型，讨论在做出选择时要考虑的关键因素，并查看市场上的一些流行选择。到最后，您将有更清晰的了解如何选择与您的项目需求和业务目标保持一致的数据库 - 为您提供更好的数据管理和分析。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Perceptron Algorithm and the Kernel Trick】感知算法和内核技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-perceptron-algorithm-and-the-kernel-trick</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;The Perceptron Algorithm is one of the earliest and most influential machine learning models, forming the foundation for modern neural networks and support vector machines (SVMs). Proposed by Frank Rosenblatt in 1958 (Rosenblatt, 1958), the perceptron is a simple yet powerful linear classifier designed for binary classification tasks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Despite its simplicity, the perceptron introduced key concepts that remain central to machine learning today, such as iterative weight updates,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;the use of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;activation functions, and learning a decision boundary (Goodfellow, Bengio &amp;amp; Courville, 2016). These ideas have directly influenced the development of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/deep-learning-via-multilayer-perceptron-classifier&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;multi-layer neural networks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; by introducing weight adjustment rules that underpin backpropagation (LeCun, Bengio &amp;amp; Hinton, 2015).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span数据 - 销售物空间=“ true”&gt;感知算法是最早，最具影响力的机器学习模型之一，为现代神经网络和支持向量机（SVMS）构成了基础。弗兰克·罗森布拉特（Frank Rosenblatt）于1958年提出的知名度（Rosenblatt，1958年），是一个简单而功能强大的线性分类器，专为二进制分类任务而设计。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;尽管它很简单，但感知到了当今机器学习仍然至关重要的关键概念，例如迭代权重更新，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data data-proserver spaces = “ true”&gt;使用&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;激活功能，并学习决策边界（Goodfellow，Bengio＆Courville，2016年）。这些想法直接影响了&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =的发展“&gt;多层神经网络&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;通过引入基础的重量调整规则反向传播（Lecun，Bengio＆Hinton，2015年）。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Simplify Your Compliance With Google Cloud Assured Workloads】简化您遵守Google Cloud保证的工作负载</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-compliance-using-google-assured-workloads</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;To navigate the complex world of cloud compliance, Google Cloud provides a tool,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;Google Cloud Assured Workloads&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;that helps organizations create a secure and compliant environment to run their workloads in Google Cloud.&lt;/span&gt; It helps organizations enforce strict data residency controls that restrict the resources to run only in specific Google Cloud Regions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assured Workloads Monitoring and Auditing&lt;/strong&gt; helps organizations identify compliance policy violations in the Google Cloud environment. Additionally, &lt;strong&gt;Assured Support&lt;/strong&gt; gives organizations control over their support experience. Organizations can decide who can access their data and restrict support personnel’s data access based on their location.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span style =“背景色：透明;”&gt;要浏览云合规性的复杂世界，Google Cloud提供了一个工具，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong style =“ backendbart-color：pransparent;”&gt; google cloud确保工作负载&lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;span style =“ background-color：透明;”&gt;可帮助组织创建一个安全且合规的环境，以在Google Cloud中运行其工作负载。&lt;/span&gt;它可以帮助组织执行严格的数据居住控制限制资源仅在特定的Google云区域运行的资源。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;确保工作负载监视和审计&lt;/strong&gt;帮助组织在Google云环境中确定违反合规性策略。此外，&lt;strong&gt;保证的支持&lt;/strong&gt;使组织控制其支持经验。组织可以决定谁可以访问其数据并根据其位置限制支持人员的数据访问。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Use Azure Cosmos DB as a Docker Container in CI/CD Pipelines】在CI/CD管道中使用Azure Cosmos DB作为Docker容器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/use-azure-cosmos-db-as-a-docker-container-in-cicd</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;There are many benefits to using Docker containers in CI/CD pipelines, especially for stateful systems like databases. For example, when you run integration tests, each CI job can start the database in an isolated container with a clean state, preventing conflicts between tests. This results in a testing environment that is reliable, consistent, and cost-effective. This approach also reduces latency and improves the overall performance of the CI/CD pipeline because the database is locally accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.microsoft.com/azure/cosmos-db/emulator-linux&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Linux-based Azure Cosmos DB emulator&lt;/a&gt; is available as a Docker container and can run on a variety of platforms, including ARM64 architectures like Apple Silicon. It allows local development and testing of applications without needing an Azure subscription or incurring service costs. You can easily run it as a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-run-docker-container-on-your-local-machine&#34;&gt;Docker container&lt;/a&gt; and use it for local development and testing:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在CI/CD管道中使用Docker容器有很多好处，尤其是对于数据库等状态系统。例如，当您运行集成测试时，每个CI作业都可以在具有干净状态的孤立容器中启动数据库，从而防止测试之间的冲突。这导致可靠，一致且具有成本效益的测试环境。这种方法还可以减少延迟，并改善CI/CD管道的整体性能，因为数据库可在本地访问。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://learn.microsoft.com/azure/cosmos-db/emulator-linux” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; linux azure azure azure cosmos cosmos cosmos db emulator db emulator &lt;/ A&gt;可作为Docker容器可用，可以在各种平台上运行，包括Arm64架构等Apple Silicon。它允许对应用程序进行本地开发和测试，而无需订阅Azure订阅或出现服务成本。您可以轻松地将其作为&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-to-run-docker-container-on-your-local-machine”&gt; docker容器&lt;/a&gt;用于本地开发和测试：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>