<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Online Developer Tools a Backdoor to Security Threat】在线开发人员工具是安全威胁的后门</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/online-developer-tools-security-risks</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-content=&#34;ai-message&#34; data-tabster=&#34;{&amp;quot;groupper&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;tabbability&amp;quot;:2},&amp;quot;focusable&amp;quot;:{}}&#34; tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2&gt;Free Online Utilities May Not Be Safe&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;Using online developer utilities, such as a JSON Viewer, can be incredibly convenient for parsing and visualizing JSON data, but they also come with significant risks. The tool, for instance, often requires users to upload JSON files or paste sensitive data directly into the tool. If the utility operates online without robust security measures, this data could be intercepted or stored without the user&#39;s knowledge, potentially exposing confidential information such as API keys, user credentials, or proprietary business logic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;One major concern is the lack of transparency in how some online tools handle uploaded data. For example, if the JSON Viewer utility does not explicitly state that it deletes data after processing, there is a risk that the data could be retained on the server, making it vulnerable to breaches. Additionally, if the tool is hosted on an unsecured or compromised website, attackers could exploit it to inject malicious scripts or steal data.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-content =“ ai-message” data-tabster =“ {” {“ groupper”：{“ tabbability”：2}，“ focusable”：{}}“ tabindex =“ 0”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2&gt;免费在线公用事业可能不安全&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;使用在线开发人员实用程序（例如JSON查看器）对于解析和可视化JSON数据可能非常方便，但它们也具有很大的风险。例如，该工具通常要求用户将JSON文件或将敏感数据直接上传到工具中。如果该公用事业公司在未经强大的安全措施的情况下在线运行，则可以在没有用户知识的情况下截获或存储此数据，可能会揭示机密信息，例如API键，用户凭据或专有业务逻辑。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;一个主要问题是某些在线工具如何处理上传数据的方式缺乏透明度。例如，如果JSON Viewer实用程序没有明确声明其处理后删除数据，则可能会保留数据在服务器上，从而使其容易遭受破坏。此外，如果该工具托管在无抵押或妥协的网站上，则攻击者可以利用其注入恶意脚本或窃取数据。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Bare Metal Bet That Made Our Multiplayer Platform Hum】使我们的多人平台嗡嗡作响的裸金属赌注</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/bare-metal-hybrid-multiplayer-infrastructure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The cloud may be fast…but it nearly slowed us down.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When we launched Hathora in 2022, we knew the infrastructure behind multiplayer games was long overdue for reinvention. Studios like EA and Blizzard had built their own complex systems to host game servers, but for most multiplayer game studios, that approach was out of reach. Our goal was to eliminate the barrier with a platform-as-a-service built specifically for multiplayer game workloads (low-latency, stateful servers ready to handle millions of connections without the overhead of managing infrastructure).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;云可能很快……但是它几乎使我们放慢了脚步。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们在2022年推出Hathora时，我们知道多人游戏背后的基础设施早就应该重塑了。 EA和Blizzard等工作室已经建立了自己的复杂系统来托管游戏服务器，但是对于大多数多人游戏工作室来说，这种方法是遥不可及的。我们的目标是通过专门为多人游戏工作负载构建的平台即服务（低延迟，状态服务器，准备处理数百万个连接而无需管理基础架构的开销）。&lt;/p&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;）。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Apache Spark With Drools: A Loan Approval Demo】将Apache Spark与流口水集成：贷款批准演示</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-apache-spark-drools-loan-approval-demo</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Near real-time decision-making systems are critical for modern business applications. Integrating &lt;strong data-end=&#34;414&#34; data-start=&#34;398&#34;&gt;Apache Spark (Streaming)&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong data-end=&#34;429&#34; data-start=&#34;419&#34;&gt;Drools&lt;/strong&gt; provides scalability and flexibility, enabling efficient handling of rule-based decision-making at scale. This article showcases their integration through a loan approval system, demonstrating its architecture, implementation, and advantages. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Problem Statement&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Applying numerous rules using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/writing-a-scalaspark-udf-options-to-consider&#34;&gt;Spark user-defined functions&lt;/a&gt; (UDFs) can become complex and hard to maintain due to extensive if-else logic.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;接近实时的决策系统对于现代业务应用至关重要。集成&lt;strong data-end =“ 414” data-start =“ 398”&gt; apache spark（streaming）&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong data-end =“ 429” data-start =“ 419”&gt; drools &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;提供可伸缩性和灵活性，可以在规模上有效地基于规则的决策。本文通过贷款批准制度展示了它们的集成，展示了其架构，实施和优势。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;问题语句&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/writing-a-scalaspark-udf-options-consider-to-consider”&gt; Spark用户 -  defined函数&lt;/a&gt;（udfs）可能变得复杂，并且由于扩大的IF-else logic logiCIC。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Accessibility in Web Development: A Developer’s Guide】掌握Web开发中的可访问性：开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dev-guide-to-mastering-accessibility-in-web-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Accessibility (a11y) is not just a feature—it’s a necessity. According to the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;World Health Organization (WHO)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;, more than 1 billion people globally have some form of disability. Ensuring that digital experiences are accessible allows everyone to use and benefit from web applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Despite its importance, many developers overlook accessibility due to a lack of awareness or perceived complexity. In this article, we’ll break down&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;key accessibility concepts, common issues, and best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;with practical examples, ensuring your web applications are&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;inclusive and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/importance-of-web-accessibility&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;WCAG-compliant&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt; &lt;span数据 - 列表空间=“ true”&gt;简介&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;可访问性（A11Y）不仅是一个功能，而且是必要的。根据&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;世界卫生组织（WHO）&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span data-pleserver spaces =“ true”&gt;，全球超过10亿人具有某种形式的残疾。确保可访问数字体验使每个人都可以从Web应用程序中使用和受益。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span数据范围=“ true”&gt;尽管其重要性，但由于缺乏意识或感知的复杂性，许多开发人员忽略了可访问性。在本文中，我们将分解&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span data data-proserver空间=“ true”&gt;关键可访问性概念，常见问题和最佳实践&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span data data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;使用实际示例，确保您的网络应用程序是&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span data data data data data data data pleserver past &lt;/ href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/importance-of-web-accosconible”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span data-preserver-spaces =“ true”&gt; wcag-compleiant &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/stand&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span data data data-proserver spaces = &lt;/stance-proserver spaces = &lt;/spas =“ true”&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Code to Customer: Building Fault-Tolerant Microservices With Observability in Mind】从代码到客户：构建耐故障的微服务，牢记可观察到</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fault-tolerant-microservices-with-observability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Microservices have become the go-to approach for building systems that need to scale efficiently and stay resilient under pressure. However, a microservices architecture comes with many potential points of failure—dozens or even hundreds of distributed components communicating over a network. To ensure your code makes it all the way to the customer without hiccups, you need to design for failure from the start. This is where fault tolerance and observability come in. By embracing Site Reliability Engineering (SRE) practices, developers can build microservices that not only survive failures but automatically detect and recover from them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, we’ll explore how to build fault-tolerant backend microservices on Kubernetes, integrating resilience patterns (retries, timeouts, circuit breakers, bulkheads, rate limiting, etc.) with robust observability, monitoring, and alerting. We’ll also compare these resilience strategies and provide practical examples—from Kubernetes health probes to alerting rules—to illustrate how to keep services reliable from code to customer.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;微服务已成为需要有效扩展并在压力下保持弹性的建筑系统的首选方法。但是，微服务体系结构带有许多潜在的故障点 - 通过网络通信的数百个甚至数百个分布式组件。为了确保您的代码在没有打ic的情况下一直向客户提供，您需要从一开始就设计故障。这是容忍度和可观察性出现的地方。通过采用站点可靠性工程（SRE）实践，开发人员可以建立微服务，这些微服务不仅可以在失败中幸存下来，而且可以自动检测并从中恢复。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨如何在kubernetes上构建容忍度的后端微服务，将弹性模式（恢复，超时，断路器，断路器，舱壁限制等）与强大的可观察性，监控性，监控性和警觉性相结合。我们还将比较这些弹性策略，并提供实用的例子，从Kubernetes健康调查到警报规则，以说明如何将服务从代码中可靠到客户。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How You Can Use Few-Shot Learning In LLM Prompting To Improve Its Performance】您如何在LLM中使用少量学习来提高其性能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-you-can-use-few-shot-learning-in-llm-prompting</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;You must’ve noticed that large language models can sometimes generate information that seems plausible but isn&#39;t factually accurate. Providing more explicit instructions and context is one of the key ways to reduce such LLM hallucinations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;515&#34; data-start=&#34;328&#34;&gt;That said, have you ever struggled to get an AI model to understand precisely what you want to achieve? Perhaps you&#39;ve provided detailed instructions only to receive outputs that fall short of the mark?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;您必须注意到，大型语言模型有时可以生成看起来合理但实际上准确的信息。提供更明确的说明和上下文是减少此类LLM幻觉的关键方法之一。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 515” data-start =“ 328”&gt;所说，您是否曾经努力获得AI模型来精确地了解您想要实现的目标？也许您提供的详细说明仅是为了接收未达到标记的输出？ &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Toward Indigenous AI: A Critical Analysis of BharatGen’s Role in Data Sovereignty and Language Equity】迈向土著AI：对Bharatgen在数据主权和语言权益中的作用的批判性分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/indigenous-ai-bharatgen-data-sovereignty-language</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-id=&#34;c786dc9f-66af-4b7e-8f3e-211f3bd61ad5&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;c786dc9f-66af-4b7e-8f3e-211f3bd61ad5&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This study critically examines BharatGen, a government-backed initiative to develop India’s foundational multimodal and multilingual &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Model (LLM)&lt;/a&gt;, as a transformative step towards indigenous &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/good-versus-evil-artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI)&lt;/a&gt;. In a landscape dominated by global LLMs, concerns over data sovereignty and underrepresentation of non-English languages have become increasingly salient. This study analyzes BharatGen’s role in addressing these issues by enhancing national control over digital data and promoting language equity across India’s diverse linguistic spectrum. This study explores BharatGen’s strategic significance in reducing dependence on external AI ecosystems, its alignment with India’s national AI policy objectives, and the challenges and opportunities associated with its deployment. Ultimately, this study argues that initiatives such as BharatGen are vital not only for technological self-reliance but also for preserving cultural identity and ensuring linguistic inclusivity in the evolving global AI ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-id=&#34;4d84afe8-0dfc-43dd-a54c-769ff6dd9d79&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keywords&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;4d84afe8-0dfc-43dd-a54c-769ff6dd9d79&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Indigenous AI, BharatGen, Data Sovereignty, Language Equity, Multilingual AI, Indian Language Technologies, Foundational Models, AI Policy in India, Digital Inclusion, Multimodal Language Models, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ethical-ai&#34;&gt;Ethical AI&lt;/a&gt;, AI for Low-Resource Languages, AI Localization, Sovereign AI Infrastructure, National AI Strategy&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-id =“ C786DC9F-66AF-4B7E-8F3E-211F3BD61AD5” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id =“ C786DC9F-66AF-4B7E-8F3E-211F3BD61AD5” style =“ Text-Align：left;”&gt;这项研究对Bharatgen进行了严格审查，该计划是政府支持的计划，旨在发展印度的基础和多语言和多语言&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-with-large-lange-language-models”&gt;大语言模型（LLM）&lt;/a&gt;，作为朝着迈向本地&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles-articles-articles-goood-versus-evil-evil-evil-ainterelligelligelligellignection-a href =”的变革一步。在以全球LLM为主导的景观中，对数据主权和非英语语言的代表性不足的担忧变得越来越突出。这项研究通过增强国家对数字数据的控制并促进印度多样化的语言范围的语言公平来分析Bharatgen在解决这些问题中的作用。这项研究探讨了Bharatgen在减少对外部AI生态系统的依赖，与印度国家AI政策目标的一致性以及与部署相关的挑战和机遇方面的战略意义。最终，这项研究认为，诸如Bharatgen之类的倡议不仅对技术自力更生至关重要，而且对于维护文化认同和确保在不断发展的全球AI生态系统中的语言包容性也至关重要。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-id =“ 4D84AFE8-0DFC-43DD-A54C-769FF6DD9D79” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;4d84afe8-0dfc-43dd-a54c-769ff6dd9d79&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Indigenous AI, BharatGen, Data Sovereignty, Language Equity, Multilingual AI, Indian Language Technologies, Foundational Models, AI Policy in India, Digital Inclusion, Multimodal Language Models, &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ethical-ai”&gt;道德AI &lt;/a&gt;，低资源语言的AI，AI本地化，主权AI基础设施，国家AI策略&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Defining Effective Microservice Boundaries - A Practical Approach To Avoiding The Most Common Mistakes】定义有效的微服务边界 - 一种避免最常见错误的实用方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/effective-microservice-boundaries-practical-tips</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Have you found yourself staring at an entire whiteboard filled with boxes and arrows, pondering whether this would become the next awesome microservices architecture or the worst distributed monolith that ever existed? Same here, and more often than I would like to admit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Last month, I was talking to one of my cofounder friends, and he mentioned, “We have 47 services!” with pride. Then two weeks later, I was going through their docs and found out that to deploy a simple feature, I need to make changes in six of their services. What I thought was their “microservices” architecture turned out to be a monolith split into pieces, with distribution complexity but no benefits whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您是否发现自己盯着整个装满盒子和箭头的白板，思考这是否会成为下一个令人敬畏的微服务架构还是存在的最糟糕的分布式整体？在这里一样，比我想承认的更多。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;上个月，我正在与我的一个联合创始人朋友交谈，他提到：“我们有47个服务！”自豪。然后两个星期后，我正在浏览他们的文档，发现要部署一个简单的功能，我需要对他们的六项服务进行更改。我认为他们的“微服务”架构被证明是一个整体分成部分，具有分配的复杂性，但没有任何好处。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kung Fu Code: Master Shifu Teaches Strategy Pattern to Po – The Functional Way】功夫代码：大师SHIFU向PO教授策略模式 - 功能方式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/functional-strategy-pattern-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&#34;There is no good or bad code. But how you write it… that makes all the difference.” - Master Shifu&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;723&#34; data-start=&#34;516&#34;&gt;The sun had just touched the tips of the Valley of Peace. Birds chirped, the wind whispered tales of warriors, and Po—the Dragon Warrior—was busy trying to &lt;strong data-end=&#34;696&#34; data-start=&#34;672&#34;&gt;write some Java code&lt;/strong&gt;. Yes, you read that right.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“没有好代码或坏代码。但是您如何编写它……这使一切都不同。” - 主shifu &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 723” data-start =“ 516”&gt;太阳刚刚触及了和平谷的尖端。鸟儿chi了，狂风的战士的故事，龙战士 - 忙于尝试&lt;strong data-end =“ 696” data-start =“ 672”&gt;写一些Java代码&lt;/strong&gt;。是的，您读了正确的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software Specs 2.0: Evolving Requirements for the AI Era (2025 Edition)】软件规格2.0：AI时代的不断发展的要求（2025 Edition）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-specs-ai-evolving-requirements</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Any form of data that we can use to make decisions for writing code, be it requirements, specifications, user stories, and the like, must have certain qualities. In agile development, for example, we have the INVEST qualities. More specifically, a user story must be Independent of all others and Negotiable, i.e., not a specific contract for features. It must be Valuable (or vertical) and &amp;nbsp;Estimable (to a good approximation). It must also be Small to fit within an iteration and Testable (in principle, even if there isn’t a test for it yet).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article goes beyond agile, waterfall, rapid application development, and the like. I will summarise a set of general and foundational qualities as a blueprint for software development.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们可以使用的任何形式的数据来制定编写代码的决策，无论是要求，规格，用户故事等，都必须具有某些素质。例如，在敏捷开发中，我们具有投资质量。更具体地说，用户故事必须独立于所有其他人，并且可以商标，即不是功能的特定合同。它必须是有价值的（或垂直），并且可以估计（近似值）。它也必须很小才能适合迭代和可测试（原则上，即使还没有测试）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文超越了敏捷，瀑布，快速应用开发等。我将以软件开发的蓝图进行总结。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>