<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Build AI Agents With MCP Server in C# and Run in VS Code】用C＃中的MCP服务器构建AI代理，并在VS代码中运行</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-ai-agents-csharp-mcp-server-vscode</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;497&#34; data-start=&#34;135&#34;&gt;Relatively newer &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-ai-agents-transform-automation-architecture?fromrel=true&#34;&gt;AI agents&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;based on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-large-language-models-and-how-they-work&#34;&gt;large language models&lt;/a&gt; (LLMs), such as GPT-4o, Claude, or Gemini, are very proficient at general reasoning and answering broad questions. However, they usually struggle with domain-specific queries—like “Give me only Dell devices information”—because they don’t have access to proprietary, internal, or organization-level data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;958&#34; data-start=&#34;499&#34;&gt;To answer these kinds of questions correctly, an LLM requires more than just a prompt: it needs contextual information made available through trusted internal sources. This article shows you how to build an AI agent that can access and use domain-specific context, thanks to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-custom-tools-model-context-protocol&#34;&gt;Model Context Protocol&lt;/a&gt; (MCP). It includes a code example of custom MCP Server creation and demonstrates how an MCP Host (in this case, VS Code) talks to the server and uses a Tool.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 497” data-start =“ 135”&gt;相对较新&lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/how-ai-ai-agents-transform-automation-automation-automation-automation-architectuct?fromrel = fromr = ai&gt; ai aigents &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-large-lange-models-models-models-and-how-they-work”&gt;大语言模型&lt;/a&gt;（llms），例如GPT-4O，Claude或Gemini，在一般的推理和回答广泛的问题上非常熟练。但是，他们通常会在特定领域的查询（例如“只给我戴尔设备信息”）中遇到困难，因为他们无法访问专有，内部或组织级别的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 958” data-start =“ 499”&gt;要正确回答这类问题，LLM不仅需要提示：它需要通过受信任的内部来源提供的上下文信息。本文向您展示了如何构建一个可以访问和使用特定域上下文的AI代理，这要归功于&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/building-custom-tools-tools-models-model-context-protocol”&gt; Model Contest Context协议&lt;/a&gt;（MCP）。它包括一个自定义MCP服务器创建的代码示例，并演示了MCP主机（在这种情况下为VS代码）如何与服务器进行交谈并使用工具。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Drift to Discipline: Operating Model for Regaining Enterprise Cloud Control】从漂移到纪律：重新恢复企业云控制的操作模型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/operating-model-cloud-control</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today’s biggest enterprise bets — AI, global scale, real-time everything — don’t just run on cloud infrastructure. &lt;a href=&#34;https://controlmonkey.io/blog/infrastructure-eats-strategy/&#34;&gt;They depend on it.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But most enterprise infrastructure &lt;a href=&#34;https://controlmonkey.io/resource/cloud-chaos/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;still operates in a state of reactive chaos&lt;/a&gt;. Cloud sprawl. Shadow resources. &lt;a href=&#34;https://thenewstack.io/developers-are-key-to-stopping-rising-api-security-threat/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Security risks hiding in plain sight&lt;/a&gt;. Infrastructure built on the best intentions… all held together by duct tape and drift.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;当今最大的企业投注 -  AI，全球范围，实时的一切 - 不仅在云基础架构上运行。 &lt;a href =“ https://controlmonkey.io/blog/infrastructure-eats-strategy/”&gt;他们依靠它。&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;但大多数企业基础架构&lt;a href =“ https://controlmonkey.io/resource/cloud-chaos/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt;仍处于反应性chaos &lt;/a&gt;的状态。云蔓延。影子资源。 &lt;a href =“ https://thenewstack.io/developers-are-key-to-stopping-rising-security-threat/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ _ blank”&gt;安全风险隐藏在普通的视线&lt;/a&gt;中。基础设施建立在最佳意图上……全部由胶带和漂移一起固定在一起。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Driven Threat Hunting: Catching Zero Day Exploits Before They Strike】AI驱动的威胁狩猎：在罢工之前捕获零一天的利用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-zero-day-threat-hunting</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Picture this: you&#39;re a cybersecurity pro up against an invisible enemy. Hidden in your network are &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-devsecops-can-combat-zero-day-threats&#34;&gt;zero-day exploits&lt;/a&gt;, which represent unknown vulnerabilities that await their moment to strike. The time you spend examining logs becomes pointless because the attack might already be causing harm. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-strategies-threat-hunting&#34;&gt;AI-driven threat hunting&lt;/a&gt; emerges as your most valuable new ally. &amp;nbsp;Your network receives a real-time protection system through AI, which functions like a super-intelligent guard dog that detects threats. The following article explains how AI detects hard-to-find threats while demonstrating its real-world impact and providing Python-based instructions to create your own threat-hunting tool. Buckle up, let’s go!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Why AI Matters in the Fight Against Zero Days&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Cybersecurity has come a long way from the days of simple virus scanners and static firewalls. Signature-based defenses were sufficient to detect known malware during the past era. Zero-day exploits operate as unpredictable threats that traditional security tools fail to detect. The technology sector saw Microsoft and &lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/threat-intelligence/2023-zero-day-trends&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Google rush to fix more than dozens of zero day vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; which attackers used in the wild during 2023. The consequences reach extreme levels because a single security breach results in major financial losses and immediate destruction of corporate reputation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;图片：您是一个网络安全专业人士，反对一个看不见的敌人。隐藏在您的网络中的是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-devsecops-can-can-combat-zero-day-day-tay-theats”&gt;零日漏洞利用&lt;/a&gt;，这代表了等待他们的时刻打击的未知漏洞。您花费检查日志的时间变得毫无意义，因为攻击可能已经造成伤害。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-strategies-trategies-threat-hunting”&gt; a-a-driend trient狩猎&lt;/a&gt;是您最有价值的新盟友。  您的网络通过AI接收实时保护系统，该系统的功能像检测威胁的超级智能护卫犬。以下文章解释了AI在展示其现实世界影响的同时如何检测到难以找到的威胁，并提供基于Python的指示来创建自己的威胁狩猎工具。系好，让我们走！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;为什么AI在与零天的战斗中很重要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;网络安全与简单病毒扫描仪和静态防火墙的时代已经走了很长一段路。在过去的时代，基于签名的防御能力足以检测已知的恶意软件。零日的利用是传统安全工具无法检测到的不可预测的威胁。 The technology sector saw Microsoft and &lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/threat-intelligence/2023-zero-day-trends&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Google rush to fix more than dozens of zero day vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt; which attackers used in the wild during 2023. The consequences reach extreme水平是因为单一的安全违规会导致重大财务损失和立即破坏公司声誉。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building AI Agents Capable of Exploring Contextual Data for Taking Action】构建能够探索上下文数据采取行动的AI代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-ai-agents-with-context</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence is on a rapid evolutionary track, and the once awe-inspiring conversational capabilities of ChatGPT raise very few eyebrows these days. AI developers are shifting into a higher gear, and these days, the focus is all about agents. They’re building more advanced AI systems that transform large language models into thinkers, decision-makers, and action-takers, which can automate many kinds of work.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;To create an AI agent, the developer must assign an LLM to a specific role, assign it a clear goal to accomplish, and provide access to the necessary resources for the agent to fulfill its mission. When AI agents are focused on a clearly defined objective and can utilise APIs, web browsers, search engines, and databases as humans do, they can autonomously determine how to perform the assigned task.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;人工智能正在快速进化，而曾经令人敬畏的Chatgpt对话能力如今引起了很少的眉毛。 AI开发人员正在转移到更高的齿轮上，如今，重点与代理有关。他们正在建立更先进的AI系统，该系统将大型语言模型转换为思想家，决策者和动作制作者，这些模型可以自动化许多类型的工作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;要创建AI代理，开发人员必须将LLM分配给特定角色，为其分配一个明确的目标，并为代理人履行其使命的必要资源提供了访问。当AI代理专注于明确定义的目标，并且可以像人类一样使用API，Web浏览器，搜索引擎和数据库，他们可以自主确定如何执行分配的任务。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Developing Secure REST API Using Spring Boot SSL Bundle Feature】使用Spring Boot SSL Bundle功能开发安全的REST API</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-secure-rest-api-ssl</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;300&#34; data-start=&#34;151&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/this-is-how-ssl-certificates-work-https-explained&#34;&gt;Secure Sockets Layer&lt;/a&gt; (SSL) is a key component in securing communication between systems, especially in layered or service-oriented architectures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;573&#34; data-start=&#34;302&#34;&gt;In such environments, a typical &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-h2-tutorial&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt; service might expose a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-restful-endpoints-a-step-by-step-guid&#34;&gt;REST endpoint&lt;/a&gt;, which is then consumed by another Spring Boot service acting as a client. When a host service exposes a secure endpoint, it must ensure that only authorized services are allowed to connect.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 300” data-start =“ 151”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/this-is-how-s-how-ssl-certificates-work-https-explated”&gt;安全插座层层&lt;/a&gt;（ssl）是确定系统之间的关键组件，尤其是在层次上架起的&lt;/a&gt;（ssl）。&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 573” data-start =“ 302”&gt;在这种环境中，典型的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/spring-h2-tutorial”&gt; spring boot &lt;/a&gt;服务可能会暴露于&lt;a a href = a href =“端点&lt;/a&gt;，然后由另一个充当客户的春季启动服务消费。当主机服务公开安全端点时，必须确保仅允许授权服务连接。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automation of IT Incident Reports Using Observability API and GenAI】使用可观察性API和Genai的IT事件报告的自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/interpreting-it-monitoring-alerts-with-ollama-on-premise</link>
      <description>【&lt;p align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;Recently, I was involved in automating the preparation of IT &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/incident-management-checklist&#34;&gt;incident reports&lt;/a&gt; by integrating monitoring solutions and generative AI. This post is to share my observations during this ongoing exercise. It outlines how to leverage the power of the AI service to interpret alerts generated by an observability solution (in this case, eG Enterprise Suite).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p align=&#34;left&#34;&gt;It utilized the Gemma AI model, running locally via Ollama for on-premise users, and the Llama-3.1 AI model with OpenAI for those with internet connectivity. The outcome of this exercise resulted in faster understanding of system issues and potential remediation steps. It automates the incident report creation by a Level 1 engineer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p align =“ left”&gt;最近，我参与了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/incident-management-checklist”&gt;事件报告&lt;/a&gt;通过集成监视解决方案和生成型AI的事件报告。这篇文章是在进行这次练习中分享我的观察结果。它概述了如何利用AI服务的功能来解释可观察性解决方案产生的警报（在这种情况下，例如企业套件）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p align =“ left”&gt;它利用了Gemma AI模型，通过Ollama在本地用户本地运行，而Llama-3.1 AI模型具有OpenAI的OpenAI，用于具有Internet连接的人。这项练习的结果使人们对系统问题和潜在的补救步骤有了更快的了解。它由1级工程师自动化事件报告创建。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How We Built a Smarter University Chatbot Using LLaMA2, AWS SageMaker, and RAG】我们如何使用Llama2，AWS Sagemaker和Rag构建更智能的大学聊天机器人</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/smarter-university-chatbot-llama2-rag-sagemaker</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Every semester, university IT helpdesks are overwhelmed by repetitive queries from students — from course registration deadlines to tuition fees and campus services. Most existing systems either rely on outdated FAQs or rigid bots that can&#39;t adapt to multiple languages or real-time updates. Recognizing this gap, we developed a smarter, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/chatbot-with-fastapi-and-google-cloud-translate&#34;&gt;multilingual chatbot&lt;/a&gt; using LLaMA2, AWS SageMaker, LangChain, and Milvus, built around a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-retrieval-augmented-generation&#34;&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) pipeline&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Need for Smarter Campus Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Higher education institutions face growing demands to modernize how students interact with campus services. Traditional IT support models don’t scale well — especially when students ask the same questions repeatedly. Even chatbots built on rule-based logic often fall short due to poor language handling, limited context awareness, and rigid workflows. By mid-semester, helpdesk queues are swamped, leading to delays and user frustration.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;每个学期，从课程注册截止日期到学费和校园服务的学生，大学的帮助演奏者不知所措。大多数现有系统要么依赖于无法适应多种语言或实时更新的过时常见问题解答或刚性机器人。认识到这一差距，我们开发了一个更聪明的人，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/chatbot-with-with-fastapi-and-google-and-google-cloud-translate”&gt;多语言chatbot &lt;/a&gt;使用llama2，aws ags sagemaker，langchain，and milvus，aws chatbot &lt;/a&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-retrieval-aigment-generated”&gt; reterieval-augmented Generation（rag）Pipeline &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;对智能校园支持的需求&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p Style =“ Text-Align：left;”&gt;高等教育机构面临着越来越多的需求，以使学生如何与校园服务互动。传统的IT支持模型不能很好地扩展 - 尤其是当学生反复问相同的问题时。甚至基于基于规则的逻辑的聊天机器人，由于语言处理糟糕，上下文意识和严格的工作流程，也常常缺乏。到学期中期，帮助台排队淹没了，导致延误和用户沮丧。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Expose IBM FS Cloud Container App to Public】如何将IBM FS Cloud Container应用程序展示到公共</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-expose-ibm-fs-cloud-container-app-to-public</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;352&#34; data-start=&#34;198&#34;&gt;Are you looking for a way to expose your containerized applications to the internet without breaking compliance with IBM Cloud for Financial Services?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;660&#34; data-start=&#34;354&#34;&gt;This guide walks through how to do just that. It shows how to securely expose your apps using the IBM Cloud Framework for Financial Services, with a focus on the IBM Cloud Private Path Service. This service helps you route external traffic to private clusters over secure, compliant VPC-to-VPC connections.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 352” data-start =“ 198”&gt;您是否正在寻找一种将您的容器化应用程序曝光到Internet而不破坏IBM Cloud的金融服务的方法？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 660” data-start =“ 354”&gt;本指南将介绍如何做到这一点。它显示了如何使用IBM云框架为金融服务安全地曝光您的应用程序，重点是IBM Cloud私人路径服务。此服务可帮助您通过安全的，符合安全的VPC-to-VPC连接将外部流量与私人群集路由。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Practical Steps to Secure the Software Supply Chain End to End】确保软件供应链端到头的实际步骤</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/practical-steps-secure-software-supply-chain</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-security-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Software Supply Chain Security: Enhancing Trust and Resilience Across the Software Development Lifecycle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The software supply chain has rapidly evolved into a critical vulnerability point and primary target for malicious actors. As we progress in 2025, organizations face an increasingly complex and dynamic threat landscape. This article offers a practical checklist for securing the software supply chain and clarifies the pivotal role of zero trust.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ font-size：17px;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;编辑注：以下是为Dzone的2025年2025年趋势报告编写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/link/link/link/link/2025-security-contribity-contributor-contributor-artilecutor-article- sepusence”增强软件开发生命周期的信任和韧性&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;软件供应链已迅速发展为恶意参与者的关键漏洞和主要目标。随着我们在2025年的发展，组织面临越来越复杂和动态的威胁格局。本文提供了一个实用的清单，用于确保软件供应链并阐明零信任的关键作用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Burn that List: Smarter Use of Allowlists and Denylists in Multi-Tenant Systems】刻录该列表：在多租户系统中更明智地使用允许清单和否定者</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/allowlist-denylist-access-control</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-essential-guide-to-multi-tenant-architecture&#34;&gt;multi-tenant systems&lt;/a&gt;—whether you&#39;re managing an API gateway, identity platform, or SaaS product—access control is essential. Two of the most widely used tools for managing that access are &lt;code&gt;allowlists&amp;nbsp;&lt;/code&gt;and &lt;code&gt;denylists&lt;/code&gt;. These mechanisms define who or what is permitted or rejected, helping isolate tenants, control risk, and enforce trust boundaries. But despite their simplicity, both lists can easily become operational liabilities if not carefully managed. This article explores real-world examples of &lt;code&gt;allowlists&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;denylists&lt;/code&gt;, how to store and govern them, and why every list needs a plan to die.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Are Allowlists and Denylists?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An &lt;code&gt;allowlist&lt;/code&gt; is a list of explicitly approved entities—users, IPs, tenants, apps, or domains—that are permitted to access a resource. Everything else is denied by default. A &lt;strong&gt;denylist&lt;/strong&gt; is the opposite: a list of explicitly blocked entities; everything else is allowed. In simple terms, &lt;code&gt;allowlists&lt;/code&gt; implement &lt;em&gt;default-deny&lt;/em&gt; behavior, while &lt;code&gt;denylists&lt;/code&gt; implement &lt;em&gt;default-allow&lt;/em&gt; with overrides. Choosing between them depends on the nature of what you&#39;re protecting, how dynamic your environment is, and how clearly you can define trust.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; in &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-sentential-guide-to-multi-tenant-architecture”&gt;多转移系统&lt;/a&gt;  - 无论您管理一个API网关，身份平台或SaaS产品还是SaaS产品，ACCESS控制都是必不可少的。管理访问的两个最广泛使用的工具是&lt;code&gt;允许列表&lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt; denylists &lt;/code&gt;。这些机制定义了允许或拒绝的是谁，有助于隔离租户，控制风险并强制执行信任边界。但是，尽管它们很简单，但如果不仔细管理，这两个列表都可以轻松成为运营责任。本文探讨了&lt;code&gt;允许清单&lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt; denylists &lt;/code&gt;，如何存储和管理它们的现实世界示例，以及为什么每个列表都需要一个计划来死亡。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是允许名单和否认者？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;code&gt;允许列表&lt;/code&gt;是明确批准的实体的列表 - 用户，IPS，租户，应用程序或域，允许访问资源。默认情况下其他所有内容都被拒绝。 &lt;strong&gt;否定主义者&lt;/strong&gt;是相反的：明确阻止的实体列表；允许其他一切。简而言之，&lt;code&gt;允许列表&lt;/code&gt; enasal &lt;em&gt; default-deny &lt;/em&gt;行为，而&lt;code&gt; denylists &lt;/code&gt; instrument &lt;em&gt; dectault-allow-allow &lt;/em&gt;带有覆盖。在它们之间进行选择取决于您要保护的内容，环境的动态程度以及您如何清楚地定义信任。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>