<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring JSON Schema for Form Validation in Web Components】探索 Web 组件中表单验证的 JSON 模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/json-schema-for-form-validation-in-web-components</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the realm of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/revolutionizing-the-web-emerging-trends-and-innova&#34;&gt;modern web development&lt;/a&gt;, ensuring data integrity and user experience is paramount. JSON Schema has emerged as a powerful tool for validating the structure of JSON data, providing developers with a standardized approach to data validation, documentation, and extensibility. When combined with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/introduction-to-web-components-and-polymer&#34;&gt;Web Components&lt;/a&gt;, JSON Schema becomes an even more potent solution for form validation, offering a modular, reusable, and maintainable approach to UI development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article will walk you through the process of integrating JSON Schema validation into a custom Web Component, using a contact form as our example.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/revolutionizing-the-web-emerging-trends-and-innova&#34;&gt;现代网络开发领域&lt;/a&gt;，确保数据完整性和用户体验至关重要。 JSON Schema 已成为验证 JSON 数据结构的强大工具，为开发人员提供了数据验证、文档记录和可扩展性的标准化方法。当与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/introduction-to-web-components-and-polymer&#34;&gt;Web 组件&lt;/a&gt;结合使用时，JSON Schema 成为表单验证的更有效的解决方案，提供模块化、可重用且可维护的 UI 开发方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文将引导您完成将 JSON 架构验证集成到自定义 Web 组件中的过程，并使用联系表单作为示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Chat With Your Code: Conversational AI That Understands Your Codebase】与您的代码聊天：理解您的代码库的对话式 AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/conversational-ai-that-understands-your-codebase</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Imagine having a tool that understands your code and can answer your questions, provide insights, and even help debug issues — all through natural language queries. In this article, we’ll walk you through the process of creating a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/evolution-of-conversational-ai&#34;&gt;conversational AI&lt;/a&gt; that allows you to talk to your code using Chainlit, Qdrant, and OpenAI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of Conversational AI for Codebases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Streamlined &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-code-review-amp-how-it-can-save-time-devel&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;code review&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Quickly review specific code modules and understand their context without spending time digging through the files.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Efficient debugging:&lt;/strong&gt; Ask questions about potential issues in the code and get targeted responses, which helps reduce the time spent on troubleshooting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced learning:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;New team members can learn about how different components in the code work without having to pair with existing experts in the code.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved documentation:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Summarizing using AI would help generate explanations for complex code, making it easier to enhance documentation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now let us look at how we made that happen.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;想象一下，有一个工具可以理解您的代码，可以回答您的问题，提供见解，甚至帮助调试问题 - 所有这些都通过自然语言查询进行。在本文中，我们将引导您完成创建允许您交谈的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/evolution-of-conversational-ai&#34;&gt;对话式 AI&lt;/a&gt; 的过程使用 Chainlit、Qdrant 和 OpenAI 编写您的代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;对话式 AI 对代码库的好处&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简化&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-code-review-amp-how-it-can-save-time-devel&#34;&gt;&lt; strong&gt;代码审查&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;：&lt;/strong&gt;快速审查特定代码模块并了解其上下文，而无需花时间挖掘文件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高效调试&lt;/strong&gt;：询问有关代码中潜在问题的问题并获得有针对性的答复，这有助于减少故障排除所花费的时间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;强化学习：&lt;/strong&gt;新团队成员可以了解代码中不同组件的工作原理，而无需与代码中的现有专家配对。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;改进文档：&lt;/strong&gt;使用 AI 进行总结有助于生成复杂代码的解释，从而更轻松地增强文档。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在让我们看看我们是如何实现这一目标的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhance Your Communication Strategy: Deliver Multimedia Messages With AWS Pinpoint】增强您的沟通策略：使用 AWS Pinpoint 传递多媒体消息</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sending-multimedia-messages-using-aws-pinpoint</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s digital world, email is the go-to channel for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rest-vs-messaging-for-microservices&#34;&gt;effective communication&lt;/a&gt;, with attachments containing flyers, images, PDF documents, etc. However, there could be business requirements for building a service for sending an SMS with an attachment as an MMS (Multimedia Messaging Service). This article delves into how to send multiple media messages (MMS), their limitations, and implementation details using the AWS Pinpoint cloud service. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Setting Up AWS Pinpoint Service&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Setting Up Phone Pool&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the AWS console, we navigate to AWS End User Messaging and set up the Phone pool. The phone pool comprises the phone numbers from which we will send the message; these are the numbers from which the end user will receive the MMS message. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的数字世界中，电子邮件是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rest-vs-messaging-for-microservices&#34;&gt;有效沟通&lt;/a&gt;的首选渠道，包含传单、图像、PDF 文档等的附件。但是，可能存在构建服务以将带有附件的 SMS 作为 MMS（多媒体消息服务）发送的服务的业务需求。本文深入探讨如何使用 AWS Pinpoint 云服务发送多条媒体消息 (MMS)、其限制以及实施细节。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;设置 AWS Pinpoint 服务&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;设置电话池&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 AWS 控制台中，我们导航到 AWS End User Messaging 并设置电话池。电话池包含我们将发送消息的电话号码；最终用户将从这些号码接收彩信。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advance Traffic Management in Canary Using Istio, Argo Rollouts, and HPA】使用 Istio、Argo 部署和 HPA 推进 Canary 流量管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advance-traffic-management-in-canary</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As enterprises mature in their CI/CD journey, they tend to ship code faster, safely, and securely. One essential strategy the DevOps team applies is releasing code progressively to production, also known as canary deployment. Canary deployment is a bulletproof mechanism that safely releases application changes and provides flexibility for business experiments. It can be implemented using open-source software like &lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/argo-rollouts/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.flagger.app/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Flagger&lt;/a&gt;. However, advanced DevOps teams want to gain granular control over their traffic and pod scaling while performing canary deployment to reduce overall costs. Many enterprises achieve advanced traffic management of canary deployment at scale using open-source Istio service mesh. We want to share our knowledge with the DevOps community through this blog.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Before we get started, let us discuss the canary architecture implemented by Argo Rollouts and Istio.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着企业在 CI/CD 之旅中日趋成熟，他们倾向于更快、更安全地交付代码。 DevOps 团队应用的一项基本策略是将代码逐步发布到生产环境，也称为金丝雀部署。金丝雀部署是一种防弹机制，可以安全地发布应用程序变更，并为业务实验提供灵活性。它可以使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://argoproj.github.io/argo-rollouts/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Argo Rollouts&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt; a href=&#34;https://docs.flaagger.app/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Flagger&lt;/a&gt;。然而，高级 DevOps 团队希望在执行金丝雀部署时获得对其流量和 Pod 扩展的精细控制，以降低总体成本。许多企业使用开源 Istio 服务网格实现大规模金丝雀部署的高级流量管理。我们希望通过此博客与 DevOps 社区分享我们的知识。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在开始之前，我们先讨论一下 Argo Rollouts 和 Istio 实现的金丝雀架构。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating Effective Exceptions in Java Code [Video]】在 Java 代码中创建有效的异常 [视频]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-effective-exceptions-in-java-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;3&#34; data-line-start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;This article will explore the critical topic of creating effective &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-exceptions-1&#34;&gt;exceptions&lt;/a&gt; in your &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; code. Exceptions are crucial in identifying when something goes wrong during code execution. They are instrumental in managing data inconsistency and business validation errors. We will outline three key steps for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-properly-use-exceptions-in-java&#34;&gt;writing effective exceptions in your Java code&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;5&#34; data-line-start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;Writing and Defining an Exception Hierarchy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;6&#34; data-line-start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;Creating a Trackable Exception Message&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;8&#34; data-line-start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;Avoiding Security Problems with Exceptions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-line-end=&#34;9&#34; data-line-start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;1. Writing and Defining an Exception Hierarchy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;11&#34; data-line-start=&#34;10&#34;&gt;Define the exception hierarchy as the first step in your design process. By considering the domain, you can begin with more general exceptions and then move towards more specific ones. This approach enables you to trace issues using the hierarchy tree or exception names.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;3&#34; data-line-start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;本文将探讨创建有效的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-exceptions- 1&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 代码中的异常&lt;/a&gt;。异常对于识别代码执行过程中何时出现错误至关重要。它们有助于管理数据不一致和业务验证错误。我们将概述&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-properly-use-exceptions-in-java&#34;&gt;在 Java 代码中编写有效的异常&lt;/a&gt;的三个关键步骤。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;5&#34; data-line-start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;编写和定义异常层次结构&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;6&#34; data-line-start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;创建可跟踪的异常消息&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;8&#34; data-line-start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;避免出现异常的安全问题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-line-end=&#34;9&#34; data-line-start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;1.编写和定义异常层次结构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;11&#34; data-line-start=&#34;10&#34;&gt;定义异常层次结构作为设计过程的第一步。通过考虑领域，您可以从更一般的例外开始，然后转向更具体的例外。这种方法使您能够使用层次结构树或异常名称来跟踪问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking the Potential of Synthetic Data for AI Development】释放合成数据在人工智能开发中的潜力</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/synthetic-data-for-ai-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;84c4&#34;&gt;Data is the bane of existence for AI models, and the accuracy and effectiveness of the AI systems significantly depend upon the completeness of the data used during the training. Although real data undoubtedly makes AI systems more effective, there are certain challenges, as the real data can be imbalanced, biased, or incomplete.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;5873&#34;&gt;Hence, to cope with the &lt;a data-href=&#34;https://stagezero.ai/blog/real-world-versus-synthetic-data-ai-model-training/&#34; href=&#34;https://stagezero.ai/blog/real-world-versus-synthetic-data-ai-model-training/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;shortages in real data&lt;/a&gt;, data scientists have to source synthetic data. Synthetic data is considerably more inexpensive than real data, but there are still some challenges, like ensuring demographic diversity, reliability, and sufficient volume accumulation, which data scientists must mitigate.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;84c4&#34;&gt;数据是 AI 模型存在的祸根，AI 系统的准确性和有效性在很大程度上取决于训练期间使用的数据的完整性。尽管真实数据无疑使人工智能系统更加有效，但也存在一定的挑战，因为真实数据可能不平衡、有偏见或不完整。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;5873&#34;&gt;因此，为了应对&lt;a data-href=&#34;https://stagezero.ai/blog/real-world-versus-synthetic-data-ai-model-training/&#34; href= “https://stagezero.ai/blog/real-world-versus-synthetic-data-ai-model-training/” rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;真实数据短缺&lt;/a&gt;，数据科学家必须获取合成数据。合成数据比真实数据便宜得多，但仍然存在一些挑战，例如确保人口多样性、可靠性和足够的数据量积累，数据科学家必须应对这些挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Safeguarding Democracy in the Digital Age: Insights from Day 1 at Black Hat 2024 and Las Vegas Officials】维护数字时代的民主：Black Hat 2024 和拉斯维加斯官员第一天的见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/safeguarding-democracy-in-the-digital-age-insights</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In an era where technology and geopolitics intersect more than ever before, the importance of cybersecurity in maintaining democratic processes cannot be overstated. At Black Hat 2024, global leaders and local officials converged to discuss the challenges and strategies for protecting elections, critical infrastructure, and the very foundations of democracy. This article delves into the insights shared at the conference, offering developers, engineers, and architects a comprehensive view of the cybersecurity landscape and its implications for democratic societies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Changing Landscape of Global Threats&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Jeff Moss, founder of Black Hat, set the stage by highlighting the rapid evolution of the threat landscape. &#34;Things are different now,&#34; Moss observed. &#34;Things have sped up. You have all the routine problems and a giant bucket of other problems, you have all these risks you didn&#39;t think about.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在一个技术和地缘政治比以往任何时候都更加交叉的时代，网络安全在维持民主进程方面的重要性怎么强调也不为过。在 Black Hat 2024 上，全球领导人和地方官员齐聚一堂，讨论保护选举、关键基础设施和民主基础的挑战和战略。本文深入探讨了会议上分享的见解，为开发人员、工程师和架构师提供了网络安全格局及其对民主社会影响的全面看法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;全球威胁的变化&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Black Hat 创始人 Jeff Moss 通过强调威胁形势的快速演变奠定了基础。 “现在情况不同了，”莫斯观察到。 “事情已经加速了。你遇到了所有常规问题和一大堆其他问题，你遇到了所有这些你没有想到的风险。”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrate Spring With Open AI】将 Spring 与开放 AI 集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrate-spring-with-open-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will discuss in a practical and objective way the integration of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-framework-tutorial-for-beginners-2&#34;&gt;Spring framework&lt;/a&gt; with the resources of the OpenAI API, one of the main artificial intelligence products on the market.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The use of artificial intelligence resources is becoming increasingly necessary in several products, and therefore, presenting its application in a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; solution through the Spring framework allows a huge number of projects currently in production to benefit from this resource.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我将以实际客观的方式讨论&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-framework-tutorial-for-beginners-2&#34;&gt;Spring框架的集成&lt;/a&gt; 拥有市场上主要人工智能产品之一 OpenAI API 的资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能资源的使用在多种产品中变得越来越必要，因此，以 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 展示其应用程序通过 Spring 框架的解决方案允许当前生产中的大量项目从该资源中受益。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top 10 C# Keywords and Features】十大 C# 关键字和功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-10-c-keywords-and-features</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The language &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/csharp&#34;&gt;C#&lt;/a&gt; stands out as the top 5th programming language in a Stack Overflow survey. It is widely used for creating various applications, ranging from desktop to mobile to cloud native. With so many language keywords and features it will be taxing to developers to keep up to date with new feature releases. This article delves into the top 10 C# keywords every C# developer should know.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Async and Await&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keywords&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;code&gt;async&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;await&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The introduction of &lt;code&gt;async&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;await&lt;/code&gt; keywords in C# make it easy to handle &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/overview-of-c-async-programming-with-thread-pools&#34;&gt;asynchronous programming in C#&lt;/a&gt;. They allow you to write code that performs operations without blocking the main thread. This capability is particularly useful for tasks that are I/O-bound or CPU-intensive. By making use of these keywords, programmers can easily handle long-running compute operations like invoking external APIs to get data or writing or reading from a network drive. This will help in developing responsive applications and can handle concurrent operations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在 Stack Overflow 调查中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/csharp&#34;&gt;C#&lt;/a&gt; 语言脱颖而出，成为排名第五的编程语言。它广泛用于创建各种应用程序，从桌面到移动再到云原生。由于语言关键字和功能如此之多，开发人员要及时了解新功能的发布将是一项艰巨的任务。本文深入探讨了每个 C# 开发人员都应该知道的 10 个最重要的 C# 关键字。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1。异步和等待&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;关键字&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;code&gt;async&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;await&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;C# 中引入 &lt;code&gt;async&lt;/code&gt; 和 &lt;code&gt;await&lt;/code&gt; 关键字，可以轻松处理&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/overview-of- c-async-programming-with-thread-pools&#34;&gt;C# 中的异步编程&lt;/a&gt;。它们允许您编写执行操作而不阻塞主线程的代码。此功能对于 I/O 密集型或 CPU 密集型任务特别有用。通过使用这些关键字，程序员可以轻松处理长时间运行的计算操作，例如调用外部 API 来获取数据或从网络驱动器写入或读取。这将有助于开发响应式应用程序并可以处理并发操作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Essential Guidelines for Building Optimized ETL Data Pipelines in the Cloud With Azure Data Factory】使用 Azure 数据工厂在云中构建优化的 ETL 数据管道的基本指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-optimized-etl-pipelines-in-the-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When building &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolution-of-data-pipelines&#34;&gt;ETL data pipelines&lt;/a&gt; using Azure Data Factory (ADF) to process huge amounts of data from different sources, you may often run into performance and design-related challenges. This article will serve as a guide in building high-performance ETL pipelines that are both efficient and scalable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below are the major guidelines to consider when building optimized ETL data pipelines in ADF:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用 Azure 数据工厂 (ADF) 构建 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolution-of-data-pipelines&#34;&gt;ETL 数据管道&lt;/a&gt;以处理大量数据时由于数据来源不同，您可能经常会遇到性能和设计相关的挑战。本文将作为构建高效且可扩展的高性能 ETL 管道的指南。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是在 ADF 中构建优化的 ETL 数据管道时要考虑的主要准则：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>