<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How You Can Avoid a CrowdStrike Fiasco】如何避免 CrowdStrike 惨败</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-you-can-avoid-a-crowdstrike-fiasco</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;By now we&#39;ve all heard about &lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp; or been affected by &lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt; the CrowdStrike fiasco. If you haven&#39;t, here&#39;s a quick recap.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An update to the CrowdStrike Falcon platform, pushed on a Friday afternoon, caused computers to crash and be unbootable. The update was pushed to all customers at once, and the only way to recover was to boot into &#34;Safe Mode&#34; and uninstall the update. That often required direct physical access to the affected computer, making recovery times even longer.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;到目前为止，我们都听说过&lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt;或受到&lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt;CrowdStrike 惨败的影响。如果您还没有，这里有一个快速回顾。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;周五下午推出的 CrowdStrike Falcon 平台更新导致计算机崩溃且无法启动。该更新被立即推送给所有客户，唯一的恢复方法是启动到“安全模式”并卸载更新。这通常需要直接物理访问受影响的计算机，从而使恢复时间更长。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Semi-Supervised Learning: How To Overcome the Lack of Labels】半监督学习：如何克服标签的缺失</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/semi-supervised-learning-overcome-lack-of-labels</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;All successfully implemented machine learning models are backed by at least two strong components: data and model. In my discussions with ML engineers, I heard many times that, instead of spending a significant amount of time on data preparation, including labeling for supervised learning, they would rather spend their time on model development. When it comes to most problems, labeling huge amounts of data is way more difficult than obtaining it in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Unlabeled data fails to provide the desired accuracy during training, and labeling huge datasets for supervised learning can be time-consuming and expensive. What if the data labeling budget was limited? What data should be labeled first? These are just some of the daunting questions facing ML engineers who would rather be doing productive work instead.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;所有成功实施的机器学习模型都至少有两个强大的组件支持：数据和模型。在与 ML 工程师的讨论中，我多次听到，他们宁愿将时间花在模型开发上，而不是花大量时间在数据准备上，包括监督学习的标签。对于大多数问题，标记大量数据比首先获取数据要困难得多。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;未标记的数据无法在训练期间提供所需的准确性，并且为监督学习标记巨大的数据集可能既耗时又昂贵。如果数据标签预算有限怎么办？首先应该标记哪些数据？这些只是 ML 工程师面临的一些令人畏惧的问题，他们宁愿从事富有成效的工作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【10 Kubernetes Cost Optimization Techniques】10 种 Kubernetes 成本优化技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/10-kubernetes-cost-optimisation-techniques</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;These are 10 strategies for reducing Kubernetes costs. We’ve split them into pre-deployment, post-deployment, and ongoing cost optimization techniques to help people at the beginning and middle of their cloud journeys, as well as those who have fully adopted the cloud and are just looking for a few extra pointers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, let’s get started.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这是降低 Kubernetes 成本的 10 种策略。我们将它们分为部署前、部署后和持续成本优化技术，以帮助人们在云之旅的开始和中期，以及那些已经完全采用云但只是寻求一些额外的帮助的人指针。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那么，让我们开始吧。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SQL Interview Preparation Series: Mastering Questions and Answers Quickly】SQL面试准备系列：快速掌握问答</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sql-interview-preparation-series-part-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the lesson of our &#34;SQL Interview Preparation Series: Mastering Questions and Answers Quickly!&#34; Throughout this series, we aim to assist you in getting ready, for SQL interviews by delving into different topics. Today we&#39;re delving into the core variances between &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/nosql-vs-sql-learning-by-differentiating&#34;&gt;SQL and NoSQL&lt;/a&gt; databases, a subject for any data focused job interview.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding SQL and NoSQL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Relational databases, commonly referred to as &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-do-we-need-databases-and-sql&#34;&gt;SQL databases&lt;/a&gt;, are crafted to handle data. They adhere to a predefined schema, which makes them well-suited for situations where data integrity and consistency are crucial. On the other side, NoSQL databases offer flexibility and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/nosql-and-data-scalability-20&#34;&gt;scalability&lt;/a&gt; by managing data and adapting to dynamic rapidly changing information. They find usage in web applications and social media platforms.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;欢迎来到我们的《SQL面试准备系列：快速掌握问答》课程！在本系列中，我们旨在通过深入研究不同的主题来帮助您为 SQL 面试做好准备。今天，我们将深入研究 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/nosql-vs-sql-learning-by- Differentiating&#34;&gt;SQL 和 NoSQL&lt;/a&gt; 数据库之间的核心差异，这是一个主题任何以数据为中心的工作面试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;了解 SQL 和 NoSQL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;关系数据库通常称为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-do-we-need-databases-and-sql&#34;&gt;SQL 数据库&lt;/a&gt;，旨在处理数据。它们遵循预定义的模式，这使得它们非常适合数据完整性和一致性至关重要的情况。另一方面，NoSQL 数据库通过管理数据和适应动态快速变化来提供灵活性和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/nosql-and-data-scalability-20&#34;&gt;可扩展性&lt;/a&gt;信息。它们在网络应用程序和社交媒体平台中得到使用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introduction to Salesforce Batch Apex [Video]】Salesforce Batch Apex 简介 [视频]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/intro-to-salesforce-batch-apex-video</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/salesforce-application-design&#34;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/a&gt; Batch Apex is a powerful tool for handling large data volumes and complex data processing tasks asynchronously. This tutorial will walk you through the core concepts and practical applications of Batch Apex in Salesforce, including the structure of an Apex batch class, writing unit tests for batch classes, scheduling batch classes, running batch classes ad hoc for testing, and understanding Batch Apex limits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Structure of an Apex Batch Class&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;An Apex Batch class in Salesforce must implement the &lt;code&gt;Database.Batchable&lt;/code&gt; interface. This interface requires the implementation of three methods:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/salesforce-application-design&#34;&gt;Salesforce&lt;/a&gt; Batch Apex 是处理大数据的强大工具异步处理大量和复杂的数据处理任务。本教程将引导您了解 Batch Apex 在 Salesforce 中的核心概念和实际应用，包括 Apex 批处理类的结构、为批处理类编写单元测试、调度批处理类、临时运行批处理类进行测试以及了解 Batch Apex限制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Apex Batch 类的结构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Salesforce 中的 Apex Batch 类必须实现 &lt;code&gt;Database.Batchable&lt;/code&gt; 接口。该接口需要实现三个方法：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Agile Product Development With AI and LLMs】利用人工智能和法学硕士加强敏捷产品开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-agile-product-development-with-ai-and-llms</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;During my 10+ years of experience in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-agile-methodology-dzone&#34;&gt;Agile product development&lt;/a&gt;, I have seen the difficulties of meeting the rapid requirements of the digital market. Manual procedures can slow down highly flexible software engineering and delivery teams, resulting in missed chances and postponed launches.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;With AI and Large Language Models (LLMs) becoming more prevalent, we are on the verge of a major change. Gartner points out a 25% increase in project success rates for those using predictive analytics (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/insights/predictive-analytics&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_new&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-03-16-gartner-identifies-top-10-data-and-analytics-technologies-trends-for-2021&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Gartner, 2021)&lt;/a&gt;. These technologies are changing the way agile product development is optimized - by automating tasks, improving decision-making, and forecasting future trends. As stated in a report from McKinsey, companies using AI experience a 20% decrease in project costs (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/quantumblack/our-insights/the-state-of-ai-in-2023-generative-ais-breakout-year&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;McKinsey &amp;amp; Company, 2023&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在我 10 多年的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-agile-methodology-dzone&#34;&gt;敏捷产品开发经验中&lt;/a&gt;，我看到了满足数字市场快速需求的困难。手动过程可能会减慢高度灵活的软件工程和交付团队的速度，从而导致错失机会和推迟发布。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;随着人工智能和大型语言模型 (LLM) 变得越来越普遍，我们正处于重大变革的边缘。 Gartner 指出，使用预测分析的项目成功率提高了 25% (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/insights/predictive-analytics&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_new&#34; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-03-16-gartner-identizes-top-10-data-and-analytics-technologies- 2021 年趋势”rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Gartner，2021 年）&lt;/a&gt;。这些技术正在改变敏捷产品开发的优化方式——通过自动化任务、改进决策和预测未来趋势。正如麦肯锡的一份报告所述，使用人工智能的公司的项目成本降低了 20% -in-2023-generative-ais-breakout-year&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;麦肯锡公司，2023&lt;/a&gt;)。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Java Application Logging: A Comprehensive Guide】增强 Java 应用程序日志记录：综合指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-java-application-logging</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;3&#34; data-line-start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/structured-logging-2&#34;&gt;Logging&lt;/a&gt; is crucial for monitoring and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-debug-remote-java-applicat&#34;&gt;debugging Java applications&lt;/a&gt;, particularly in production environments. It provides valuable insights into application behavior, aids in issue diagnosis, and ensures smooth operation. This article will walk you through creating effective logs in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; applications, emphasizing three key aspects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;5&#34; data-line-start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;Logging Good Information&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;6&#34; data-line-start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;Creating Trackable Logs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;8&#34; data-line-start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;Ensuring Security and Avoiding Data Breaches&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;9&#34; data-line-start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;We will use the &lt;code&gt;java.util.logging&lt;/code&gt; package for demonstration, but these principles apply to any logging framework.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;3&#34; data-line-start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/structed-logging-2&#34;&gt;日志记录&lt;/a&gt;至关重要用于监视和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-debug-remote-java-applicat&#34;&gt;调试 Java 应用程序&lt;/a&gt;，特别是在生产环境中。它提供了有关应用程序行为的宝贵见解，有助于问题诊断并确保平稳运行。本文将引导您在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 应用程序中创建有效的日志，强调三个关键方面。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;5&#34; data-line-start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;记录有用信息&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;6&#34; data-line-start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;创建可跟踪日志&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-line-end=&#34;8&#34; data-line-start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;确保安全并避免数据泄露&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;9&#34; data-line-start=&#34;8&#34;&gt;我们将使用 &lt;code&gt;java.util.logging&lt;/code&gt; 包进行演示，但这些原则适用于任何日志记录框架。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 12:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker vs. Podman: Exploring Container Technologies for Modern Web Development】Docker 与 Podman：探索现代 Web 开发的容器技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-vs-podman-exploring-container-technologies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Among the most often used containerizing technologies in the realm of software development are Docker and Podman. Examining their use cases, benefits, and limitations, this article offers a thorough comparison of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docker.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://podman.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Podman&lt;/a&gt;. We will also go over useful cases of deploying web apps utilizing both technologies, stressing important commands and factors for producing container images.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/what-is/containerization/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Containerization&lt;/a&gt; has become an essential technique for creating, transporting, and executing applications with unmatched uniformity across various computer environments. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker,&lt;/a&gt; a pioneer in this field, has transformed software development techniques by introducing developers to the capabilities and adaptability of containers. This technology employs containerization to package an application and all its necessary components into a self-contained entity. This provides consistent functionality regardless of variations in development, staging, and production environments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;软件开发领域最常用的容器化技术是 Docker 和 Podman。本文通过检查它们的用例、优点和局限性，对 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docker.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; 进行了全面比较和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://podman.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Podman&lt;/a&gt;。我们还将回顾利用这两种技术部署 Web 应用程序的有用案例，强调生成容器映像的重要命令和因素。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/what-is/containerization/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;容器化&lt;/a&gt;已成为创建、在各种计算机环境中以无与伦比的一致性传输和执行应用程序。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker 是该领域的先驱&lt;/a&gt;，它通过向开发人员介绍功能和功能，改变了软件开发技术。容器的适应性。该技术采用容器化将应用程序及其所有必要组件打包到一个独立的实体中。无论开发、登台和生产环境如何变化，这都可以提供一致的功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Check and Update Newer Versions for Dependencies in Maven Projects】如何检查和更新 Maven 项目中依赖项的新版本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/update-versions-dependencies-in-maven-projects</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;45b9&#34;&gt;With the passing of time, new versions of the dependencies are released into the market. We need to update the respective dependencies versions in the project as these versions have new changes and fixes for the security vulnerabilities. It is better to update the dependencies frequently in the project.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;45b9&#34;&gt;Now arises the question:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;45b9&#34;&gt;随着时间的推移，新版本的依赖项被发布到市场上。我们需要更新项目中各自的依赖版本，因为这些版本对安全漏洞有新的更改和修复。项目中最好经常更新依赖。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;45b9&#34;&gt;现在出现问题：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Create and Run A Job In Jenkins Using Jenkins Freestyle Project】如何使用 Jenkins Freestyle 项目在 Jenkins 中创建和运行作业</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/create-and-run-job-jenkins-freestyle</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As per the official Jenkins wiki information, a Jenkins freestyle project is a typical build job or task. This may be as simple as building or packaging an application, running tests, building or sending a report, or even merely running a few commands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Collating data for tests can also be done by Jenkins. For instance, a real-world scenario could involve Jenkins allowing you to submit reports to log management at any specified stage concerning management, which may include details about artifacts or shipping application logs. In this Jenkins tutorial, we will dive deeper into how to create a job in Jenkins and eventually, a Jenkins freestyle project. Let’s find out more about Jenkins Build Job before we begin creating a Freestyle Project.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;根据 Jenkins 官方 wiki 信息，Jenkins 自由式项目是典型的构建作业或任务。这可能就像构建或打包应用程序、运行测试、构建或发送报告，甚至只是运行一些命令一样简单。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;整理测试数据也可以由 Jenkins 完成。例如，现实场景可能涉及 Jenkins，允许您在涉及管理的任何指定阶段向日志管理提交报告，其中可能包括有关工件或传送应用程序日志的详细信息。在本 Jenkins 教程中，我们将深入探讨如何在 Jenkins 中创建工作，并最终创建 Jenkins 自由式项目。在开始创建 Freestyle 项目之前，让我们了解有关 Jenkins Build Job 的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>