<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Product Recommendations With Oracle CDC, Flink, and MongoDB】AI驱动的产品推荐与Oracle CDC，Flink和MongoDB</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-product-recommendations-oracle-cdc-flink-mongodb</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Planning a weekend hike? River Runners has you covered, with lightweight pants, trail shoes, and now, eerily good product recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Okay, River Runners isn’t real. It’s a fake outdoor running company I created to show how real-time AI can turn any store into something that feels smart and personalized. The kind of experience where the site seems to know what you need before you do.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;计划周末远足？ River Runners为您提供了轻巧的裤子，越野鞋，现在是好的产品建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;好吧，河流跑步者不是真实的。我创建了这是一家虚假的户外跑步公司，以展示实时AI如何将任何商店变成聪明和个性化的商店。该网站似乎在您需要之前知道您需要什么的经验。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Revolutionizing the Command Line: An Introduction to Gemini CLI】革命性的命令行：双子座CLI简介</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/google-gemini-cli-ai-tool</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/secrets-at-the-command-line-cheat-sheet-included&#34;&gt;command-line interface&lt;/a&gt; (CLI) has been a cornerstone of developer workflows for decades. It offers power, precision, and control that graphical interfaces often lack. Yet, as software development grows more complex, even the CLI must evolve. Enter Gemini CLI, a tool developed by Google that brings artificial intelligence right into your terminal. With Gemini CLI, developers are empowered to build faster, debug smarter, and automate more, all from within a familiar interface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Gemini?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As of July 2025, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/grounding-gemini-google-search-data-sources&#34;&gt;Gemini&lt;/a&gt; is Google&#39;s latest family of multimodal AI models, developed under the broader Google AI initiative. These models are designed to process and generate across various inputs including text, code, images, and documents. Gemini 1.5 Pro, the current flagship model, supports up to 1 million tokens of context, making it highly effective for deep code understanding, document summarization, and rich interactions involving multiple data types.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/secrets-at-the-command-line-cheat-cheat-sheet-included”&gt; command-line接口&lt;/a&gt;（cli）一直是开发人员工作流程的基石。它提供了图形接口通常缺乏的功率，精度和控制。但是，随着软件开发变得更加复杂，即使CLI也必须发展。输入Gemini CLI，这是由Google开发的一种工具，可将人工智能直接带入您的终端。使用Gemini CLI，开发人员有权从熟悉的界面中更快地构建更快，更智能和自动化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是双子座？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;截至2025年7月，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/grounding-gemini-google-search-data-sources”&gt; gemini &lt;/a&gt;是Google最新的多模型模型家族，在广泛的Google AI Iniative下开发。这些模型旨在在各种输入中进行处理和生成，包括文本，代码，图像和文档。 Gemini 1.5 Pro是当前的旗舰模型，最多支持100万个标记的上下文，使其非常有效地理解，文档摘要和涉及多种数据类型的丰富互动。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What Developers Need to Know About IP API Privacy in Mobile Apps (2025 Update)】开发人员需要了解有关移动应用中IP API隐私的知识（2025 Update）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ip-api-privacy-mobile-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In 2025, mobile applications are smarter, faster, and increasingly location-aware. From e-commerce personalization to regional compliance, knowing where a user is located adds critical context to the user experience. While GPS provides the most accurate location data, it isn’t always available — or preferred by users. That’s why many developers integrate IP API into their mobile geolocation apps to determine user location without relying on GPS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But as privacy laws around the world continue to evolve, developers can’t afford to treat IP-based data as harmless. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-check-ip-addresses-for-known-threats-and-to&#34;&gt;IP addresses&lt;/a&gt;, when tied to location or behavioral data, are now widely recognized as personal data under privacy laws like GDPR, CCPA/CPRA, India’s DPDP Act, and others.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在2025年，移动应用程序更聪明，更快且越来越多地感知位置。从电子商务个性化到区域合规性，了解用户所在的位置为用户体验增加了关键上下文。尽管GPS提供了最准确的位置数据，但并非总是可用的，也不是用户首选的。这就是为什么许多开发人员将IP API集成到其移动地理位置应用程序中以确定不依赖GPS的用户位置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;，但是随着世界各地的隐私法律不断发展，开发人员无力将基于IP的数据视为无害。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-to-check-ip-addresses-for-nown--warreat-anreats-and-to-”&gt; ip地址&lt;/a&gt;当与位置或行为数据息息相关时，现在被广泛认可为GDPR，ccpa/ccpa/cpra，India dpdp and ppdp act and p. &lt;/其他的个人数据，如</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Amazon Q Developer: The Future of AI-Enhanced Coding Productivity】亚马逊Q开发人员：AI增强编码生产率的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/amazon-q-developer-ai-coding-productivity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;If you are like me, a developer who often has to balance productivity and curiosity in the workplace, then you are always on the lookout for tools that actually make life easier. So, when Amazon came up with Amazon Q Developer, a new AI-powered coding companion that can be embedded in popular IDEs like Visual Studio Code, I was more than just interested. Having used it for a week now, I can safely say it’s like having a personal coding buddy who can give you some pretty helpful tips when you need them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But what is Amazon Q Developer, and why should anyone care? Stay tuned and find out.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;如果您像我一样，一个通常必须在工作场所中的生产力和好奇心平衡的开发人员，那么您总是在寻找真正使生活更轻松的工具。因此，当亚马逊提出Amazon Q Developer，这是一种新的AI驱动的编码伴侣，可以嵌入到Visual Studio Code等流行的IDE中，我不仅仅是感兴趣。使用了一个星期后，我可以肯定地说，这就像拥有一个个人编码好友，可以在需要时给您一些非常有用的提示。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是亚马逊Q开发人员是什么，为什么有人要关心？请继续关注并找出答案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Accessibility Basics for Building Telehealth Platforms With React Code Examples】使用React代码示例构建远程医疗平台的可访问性基础知识</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/accessibility-basics-telehealth-platforms-with-react</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Let’s cut to the chase: telehealth platforms aren’t just fancy video call apps. They’re lifelines for people with disabilities, chronic illnesses, and mobility challenges. But here’s the kicker — if your platform isn’t accessible, you’re slamming the door in the face of the very people who need it most.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this guide, we’ll break down accessibility basics for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-react-developers-guide-to-designing-telehealth-platforms&#34;&gt;telehealth platforms using React&lt;/a&gt;, complete with code examples that’ll make your UI not just compliant, but &lt;em&gt;compassionate&lt;/em&gt;. No jargon, no fluff — just actionable steps to avoid building a digital hospital that’s “stairs-only.”&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;让我们剪下追逐：远程医疗平台不仅仅是花哨的视频通话应用程序。它们是残疾人，慢性病和流动性挑战的生命线。但这是踢脚者 - 如果您的平台无法访问，那么您面对最需要它的人就在撞门。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本指南中，我们将分解&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a-react-developers-guide-guide-tovelopers-guide-to-depleveling-telehealth-platforms”&gt;使用React telehealth平台的代码示例，与您不仅会使您的ui ui ii norect &lt;/empsiant &lt;/em em em emssimante &lt;/没有行话，没有绒毛 - 只是避免建造“仅楼梯”的数字医院的可行步骤。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Choosing Between GCP Workflows, AWS Step Functions, and Temporal for Stateful Workflow Orchestration】在GCP工作流程，AWS步骤功能和暂时性工作流安排之间选择</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/choosing-between-gcp-workflows-aws-step-functions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Stateful workflow orchestration tools help engineers reliably coordinate multi-step processes across services. Google Cloud Workflows (GCP Workflows) and AWS Step Functions are fully managed cloud services for defining workflows as a series of steps/states, whereas &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-visualize-temporalio-workflows&#34;&gt;Temporal &lt;/a&gt;is an open-source orchestration engine that developers can self-host or use via a managed offering . All three aim to handle long-running, stateful sequences of tasks with built-in reliability. This article compares &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-processing-in-gcp-with-apache-airflow&#34;&gt;GCP Workflows&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-ultimate-guide-to-aws-step-functions&#34;&gt;AWS Step Functions&lt;/a&gt;, and Temporal from a senior engineer’s perspective, focusing on developer usability and experience. We examine their workflow modeling approaches, error handling capabilities, observability, cost and scalability considerations, and deployment models. The goal is to help you choose the right tool for your use case in a vendor-neutral way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workflow Modeling Approach (Visual vs. Code-Based)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GCP Workflows and AWS Step Functions – Declarative Definitions:&lt;/strong&gt; Both GCP Workflows and AWS Step Functions use a declarative syntax to model workflows, though in different flavors. AWS Step Functions expresses workflows in the Amazon States Language (JSON-based, with YAML support via tools). Each state machine (workflow) in Step Functions is defined by states and transitions in JSON, and you can design it visually using AWS’s Workflow Studio. Google Cloud Workflows uses its own YAML-based DSL (or JSON) to describe a sequence of &lt;strong&gt;steps&lt;/strong&gt; that execute in order . In GCP’s YAML, steps implicitly flow to the next unless directed otherwise, similar to a coding style . Both systems support conditional branches (e.g. AWS &lt;em&gt;Choice&lt;/em&gt; state, GCP &lt;em&gt;switch&lt;/em&gt; statements) and loops, but you author them as config rather than writing general-purpose code.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;状态工作流程编排工具可帮助工程师可靠地协调跨服务的多步骤过程。 Google Cloud Workflows（GCP工作流）和AWS步骤功能是完全管理的云服务，用于将工作流程定义为一系列步骤/状态，而&lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/articles/articles/how-tem-visualize-temporize-temporalio-workflows-tormalio-workflows-临时范围“&gt;临时”是开放式服务的，可以通过式托管服务器来开发。这三个目标旨在处理具有内置可靠性的长期，状态的任务序列。 This article compares &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-processing-in-gcp-with-apache-airflow&#34;&gt;GCP Workflows&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-ultimate-guide-to-aws-step-functions&#34;&gt;AWS Step Functions&lt;/a&gt;, and Temporal from a senior engineer’s观点，专注于开发人员的可用性和经验。我们检查了他们的工作流建模方法，错误处理功能，可观察性，成本和可伸缩性注意事项以及部署模型。目标是帮助您以供应商中立的方式为使用情况选择合适的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;工作流建模方法（基于代码与代码）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; GCP工作流程和AWS步骤函数 - 声明性定义：&lt;/strong&gt; GCP工作流和AWS步骤函数都使用声明语法来建模工作流，尽管以不同的风格。 AWS步骤功能在Amazon States语言中表达工作流（基于JSON，通过工具提供YAML支持）。步骤功能中的每个状态机（工作流）均由JSON中的状态和过渡定义，您可以使用AWS的Workflow Studio视觉设计它。 Google Cloud Workflows使用自己的基于YAML的DSL（或JSON）来描述按顺序执行的&lt;strong&gt;步骤&lt;/strong&gt;的顺序。在GCP的YAML中，除非另有针对编码样式，否则步骤隐含地流向下一个。这两个系统都支持条件分支（例如AWS &lt;em&gt;选择&lt;/em&gt; state，GCP &lt;em&gt; switch &lt;/em&gt;语句）和循环，但是您可以将它们作为config而不是编写通用代码。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Set Up OpenID Connect With Keycloak: A Step-by-Step Guide】与KeyCloak设置OpenID连接：逐步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/setup-openid-connect-with-keycloak</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this blog, you will learn how to set up the OpenID Connect Authorization Code Flow using Keycloak. You will execute the flow yourself in order to get a better understanding of OIDC. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adding security to your application is almost always necessary. It is also something developers seem to find difficult to grasp. Therefore, you need to understand the concepts of security. Nowadays, the default is to use OpenID Connect (OIDC) for authentication. OIDC is a layer on top of OAuth 2.0 that takes care of the authorization. Authentication is about identifying the person (or system) who logs in to an application, and authorization is about which permissions you are granted in the application.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在此博客中，您将学习如何使用KeyCloak设置OpenID连接授权代码流。您将自己执行流程，以便更好地了解OIDC。享受！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在应用程序中添加安全性几乎总是必要的。这也是开发人员似乎很难掌握的东西。因此，您需要了解安全的概念。如今，默认值是使用OpenID Connect（OIDC）进行身份验证。 OIDC是OAuth 2.0顶部的一层，它负责授权。身份验证是关于识别登录应用程序的人（或系统），授权是您在应用程序中授予的权限。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Vibe Coding: Conversational Software Development — Part 3: Prompt Discipline】VIBE编码：对话软件开发 - 第3部分：及时纪律</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vibe-coding-prompt-discipline</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It is speculated that vibe coding could fundamentally change how we build software. Instead of writing lines of code, we will describe our goals in plain English, and working software will be generated in response.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/vibe-coding-in-practice&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;last post&lt;/a&gt;, I experimented with a few vibe coding tools and shared my hands-on experience. If you have been following closely, you might have noticed something subtle but important that I am using natural language as an interface. The words I choose shape how AI interprets and builds software. And behind that process lies a critical yet often overlooked layer of the system prompt.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;据推测，Vibe编码可以从根本上改变我们构建软件的方式。我们将用普通英语描述我们的目标，而不是编写代码行，并且将生成工作软件。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/vibe-coding-in-practice” target =“ _ blank”&gt;上一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;，我尝试了一些氛围编码工具并分享了我的手上经验。如果您一直在密切关注，您可能会注意到一些微妙的东西，但重要的是我使用自然语言作为界面。我选择的单词塑造了AI如何解释和构建软件。在该过程的背后是系统提示的关键但经常被忽略的层。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Raw Data to Model Serving: A Blueprint for the AI/ML Lifecycle With Kubeflow】从原始数据到模型服务：带有KubeFlow的AI/ML生命周期的蓝图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-ml-lifecycle-kubeflow-model-serving-blueprint</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for a practical, reproducible way to take a machine learning project from raw data all the way to a deployed, production-ready model? This post is your blueprint for the AI/ML lifecycle: you’ll learn how to use &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kubeflow.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt; and open-source tools such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/feast-dev/feast&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Feast&lt;/a&gt; to build a workflow you can run on your laptop and adapt to your own projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ll walk through the entire ML lifecycle — from data preparation to live inference — leveraging the Kubeflow platform to create a cohesive, production-grade MLOps workflow.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否正在寻找一种实用的，可重复的方法，将机器学习项目从原始数据一直到已部署的，可供生产就绪的模型中获取？这篇文章是AI/ML生命周期的蓝图：您将学习如何使用&lt;a href =“ https：//wwwww.kubeflow.org/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” noopener noreferrer“ target =” _ blank _ _ black“ _&gt; kubeflow”&gt; kubeflow &lt;/a&gt;和开放式工具rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; feast &lt;/a&gt;要构建一个可以在笔记本电脑上运行并适应自己的项目的工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将浏览整个ML生命周期 - 从数据准备到实时推理 - 利用KubeFlow平台创建一个凝聚力的生产级MLOPS工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a VS Code-Like Online IDE With Next.js 15, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, and Goose AI】使用Next.js 15，打字稿，尾风CSS和Goose AI构建类似于代码的在线IDE。</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/online-ide-vscode-nextjs-typescript-tailwind-goose-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;section name=&#34;271e&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;728d&#34;&gt;In this tutorial, we&#39;ll build an online IDE inspired by Visual Studio Code using modern web technologies: &lt;strong&gt;Next.js 15&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;TypeScript&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Tailwind CSS&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Goose AI&#39;s API&lt;/strong&gt;. This IDE will provide real-time code suggestions based on what you type or any inline comment prompts you to write.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;8c8e&#34;&gt;By the end of this guide, you&#39;ll have an interactive coding environment featuring:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;部分名称=“ 271E”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name =“ 728D”&gt;在本教程中，我们将使用现代网络技术启发，使用现代网络技术启发：&lt;strong&gt; next.js 15 &lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;strong&gt; typeScript &lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;strong&gt; tailwind css &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt; goose goose ai ai ai的api &lt;/strong&gt;。此IDE将根据您键入的内容或任何内联注释提示您编写实时代码建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name =“ 8c8e”&gt;在本指南的末尾，您将拥有一个交互式编码环境：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>