<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Revolutionizing KYC: Leveraging AI/ML for Regulatory Compliance】革新KYC：利用AI/ML进行监管合规性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kyc-leveraging-ai-ml-regulatory-compliance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Know Your Customer (KYC) embodies a sophisticated and proactive compliance framework strategically adopted by financial institutions to methodically scrutinize and validate client identities, transactional behaviors, and risk exposures. Beyond mere regulatory formality, KYC constitutes an integral pillar for institutional integrity, meticulously architected to mitigate systemic vulnerabilities such as identity fraud, illicit financial flows, and potential terrorist financing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fundamentally, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-computings-role-in-transforming-aml-and-kyc-1&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;KYC&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;represents an intersection of regulatory rigor and advanced analytical methodologies. It encompasses a structured process of gathering detailed identity evidence—ranging from government-issued documentation to transactional patterns—and applying intricate risk-scoring models to ascertain and continuously reassess customer authenticity, credibility, and behavioral consistency.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;了解您的客户（KYC）体现了一个复杂而积极的合规框架，该框架在战略上采用了有条不紊地审查和验证客户身份，交易行为和风险风险的策略性。除了单纯的法规形式之外，KYC还构成了机构完整性的一体不可或缺的支柱，精心构建可以减轻系统漏洞，例如身份欺诈，非法财务流动和潜在的恐怖融资。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从根本上讲，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-computings-computings-computings-computings-role-in-transforming-aml-and-yml-and-kyc-1” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; kyc &lt;/a&gt;代表了法规条例性的严格方法和先进的分析方法。它涵盖了一个结构化的过程，即收集详细的身份证据（从政府发行的文件到交易模式），并应用复杂的风险计算模型来确定和不断地重新评估客户的真实性，信誉和行为一致性。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PostgreSQL Performance Tuning】PostgreSQL性能调整</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-performance-tuning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/manual-sharding-postgresql-implementation-guide&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt; is already known for its reliability, extensibility, and open-source pedigree and continues to grow and evolve with each release. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/incremental-backups-pg-basebackup-postgresql&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL 17&lt;/a&gt; introduces several performance improvements and features that make it a powerhouse for Online Transaction Processing (OLTP) and Online Analytical Processing (OLAP) workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This blog will explore advanced performance tuning techniques for PostgreSQL 17 and highlight key improvements compared to versions 15 and 16.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/manual-sharding-postgresql-implementation-guide-g rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; postgresql &lt;/a&gt;已经知道其可靠性，可靠性，可扩展性，可扩展性，持续和持续的速度和持续性，并持续且持续和持续供应。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/incremental-backups-pg-basebackup-postgresql”&gt; PostgreSQL 17 &lt;/a&gt;引入了一些绩效改进和功能，使其成为在线交易处理（OLTP）和在线分析处理（OLAP）工作（OLAP）工作量的功能。&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;此博客将探索PostgreSQL 17的高级性能调整技术，并与版本15和16相比，突出了关键改进。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing DevOps Pipelines: A Practical Guide to Balancing Speed and Security】确保DevOps管道：平衡速度和安全的实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devops-pipelines-balancing-speed-and-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Security has been a major concern in today’s world. Security issues lead to data breaches with consequences such as data loss and financial losses. As a result, there is a need to focus on enhancing security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OWASP top 10 is a good guide for DevOps teams to mitigate key web application security risks. Integrating security strategies from the beginning to the end of the process can enable DevOps teams to enhance the overall security of the applications&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;安全一直是当今世界上的主要问题。安全问题导致数据泄露，并带来诸如数据丢失和财务损失之类的后果。结果，有必要专注于增强安全性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OWASP前十名是DevOps团队减轻关键Web应用程序安全风险的好指南。从过程开始到结束时整合安全策略可以使DevOps团队能够增强应用程序的整体安全性&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Improve Copilot&#39;s Accuracy and Performance in Power BI】如何提高副驾驶在Power BI中的准确性和性能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/improve-copilot-accuracy-performance-power-bi</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Copilot in Power BI has been a powerful advancement in making data analysis accessible to everyone. But the quality of Copilot&#39;s output is heavily dependent on the foundation it sits upon — your Power BI data model and metadata. If Copilot doesn&#39;t understand your data structure clearly, its responses can become vague, inaccurate, or not business-friendly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article will explain how building a strong semantic model and using rich metadata and descriptions could improve Copilot’s accuracy in Power BI.&lt;/p&gt;】Power BI中的Copilot在使每个人都可以访问数据分析方面是一个有力的进步。但是，副铜的产出质量在很大程度上取决于它所属于的基础 - 您的Power BI数据模型和元数据。如果Copilot无法清楚地理解您的数据结构，则其响应可能会变得模糊，不准确或不友好。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文将解释如何构建强大的语义模型并使用丰富的元数据和描述可以提高副驾驶在Power BI中的准确性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enterprise Data Loss Prevention (DLP) Security Policies and Tuning】企业数据损失预防（DLP）安全策略和调整</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-loss-prevention-dlp-security-policies-tuning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I’ve worked with a lot of enterprise customers over the years—big ones, too—and a common struggle I see is with their Data Loss Prevention (DLP) policies. Even though they’ve had the product for years, they often face one of two issues: either the policies are too weak and don’t flag anything, or they’re too strict, overwhelming teams with false alerts. When DLP policies aren’t properly tuned, it creates gaps that can lead to business disruptions and even huge losses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A well-known example is NASA’s ITAR email filtering issue in 2019, where an excessively strict DLP policy blocked legitimate emails, grinding operations to a halt. While there are many such cases, enterprises rarely disclose disruptions caused by poor policy design. The stakes are simply too high—reputation, confidential information, and, most importantly, customer trust are all on the line. Because of this, companies are often reluctant to seek external help in refining their security policy infrastructure, even when expert guidance could prevent costly mistakes. Ultimately, security software vendors play a crucial role in simplifying policy tuning, ensuring enterprises can strike the right balance between protection and usability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;多年来，我也与许多企业客户合作（也是企业客户），我看到的常见斗争是预防数据丢失（DLP）政策。即使他们拥有多年的产品，他们也经常面临两个问题之一：要么政策太弱，而且没有标记任何东西，要么他们太严格，压倒性的团队具有虚假的警报。当DLP政策未正确调整时，它会产生差距，从而导致业务中断甚至巨大损失。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;一个众所周知的例子是NASA在2019年的ITAR电子邮件过滤问题，在该问题中，过度严格的DLP策略阻止了合法的电子邮件，将操作局限于停顿。尽管有许多这样的案例，但企业很少披露政策设计不佳造成的中断。赌注太高了 - 意见，机密信息，最重要的是，客户信任都在线。因此，即使专家指导可以防止昂贵的错误，公司通常不愿寻求外部帮助来完善其安全政策基础设施。最终，安全软件供应商在简化策略调整方面发挥了至关重要的作用，确保企业可以在保护和可用性之间取得正确的平衡。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Truth About AI and Job Loss】关于人工智能和失业的真相</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-truth-about-ai-and-job-loss</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I keep finding myself in conversations with family and friends asking, &lt;em&gt;“Is AI coming for our jobs?”&lt;/em&gt; Which roles are getting Thanos-snapped first? And will there still be space for junior individual contributors in organizations? And many more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;With so many conflicting opinions, I felt overwhelmed and anxious, so I decided to take action instead of staying stuck in uncertainty. So, I began collecting historical data and relevant facts to gain a clearer understanding of the direction and impact of the current AI surge.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;我一直在与家人和朋友的对话中发现自己，&lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;“ ai是为了我们的工作？组织中的初级个人贡献者还有空间吗？还有更多。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;有这么多矛盾的意见，我感到不知所措和焦虑，所以我决定采取行动，而不是陷入不确定性。因此，我开始收集历史数据和相关事实，以更清楚地了解当前AI激增的方向和影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MySQL Formatter: How to Make Beautiful Code and Why You Need It】mysql格式化：如何制作美丽的代码以及为什么需要它</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mysql-formatter-make-beautiful-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;A MySQL formatter makes code beautiful. But have you ever wondered what beautiful code looks like?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;You might think that this is not so important.&amp;nbsp;As long as&amp;nbsp;it works as intended, why make a case about it?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt; mysql formatter使代码变得美丽。但是，您是否曾经想过什么美丽的代码是什么样的？&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span-ccp-props =“ {}”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;您可能认为这不是那么重要。 只要它按预期工作，为什么要对此有所了解？&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {}”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Hype to Harm: Why AI Governance Needs More Than Good Intentions】从炒作到伤害：为什么AI治理需要的不仅仅是良好意图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-governance-needs-more-than-intentions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The race to implement AI technologies has created a significant gap between intention and implementation, particularly in governance. According to recent data from the IAPP and Credo AI&#39;s 2025 report, while 77% of organizations are working on AI governance, only a fraction have mature frameworks in place. This disconnect between aspirational goals and practical governance has real consequences, as we&#39;ve witnessed throughout 2024-2025 with high-profile failures and data breaches.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve spent the last decade working with organizations implementing AI solutions, and the pattern is distressingly familiar: enthusiasm for AI capabilities outpaces the willingness to establish robust guardrails.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;实施AI技术的竞赛在意图和实施之间，尤其是在治理方面造成了显着差距。根据IAPP和Credo AI的2025年报告的最新数据，尽管有77％的组织正在研究AI治理，但只有一小部分具有成熟的框架。我们在2024  -  2025年期间目睹的，良好的目标与实践治理之间的这种脱节会产生真正的后果，并引起了人们的备受瞩目的失败和数据泄露。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去十年来，我已经与实施AI解决方案的组织合作，这种模式令人沮丧：对AI功能的热情超过了建立强大的护栏的意愿。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Smart Contracts: The Future Of Automated Decision-Making】AI驱动的智能合约：自动决策的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-smart-contracts-will-drive-automated-decision-making</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I&#39;ve seen many people struggle with slow, error-prone contracts. It&#39;s frustrating when deals get held up by paperwork or mistakes. I get it — I&#39;ve been there too. But here&#39;s some good news: AI-powered smart contracts are changing the game.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I&#39;ve done a ton of research on this topic. When AI and blockchain team up, they work together to make contracts smarter and faster because they use tech like natural language processing to understand contracts better. I&#39;ll show you how these smart contracts can speed up your work and cut down on errors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我已经看到许多人在缓慢而容易出错的合同中挣扎。当交易因文书工作或错误而陷入困境时，这令人沮丧。我明白了 - 我也去过那里。但这是一些好消息：AI驱动的智能合约正在改变游戏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我已经对此主题进行了大量研究。当AI和区块链合作时，他们共同努力，使合同更聪明，更快，因为他们使用自然语言处理等技术来更好地理解合同。我将向您展示这些智能合约如何加快您的工作并减少错误。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Domain-Centric Agile Modeling for Legacy Insurance Systems】以领域为中心的遗产保险系统的敏捷建模</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/domain-centric-agile-modeling-for-legacy-insurance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Legacy insurance systems have accumulated decades of complexity in their codebases and business logic. This complexity is spread across batch jobs and shaped by regulation, rather than architecture. Directly applying modern Agile modeling to such a landscape often throws developers off track and into frustration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;That is where Agile can work, but only when recentered around the realities of the domain. A domain-first perspective is captured by the fact that success in these environments cannot be achieved by providing screens and endpoints but by replicating the essence of how the business operates.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;传统保险系统在其代码库和业务逻辑中积累了数十年的复杂性。这种复杂性分布在批处理工作中，并由监管而不是体系结构塑造。直接将现代敏捷建模应用于这样的景观通常会使开发人员脱离轨道并陷入挫败感。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这是敏捷可以工作的地方，但只有在围绕域的现实围绕现实时才能使用。通过提供屏幕和端点，可以通过复制业务运作方式的本质来实现这些环境中的成功来捕获一个领域优先的观点。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>