<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Doesn&#39;t Postgres Use My Index?】为什么 Postgres 不使用我的索引？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-doesnt-postgres-use-my-index</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;It may happen that we create an index, but PostgreSQL doesn’t use it. What could be the reason, and how can we fix it? We identified 11 distinct scenarios. Read on to find out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Important Things&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Indexes may be tricky. We already covered how they work in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/indexes-under-the-hood&#34;&gt;another article&lt;/a&gt;. Let’s quickly recap the important parts of how they work.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;有可能我们创建了索引，但 PostgreSQL 不使用它。可能是什么原因，我们该如何解决？我们确定了 11 种不同的场景。请继续阅读以找出答案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;重要的事情&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;索引可能很棘手。我们已经在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/indexes-under-the-hood&#34;&gt;另一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;中介绍了它们的工作原理。让我们快速回顾一下它们工作原理的重要部分。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Polling With RxJS】使用 RxJS 实现轮询</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-polling-with-rxjs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In most front-end applications, fetching data from the back-end is a common requirement to provide up-to-date information to the user. Typically, this process is straightforward: know the API endpoint, create a function, call it, process the response, and display it on the page. However, there are scenarios — often rare or specific to certain business needs — where client-server communication must be more sophisticated. In this article, we’ll explore one such case: implementing repetitive API calls (polling) using RxJS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;RxJS Refresher&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before diving into polling, let’s take a moment to refresh our understanding of RxJS. For those new to it, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/rxjs-streams&#34;&gt;RxJS (Reactive Extensions for JavaScript)&lt;/a&gt; is a library that brings reactive programming concepts into the JavaScript ecosystem. It’s particularly useful for managing asynchronous operations, offering powerful tools like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/angular-observables-and-promises-how-to-use-them&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observables&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Observers&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Subjects&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/angular-rxjs-reactive-operators&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在大多数前端应用程序中，从后端获取数据是向用户提供最新信息的常见要求。通常，此过程很简单：了解 API 端点、创建函数、调用它、处理响应并将其显示在页面上。然而，在某些情况下（通常很少见或特定于某些业务需求），客户端-服务器通信必须更加复杂。在本文中，我们将探讨这样一个案例：使用 RxJS 实现重复的 API 调用（轮询）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;RxJS 复习&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在深入讨论轮询之前，让我们花点时间回顾一下对 RxJS 的理解。对于新手来说，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/rxjs-streams&#34;&gt;RxJS（JavaScript 响应式扩展）&lt;/a&gt; 是一个将响应式编程概念引入 JavaScript 生态系统的库。它对于管理异步操作特别有用，提供强大的工具，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/angular-observables-and-promises-how-to-use-them&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observables&lt;/ strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;观察者&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;主题&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/angular-rxjs-reactive-operators&#34;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;操作员&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Create a Search Engine and Algorithm With ClickHouse and Snowflake】如何使用 ClickHouse 和 Snowflake 创建搜索引擎和算法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/create-a-search-engine-with-clickhouse-and-snowflake</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/clickhouse-made-easy-getting-started-with-a-few-cl&#34;&gt;ClickHouse&lt;/a&gt; is an open-source data warehousing solution that is architected as a &lt;a href=&#34;https://clickhouse.com/docs/en/faq/general/columnar-database&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;columnar database management system&lt;/a&gt;. This makes it extremely powerful to work with massive datasets, especially ones that are long as they can be aggregated, ordered, or computed with low latency. When working with the same data type, it&#39;s very efficient for fast scanning and filtering of the data. This makes it a great use case for implementing a search engine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A lot of applications use &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-elasticsearch-1&#34;&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/a&gt; as their search engine solution. However, such an implementation can be expensive both in terms of cost and time. Copying the data over to Elasticsearch can also cause lags because data is being migrated to another data store. Also, &lt;a href=&#34;https://logz.io/blog/elasticsearch-cluster-tutorial/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;setting up the Elasticsearch cluster&lt;/a&gt;, configuring the nodes and defining and fine-tuning indexes can take more programmatic work, which may not be justified for all projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/clickhouse-made-easy-getting-started-with-a-few-cl&#34;&gt;ClickHouse&lt;/a&gt; 是一个开源数据仓库解决方案其架构为&lt;a href=&#34;https://clickhouse.com/docs/en/faq/general/columnar-database&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;列式数据库管理系统&lt;/a&gt; 。这使得处理海量数据集变得非常强大，尤其是那些可以低延迟聚合、排序或计算的数据集。当处理相同的数据类型时，它对于快速扫描和过滤数据非常有效。这使其成为实现搜索引擎的绝佳用例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多应用程序使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-elasticsearch-1&#34;&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/a&gt; 作为其搜索引擎解决方案。然而，这样的实施在成本和时间方面都可能是昂贵的。将数据复制到 Elasticsearch 也可能会导致滞后，因为数据正在迁移到另一个数据存储。另外，&lt;a href=&#34;https://logz.io/blog/elasticsearch-cluster-tutorial/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;设置 Elasticsearch 集群&lt;/a&gt;、配置节点和定义和微调索引可能需要更多的编程工作，这可能并不适合所有项目。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top 6 Cybersecurity Threat Detection Use Cases: How AI/ML Can Help Detect Advanced and Emerging Threats】六大网络安全威胁检测用例：AI/ML 如何帮助检测高级和新兴威胁</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-6-cybersecurity-threat-detection-use-cases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI/ML tools and technologies heavily influence the modern digital landscape by introducing numerous use cases involving &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-genetic-algorithm-in-malware-detection&#34;&gt;AI-based malware detection&lt;/a&gt;, preventing social engineering attacks, and threat identification and remediation. Many organizations have acknowledged AI/ML&#39;s prominence in the cybersecurity threat landscape and have started to leverage AI/ML in their business and security requirements. AI/ML-based solutions assist employees to complete their day-to-day tasks more efficiently and in no time. However, at the same time, we have also witnessed an exponential increase in the cybersecurity threat landscape. Hence, cybersecurity professionals and software developers have also started using AI/ML to build more innovative, adaptive, and robust systems and applications to protect an organization&#39;s IT and network infrastructure. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Statistics: AI/ML in Cybersecurity&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In recent times, we have witnessed the widespread adoption and exponential growth of&amp;nbsp;AI and ML technologies. Below are the statistics taken after thorough research highlighting the impact of&amp;nbsp;AI/ML tools and techniques&amp;nbsp;on&amp;nbsp;cybersecurity threat detection&amp;nbsp;and increasing overall cybersecurity performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能/机器学习工具和技术通过引入大量涉及人工智能的用例，对现代数字格局产生了重大影响基于的恶意软件检测，防止社会工程攻击，以及威胁识别和修复。许多组织已经认识到人工智能/机器学习在网络安全威胁领域的突出地位，并开始在其业务和安全需求中利用人工智能/机器学习。基于人工智能/机器学习的解决方案可帮助员工更高效、更迅速地完成日常任务。但与此同时，我们也目睹了网络安全威胁形势呈指数级增长。因此，网络安全专业人员和软件开发人员也开始使用 AI/ML 来构建更具创新性、适应性和强大的系统和应用程序，以保护组织的 IT 和网络基础设施。    &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;统计数据：网络安全中的人工智能/机器学习&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;近年来，我们见证了 AI 和 ML 技术的广泛采用和指数级增长。以下是经过深入研究后得出的统计数据，强调了人工智能/机器学习工具和技术对网络安全威胁检测和提高整体网络安全性能的影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transforming Manufacturing: AI-Driven Quality Control and Predictive Maintenance Using Cloud and IoT】制造业转型：利用云和物联网进行人工智能驱动的质量控制和预测性维护</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-manufacturing-ai-driven-quality-control</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In modern manufacturing, the key to sustaining product reliability, compliance with regulatory standards, and maintaining operational efficiency lies in robust quality control and advanced maintenance management. This study delves into the integration of AI technologies to interpret sensor data from production equipment. By employing predictive modeling techniques such as Stacked LSTM networks, RNNs, Random Forests, Gradient Boosting, SVM, ARIMA, and SARIMA, the goal is to forecast potential equipment failures, implement proactive maintenance solutions, and uphold rigorous quality checks through automated systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This research showcases how AI-driven insights can be displayed through interactive dashboards and comprehensive reports, aiding in meeting regulatory standards while substantially improving operational dependability in manufacturing. Beyond the immediate benefits of reduced downtime and increased productivity, anomaly detection, especially in rotating machinery, plays a pivotal role in AI-driven predictive maintenance (PdM). The findings highlight how predictive modeling transforms equipment management, fostering innovation and supporting sustainability across various industries by utilizing sensors, cameras, and laser beam sensing technology.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在现代制造业中，维持产品可靠性、符合监管标准和保持运营效率的关键在于强大的质量控制和先进的维护管理。这项研究深入探讨了人工智能技术的集成，以解释来自生产设备的传感器数据。通过采用堆叠 LSTM 网络、RNN、随机森林、梯度提升、SVM、ARIMA 和 SARIMA 等预测建模技术，目标是预测潜在的设备故障，实施主动维护解决方案，并通过自动化系统进行严格的质量检查。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;这项研究展示了如何通过交互式仪表板和综合报告显示人工智能驱动的见解，帮助满足监管标准，同时大幅提高制造中的运营可靠性。除了减少停机时间和提高生产率等直接好处之外，异常检测（尤其是旋转机械中的异常检测）在人工智能驱动的预测性维护 (PdM) 中发挥着关键作用。研究结果强调了预测建模如何利用传感器、摄像头和激光束传感技术来改变设备管理、促进创新并支持各个行业的可持续发展。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding the Dependency Injection Lifecycle: Singleton, Scoped, and Transient With Detailed Examples】了解依赖注入生命周期：单例、作用域和瞬态以及详细示例</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-the-dependency-injection-lifecycle</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Developers may be aware of the lifecycle of service instances when using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/about-dependency-injection&#34;&gt;dependency injection&lt;/a&gt;, but many don’t fully grasp how it works. You can find numerous articles online that clarify these concepts, but they often just reiterate definitions that you might already know. Let me illustrate with a detailed example that simplifies the explanation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When implementing dependency injection, developers have three options that determine the life cycle of the instances:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;开发人员在使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/about-dependency-injection&#34;&gt;依赖注入&lt;/a&gt;时可能会了解服务实例的生命周期，但许多人并没有完全了解掌握它是如何运作的。您可以在网上找到许多文章来阐明这些概念，但它们通常只是重申您可能已经知道的定义。让我用一个详细的例子来说明，以简化解释。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在实现依赖注入时，开发人员有三个选项来确定实例的生命周期：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Key Considerations for Effective AI/ML Deployments in Kubernetes】在 Kubernetes 中有效部署 AI/ML 的关键考虑因素</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/effective-AL-ML-deployments-Kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-kubernetes-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes in the Enterprise: Once Decade-Defining, Now Forging a Future in the SDLC&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes has become a cornerstone in modern infrastructure, particularly for deploying, scaling, and managing artificial intelligence and machine learning (AI/ML) workloads. As organizations increasingly rely on machine learning models for critical tasks like data processing, model training, and inference, Kubernetes offers the flexibility and scalability needed to manage these complex workloads efficiently. By leveraging Kubernetes&#39; robust ecosystem, AI/ML workloads can be dynamically orchestrated, ensuring optimal resource utilization and high availability across cloud environments. This synergy between Kubernetes and AI/ML empowers organizations to deploy and scale their ML workloads with greater agility and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-kubernetes-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;企业中的 Kubernetes：曾经定义十年，现在在 SDLC 中打造未来&lt;/em&gt;&lt; /a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 已成为现代基础设施的基石，特别是在部署、扩展和管理人工智能和机器学习 (AI/ML) 工作负载方面。随着组织越来越依赖机器学习模型来完成数据处理、模型训练和推理等关键任务，Kubernetes 提供了有效管理这些复杂工作负载所需的灵活性和可扩展性。通过利用 Kubernetes 强大的生态系统，可以动态编排 AI/ML 工作负载，确保跨云环境的最佳资源利用率和高可用性。 Kubernetes 和 AI/ML 之间的这种协同作用使组织能够以更高的敏捷性和可靠性部署和扩展其 ML 工作负载。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Supercharge Your Search With GenAI: From Simple Queries to Smarter Results】使用 GenAI 增强您的搜索：从简单查询到更智能的结果</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/supercharge-your-search-with-genai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In specialized fields like law, medicine, or even fashion, search engines are critical tools that professionals use to find accurate, relevant information quickly. However, traditional search engines often struggle to interpret complex, domain-specific queries. That’s where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;Generative AI (GenAI)&lt;/a&gt; can revolutionize the process by transforming simple queries into powerful search instructions through query expansion and reformulation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;By integrating &lt;strong&gt;Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting&lt;/strong&gt; with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, you can significantly enhance the precision and relevance of search results. This tutorial will show you how to implement &lt;strong&gt;Flan-T5&lt;/strong&gt; (or similar models) for advanced query expansion and reformulation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在法律、医学甚至时尚等专业领域，搜索引擎是专业人士用来快速查找准确、相关信息的重要工具。然而，传统的搜索引擎通常很难解释复杂的、特定领域的查询。这就是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;生成式人工智能 (GenAI)&lt;/a&gt; 可以通过以下方式彻底改变这一过程：将简单的查询转换为强大的搜索指令查询扩展和重构。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;通过将&lt;strong&gt;思想链 (CoT) 提示&lt;/strong&gt;与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large- language-models&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;，可以显着提高搜索结果的精确度和相关性。本教程将向您展示如何实现&lt;strong&gt;Flan-T5&lt;/strong&gt;（或类似模型）以进行高级查询扩展和重构。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Comprehensive Guide to Database Sharding: Building Scalable Systems】数据库分片综合指南：构建可扩展系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-comprehensive-guide-to-database-sharding</link>
      <description>【&lt;section name=&#34;3377&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;b7f3&#34;&gt;In this article, we’ll dive deep into the concept of database sharding, a critical technique for scaling databases to handle large volumes of data and high levels of traffic. Here’s what you can expect to learn:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;c110&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Sharding?:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;We’ll start by defining what sharding is and why it’s essential for modern, high-performance databases. You’ll understand how sharding can help overcome the limitations of traditional database scaling methods.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;125e&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Types of Sharding:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Next, we’ll explore the different types of sharding, including horizontal and vertical sharding. We’ll discuss the benefits and challenges of each approach, helping you decide which might be best for your use case.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;8cc5&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Selecting a Shard Key:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Choosing the right shard key is crucial for the success of a sharded database. In this section, we’ll walk through the factors to consider when selecting a shard key, common mistakes to avoid, and how to balance performance with even data distribution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;7bb6&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Routing Requests to Shards:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Finally, we’ll cover the methods for routing queries to the correct shard. This section will provide insights into the architecture and strategies to ensure efficient query processing in a sharded environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;7743&#34;&gt;By the end of this guide, you’ll have a comprehensive understanding of database sharding, enabling you to implement it effectively in your systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;部分名称=“3377”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;b7f3&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将深入探讨数据库分片的概念，这是一种扩展数据库以处理大量数据和高流量的关键技术。以下是您可以学到的内容：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;c110&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是分片？：&lt;/strong&gt;我们首先定义什么是分片以及为什么它对于现代高性能数据库至关重要。您将了解分片如何帮助克服传统数据库扩展方法的局限性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;125e&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;分片类型：&lt;/strong&gt;接下来，我们将探讨不同类型的分片，包括水平分片和垂直分片。我们将讨论每种方法的优点和挑战，帮助您确定哪种方法最适合您的用例。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;8cc5&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;选择分片键：&lt;/strong&gt;选择正确的分片键对于分片数据库的成功至关重要。在本节中，我们将介绍选择分片键时要考虑的因素、要避免的常见错误，以及如何在性能与均匀数据分布之间取得平衡。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;7bb6&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;将请求路由到分片：&lt;/strong&gt;最后，我们将介绍将查询路由到正确分片的方法。本部分将深入介绍确保分片环境中高效查询处理的架构和策略。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;7743&#34;&gt;读完本指南后，您将全面了解数据库分片，从而能够在您的系统中有效地实施它。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hyperscale Data Centers Ignite Construction Surge】超大规模数据中心引发建设热潮</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/hyperscale-data-centers-ignite-construction-surge</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Despite the lack of a universal definition for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-lies-ahead-for-data-center-operators&#34;&gt;hyperscale data centers&lt;/a&gt;, many people view them as massive facilities that typically handle mission-critical workloads distributed across numerous servers. These buildings have collectively contributed to a data center construction boom, emphasizing the world’s substantial and growing dependence on technologies and the infrastructure supporting them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Emerging Technologies Spurring Data Center Construction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When a February 2024 study examined the state of the global data center industry, the results revealed some of the primary drivers of the current construction boom. One finding was many of the largest hyperscale providers increasingly accommodate clients’ artificial intelligence applications and other computing-intensive requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;尽管&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-lies-ahead-for-data-center-operators&#34;&gt;超大规模数据中心缺乏通用定义&lt; /a&gt;，许多人将它们视为大型设施，通常处理分布在众多服务器上的关键任务工作负载。这些建筑共同推动了数据中心建设热潮，凸显了世界对技术及其支持基础设施的日益依赖。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;新兴技术推动数据中心建设&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;2024 年 2 月的一项研究调查了全球数据中心行业的状况，结果揭示了当前建设热潮的一些主要驱动因素。一项发现是，许多最大的超大规模提供商越来越多地满足客户的人工智能应用程序和其他计算密集型需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>