<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Containerized Intelligence: Running LLMs at Scale Using Docker and Kubernetes】集装箱智能：使用Docker和Kubernetes大规模运行LLMS</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llm-deployment-docker-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;431&#34; data-start=&#34;68&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Models&lt;/a&gt; (LLMs) such as GPT, LLaMA, and Mistral have transformed the way applications interpret and generate natural language, driving innovation across a wide range of industries. Yet, operationalizing these models at scale introduces a host of technical challenges, including dependency management, GPU integration, orchestration, and auto-scaling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;895&#34; data-start=&#34;433&#34;&gt;The rapid evolution of LLMs presents immense opportunities for building intelligent, language-aware applications. However, deploying and managing these compute-intensive models in production environments requires a reliable and scalable infrastructure. This is where containerization with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; and orchestration with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; come into play—offering a powerful combination to streamline LLM deployment, ensure reproducibility, and support horizontal scaling.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;431&#34; data-start=&#34;68&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Models&lt;/a&gt; (LLMs) such as GPT, LLaMA, and Mistral have transformed the way applications interpret and generate natural language, driving innovation across a wide range of industries.然而，大规模运营这些模型会引入许多技术挑战，包括依赖性管理，GPU集成，编排和自动规模。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 895” data-start =“ 433”&gt; LLMS的快速发展为构建智能，语言意识的应用提供了巨大的机会。但是，在生产环境中部署和管理这些计算密集型模型需要可靠且可扩展的基础架构。在这里，使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-with-with-with-docker-1”&gt; docker &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ https:///dzone.com/article.com/Articles/demystifying-kubernetes a&gt; kubernetes &lt;/kubernetnets &lt;/afembernetsementline&gt; LLM部署，确保可重复性并支持水平缩放。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Talk to Your BigQuery Data Using Claude Desktop】使用Claude Desktop与您的BigQuery数据交谈</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/talk-to-your-bigquery-data-using-claude-desktop</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Have you ever thought about talking to your data in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/control-access-to-google-bigquery-data&#34;&gt;Google Cloud BigQuery&lt;/a&gt; using natural language queries? If I told you a year ago that it was possible, you might think that I am out of my mind. But with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-custom-tools-model-context-protocol&#34;&gt;MCP (Model Context Protocol)&lt;/a&gt;, it is now totally possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we get into the nitty-gritty details of how it is done, let us first look at a simple diagram explaining how we can connect and talk to our BigQuery data using natural language via MCP. We will then talk about each of the components and how they are set up, and then we will look at how the whole thing works.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否曾经考虑过在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/control-access-to-google-bigquery-data”&gt; Google Cloud Cloud BigQuery &lt;/a&gt;使用自然语言查询？如果我一年前告诉你这是可能的，那么您可能会认为我不知所措。但是使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/building-custom-tools-model-context-protocol”&gt; mcp（模型上下文协议）&lt;/a&gt;现在是完全可能的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们了解如何完成的细节详细信息之前，让我们首先查看一个简单的图表，说明如何使用MCP使用自然语言来解释我们如何连接并与大Query数据进行交谈。然后，我们将讨论每个组件以及它们的设置方式，然后我们将研究整个事情的工作原理。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Engineering for AI-Native Architectures: Designing Scalable, Cost-Optimized Data Pipelines to Power GenAI, Agentic AI, and Real-Time Insights】AI-NATIANITERTURES的数据工程：设计可扩展的，成本优化的数据管道为Power Genai，Agesic AI和实时见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-engineering-for-ai-native-architectures</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-data-engineering-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Data Engineering: Scaling Intelligence With the Modern Data Stack&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The data engineering landscape has undergone a fundamental transformation with a complete reimagining of how data flows through organizations. Traditional business intelligence (BI) pipelines were built for looking backward, answering questions like &#34;How did we perform last quarter?&#34; Today&#39;s AI-native architectures demand systems that can feed real-time insights to recommendation engines, provide context to large language models, and maintain the massive vector stores that power retrieval-augmented generation (RAG).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ font-size：17px;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;编辑注：以下是为Dzone的2025年趋势报告编写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/link/link/link/link/2025-tr-data-tr-data-wribeering-contributor-contributor-contributor-utor-contributor-utor-contributor-utor-contributor-utor-contributor-article-concon-no noore =” noore&gt;工程：使用现代数据堆栈缩放智能&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;数据工程格局经历了基本的转变，并完整地重新构想了数据如何通过组织流动。传统的商业智能（BI）管道是为了向后看的，回答了诸如“我们上季度如何表现？”之类的问题。当今的AI-Native架构需求系统，可以将实时见解提供给推荐引擎，为大型语言模型提供背景，并维护庞大的向量存储，以获取功率检索功能增强的生成（RAG）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Not only AI: What Else Drives Team Performance Today?】不仅是AI：还有什么驱动今天的团队表现？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/improving-team-output-without-more-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today’s world is obsessed with AI, and performance conversations often center on models, automation, and tooling. But when it comes to real, sustainable productivity gains, it’s not just about adding more AI. It&#39;s about designing better systems. In high-speed product environments (whether driven by AI or not) execution is urgent, but effectiveness depends on how you enable people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;At GlobalLogic, I joined an early-stage &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/trendreports/generative-ai&#34;&gt;GenAI&lt;/a&gt; product team. The stakes were high, timelines were tight, and yet, within three months, we boosted team performance by 20%. But we didn’t get there by chasing every shiny AI solution. We got there by doing the basics right: building clarity, creating smart feedback loops, and empowering decision-makers.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;当今世界对AI着迷，性能对话通常以模型，自动化和工具为中心。但是，当涉及到真实，可持续的生产力提高时，这不仅仅是添加更多的AI。这是关于设计更好的系统。在高速产品环境（无论是否由AI驱动）中，执行是紧迫的，但有效性取决于您如何使人。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在Globallogic上，我加入了一个早期&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/trendreports/generative-ai”&gt; genai &lt;/aai &lt;/aai &lt;/a&gt;产品团队。赌注很高，时间表很紧，但是在三个月内，我们将团队绩效提高了20％。但是我们没有通过追逐所有闪亮的AI解决方案来到那里。我们通过正确的基础来到达那里：建立清晰度，创建智能反馈循环并赋予决策者权力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MCP Client-Server Integration With Semantic Kernel】MCP客户端服务器与语义内核集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mcp-client-server-integration-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern AI applications gain real popularity when they translate natural language prompts to execute external services. This article describes the basic understanding of the key components: semantic kernel, Azure OpenAI, and MCP Client-Server. It also describes the implementation to connect the Semantic Kernel to an Azure-hosted OpenAI resource so that an LLM can be queried directly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, you will learn how to create an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mcp-client-agent-architecture-amp-implementation&#34;&gt;MCP Client&lt;/a&gt;, run the MCP Server, and expose the MCP tools. The tools that are discovered can then be registered as kernel functions in the Semantic Kernel and thus, augment the LLM with the ability to execute external tools as a Service that are provided through the MCP Server.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代AI应用程序翻译自然语言提示执行外部服务时，它们就会获得真正的知名度。本文介绍了关键组件的基本理解：语义内核，Azure OpenAI和MCP客户端服务器。它还描述了将语义内核连接到Azure托管的OpenAI资源的实现，以便可以直接查询LLM。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，您将学习如何创建&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mcp-client-agent-archituction-archituction-architecture-amp-implementation”&gt; mcp client &lt;/a&gt;，运行MCP服务器，并曝光MCP工具。然后，发现的工具可以在语义内核中注册为内核函数，因此可以通过MCP服务器提供的外部工具来增加LLM的LLM。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting Started With PyIceberg: A Pythonic Approach to Managing Apache Iceberg Tables】Pyiceberg入门：一种管理Apache Iceberg桌子的Pythonic方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/managing-iceberg-tables-with-pyiceberg</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;740&#34; data-start=&#34;454&#34;&gt;Modern data platforms are evolving rapidly—driven by a need for scalability, flexibility, and analytics at scale. Lakehouse architecture sits at the center of this evolution, combining the low-cost storage of data lakes with the reliability and structure of data warehouses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1147&#34; data-start=&#34;742&#34;&gt;To power these &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-of-data-lakehouses-apache-iceberg&#34;&gt;lakehouses&lt;/a&gt;, organizations are turning to open table formats like Apache Iceberg. Originally developed at Netflix, Apache Iceberg was built to manage petabyte-scale analytics in cloud object storage. It brings database-style features—ACID transactions, schema evolution, partition pruning, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-data-time-travel&#34;&gt;time travel&lt;/a&gt;—to large-scale files stored in systems like Amazon S3 or Azure Data Lake.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 740” data-start =“ 454”&gt;现代数据平台正在迅速发展，这是由于对可伸缩性，灵活性和分析的需求驱动。 Lakehouse建筑位于此演变的中心，将数据湖的低成本存储与数据仓库的可靠性和结构相结合。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1147” data-start =“ 742”&gt;为这些&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-of-data-lakehouses-apache-aceberg-”&gt; lakehouses &lt;/a&gt; Apache Iceberg最初是在Netflix开发的，旨在管理Cloud Object Storage中的Petabyte尺度分析。它带来了数据库风格的功能 - 酸交易，架构进化，分区修剪和&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-data time-time-travel”&gt;时间旅行&lt;/a&gt;  - 在像Amazon S3或Azure数据湖等系统中存储的大型文件&lt;/a&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Program a Quantum Computer: A Beginner&#39;s Guide】如何编程量子计算机：初学者指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-program-a-quantum-computer-a-beginners-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-discover=&#34;true&#34; href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-computing-unleashing-the-power-of-a-new-er&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Quantum computing&lt;/a&gt; might sound familiar, but have you ever tried using it yourself? Despite the reputation for complex math, the fundamentals of quantum computing are surprisingly easy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide offers a beginner-friendly walkthrough for working with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/unraveling-the-power-of-quantum-bits-a-glimpse-int&#34;&gt;qubits&lt;/a&gt;. You’ll learn how to build your first &lt;strong&gt;quantum program&lt;/strong&gt; and see it generate numeric output, step by step.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a data-discover =“ true” href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-computing-unleashing-unleashing-the-power-the-power-the-power-of-a-new-er“ rel =“ noopener”&gt;量子计算&lt;/a&gt;听起来可能很熟悉，但是您自己尝试过吗？尽管复杂数学的声誉，但量子计算的基本面非常容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南提供了与&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/unraveling-the-power-the-power-the-power-the-power----------------------------------------------------- quantum-bits-a-glimpse-int”&gt; Qubits&#39;&gt; Qubits &lt;/a&gt;一起提供初学者友好的演练。您将学习如何构建第一个&lt;strong&gt; Quantum程序&lt;/strong&gt;并逐步生成数字输出。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Prompt Engineering Wasn&#39;t Enough; Context Engineering Is What Came Next】及时的工程还不够。上下文工程是接下来的</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/prompt-engineering-context-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Over the last few years, the conversation around AI has slowly shifted from prompt engineering to something more structured and more powerful: context engineering.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you are working on a chatbot that answers questions around a knowledge base or working on an agentic AI framework that is very complex, the way you architect context depends entirely on the problem you are solving. Simply put, context complexity scales with the task uncertainty. Simple, predictable tasks require minimal context structuring, while complex, multi-step tasks require sophisticated context orchestration.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在过去的几年中，围绕AI的对话已逐渐从及时的工程转变为更具结构化和更强大的东西：上下文工程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您处理聊天机器人时，该聊天机器人围绕知识库回答问题或处理非常复杂的代理AI框架时，您的架构架构上下文的方式完全取决于您正在解决的问题。简而言之，与任务不确定性相关的上下文复杂性尺度。简单，可预测的任务需要最小的上下文结构，而复杂的多步任务需要复杂的上下文编排。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bridging the Gap: Integrating Graphic Design Principles into Front-End Development】弥合差距：将图形设计原理整合到前端开发中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/graphic-design-for-developers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;The line between design and development is becoming increasingly blurred. Websites and applications no longer compete solely based on functionality—they must also deliver intuitive, visually appealing user experiences. For front-end developers, understanding and applying basic graphic design principles is no longer a luxury but a necessity. This blog explores how developers can harness design fundamentals to create beautiful, effective user interfaces that not only function well but also delight users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Need for Design Literacy in Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, the design and development worlds were siloed. Designers handled aesthetics, while developers focused on code. But as &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-agile-workflows-in-dynamic-environments&#34;&gt;agile workflows&lt;/a&gt;, collaborative tools, and lean UX practices became the norm, the need for developers to be visually literate grew.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;设计和开发之间的界线变得越来越模糊。网站和应用程序不再仅基于功能竞争，它们还必须提供直观，视觉上吸引人的用户体验。对于前端开发人员而言，理解和应用基本的图形设计原理不再是奢侈品，而是必要的。该博客探讨了开发人员如何利用设计基础来创建漂亮，有效的用户界面，不仅功能良好，而且使用户感到满意。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;开发设计素养的需求&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统上，设计和开发世界被孤立。设计师处理了美学，而开发人员则专注于代码。但是，由于&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-agile-workflows-in-dynamic-encronments”&gt;敏捷的工作流程&lt;/a&gt;，协作工具和精益UX的实践成为规范，需要开发者，因此可以从视觉上识字。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Amadeus Cloud Migration on Ampere Altra Instances】Amadeus云迁移在Ampere Altra实例上</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/amadeus-cloud-migration-ampere-altra</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;“You might not be familiar with Amadeus, because it is a B2B company [but] when you search for a flight or a hotel on the Internet, there is a good chance that you are using an Amadeus-powered service behind the scenes,” according to Didier Spezia, a cloud architect for Amadeus. Amadeus is a leading global travel IT company, powering the activities of many actors in the travel industry: airlines, hotel chains, travel agencies, airports, among others.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of Amadeus’ activities is to provide shopping services to search and price flights for travel agencies and companies like Kayak or Expedia. Amadeus also supports more advanced capabilities, such as budget-driven queries and calendar-constrained queries, which require pre-calculating multi-dimensional indexes. Searching for suitable flights with available seats among many airlines is surprisingly difficult.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;“您可能不熟悉Amadeus，因为它是一家B2B公司[但是]当您在互联网上搜索航班或酒店时，您很有可能在幕后使用Amadeus驱动的服务，” Didier Spezia表示，Amadeus的云建筑师Didier Spezia说。 Amadeus是一家领先的全球旅行IT公司，为许多演出行业中的许多演员的活动提供动力：航空公司，酒店连锁店，旅行社，机场等。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Amadeus的一项活动是为旅行社和像皮划艇或Expedia等公司的搜索和价格航班提供购物服务。 Amadeus还支持更高级的功能，例如预算驱动的查询和日历约束的查询，这些查询需要预先计算的多维指数。在许多航空公司中搜索合适的航班带有可用座位的航班非常困难。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>