<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Interference in A/B Tests】A/B 测试中的干扰</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/interference-in-ab-tests</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A/B testing is the gold standard for online experimentation used by most companies to test out their product features. Whereas A/B test experimentation works just fine in most settings, it is particularly susceptible to interference bias, particularly in the case of online marketplaces or social networks. In this article, we aim to look at the situations with interference bias and some potential ways to mitigate its effect on evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;SUTVA, the Fundamental Assumption of A/B Testing and Its Violations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;One of the fundamental assumptions of A/B Testing is SUTVA — Stable Unit Treatment Value Assumption. The potential outcome of treatment in the randomization unit depends only on the treatment they receive and not on the treatments assigned to other subjects.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A/B 测试是大多数公司用来测试其产品功能的在线实验的黄金标准。尽管 A/B 测试实验在大多数情况下效果都很好，但它特别容易受到干扰偏差的影响，尤其是在在线市场或社交网络的情况下。在本文中，我们旨在研究存在干扰偏差的情况以及减轻其对评估影响的一些潜在方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;SUTVA，A/B 测试的基本假设及其违规&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A/B 测试的基本假设之一是 SUTVA — 稳定单位处理值假设。随机化单元中治疗的潜在结果仅取决于他们接受的治疗，而不取决于分配给其他受试者的治疗。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Merge Multiple PDFs in MuleSoft】在 MuleSoft 中合并多个 PDF</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/merge-multiple-pdfs-in-mulesoft</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Suppose there is a scenario where you have to merge multiple PDFs into one PDF and send the merged PDF as a response back to the source system or store the merged PDF in a file location. In this article, you will learn how to do this. There is no such &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/custom-icon-for-mule-4-custom-connector&#34;&gt;connector in MuleSoft&lt;/a&gt; that you can use to merge the PDFs. You will have to use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; library &lt;strong&gt;org.apache.pdfbox.multipdf&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;to merge the PDFs. It contains all necessary Java libraries for merging multiple PDFs into one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Implementation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Step 1&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Add the dependency as shown below in &lt;strong&gt;pom.xml:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;假设有一种情况，您必须将多个 PDF 合并为一个 PDF，并将合并的 PDF 作为响应发送回源系统或将合并的 PDF 存储在文件位置。在本文中，您将学习如何执行此操作。 MuleSoft 中没有可用于合并 PDF 的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/custom-icon-for-mule-4-custom-connector&#34;&gt;连接器&lt;/a&gt;。您必须使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 库&lt;strong&gt;org.apache.pdfbox.multipdf &lt;/strong&gt;来合并 PDF 。它包含将多个 PDF 合并为一个所需的所有 Java 库。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;实施&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;步骤 1&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;strong&gt;pom.xml中添加如下所示的依赖项：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ensuring Data Integrity Through Anomaly Detection: Essential Tools for Data Engineers】通过异常检测确保数据完整性：数据工程师的基本工具</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-integrity-through-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the trending landscape of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt; and AI, companies are tirelessly innovating to deliver cutting-edge solutions for their customers. However, amidst this rapid evolution, ensuring a robust data universe characterized by high quality and integrity is indispensable. While much emphasis is often placed on refining AI models, the significance of pristine datasets can sometimes be overshadowed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article sets out to explore some of the essential tools required by organizations in the domain of data engineering to efficiently improve &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/strategies-for-governing-data-quality-accuracy-and&#34;&gt;data quality&lt;/a&gt; and triage/analyze data for effective business-centric machine learning analytics, reporting, and anomaly detection. To illustrate these tools/frameworks and their importance, let us consider a scenario within the fintech industry.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习&lt;/a&gt;和人工智能的趋势中，公司正在孜孜不倦地创新，为以下领域提供尖端解决方案：他们的客户。然而，在这种快速发展的过程中，确保以高质量和完整性为特征的强大数据世界是必不可少的。虽然人们通常非常重视改进人工智能模型，但原始数据集的重要性有时可能会被掩盖。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文旨在探讨数据工程领域组织有效提高&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/strategies-for-governing-data-quality”所需的一些基本工具-准确性和&#34;&gt;数据质量&lt;/a&gt;和分类/分析数据，以实现有效的以业务为中心的机器学习分析、报告和异常检测。为了说明这些工具/框架及其重要性，让我们考虑金融科技行业内的一个场景。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The One-Pixel Threat: How Minuscule Changes Can Fool Deep Learning Systems】单像素威胁：微小的变化如何欺骗深度学习系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-one-pixel-threat</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI vulnerabilities: From medical diagnostics to autonomous vehicles, discover how changing a single pixel can compromise advanced deep learning models and explore the critical challenges to securing our AI-powered future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-ai-machine-learning-and-deep-learning&#34;&gt;Deep learning (DL)&lt;/a&gt; is a fundamental component of Artificial Intelligence (AI). It aims to enable machines to perform tasks that require decision-making mechanisms that tend to approximate those of human reasoning. DL models are at the heart of many advanced applications, such as medical diagnostics and autonomous vehicle driving.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能漏洞：从医疗诊断到自动驾驶汽车，了解改变单个像素如何影响先进的深度学习模型，并探索确保人工智能驱动的未来面临的关键挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-ai-machine-learning-and-deep-learning&#34;&gt;深度学习 (DL)&lt;/a&gt; 是人工智能的基本组成部分 (人工智能）。它的目的是使机器能够执行需要接近人类推理机制的决策机制的任务。深度学习模型是许多高级应用的核心，例如医疗诊断和自动驾驶汽车。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【3 Reasons Why VPs of Engineering Are Choosing Low-Code】工程副总裁选择低代码的 3 个原因</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/3-reasons-vps-of-engineering-are-choosing-low-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I often hear the phrases &#34;Low code is not flexible&#34; and &#34;Scaling is the major issue with low code&#34; when talking to developers who have used it to build complex use cases like food ordering apps, e-commerce apps, and tools like that. For any type of application building, it&#39;s important to understand who you are developing it for, what is the ROI, and what they are going to achieve.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/low-code-application-development&#34;&gt;Low code&lt;/a&gt; is something that can be best used when you want to build apps for internal use, rich data dashboards, CMS apps, or any app for operational needs within your organization. Developers, the primary creators, benefit hugely from pre-built UI components, ready databases, and API integrations. Important stat: &lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-11-10-gartner-says-cloud-will-be-the-centerpiece-of-new-digital-experiences&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;70% of new applications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; created by enterprises are expected to utilize low-code or no-code technologies, stats Gartner findings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在与使用它构建复杂用例（例如食品订购应用程序、电子商务应用程序和应用程序）的开发人员交谈时，我经常听到“低代码不灵活”和“扩展是低代码的主要问题”这样的说法。之类的工具。对于任何类型的应用程序构建，重要的是要了解您正在为谁开发它、投资回报率是多少以及他们将实现什么目标。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/low-code-application-development&#34;&gt;低代码&lt;/a&gt;是当您想要构建供内部使用的应用程序时最好使用的东西，丰富的数据仪表板、CMS 应用程序或满足组织内运营需求的任何应用程序。开发人员（主要创建者）可以从预构建的 UI 组件、现成的数据库和 API 集成中获益匪浅。重要统计数据：&lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2021-11-10-gartner-says-cloud- will-be-the-centerpiece-of-new-digital-experiences&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;70% 的企业创建的新应用&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;预计将Gartner 调查结果显示，利用低代码或无代码技术。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agile-Regulated Industries?】敏捷监管行业？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agile-regulated-industries</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are there agile-regulated industries, or is that an oxymoron?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I received a project alert from an organization looking for a Scrum Master with “at least two years knowledge of information systems for rail and public transport travelers.”&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;是否存在敏捷监管的行业，或者这是一个矛盾的说法？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近，我收到了一家组织的项目提醒，该组织正在寻找一位“至少拥有两年铁路和公共交通旅客信息系统知识”的 Scrum Master。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Navigating BNPL Integration: Key Steps and Best Practices for Developers】BNPL 集成导航：开发人员的关键步骤和最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/bnpl-integration-key-steps-and-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-buy-now-pay-later-payment-solution&#34;&gt;Buy Now, Pay Later (BNPL) solutions&lt;/a&gt; are altering the way in which clients connect to payment systems by offering financial flexibility and enhancing the checkout experience. This guide offers developers and architects comprehensive knowledge on integrating your checkout process with BNPL as well as technical details, best practices, and common challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Importance of BNPL for Developers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Enhanced Conversion Rates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The abandonment of carts is reduced by the use of BNPL solutions that provide flexible payment options; hence, making it possible for users to complete their transactions. Users will not easily abandon their carts due to high upfront costs whenever payments can be broken down into small manageable amounts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-buy-now-pay-later- payment-solution&#34;&gt;先买后付 (BNPL) 解决方案&lt;/a&gt;正在改变通过提供财务灵活性和增强结账体验，客户连接支付系统的方式。本指南为开发人员和架构师提供了有关将结账流程与 BNPL 集成的全面知识，以及技术细节、最佳实践和常见挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;BNPL 对开发者的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;提高转化率&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;使用提供灵活支付选项的 BNPL 解决方案可以减少购物车的废弃情况；因此，使用户可以完成交易。只要可以将付款分解为可管理的小额金额，用户就不会因为高昂的前期成本而轻易放弃购物车。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【My Journey to Master SQL Data Analysis】我的 SQL 数据分析之旅</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/my-journey-to-master-sql-data-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Dealing with sales data can feel like a task especially when you&#39;re trying to extract insights for important business decisions. In this article, we&#39;ll delve into the experience of a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-data-analytics-understanding-data-analytic&#34;&gt;data analyst&lt;/a&gt; tackling these challenges and delve into why &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sql-commands-a-brief-guide&#34;&gt;mastering SQL&lt;/a&gt; is key to achieving success. By the end, you&#39;ll grasp the role that data analysts play and how they can transform data into actionable information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the Role of a Data Analyst&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data analysts often go unnoticed in organizations. They play a role. Their job involves sorting through volumes of data to identify patterns, trends, and insights that drive decision-making processes. Whether it&#39;s analyzing sales figures, customer feedback, or market research findings, data analysts are responsible for making sense of this information. However, this isn&#39;t a task. This demands a specific skill set that includes a solid grasp of SQL (Structured Query Language).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;处理销售数据感觉像是一项任务，尤其是当您尝试提取重要业务决策的见解时。在本文中，我们将深入探讨&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-data-analytics-understanding-data-analytic&#34;&gt;数据分析师&lt;/a&gt;处理问题的经验这些挑战并深入探讨为什么&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sql-commands-a-brief-guide&#34;&gt;掌握 SQL&lt;/a&gt; 是取得成功的关键。最后，您将了解数据分析师所扮演的角色以及他们如何将数据转换为可操作的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解数据分析师的角色&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据分析师在组织中经常被忽视。他们发挥作用。他们的工作包括对大量数据进行排序，以识别驱动决策过程的模式、趋势和见解。无论是分析销售数据、客户反馈还是市场研究结果，数据分析师都有责任理解这些信息。然而，这不是一个任务。这需要一套特定的技能，其中包括对 SQL（结构化查询语言）的扎实掌握。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging Time Series Databases for Cutting-Edge Analytics: Specialized Software for Providing Timely Insights at Scale】利用时间序列数据库进行前沿分析：提供大规模及时洞察的专业软件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/leverage-time-series-databases-analytics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-database-systems-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Database Systems: Modernization for Data-Driven Architectures&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Time series data has become an essential part of data collection in various fields due to its ability to capture trends, patterns, and anomalies. Through continuous or periodic observation, organizations are able to track how key metrics are changing over time. This simple abstraction powers a broad range of use cases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-database-systems-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;数据库系统：数据驱动架构的现代化&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。 p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;时间序列数据因其捕捉趋势、模式和异常的能力而成为各个领域数据收集的重要组成部分。通过连续或定期观察，组织能够跟踪关键指标如何随时间变化。这种简单的抽象为广泛的用例提供了支持。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 10:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Fix the OWASP Top 10 Vulnerability in Angular 18.1.1v】如何修复 Angular 18.1.1v 中的 OWASP Top 10 漏洞</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fix-the-owasp-top-10-vulnerability-in-angular-1811v</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-id=&#34;c54ea437-14f1-455a-a6da-1e6dae0233f0&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;The latest release of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/angularjs-essentials&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt;, which is presently version 18.1.1, offers a wide range of features for developing robust and scalable web applications in Angular. However, safety continues to be of concern. In this article, we will discuss the configurations and see examples of how to mitigate these vulnerabilities in an Angular web application 18.1.1v in detail.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-id=&#34;c54ea437-14f1-455a-a6da-1e6dae0233f0&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Injection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;14af506e-398c-4b47-848f-b2bfbce6321a&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/code-injection-examples-and-prevention&#34;&gt;Injection flaws&lt;/a&gt; (SQL, NoSQL, and OS command injection) occur when untrusted data is send to an interpreter situated among a machine or query.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-id=&#34;c54ea437-14f1-455a-a6da-1e6dae0233f0&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;最新版本的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/angularjs -essentials&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Angular&lt;/a&gt; 目前版本为 18.1.1，提供了广泛的功能，用于在 Angular 中开发健壮且可扩展的 Web 应用程序。然而，安全仍然令人担忧。在本文中，我们将讨论配置并查看如何详细缓解 Angular Web 应用程序 18.1.1v 中这些漏洞的示例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-id=&#34;c54ea437-14f1-455a-a6da-1e6dae0233f0&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;注入&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;14af506e-398c-4b47-848f-b2bfbce6321a&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/code-injection-examples -and-prevention&#34;&gt;当不受信任的数据发送到位于机器或查询之间的解释器时，会出现注入缺陷&lt;/a&gt;（SQL、NoSQL 和操作系统命令注入）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>