<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Evaluating AI Vulnerability Detection: How Reliable Are LLMs for Secure Coding?】评估人工智能漏洞检测：法学硕士在安全编码方面有多可靠？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-vulnerability-detection-llm-reliability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Large language models (LLMs)&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;can be used to generate source code, and these AI coding assistants have changed the landscape for how we produce software.&lt;/span&gt; Speeding up boilerplate tasks like syntax checking, generating test cases, and suggesting bug fixes accelerates the time to deliver production-ready code. What about securing our code from vulnerabilities?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If AI can understand entire repositories within a context window, one might jump to the conclusion that they can also be used to replace traditional security scanning tools that are based on static analysis of source code.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;可用于生成源代码，这些 AI 编码助手改变了我们生产软件的方式。&lt;/span&gt;加快语法检查、生成测试用例和建议错误修复等样板任务，可以加快交付可投入生产的代码的时间。如何保护我们的代码免受漏洞影响？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果人工智能可以理解上下文窗口中的整个存储库，人们可能会得出这样的结论：它们也可以用来取代基于源代码静态分析的传统安全扫描工具。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【5 Agent CI/CD Evaluation Best Practices】5 代理 CI/CD 评估最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/5-agent-cicd-evaluation-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Building reliability into your production applications isn’t flashy, but evaluations are critical to success.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is especially true when it comes to testing the impact of system changes, as small tweaks to your AI agents — like prompt versions, agent orchestration, and model changes — &amp;nbsp;can have a large impact.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;将可靠性构建到生产应用程序中并不华而不实，但评估对于成功至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在测试系统更改的影响时尤其如此，因为对 AI 代理的小调整（例如提示版本、代理编排和模型更改）可能会产生很大的影响。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Spectre and Meltdown: How Modern CPUs Traded Security for Speed】幽灵与崩溃：现代 CPU 如何以安全性换取速度</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/modern-cpu-security-vs-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;594&#34; data-start=&#34;309&#34;&gt;For years, CPU designers focused on making processors faster. Techniques like out-of-order and speculative execution became standard to keep every part of the chip busy. These tricks helped achieve huge performance gains, but they also opened the door to a new kind of vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;882&#34; data-start=&#34;596&#34;&gt;In 2018, two major security flaws, Spectre and Meltdown, showed that the very features that made processors efficient could be used to steal private data from memory. These attacks broke some of the most fundamental assumptions about isolation between programs and the operating system.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;594&#34; data-start=&#34;309&#34;&gt;多年来，CPU 设计人员一直致力于提高处理器速度。乱序和推测执行等技术成为标准，以保持芯片的每个部分都忙碌。这些技巧帮助实现了巨大的性能提升，但它们也为一种新的漏洞打开了大门。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;882&#34; data-start=&#34;596&#34;&gt;2018 年，两个重大安全漏洞 Spectre 和 Meltdown 表明，提高处理器效率的功能可用于从内存中窃取私有数据。这些攻击打破了有关程序和操作系统之间隔离的一些最基本的假设。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Ingestion Using Logstash: PostgreSQL to Elasticsearch】使用 Logstash 进行数据摄取：PostgreSQL 到 Elasticsearch</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/logstash-postgresql-to-elasticsearch</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;What Is Logstash?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logstash is an open-source data processing pipeline from Elastic. It is being used to ingest, transform, and ship data to different sources, including Elasticsearch, Kafka, flat files, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logstash pipeline includes three different processes:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;什么是 Logstash？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logstash 是 Elastic 的开源数据处理管道。它用于提取、转换数据并将其发送到不同的来源，包括 Elasticsearch、Kafka、平面文件等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logstash 管道包括三个不同的进程：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Best Practices for Migrating Data From Legacy Systems With AI】使用 AI 从旧系统迁移数据的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-data-migration-legacy-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Data migration is one of the most challenging and high-risk parts of legacy system modernization. No wonder engineers and business leaders are experimenting with modern tools to speed up this process. AI is among the most promising.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, I will share my experience with AI-powered data migration, including what worked well and key lessons learned along the way.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;数据迁移是遗留系统现代化中最具挑战性和高风险的部分之一。难怪工程师和商业领袖正在尝试使用现代工具来加速这一过程。人工智能是最有前途的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我将分享我在人工智能驱动的数据迁移方面的经验，包括行之有效的方法以及在此过程中学到的重要经验教训。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How the Craft of Software Engineering is Evolving With AI Advancement】软件工程技术如何随着人工智能的进步而发展</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolving-crafts-of-software-engineering-with-a</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence is transforming the nature of software engineering, shifting it from a primarily code-centric discipline toward one that emphasizes systems thinking, verification, and orchestration. Emerging paradigms such as “vibe coding” and defensive AI programming illustrate how the field now demands not just technical mastery but also a broader understanding of how intelligent systems interact and evolve. While AI offers unprecedented productivity gains to those who integrate it effectively, engineers must cultivate the discernment and methodological structure required to maintain reliability, quality, and correctness at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Evolution from Builders to Curators&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Software engineering has long been associated primarily with coding. Entry-level engineers focus on churning out code, and as they grow in their careers, they learn more about system design, architecture, etc. But with the rise of AI-assisted coding tools, that primary identity is shifting.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;摘要&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能正在改变软件工程的性质，将其从主要以代码为中心的学科转变为强调系统思考、验证和编排的学科。 “氛围编码”和防御性人工智能编程等新兴范式表明，该领域现在不仅需要掌握技术，还需要对智能系统如何交互和发展有更广泛的理解。虽然人工智能为那些有效集成人工智能的人提供了前所未有的生产力提升，但工程师必须培养维持大规模可靠性、质量和正确性所需的洞察力和方法结构。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;从构建者到策展人的演变&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;软件工程长期以来主要与编码相关。入门级工程师专注于编写代码，随着他们职业生涯的成长，他们会更多地了解系统设计、架构等。但随着人工智能辅助编码工具的兴起，这种主要身份正在发生变化。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Proactive vs Reactive: Rethinking Your AWS Monitoring Approach】主动与被动：重新思考您的 AWS 监控方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/proactive-vs-reactive-rethinking-aws-monitoring</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Keeping your AWS environment healthy is no longer just about responding to alerts when something goes wrong. As workloads scale and get more complex, relying on reactive monitoring leaves you exposed to downtime, security risks, and performance issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Forward-thinking teams are reevaluating their AWS monitoring strategies — transitioning from reactive to proactive monitoring that prevents problems before they arise. This is not just a technical upgrade, it’s a strategic shift in how cloud architects, CTOs, and DevOps leaders ensure reliability, optimize resources, and security across modern infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;保持 AWS 环境健康不再只是在出现问题时响应警报。随着工作负载规模扩大并变得更加复杂，依赖被动监控会让您面临停机、安全风险和性能问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;具有前瞻性思维的团队正在重新评估他们的 AWS 监控策略 — 从被动监控转变为主动监控，以预防问题出现。这不仅仅是一次技术升级，更是云架构师、CTO 和 DevOps 领导者如何确保现代基础设施的可靠性、优化资源和安全性的战略转变。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring MCP, A2A, and Functional Calling: The Modern Innovations for Enterprise LLM Architecture】探索 MCP、A2A 和功能调用：企业 LLM 架构的现代创新</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-mcp-a2a-and-functional-calling-the-moder</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence is moving away from experimental prototypes to mission-critical enterprise-level infrastructure. Creating systems that work under the constraints and requirements present in the enterprise world has never been more challenging for developers. There are three innovative architectural patterns that will define production-grade AI solutions: model-context protocol (MCP), agent-to-agent Protocol (A2A), and functional calling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model-Context Protocol (MCP): Context Execution Modality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LLMs are limited in their handling of state, memory specific to the application, and context window. MCP addresses these issues by treating context as an architectural component. In MCP, context is not static but dynamic, based on sophisticated retrieval that injects the relevant data just in time.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能正在从实验原型转向关键任务的企业级基础设施。对于开发人员来说，创建在企业世界中存在的约束和要求下工作的系统从未如此具有挑战性。三种创新架构模式将定义生产级人工智能解决方案：模型上下文协议（MCP）、代理到代理协议（A2A）和功能调用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;模型上下文协议 (MCP)：上下文执行模式&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LLM 在处理状态、特定于应用程序的内存和上下文窗口方面受到限制。 MCP 通过将上下文视为架构组件来解决这些问题。在 MCP 中，上下文不是静态的，而是动态的，基于及时注入相关数据的复杂检索。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Smarter Systems: Architecting AI Agents for Real-World Tasks】构建更智能的系统：为现实世界的任务构建人工智能代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-smarter-systems-architecting-ai-agents-fo</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI agents are emerging as powerful building blocks for modern software systems. An &lt;strong&gt;AI agent&lt;/strong&gt; is an autonomous software component that can observe its environment, make decisions, and act towards achieving a goal. &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Crucially, it operates with a degree of independence using real-time data, adapting to changing conditions, &lt;em&gt;“unlike traditional scripts or workflows,”&lt;/em&gt; which follow fixed logic.&lt;/span&gt; This flexibility makes AI agents ideal for &lt;strong&gt;real-world tasks&lt;/strong&gt; that involve complex, dynamic workflows. In this article, we’ll explore how to architect AI agents for workflow automation in a way that senior engineers can appreciate – focusing on clear language, practical tools (like Python’s LangChain and FastAPI), and sound engineering practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;AI Agents in Workflow Automation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One high-impact application of AI agents is &lt;strong&gt;workflow automation&lt;/strong&gt;. These agents can handle routine, repetitive tasks across business processes – from triaging support tickets and updating CRM records to validating form submissions or flagging errors in system logs. For example, instead of a human manually sorting incoming emails or a static script moving files on a schedule, an AI agent can &lt;em&gt;understand&lt;/em&gt; the content and context, then decide the appropriate action. Unlike traditional automation tools that rigidly follow pre-defined rules, an AI agent adjusts its behavior based on context and goals. This means that if conditions change (for example, a new type of support issue arises), the agent can reason about how to handle it rather than needing a manual code update. The result is smarter workflow automation that can save time and reduce errors in real-world operations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能代理正在成为现代软件系统的强大构建模块。 &lt;strong&gt;人工智能代理&lt;/strong&gt;是一种自主软件组件，可以观察其环境、做出决策并采取行动以实现目标。 &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;至关重要的是，它使用实时数据以一定程度的独立性运行，适应不断变化的条件，&lt;em&gt;“与传统脚本或工作流程不同，&lt;/em&gt;遵循固定的逻辑。&lt;/span&gt;这种灵活性使人工智能代理非常适合涉及复杂、动态工作流程的&lt;strong&gt;现实世界任务&lt;/strong&gt;。在本文中，我们将探讨如何以高级工程师能够欣赏的方式构建用于工作流自动化的人工智能代理 - 重点关注清晰的语言、实用的工具（如 Python 的 LangChain 和 FastAPI）以及完善的工程实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;工作流自动化中的人工智能代理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能代理的一个高影响力应用是&lt;strong&gt;工作流程自动化&lt;/strong&gt;。这些代理可以处理跨业务流程的例行重复性任务 - 从分类支持票证和更新 CRM 记录到验证表单提交或标记系统日志中的错误。例如，人工智能代理可以&lt;em&gt;理解&lt;/em&gt;内容和上下文，然后决定适当的操作，而不是人工对传入的电子邮件进行手动排序或静态脚本按计划移动文件。与严格遵循预定义规则的传统自动化工具不同，人工智能代理会根据上下文和目标调整其行为。这意味着，如果情况发生变化（例如，出现新型支持问题），代理可以推理如何处理它，而不需要手动更新代码。其结果是更智能的工作流程自动化，可以节省时间并减少实际操作中的错误。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data-Driven Enterprise Apps: How Laravel Simplifies Analytics Integration】数据驱动的企业应用程序：Laravel 如何简化分析集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-driven-enterprise-apps-how-laravel-simplifies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Data has become the very foundation of modern digital systems; it is the very essence of decision-making, innovation, and, ultimately, growth in the contemporary business world. Companies make extensive use of analytics to gain a deeper understanding of their customers, improve business operations, and make more accurate predictions. On the other hand, integrating data analysis into enterprise applications presents numerous challenges, including the need for scalability and flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;At this point, Laravel, the favored PHP framework, comes into play as the ideal tool. Laravel is widely regarded for its readability and ease of hiring Laravel developers. It is a structured method of building powerful, data-driven enterprise applications. And most importantly, it simplifies the process of embedding analytics, which is becoming increasingly vital in enterprise app development.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;数据已成为现代数字系统的基础；它是当代商业世界决策、创新以及最终增长的本质。公司广泛使用分析来更深入地了解客户、改善业务运营并做出更准确的预测。另一方面，将数据分析集成到企业应用程序中会带来许多挑战，包括对可扩展性和灵活性的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;此时，备受青睐的 PHP 框架 Laravel 作为理想的工具开始发挥作用。 Laravel 因其可读性和易于雇用 Laravel 开发人员而受到广泛认可。它是一种构建强大的、数据驱动的企业应用程序的结构化方法。最重要的是，它简化了嵌入分析的过程，这在企业应用程序开发中变得越来越重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>