<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Call Graphs for Code Exploration Using Tree-Sitter】使用 Tree-Sitter 构建用于代码探索的调用图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/call-graphs-code-exploration-tree-sitter</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Code exploration for large legacy codebases is a heavy-lifting task. Manual exploration can become error-prone and time-consuming. Automated data collection and visualization can ease the process to some extent. To extract key insights like Code composition, LoC, etc., we may need to use various data collection tools. However, using those tools is challenging as most of them are commercial. The available FOSS tools either support only smaller code sizes or only support a limited set of technology stacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One such tool is Doxygen, which generates documentation out of codebases and helps extract various metadata elements that can be processed and used for further exploration. However, the challenge with this tool is that it allows very little control over how it collects data and is very heavy to run on large code bases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大型遗留代码库的代码探索是一项繁重的任务。手动探索可能容易出错且耗时。自动化数据收集和可视化可以在一定程度上简化该过程。为了提取代码组成、LoC 等关键见解，我们可能需要使用各种数据收集工具。然而，使用这些工具具有挑战性，因为它们大多数都是商业工具。可用的 FOSS 工具要么仅支持较小的代码大小，要么仅支持一组有限的技术堆栈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;Doxygen 就是这样的工具之一，它从代码库中生成文档，并帮助提取可以处理和用于进一步探索的各种元数据元素。然而，该工具面临的挑战是它对数据收集方式的控制非常少，并且在大型代码库上运行非常繁重。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Phased Migration Strategy for Zero Downtime in Systems】系统零停机的分阶段迁移策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/phased-migration-strategy-zero-downtime</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In distributed systems, multiple services work together to complete a task, each managed by different teams and evolving independently. This often leads to the need for dependency migrations, such as database schema updates, external service upgrades, or changes in data sources. These migrations are a crucial part of the development lifecycle and require thorough planning and execution to prevent rollbacks, data inconsistencies, and operational disruptions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Examples of Software Migration&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before exploring migration strategies, it&#39;s important to understand common scenarios that necessitate software migrations and require detailed planning:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在分布式系统中，多个服务协同工作来完成一项任务，每个服务由不同的团队管理并独立发展。这通常会导致需要依赖项迁移，例如数据库架构更新、外部服务升级或数据源更改。这些迁移是开发生命周期的重要组成部分，需要彻底的规划和执行，以防止回滚、数据不一致和运营中断。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;软件迁移示例&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在探索迁移策略之前，了解需要软件迁移并需要详细规划的常见场景非常重要：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Event-Driven Ansible Works for Configuration Monitoring】事件驱动的 Ansible 如何进行配置监控</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/event-driven-ansible-configuration-monitoring</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Configuration files control how applications, systems, and security policies work, making them crucial for keeping systems reliable and secure. If these files are changed accidentally or without permission, it can cause system failures, security risks, or compliance issues. Manually checking configuration files takes a lot of time, is prone to mistakes, and isn’t reliable, especially in complex IT systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-event-driven-ansible-to-monitor-your-web-app&#34;&gt;Event-driven Ansible&lt;/a&gt; offers a way to automatically monitor and manage configuration files. It reacts to changes as they happen, quickly detects them, takes automated actions, and works seamlessly with the tools and systems you already use.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;配置文件控制应用程序、系统和安全策略的工作方式，这使得它们对于保持系统可靠和安全至关重要。如果这些文件被意外或未经许可更改，可能会导致系统故障、安全风险或合规性问题。手动检查配置文件需要花费大量时间，容易出错，而且不可靠，尤其是在复杂的IT系统中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-event-driven-ansible-to-monitor-your-web-app&#34;&gt;事件驱动Ansible&lt;/a&gt; 提供了一种自动监控和管理配置文件的方法。它会对发生的变化做出反应，快速检测变化，采取自动化操作，并与您已经使用的工具和系统无缝协作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Accelerating HCM Cloud Implementation With RPA】使用 RPA 加速 HCM 云实施</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/accelerating-hcm-cloud-implementation-with-rpa</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Human Capital Management (HCM) cloud systems, such as Oracle HCM and Workday, are vital for managing core HR operations. However, migrating to these systems and conducting necessary testing can be complex. Robotic Process Automation (RPA) provides a practical solution to streamline these processes. Organizations can accelerate the implementation and operationalization of HCM cloud applications through data migration, managing multi-factor authentication (MFA), assigning roles post-deployment, and conducting User Acceptance Testing (UAT).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This article offers practical guidance for finance and IT teams on leveraging RPA tools to enhance &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-workforce-management-in-service-industr&#34;&gt;HCM cloud implementation&lt;/a&gt;. By sharing best practices and real-world examples, we aim to present a roadmap for effectively applying RPA across various HCM platforms to overcome common implementation challenges.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;人力资本管理 (HCM) 云系统（例如 Oracle HCM 和 Workday）对于管理核心人力资源运营至关重要。然而，迁移到这些系统并进行必要的测试可能很复杂。机器人流程自动化 (RPA) 提供了简化这些流程的实用解决方案。组织可以通过数据迁移、管理多重身份验证 (MFA)、部署后分配角色以及进行用户验收测试 (UAT) 来加速 HCM 云应用程序的实施和运营。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;本文为财务和 IT 团队提供了利用 RPA 工具增强的实用指南&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-workforce-management- in-service-industr&#34;&gt;HCM 云实施&lt;/a&gt;。通过分享最佳实践和现实示例，我们旨在提供一个路线图，以便在各种 HCM 平台上有效应用 RPA，以克服常见的实施挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multi-Tenancy and Its Improved Support in Hibernate 6.3.0】Hibernate 6.3.0 中的多租户及其改进的支持</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/multi-tenancy-improved-support-hibernate-6-3-0</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multi-tenancy&lt;/strong&gt; has become an important feature for modern enterprise applications that need to serve multiple clients (tenants) from a single application instance. While an earlier version of Hibernate had support for multi-tenancy, its implementation required significant manual configuration and custom strategies to handle tenant isolation, which resulted in higher complexity and slower processes, especially for applications with a number of tenants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The latest version of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/marco-codes-live-gavin-king-and-hibernate-63-video&#34;&gt;Hibernate 6.3.0&lt;/a&gt;, which was released on December 15, 2024, addressed the above limitations with enhanced multi-tenancy support through better tools for tenant identification, schema resolution, and enhanced performance for handling tenant-specific operations. This article talks about how Hibernate 6.3.0 enhanced the traditional multi-tenancy implementation significantly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;多租户&lt;/strong&gt;已成为需要从单个应用程序实例为多个客户端（租户）提供服务的现代企业应用程序的重要功能。虽然 Hibernate 的早期版本支持多租户，但其实现需要大量的手动配置和自定义策略来处理租户隔离，这会导致更高的复杂性和更慢的流程，特别是对于具有多个租户的应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最新版本的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/marco-codes-live-gavin-king-and-hibernate-63-video&#34;&gt;Hibernate 6.3.0&lt;/a&gt;，该版本于 2024 年 12 月 15 日发布，通过更好的租户识别、架构解析工具和增强处理租户特定操作的性能，增强了多租户支持，解决了上述限制。本文讨论 Hibernate 6.3.0 如何显着增强传统的多租户实现。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【CubeFS: High-Performance Storage for Cloud-Native Apps】Cubefs：用于云本地应用的高性能存储</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cubefs-cncf-graduation-cloud-native-file-system</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Through achieving graduation status from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/announcements/2025/01/21/cloud-native-computing-foundation-announces-cubefs-graduation/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Cloud Native Computing Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, CubeFS reaches an important breakthrough as a distributed file system created by community input. CubeFS&#39;s graduation status demonstrates its achieved technical sophistication while establishing its reliable history of managing production workloads on a large scale. CubeFS provides low-latency file lookups and high throughput storage with strong protection through separate handling of metadata and data storage while remaining suited for numerous types of computing workloads.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The inherent compatibility between CubeFS&#39;s cloud-native design and Kubernetes achieves full automation of deployments together with rolling upgrades as well as scalable node adaptation to meet increasing data needs. CubeFS establishes itself as a trustworthy high-performance solution for container-based organizations wanting to upgrade their storage systems because of its dedicated open-source community support and adherence to the CNCF quality standards.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;通过 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/announcements/2025/01/21/cloud-native-computing-foundation-announces-cubefs-graduation/&#34; rel=&#34; 获得毕业状态noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;云原生计算基金会&lt;/a&gt;，CubeFS 作为社区投入创建的分布式文件系统取得了重要突破。 CubeFS 的毕业状态证明了其技术成熟度，同时建立了大规模管理生产工作负载的可靠历史。 CubeFS 通过单独处理元数据和数据存储提供低延迟文件查找和高吞吐量存储以及强大的保护，同时仍然适合多种类型的计算工作负载。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CubeFS的云原生设计与Kubernetes之间固有的兼容性，实现了部署的完全自动化以及滚动升级以及可扩展的节点适配，以满足不断增长的数据需求。 CubeFS 凭借其专门的开源社区支持和对 CNCF 质量标准的遵守，成为想要升级存储系统的基于容器的组织值得信赖的高性能解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【&#34;Fix with AI&#34; Button to Automate Playwright Test Fixes】“使用AI修复”按钮可自动化剧作家测试修复</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fix-with-ai-playwright-test-fixes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;End-to-end tests are essential for ensuring the reliability of your application, but they can also be a source of frustration. Even small changes to the user interface can cause tests to fail, leading developers and QA teams to spend hours troubleshooting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I’ll show you how to utilize AI tools like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-must-be-aware-of-about-chatgpt&#34;&gt;ChatGPT&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-github-copilot-top-25-metrics-redefining&#34;&gt;Copilot&lt;/a&gt; to automatically fix Playwright tests. You’ll learn how to create an AI prompt for any test that fails and attach it to your HTML report. This way, you can easily copy and paste the prompt into AI tools for quick suggestions on fixing the test. Join me to streamline your testing process and improve application reliability!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;端到端测试对于确保应用程序的可靠性至关重要，但它们也可能令人沮丧。即使对用户界面进行很小的更改也可能导致测试失败，从而导致开发人员和 QA 团队花费数小时进行故障排除。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇博文中，我将向您展示如何利用 AI 工具，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-must-be-aware-of-about-chatgpt&#34; &gt;ChatGPT&lt;/a&gt; 或 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-github-copilot-top-25-metrics-redefining&#34;&gt;Copilot&lt;/a&gt; 自动修复 Playwright 测试。您将学习如何为任何失败的测试创建 AI 提示并将其附加到您的 HTML 报告中。这样，您可以轻松地将提示复制并粘贴到 AI 工具中，以获得修复测试的快速建议。与我一起简化您的测试流程并提高应用程序可靠性！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI/ML Techniques for Real-Time Fraud Detection】用于实时欺诈检测的 AI/ML 技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-ml-techniques-real-time-fraud-detection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s technologically advanced society, fraud detection is a major concern. According to the Association of Certified Fraud Examiners (ACFE), fraud costs companies trillions of dollars worldwide, or nearly 5% of their yearly sales (&lt;a href=&#34;https://legacy.acfe.com/report-to-the-nations/2024/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;ACFE Report to the Nations 2024&lt;/a&gt;). Businesses are increasingly using cutting-edge technology like artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) as fraudsters become more skilled. Behavioral analytics is at the forefront of this movement and directly fights fraud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Problem Statement&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In today&#39;s modern era, fraud is growing beyond conventional methods because of utilizing the volume and velocity of online transactions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今技术先进的社会中，欺诈检测是一个主要问题。根据认证欺诈审查员协会（ACFE）的数据，欺诈使公司在全球范围内数万亿美元，或其年度销售额的近5％（&lt;a href =“ https://legacy.acfe.com/report-to-te-to-to-te-to-te-te-to-te-the-come-com， Nation/2024/“ RER =” Noopener noreferrer“ target =“ _ blank”&gt; ACFE向国家报告2024 &lt;/a&gt;）。随着欺诈者的发展，企业越来越多地使用人工智能（AI）和机器学习（ML）等尖端技术。行为分析处于这一运动的最前沿，直接与欺诈作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;问题语句&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在当今的现代时代，由于利用在线交易的数量和速度，欺诈行为正在超越常规方法。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Balancing Security and UX With Iterative Experimentation】平衡安全性和UX与迭代实验</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/balancing-security-user-experience-iterative-experimentation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As transitioning to the digital world is the norm today, businesses face the challenge of constantly maximizing performance while keeping a lookout for potential threats. However, whether it’s spotting fraud in banking and eCommerce, moderating content on social media and any other sites with user-generated content, or identifying anomalies, it is a balancing act between strong security and a smooth user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The iterative experimentation supported by &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-ab-testing-in-website-development-and&#34;&gt;A/B testing&lt;/a&gt; can serve as a valuable mechanism to fine-tune algorithms and the overall user experience across services in multiple sectors under the right conditions. Not only do these methods enhance people’s productivity — they develop trust and satisfaction from users as well.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;由于过渡到数字世界是当今的常态，企业面临着不断提高绩效的挑战，同时一直在寻找潜在的威胁。但是，无论是在银行和电子商务中发现欺诈，在社交媒体和任何其他具有用户生成内容的网站上的内容还是识别异常，这都是强大的安全性和平稳的用户体验之间的平衡行为。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;由&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-ob-ob-testing-in-website-developments支持的迭代实验测试&lt;/a&gt;可以作为微调算法和在正确条件下多个领域的服务的总体用户体验的宝贵机制。这些方法不仅可以提高人们的生产力 - 他们也会增强用户的信任和满意。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Jenkins Pipelines With Centralized Error Codes and Fail-Fast】詹金斯管道带有集中式错误代码和失败速度</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/jenkins-pipelines-centralized-error-codes-fail-fast</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Effective error management is paramount to the success of any continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD) pipeline. Jenkins, being a widely adopted tool for automating software deployment workflows, introduces numerous complexities when managing errors across its stages. Centralized error codes, coupled with detailed error descriptions and a structured troubleshooting guide, significantly enhance the efficiency of identifying, resolving, and mitigating issues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article explores the implementation of a centralized error code system and integrates a fail-fast strategy to enable rapid issue detection and resolution. The goal is to provide a robust framework for organizations to ensure streamlined Jenkins pipeline operations and mitigate delays caused by errors in critical pipeline stages.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;有效错误管理对于任何连续集成和连续交付（CI/CD）管道的成功至关重要。詹金斯（Jenkins）是自动化软件部署工作流程的广泛采用的工具，在管理阶段的错误时会引入许多复杂性。集中式错误代码，再加上详细的错误描述和结构化故障排除指南，可显着提高识别，解决和缓解问题的效率。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;本文探讨了集中式错误代码系统的实现，并集成了失败的策略，以实现快速发行检测和解决方案。目的是为组织提供一个强大的框架，以确保精简的Jenkins管道操作和减轻因关键管道阶段错误而造成的延迟。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>