<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Biggest Software Bugs and Tech Fails】最大的软件错误和技术失败</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/biggest-software-bugs-and-tech-fails</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;While the objective of software testing is to look for bugs even before they reach the users&#39; hands, it doesn&#39;t mean that the most stringent testing procedures will go so wrong. From embarrassing mistakes to catastrophically collapsing systems, these examples will drive home just how crucial proper testing procedures are.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This blog will discuss some of the most shocking examples of software problems and technological problems resulting from test problems, and the lessons we can learn from them.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;，而软件测试的目的甚至是在触及用户手之前寻找错误，这并不意味着最严格的测试过程将走错了。从令人尴尬的错误到灾难性崩溃的系统，这些示例将使回家的适当测试程序的关键程度。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;此博客将讨论一些最令人震惊的软件问题和测试问题的技术问题的示例，以及我们可以从中吸取的教训。&lt;/ P&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【CUI Document Identification and Classification】CUI文档标识和分类</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cui-document-identification-and-classification</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Controlled Unclassified Information (CUI) requires careful identification and classification to ensure compliance with frameworks like CMMC and FedRAMP. For developers, building automated systems to classify CUI involves integrating machine learning, natural language processing (NLP), and metadata analysis into document-handling workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Challenges in CUI Document Classification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Ambiguity in Definitions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CUI categories often overlap with non-sensitive data, making manual classification error-prone.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;受控的未分类信息（CUI）需要仔细的识别和分类，以确保遵守CMMC和FedRamp等框架。对于开发人员，构建自动化系统以对CUI进行分类，涉及将机器学习，自然语言处理（NLP）和元数据分析整合到文档处理工作流程中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; CUI文档分类中的关键挑战&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。定义中的歧义&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; CUI类别通常与非敏感数据重叠，使手动分类容易出错。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS Lambda Enhances Local IDE Experience With AI Support】AWS Lambda通过AI支持增强了本地IDE的体验</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-lambda-local-ide-ai-support</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AWS Lambda is enhancing the local IDE experience to make developing Lambda-based applications more efficient. These new features enable developers to author, build, debug, test, and deploy Lambda applications seamlessly within their local IDE using Visual Studio Code (VS Code).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The improved IDE experience is part of the AWS Toolkit for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-visual-studio-code&#34;&gt;Visual Studio Code&lt;/a&gt;. It includes a guided setup walkthrough that helps developers configure their local environment and install necessary tools. The toolkit also includes sample applications that demonstrate how to iterate on your code both locally and in the cloud. Developers can save and configure build settings to accelerate application builds and generate configuration files for setting up a debugging environment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; aws lambda正在增强本地IDE经验，以使开发基于Lambda的应用程序更加有效。这些新功能使开发人员能够使用Visual Studio Code（VS Code）在本地IDE中无缝地在本地IDE中作者，构建，调试，测试和部署Lambda应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;改进的IDE体验是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-to-visual-studio-code”&gt; Visual Studio Code &lt;/a&gt;的AWS工具包的一部分。它包括指导的设置演练，可帮助开发人员配置其本地环境并安装必要的工具。该工具包还包括示例应用程序，这些应用程序演示了如何在本地和云中迭代代码。开发人员可以保存和配置构建设置以加速应用程序构建并生成配置文件，以设置调试环境。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating AI With Spring Boot: A Beginner’s Guide】将AI与Spring Boot集成：初学者指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-ai-with-spring-boot-beginners-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Do you need to integrate artificial intelligence into your Spring Boot application? Spring AI reduces complexity using abstractions you are used to apply within Spring Boot. Let’s dive into the basics in this blog post. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence is not a Python-only party anymore. LangChain4j basically opened the Java toolbox for integrating with AI. Spring AI is the Spring solution for AI integration. It tries to reduce the complexity of integrating AI within a Java application, just like LangChain4j is doing. The difference is that you can use the same abstractions as you are used to apply within Spring Boot.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否需要将人工智能集成到您的春季启动应用程序中？ Spring AI使用用于在Spring Boot中应用的抽象来降低复杂性。让我们在此博客文章中深入研究基础知识。享受！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能不再是仅仅是Python的聚会。 langchain4j基本上打开了Java工具箱，用于与AI集成。弹簧AI是AI集成的弹簧解决方案。就像Langchain4J所做的那样，它试图减少将AI集成在Java应用程序中的复杂性。不同之处在于，您可以使用与用于在Spring Boot中应用的相同抽象。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Database Release and End-to-End Testing】数据库发布和端到端测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/database-release-and-end-to-end-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the world of software development, rigorous testing and controlled releases have been standard practice for decades. But what if we could apply these same principles to databases and data warehouses? Imagine being able to define a set of criteria with test cases for your data infrastructure, automatically applying them to every new &#34;release&#34; to ensure your customers always see accurate and consistent data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Challenge: Why End-to-End Testing Isn&#39;t Common in Data Management&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While this idea seems intuitive, there&#39;s a reason why &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-end-to-end-testing-e2e-testing-tutorial-wi&#34;&gt;end-to-end testing&lt;/a&gt; isn&#39;t commonly practiced in data management: it requires a primitive clone or snapshot for databases or data warehouses, which most data systems don&#39;t provide.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在软件开发领域，严格的测试和受控版本一直是数十年来的标准实践。但是，如果我们可以将这些相同的原理应用于数据库和数据仓库，该怎么办？想象一下，能够通过数据基础架构定义一组标准，将它们自动应用于每个新的“发布”，以确保您的客户始终看到准确，一致的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;挑战：为什么端到端测试在数据管理中不常见&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然这个想法似乎很直观，但有一个原因，为什么&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-end-is-end-to-to-desting-testing-e2e-testing-testing-testing-tutorial-wi&gt; end&gt; end - 到末端测试&lt;/a&gt;数据管理中通常不会实践：它需要用于数据库或数据仓库的原始克隆或快照，大多数数据系统不提供。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Evaluating LLMs and RAG Systems】评估LLM和抹布系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/evaluating-llms-and-rag-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) systems have garnered significant attention for their ability to combine the strengths of information retrieval and large language models (LLMs) to generate contextually enriched responses. Through retrieved information, RAG systems address some limitations of standalone LLMs, such as hallucination and lack of domain specificity. However, the performance of such systems depends critically on two components: the relevance and accuracy of the retrieved information and the language model&#39;s ability to generate coherent, factually accurate, and contextually aligned responses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Building on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-retrieval-augmented-generation&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;foundational concepts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;of RAG systems, this article outlines robust evaluation strategies for RAG pipelines and their individual components, including the LLM, the retriever, and their combined efficacy in downstream tasks. We also explore a framework for evaluating LLMs, focusing on critical aspects such as model complexity, training data quality, and ethical considerations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;检索功能的生成（RAG）系统，由于其结合信息检索和大型语言模型（LLMS）的优势以生成上下文丰富的响应的能力而引起了极大的关注。通过检索信息，RAG系统解决了独立LLM的某些局限性，例如幻觉和缺乏域特异性。但是，此类系统的性能在很大程度上取决于两个组成部分：检索信息的相关性和准确性以及语言模型生成相干，实际上准确且上下文一致的响应的能力。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-retrieval-aigmented-generation”上建立构建，本文概述了抹布管道及其各个组件的强大评估策略，包括LLM，猎犬及其在下游任务中的综合功效。我们还探索了评估LLM的框架，重点关注诸如模型复杂性，培训数据质量和道德考虑之类的关键方面。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Tools for Object Storage and Data Management】对象存储和数据管理的顶级工具</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-tools-object-storage-data-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Whether you are a seasoned cloud architect or a newbie getting to understand the nuances of the cloud, at some point, you will come across an interesting storage option called object storage to store or archive your unstructured data. In this article, you will be introduced to object storage and key tools like MinIO, Cyberduck, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding Object Storage&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Object storage is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-architectures-emphasis-on-emerging-trends&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;data storage architecture&lt;/a&gt; that manages information as discrete units called &lt;strong&gt;objects&lt;/strong&gt;, rather than as files in folders or blocks on servers. Each object typically includes the data itself, a variable amount of metadata, and a globally unique identifier. This approach offers several advantages over traditional storage methods, particularly when dealing with large volumes of unstructured data.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;无论您是经验丰富的云架构师还是新手都可以理解云的细微差别，在某个时候，您会遇到一个有趣的存储选项，称为“对象存储”来存储或存档您的非结构化数据。在本文中，您将介绍对象存储和关键工具，例如Minio，Cyber​​duck等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解对象存储&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对象存储是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/data-Architectures-emphasis-emphasis-on-emerging-trends” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt;数据存储架构/a&gt;将信息作为离散单元的管理，称为&lt;strong&gt;对象&lt;/strong&gt;，而不是在服务器上的文件夹或块中作为文件。每个对象通常包括数据本身，可变数量的元数据和全球唯一标识符。这种方法比传统存储方法具有多种优势，尤其是在处理大量非结构化数据时。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Get Started With Vector Search in Azure Cosmos DB】在Azure Cosmos DB中开始搜索矢量搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/get-started-with-vector-search-in-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This is a guide for folks who are looking for a way to quickly and easily try out the Vector Search feature in Azure Cosmos DB for NoSQL. This app uses a simple dataset of movies to find similar movies based on a given criteria. It&#39;s implemented in four languages — Python, TypeScript, .NET and Java. There are instructions that walk you through the process of setting things up, loading data, and then executing similarity search queries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-are-vector-databases&#34;&gt;vector database&lt;/a&gt; is designed to store and manage vector embeddings, which are mathematical representations of data in a high-dimensional space. In this space, each dimension corresponds to a feature of the data, and tens of thousands of dimensions might be used to represent data. A vector&#39;s position in this space represents its characteristics. Words, phrases, or entire documents, and images, audio, and other types of data can all be vectorized. These vector embeddings are used in similarity search, multi-modal search, recommendations engines, large language models (LLMs), etc.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这是为正在寻找一种方法来快速，轻松尝试NOSQL中Azure Cosmos DB中的矢量搜索功能的人们的指南。该应用使用简单的电影数据集根据给定的标准查找类似的电影。它以四种语言实现：Python，Typescript，.Net和Java。有指令可以使您完成设置，加载数据然后执行相似性搜索查询的过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; a &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-are-are-vector-databases”&gt;向量数据库&lt;/a&gt;旨在存储和管理向量嵌入，这是数据的数学表示，这些表示是数据的数学表示高维空间。在这个空间中，每个维度对应于数据的特征，并且可以使用数万个维度来表示数据。向量在这个空间中的位置代表其特征。单词，短语或整个文档，图像，音频和其他类型的数据都可以矢量化。这些向量嵌入在相似性搜索，多模式搜索，建议引擎，大语言模型（LLMS）等中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Working With Vision AI to Test Cloud Applications】与Vision AI一起测试云应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/working-with-vision-ai-to-test-cloud-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Recently, I’ve been looking into Tricentis Tosca to better understand how its testing suite can benefit my app development workflow. In my &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-qr-codes-in-your-applications&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;last article about Tosca&lt;/a&gt;, I wrote about some of the tool’s visual capabilities, such as QR code testing. Testing QR codes is great if you need an effective way to validate that specific part of your app. Then, I discovered Tosca’s Vision AI tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Imagine giving your testing tool some simple visual cues for how your system should work and then building the functionality to make the tests pass. That’s what these tools are designed to do.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;最近，我一直在研究Tricentis Tosca，以更好地了解其测试套件如何使我的应用程序开发工作流程受益。在我的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/test-qr-codes-in-your-applications”中我写了一些有关该工具的视觉功能的文章，例如QR码测试。如果您需要一种有效的方法来验证应用程序的特定部分，则测试QR码非常好。然后，我发现了Tosca的Vision AI工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;想象一下您的测试工具一些简单的视觉提示，以使您的系统应如何工作，然后构建功能以使测试通过。这些工具就是为此设计的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Comparing SDLC With and Without AI/ML Integration】在有或没有AI/ML集成的情况下比较SDLC</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/comparing-sdlc-with-vs-without-ai-ml-integration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The software conception, development, testing, deployment, and maintenance processes have fundamentally changed with the use of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) in the software development life cycle (SDLC). Businesses today want to automate their development processes in any way they can with the goals of increasing efficiency, positively impacting time to market, improving the quality of software, and being data-driven in their approaches. AI/ML is instrumental in achieving these goals as it helps in automating repetitive work processes, assists with predictive analytics and empowers intelligent systems that respond to changing needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article discusses the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aiml-tools-and-frameworks-a-comprehensive-comparis&#34;&gt;role of AI/ML&lt;/a&gt; at each stage of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/software-development-life-cycle-the-ultimate-guide&#34;&gt;SDLC&lt;/a&gt;, how they are able to add value to it, and the challenges organizations face or will face in order to exploit them to the maximum.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在软件开发生命周期（SDLC）中，随着人工智能（AI）和机器学习（ML）的使用（SDLC），软件概念，开发，测试，部署和维护过程从根本上发生了变化。当今的企业希望以提高效率的目标，积极影响上市时间，提高软件质量并以数据为驱动的方法，以提高效率的目标，从而以任何方式自动化其开发流程。 AI/ML有助于实现这些目标，因为它有助于自动化重复的工作流程，协助预测分析，并使智能系统能够响应不断变化的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文讨论了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/aiml-tools-and-frameworks-a-comprehend-comparis”&gt; ai/ml的角色&lt;/a&gt;在每个阶段&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/software-development-life-cycle-the-thimate-guide”&gt; sdlc &lt;/a&gt;，他们如何能够为其增加价值及其挑战组织面对或将面对以利用它们最大。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>