<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero Trust in CI/CD Pipelines: A Practical DevSecOps Implementation Guide】CI/CD 管道中的零信任：实用 DevSecOps 实施指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-in-cicd-pipelines-implementation-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Securing modern CI/CD pipelines has become significantly more challenging as teams adopt &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/design-scalable-and-secure-cloud-native-architectures&#34;&gt;cloud-native architectures&lt;/a&gt; and accelerate their release cycles. Attackers now target build systems, deployment workflows, and the open-source components organizations rely on every day. This tutorial provides a practical look at how Zero Trust principles can strengthen the entire software delivery process. It walks through real steps you can apply immediately using identity-based authentication, automated scanning, policy checks, and hardened Kubernetes deployments. The goal is simple: make sure that only trusted code, moving through a trusted pipeline, reaches production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As organizations continue transitioning to cloud-native applications and distributed systems, the CI/CD pipeline has become a critical part of the software supply chain. Unfortunately, this also makes it an increasingly attractive target for attackers. Compromising a build system or deployment workflow can lead to unauthorized code changes, credential theft, or even the silent insertion of malicious workloads into production.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着团队采用&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/design-scalable-and-secure-cloud-native-architectures&#34;&gt;云原生架构&lt;/a&gt;并加快发布周期，确保现代 CI/CD 管道的安全变得更加具有挑战性。攻击者现在的目标是构建系统、部署工作流程以及组织日常依赖的开源组件。本教程提供了零信任原则如何加强整个软件交付流程的实用视角。它逐步介绍了您可以使用基于身份的身份验证、自动扫描、策略检查和强化 Kubernetes 部署立即应用的实际步骤。目标很简单：确保只有受信任的代码通过受信任的管道才能到达生产环境。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着组织不断过渡到云原生应用程序和分布式系统，CI/CD 管道已成为软件供应链的关键部分。不幸的是，这也使其成为对攻击者越来越有吸引力的目标。损害构建系统或部署工作流程可能会导致未经授权的代码更改、凭据盗窃，甚至将恶意工作负载静默插入生产中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ITBench, Part 3: IT Compliance Automation with GenAI CISO Assessment Agent】ITBench，第 3 部分：使用 GenAI CISO 评估代理实现 IT 合规自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/itbench-part-3-it-compliance-automation-with-genai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Developed as part of IBM&#39;s ITBench framework, which we introduced in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/itbench-next-gen-benchmarking-it-automation&#34; target=&#34;_self&#34;&gt;ITBench, Part 1: Next-Gen Benchmarking for IT Automation Evaluation&lt;/a&gt;, the Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) Compliance Assessment Agent (CAA) represents a pioneering methodology for automating cybersecurity compliance processes in modern IT environments. This AI-powered agent addresses the critical challenge of scaling security compliance operations in complex, rapidly evolving IT environments and technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional compliance approaches that rely on dedicated security teams to manually identify weaknesses and assess compliance posture are no longer viable for modern organizations operating at scale.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;首席信息安全官 (CISO) 合规性评估代理 (CAA) 是作为 IBM ITBench 框架的一部分开发的，我们在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/itbench-next-gen-benchmarking-it-automation&#34; target=&#34;_self&#34;&gt;ITBench，第 1 部分：IT 自动化评估的下一代基准测试&lt;/a&gt;中介绍了该框架，首席信息安全官 (CISO) 合规性评估代理 (CAA) 代表了现代 IT 环境中网络安全合规性流程自动化的开创性方法。这种人工智能驱动的代理解决了在复杂、快速发展的 IT 环境和技术中扩展安全合规操作的关键挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;依赖专门的安全团队手动识别弱点并评估合规状况的传统合规方法对于大规模运营的现代组织来说不再可行。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Secrets in Code: Understanding Secret Detection and Its Blind Spots】代码中的秘密：了解秘密检测及其盲点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secrets-in-code-detection-and-its-blind-spots</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In a world where attackers routinely scan public repositories for leaked credentials, secrets in source code represent a high-value target. But even with the growth of secret detection tools, many valid secrets still go unnoticed. It’s not because the secrets are hidden, but because the detection rules are too narrow or overcorrect in an attempt to avoid false positives. This creates a trade-off between wasting development time investigating false signals and risking a compromised account.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article highlights &lt;a href=&#34;https://semgrep.dev/blog/2025/secrets-story-and-prefixed-secrets/&#34;&gt;research that uncovered hundreds of valid secrets&lt;/a&gt; from various third-party services publicly leaked on GitHub. Responsible disclosure of the specific findings is important, but the broader learnings include which types of secrets are common, the patterns in their formatting that cause them to be missed, and how scanners work so that their failure points can be improved.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在攻击者经常扫描公共存储库以查找泄露凭据的世界中，源代码中的秘密代表了高价值目标。但即使秘密检测工具不断发展，许多有效的秘密仍然未被注意到。这并不是因为秘密被隐藏，而是因为为了避免误报，检测规则过于狭窄或过于正确。这就需要在浪费开发时间调查虚假信号和冒帐户被盗风险之间进行权衡。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文重点介绍了&lt;a href=&#34;https://semgrep.dev/blog/2025/secrets-story-and-prefixed-secrets/&#34;&gt;从 GitHub 上公开泄露的各种第三方服务中发现了数百个有效秘密的研究&lt;/a&gt;。负责任地披露具体调查结果很重要，但更广泛的了解包括哪些类型的秘密是常见的、导致它们被遗漏的格式模式，以及扫描仪如何工作以改进其故障点。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Synergizing Intelligence and Orchestration: Transforming Cloud Deployments with AI and Kubernetes】协同智能和编排：利用 AI 和 Kubernetes 转变云部署</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-deployments-ai-and-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Artificial Intelligence&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is reshaping the way today&#39;s cloud infrastructure is operated and deployed natively with Kubernetes. AI has become a major driver in helping global businesses streamline resources, scale workloads, and automate several activities. By incorporating AI with Kubernetes, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/strategies-and-guidance-for-effective-cloud-manage&#34;&gt;cloud management&lt;/a&gt; advances to an entirely new level, enabling smarter decision making, automation, and complete optimization of resources. In this article, we describe how AI can support cloud platforms — especially those powered by Kubernetes — outlining the barriers to adoption and the concrete results achieved when these technologies are applied.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As cloud computing matures, the demand for more efficient, scalable and automated cloud deployment continues to grow, pushing organizations to redefine their cloud environments. Kubernetes, the open-source container orchestration platform, has become fundamental for managing container-based applications in the cloud. AI is transforming how cloud resources are utilized, and Kubernetes provides an advanced platform for deploying containerized applications automatically. Together, they form a strong foundation for an ecosystem that fosters innovation, scalability and cost-effectiveness. This article discusses how the combination of AI and Kubernetes is streamlining cloud operations and enabling unprecedented levels of efficiency and creativity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;人工智能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能 (AI) 正在重塑当今云基础设施通过 Kubernetes 本地运行和部署的方式。人工智能已成为帮助全球企业简化资源、扩展工作负载和自动化多项活动的主要驱动力。通过将人工智能与 Kubernetes 相结合，云管理提升到一个全新的水平，实现更智能的决策、自动化和全面的资源优化。在本文中，我们描述了人工智能如何支持云平台——尤其是由 Kubernetes 提供支持的云平台——概述了采用这些技术的障碍以及应用这些技术时所取得的具体成果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着云计算的成熟，对更高效、可扩展和自动化云部署的需求持续增长，推动组织重新定义其云环境。 Kubernetes 是开源容器编排平台，已成为管理云中基于容器的应用程序的基础。人工智能正在改变云资源的利用方式，而 Kubernetes 提供了自动部署容器化应用程序的高级平台。它们共同为促进创新、可扩展性和成本效益的生态系统奠定了坚实的基础。本文讨论人工智能和 Kubernetes 的结合如何简化云运营并实现前所未有的效率和创造力水平。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Blockchain Use Cases in Test Automation You’ll See Everywhere in 2026】2026 年，测试自动化中的区块链用例将随处可见</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/blockchain-use-cases-in-test-automation-youll-see</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;773&#34; data-start=&#34;319&#34;&gt;The rapid evolution of digital ecosystems has placed test automation at the center of quality assurance for modern software. But as systems grow increasingly distributed, data-sensitive, and security-driven, traditional automation approaches struggle to maintain transparency, consistency, and trust. This is why &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-can-we-benefit-from-using-blockchain-technolog&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;blockchain technology&lt;/a&gt; — once associated primarily with cryptocurrencies — is now becoming a fundamental part of enterprise testing processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1248&#34; data-start=&#34;775&#34;&gt;By 2026, blockchain-backed test automation frameworks are no longer conceptual — they are mainstream. Leading enterprises, development teams, and innovative test automation companies are leveraging blockchain to improve traceability, ensure integrity, and create tamper-proof testing ecosystems. Blockchain’s inherent strengths — immutability, decentralization, transparency, and cryptographic security — make it an ideal solution to strengthen test automation pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;773&#34; data-start=&#34;319&#34;&gt;数字生态系统的快速发展使测试自动化成为现代软件质量保证的中心。但随着系统变得越来越分布式、数据敏感和安全驱动，传统的自动化方法很难保持透明度、一致性和信任。这就是为什么&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-can-we-benefit-from-using-blockchain-technolog&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;区块链技术&lt;/a&gt;（曾经主要与加密货币相关）现在正在成为企业测试流程的基本组成部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1248&#34; data-start=&#34;775&#34;&gt;到 2026 年，区块链支持的测试自动化框架不再是概念性的 - 它们已成为主流。领先的企业、开发团队和创新的测试自动化公司正在利用区块链来提高可追溯性、确保完整性并创建防篡改的测试生态系统。区块链的固有优势——不变性、去中心化、透明性和加密安全性——使其成为加强测试自动化管道的理想解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Observability Gap: Why Your Monitoring Strategy Isn&#39;t Ready for What&#39;s Coming Next】可观察性差距：为什么您的监控策略还没有为接下来的情况做好准备</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/observability-gap-why-monitoring-isnt-ready</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Anyone who’s been to London knows the announcements at the Tube to “Mind the gap,” but what about the gap that’s developing in our monitoring and observability strategies? I’ve been through this ordeal before, and have run a distributed system that was humming along perfectly. My alerts were manageable, my dashboards made sense, and when things broke, I could usually track down the issue in a reasonable amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fast forward 3–5 years, and things have changed. We added Kubernetes, embraced microservices, and maybe even sprinkled in some AI-powered features these days. Suddenly, you&#39;re drowning in telemetry data, your alert fatigue is real, and correlating issues across your distributed architecture feels stressful.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;任何去过伦敦的人都知道地铁上的公告“注意差距”，但是我们的监控和可观察性策略中正在形成的差距又如何呢？我以前经历过这种考验，并且运行过一个运行完美的分布式系统。我的警报是可管理的，我的仪表板很有意义，当出现问题时，我通常可以在合理的时间内找到问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;快进 3-5 年，情况发生了变化。我们添加了 Kubernetes，采用了微服务，甚至现在还加入了一些人工智能驱动的功能。突然间，您淹没在遥测数据中，您的警报疲劳是真实存在的，并且在分布式架构中关联问题感到压力很大。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Test POST Requests With REST Assured Java for API Testing: Part II】如何使用 REST Assured Java 测试 POST 请求以进行 API 测试：第二部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rest-assured-java-test-post-requests-part-ii</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;2106&#34;&gt;In the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-post-requests-rest-assured-java&#34;&gt;previous article&lt;/a&gt;, we learnt the basics, setup, and configuration of the REST Assured framework for API test automation. We also learnt to test a POST request with REST Assured by sending the request body as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;71be&#34;&gt;String&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;2312&#34;&gt;JSON Array/ JSON Object&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;ac2f&#34;&gt;Using Java Collections&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;9cb0&#34;&gt;Using POJO&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;cc9b&#34;&gt;In this tutorial article, we will learn the following:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;2106&#34;&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-post-requests-rest-assured-java&#34;&gt;上一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;中，我们了解了用于 API 测试自动化的 REST Assured 框架的基础知识、设置和配置。我们还学会了通过发送请求正文来使用 REST Assured 测试 POST 请求：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;71be&#34;&gt;字符串&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;2312&#34;&gt;JSON 数组/JSON 对象&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;ac2f&#34;&gt;使用 Java 集合&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li name=&#34;9cb0&#34;&gt;使用 POJO&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;cc9b&#34;&gt;在本教程文章中，我们将学习以下内容：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Modern Blueprint for Privacy-First AI/ML Systems】隐私优先 AI/ML 系统的现代蓝图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/modern-blueprint-for-privacy-first-aiml-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;The era of &lt;strong&gt;identifier-driven machine learning&lt;/strong&gt; is over. The next decade belongs to &lt;strong&gt;privacy-preserving architectures&lt;/strong&gt; where systems learn from &lt;strong&gt;patterns&lt;/strong&gt;, not people. Here’s what that means in practice&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Process and anonymize data &lt;strong&gt;on the device&lt;/strong&gt;, not in the cloud.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Design and run experiments that &lt;strong&gt;do not require specific user identifiers&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Train global models through &lt;strong&gt;federated learning&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Treat data as &lt;strong&gt;perishable by design&lt;/strong&gt;, not as a policy checkbox.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;If you’re building ML or analytics infrastructure today, privacy isn’t an add-on. You need to treat it as a &lt;strong&gt;core architectural constraint&lt;/strong&gt; and a &lt;strong&gt;trust multiplier&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;标识符驱动的机器学习&lt;/strong&gt;时代已经结束。下一个十年属于&lt;strong&gt;隐私保护架构&lt;/strong&gt;，系统从&lt;strong&gt;模式&lt;/strong&gt;学习，而不是从人学习。这在实践中意味着什么&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在设备上&lt;/strong&gt;处理和匿名化数据，而不是在云端。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;设计并运行&lt;strong&gt;不需要特定用户标识符&lt;/strong&gt;的实验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;通过&lt;strong&gt;联合学习&lt;/strong&gt;训练全球模型。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;将数据视为&lt;strong&gt;设计上容易失效&lt;/strong&gt;，而不是政策复选框。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;如果您现在正在构建机器学习或分析基础设施，隐私并不是一个附加项。您需要将其视为&lt;strong&gt;核心架构约束&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;信任乘数&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Tinker and the Tool: Lessons Learned for Using AI in Daily Development】修补匠和工具：在日常开发中使用人工智能的经验教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-tinker-and-the-tool-lessons-learned-for-using</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI tools have swept through the development landscape like a storm. From co-pilots integrated directly into IDEs (such as GitHub Copilot and Amazon CodeWhisperer) to large language models (LLMs) used for conceptual design (such as Claude and custom agents), AI can write code faster than any engineer. It can review pull requests, write unit tests, and even analyze project structure. The value is undeniable: AI can support massive productivity gains.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Yet, beyond the market hype, there is a fundamental lesson to be learned: AI is a powerful tool, but it is not a replacement for human intellect.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能工具像风暴一样席卷了开发领域。从直接集成到 IDE 中的副驾驶（例如 GitHub Copilot 和 Amazon CodeWhisperer）到用于概念设计的大型语言模型 (LLM)（例如 Claude 和自定义代理），AI 可以比任何工程师更快地编写代码。它可以审查拉取请求、编写单元测试，甚至分析项目结构。其价值是不可否认的：人工智能可以大幅提高生产力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;然而，除了市场炒作之外，我们还需要吸取一个基本教训：人工智能是一种强大的工具，但它并不能取代人类智力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Taming Gen AI Video: An Architectural Approach to Addressing Identity Drift and Hallucination】Taming Gen AI 视频：解决身份漂移和幻觉的架构方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gen-ai-video-approach-to-identity-drift-and-hallucination</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If you&#39;ve spent any time experimenting with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/leveraging-generative-ai-for-video-creation-a-deep&#34;&gt;generative AI video&lt;/a&gt; tools like Runway or Google&#39;s Veo, you&#39;ve seen the magic. You&#39;ve also, almost certainly, hit the architectural roadblocks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A character&#39;s face subtly morphs from one scene to the next until they’re unrecognizable by the tenth clip. Objects you never prompted mysteriously pop up in the background. These aren&#39;t just minor bugs; they are critical consistency failures that can derail any serious AI video project.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果您花时间尝试过 Runway 或 Google 的 Veo 等&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/leveraging-generative-ai-for-video-creation-a-deep&#34;&gt;生成式 AI 视频&lt;/a&gt;工具，您就会看到它的魔力。几乎可以肯定，您还遇到了架构障碍。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;角色的脸部从一个场景巧妙地变形到下一个场景，直到第十个剪辑无法识别他们。您从未提示过的对象会神秘地在后台弹出。这些不仅仅是小错误；它们是严重的一致性故障，可能会破坏任何严肃的人工智能视频项目。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>