<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Centralized Configuration Management With Consul】使用 Consul 进行集中配置管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/centralized-configuration-management-with-consul</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;What Is Centralized Configuration?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In modern microservice architectures, multiple applications often share common configuration data (e.g., database settings). These might be multiple instances of the same service or entirely different services. Regardless of the service behavior, instead of maintaining configuration at the service level, we can centralize it in one place and distribute it across all services. HashiCorp Consul provides a solution for this.&lt;span class=&#34;fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib&#34; style=&#34;width: 808px;&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fr-img-wrap&#34;&gt;&lt;img data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;227.7 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1752609488661&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;07/15/2025 07:58 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18527030-consul-distributed-config-b.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;227699&#34; data-name=&#34;consul-distributed-config-b.png&#34; data-id=&#34;18527030&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18527030-consul-distributed-config-b.png&#34; alt=&#34;Consul config distribution&#34; class=&#34;lazyload&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption aria-label=&#34;To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings&#34; class=&#34;fr-inner&#34; contenteditable=&#34;true&#34; spellcheck=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;Consul config distribution&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;什么是集中配置？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在现代微服务架构中，多个应用程序通常共享公共配置数据（例如数据库设置）。这些可能是同一服务的多个实例或完全不同的服务。无论服务行为如何，我们都可以将其集中在一个地方并将其分布在所有服务中，而不是在服务级别维护配置。 HashiCorp Consul 为此提供了解决方案。&lt;span class=&#34;fr-img-caption fr-fic fr-dib&#34; style=&#34;width: 808px;&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fr-img-wrap&#34;&gt;&lt;img data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;227.7 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1752609488661&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;07/15/2025 07:58 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18527030-consul-distributed-config-b.png&#34; data-modificationdate =“null”data-size =“227699”data-name =“consul-distributed-config-b.png”data-id =“18527030”data-src =“https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18527030-consul-distributed-config-b.png”alt =“Consul配置” 分布&#34; class=&#34;lazyload&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption aria-label=&#34;为了丰富屏幕阅读器交互，请在 Grammarly 扩展设置中激活辅助功能&#34; class=&#34;fr-inner&#34; contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;pellcheck=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;figcaption contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;em&gt;Consul 配置分发&lt;/em&gt;&#xA; &lt;/图标题&gt;&#xA; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图标题&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Fault-Tolerant Microservices Architecture With Kubernetes, gRPC, and Circuit Breakers】使用 Kubernetes、gRPC 和断路器构建容错微服务架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/microservices-kubernetes-grpc-circuit-breakers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Over the last decade, microservice architectures have become commonplace when designing scalable, maintainable, and independently deployable applications. Breaking down a system into multiple, domain-focused services, development squads can quickly develop, have varying technology stacks per service, and independently scale an application&#39;s constituent pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But this flexibility has its cost: operational complexity and failure propagation. Unlike monoliths, whose failures may be localized to one runtime, microservices communicate over networks. Each service-to-service invocation creates a possibility of latency, partial failure, or total unavailability. In a critical dependency, when this occurs, it causes cascading failures — where one service&#39;s downtime propagates through the system, ruining the user experience or even causing complete outages.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在过去十年中，在设计可扩展、可维护和可独立部署的应用程序时，微服务架构已变得司空见惯。将系统分解为多个以领域为中心的服务，开发团队可以快速开发，每个服务具有不同的技术堆栈，并独立扩展应用程序的组成部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;但这种灵活性是有代价的：操作复杂性和故障传播。与整体架构不同，微服务的故障可能局限于一个运行时，而微服务通过网络进行通信。每个服务到服务的调用都可能导致延迟、部分失败或完全不可用。在关键依赖项中，当发生这种情况时，它会导致级联故障 - 一项服务的停机时间会在系统中传播，破坏用户体验，甚至导致完全中断。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Domain-Driven Design Is Still Essential in Modern Software Development】为什么领域驱动设计在现代软件开发中仍然至关重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/domain-driven-design-modern-software-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;There’s no doubt that&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;has become the invisible infrastructure of our modern world. Over a decade ago,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Forbes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;published a prophetic article titled&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forbes.com/sites/techonomy/2011/11/30/now-every-company-is-a-software-company/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Now Every Company Is a Software Company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;At the time, that sounded bold — today, it feels like common sense. Whether in banking, healthcare, logistics, or agriculture, software has moved from the background to the core of business strategy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;This means that every company, regardless of industry, is now a&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;software-driven organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;Success no longer depends only on market reach or physical infrastructure but also on how effectively a business translates its goals into code. In other words, the quality of your software often determines the quality of your company’s decisions, processes, and customer experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;毫无疑问&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;软件&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;已成为现代世界隐形的基础设施。十多年前，&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;福布斯&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; 发表了一篇预言性文章，标题为&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forbes.com/sites/techonomy/2011/11/30/now-every-company-is-a-software-company/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;现在每个公司都是软件公司&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;。”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;当时，这听起来很大胆 - 如今，这感觉像是常识。无论是在银行、医疗保健、物流还是农业领域，软件已经从业务战略的背景转变为核心。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;这意味着每家公司，无论属于哪个行业，现在都是一家&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;软件驱动型组织&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; 成功不再仅仅取决于市场覆盖范围或物理基础设施，还取决于如何 企业可以有效地将其目标转化为代码。换句话说，软件的质量通常决定公司决策、流程和客户体验的质量。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python Development With Asynchronous SQLite and PostgreSQL】使用异步 SQLite 和 PostgreSQL 进行 Python 开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-async-sqlite-postgresql-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;After years of working from the comfort of Python and Django, I moved to the wild asynchronous world of FastAPI to improve latency in web-based AI applications. &lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;I started with FastAPI and built an open-source stack called&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Oppkey/fastopp&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;FastOpp&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;which adds command-line and web tools similar to Django.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Initially, things went smoothly using SQLite and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/omnilib/aiosqlite&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;aiosqlite&lt;/a&gt; to add AsyncIO to SQLite. I used &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sqlalchemy.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SQLAlchemy&lt;/a&gt; as my Object Relational Mapper (ORM) and Alembic as the database migration tool. Everything seemed to work easily, so I added a Python script to make things similar to Django’s &lt;code&gt;migrate.py&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在 Python 和 Django 的舒适环境下工作多年后，我转向 FastAPI 的疯狂异步世界，以改善基于 Web 的 AI 应用程序的延迟。 &lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;我从 FastAPI 开始，构建了一个名为&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Oppkey/fastopp&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;FastOpp&lt;/a&gt;的开源堆栈，&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;添加了类似的命令行和网络工具 到姜戈。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最初，使用 SQLite 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/omnilib/aiosqlite&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;aiosqlite&lt;/a&gt; 将 AsyncIO 添加到 SQLite 的过程进展顺利。我使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sqlalchemy.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SQLAlchemy&lt;/a&gt; 作为对象关系映射器 (ORM)，使用 Alembic 作为数据库迁移工具。一切看起来都很容易，所以我添加了一个 Python 脚本来制作类似于 Django 的 &lt;code&gt;migrate.py&lt;/code&gt; 的东西。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Distributed Locking in Cloud-Native Applications: Ensuring Consistency Across Multiple Instances】云原生应用程序中的分布式锁定：确保多个实例之间的一致性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/distributed-locking-cloud-native-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am sure that most of us may have used some kind of locking during development, or may have faced issues of incorrect results in some states that are difficult to reproduce. Things are not that complex when we need to manage them within the process or even multiple processes, but on the same machine. It is also very common these days that most of us are involved in making cloud-native applications/services, where there are multiple instances of the service[s], either due to high availability/load balancing. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In case of multiple instances of service[s], things become trickier when you face a situation where you need to make sure that certain operations must be performed in a synchronized manner, and it&#39;s not about multiple threads/processes but multiple pods/nodes in a native environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我确信我们大多数人可能在开发过程中使用过某种锁定，或者可能在某些状态下遇到过结果不正确且难以重现的问题。当我们需要在进程内甚至多个进程内但在同一台机器上管理它们时，事情并不那么复杂。如今，我们大多数人都参与制作云原生应用程序/服务，其中由于高可用性/负载平衡而存在多个服务实例，这也是很常见的。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在服务的多个实例的情况下，当您面临需要确保某些操作必须以同步方式执行的情况时，事情会变得更加棘手，并且这不是关于多个线程/进程，而是关于本机环境中的多个 Pod/节点。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Era of AI-First Backends: What Happens When APIs Become Contextualized Through LLMs?】人工智能优先后端时代：当 API 通过法学硕士融入情境时会发生什么？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-era-of-ai-first-backends-what-happens-when-api</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Introduction: What Happens When APIs Start Thinking?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Wondered what your backend might &#34;think&#34; about? Up until now, we have viewed LLMs (e.g., OpenAI&#39;s GPT series) as a code assistant or a chatbot. However, behind the scenes of those experiences is something that can take things to a much more impactful level: an AI-first backend experience. In this type of environment, APIs do not simply follow the pre-packaged flow, http status codes, or utility functions of a backend. Instead, they think, adapt, and develop logic dynamically at runtime based on LLMs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Imagine the API you are building does not adhere to the rigid flow of a flowchart or the meticulously precise steps of an HTTP post or get setup within your functionality. Rather, it responds and adapts logic based on the tone of the user, the prosody of the interaction, or state of the world (trends and behaviors at the time). Sounds like science fiction? Not anymore. Let&#39;s unpack how this works, why it will change the way you think about your applications, and how you can &#34;test&#34; it out today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;简介：当 API 开始思考时会发生什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;想知道您的后端可能会“思考”什么？到目前为止，我们将 LLM（例如 OpenAI 的 GPT 系列）视为代码助手或聊天机器人。然而，在这些体验的幕后，可以将事情提升到更具影响力的水平：人工智能优先的后端体验。在这种类型的环境中，API 并不简单地遵循后端的预打包流程、http 状态代码或实用函数。相反，他们基于法学硕士在运行时动态思考、适应和开发逻辑。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;想象一下，您正在构建的 API 不遵守严格的流程图流程或 HTTP post 的严格精确步骤，或在您的功能中进行设置。相反，它根据用户的语气、交互的韵律或世界的状态（当时的趋势和行为）来响应和调整逻辑。听起来像科幻小说吗？不再。让我们来了解一下它是如何工作的，为什么它会改变您对应用程序的看法，以及今天如何“测试”它。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Types of Web 3 APIs】Web 3 API 的类型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/types-of-web-3-apis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;An API (Application package interface) is a software tool that enables researchers and developers to access some third-party data and functionality within a main software. Usually, it’s a collection of software commands that act as an interface to an external database. Web 3 APIs act as translators, enabling applications to interact with features like smart contracts and on-chain data, empowering you to harness the power of Web3 without diving deep into technical complexities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Various API categories —REST, SOAP, RPC, and WebSocket— offer unique strengths tailored to different use cases:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;API（应用程序包接口）是一种软件工具，使研究人员和开发人员能够访问主软件中的一些第三方数据和功能。通常，它是充当外部数据库接口的软件命令的集合。 Web 3 API 充当翻译器，使应用程序能够与智能合约和链上数据等功能进行交互，使您能够利用 Web3 的强大功能，而无需深入研究技术复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;各种 API 类别（REST、SOAP、RPC 和 WebSocket）提供针对不同用例量身定制的独特优势：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Indexing Across Data Models: From Tables to Documents to Text】跨数据模型索引：从表到文档到文本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-model-indexing-tables-documents-text</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Every modern software application relies on a database to persist and manage its data. The choice of database technology is largely influenced by the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;application’s data model and its read and write throughput&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;For large datasets, query efficiency is critical. An inefficient query that works on a small dataset can quickly turn into a performance bottleneck when scaled to hundreds of thousands or millions of data points. While query optimization helps, it alone cannot guarantee high throughput. Factors such as data modeling, normalization, partitioning strategies, indexing, and even hardware resources&amp;nbsp;all play a role in determining how quickly a system can serve reads and process writes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;每个现代软件应用程序都依赖数据库来保存和管理其数据。数据库技术的选择很大程度上取决于应用程序的数据模型及其读写吞吐量&lt;span&gt;。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;对于大型数据集，查询效率至关重要。在小型数据集上运行的低效查询在扩展到数十万或数百万数据点时可能会很快变成性能瓶颈。虽然查询优化有所帮助，但仅靠它并不能保证高吞吐量。数据建模、规范化、分区策略、索引甚至硬件资源等因素都在决定系统提供读取和处理写入的速度方面发挥着作用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Secrets Manager: Designing Zero-Retention Secrets in AWS With Ephemeral Access Patterns】超越 Secrets Manager：使用临时访问模式在 AWS 中设计零保留密钥</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-retention-secrets-aws-ephemeral-access</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Secrets management in AWS has traditionally relied on long-lived secrets stored in Secrets Manager or Parameter Store. But as attack surfaces grow and threat actors become faster at exploiting exposed credentials, even rotated secrets begin to look like liabilities. The future of security in AWS leans toward ephemeral access, where credentials are generated just-in-time, scoped to the minimum needed permission, and vanish as soon as they are no longer needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article explores how to build a zero-retention secrets architecture in AWS, one that minimizes persistent secrets and instead leverages IAM roles, STS, session policies, and Lambda-based brokers. No Vault, no standing tokens, just-in-time, context-aware access.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS 中的密钥管理传统上依赖于存储在 Secrets Manager 或 Parameter Store 中的长期密钥。但随着攻击面的扩大和威胁行为者利用暴露凭证的速度越来越快，即使是轮换的秘密也开始看起来像是负债。 AWS 的安全性未来倾向于临时访问，其中凭证会及时生成，范围仅限于所需的最低权限，并在不再需要时立即消失。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文探讨了如何在 AWS 中构建零保留秘密架构，该架构可以最大程度地减少持久秘密，并利用 IAM 角色、STS、会话策略和基于 Lambda 的代理。没有保险库，没有常设令牌，即时、上下文感知的访问。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Senior Developers, What to Read Next?】高级开发人员，下一步该读什么？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/senior-developers-what-to-read-next</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Recently, one of my best friends, who is, in the meantime, one of the smartest developers I have the luck to know, asked me what book he should read next to further develop his skills. It took me some time to gather my thoughts, and it might be useful for others, too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;Spoiler alert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;: I could not find a single book that I would say is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;the one&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;to read as a senior developer.&lt;/span&gt; Instead, I summarized the books that I found good for one reason or another. As the summary also declared, this is a subjective list; feel free to agree or disagree with my choices, as well as feel free to leave a comment or contact me in any other way to share your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;最近，我最好的朋友之一（同时也是我有幸认识的最聪明的开发人员之一）问我他下一步应该读什么书来进一步发展他的技能。我花了一些时间来整理我的想法，这可能对其他人也有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;剧透警告&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;：我找不到一本我认为适合作为高级开发人员阅读的书&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color:透明;&#34;&gt;。&lt;/span&gt;相反，我总结了以下书籍： 出于这样或那样的原因，我发现很好。正如摘要中还声明的那样，这是一个主观列表；请随意同意或不同意我的选择，也请随意发表评论或以任何其他方式与我联系以分享您的想法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>