<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure AI and GPT-4: Real-World Applications and Best Practices】Azure AI 和 GPT-4：实际应用程序和最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/azure-ai-gpt-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Microsoft’s Azure AI has integrated GPT-4, delivering advanced natural language processing (NLP) capabilities through the cloud. This integration enables developers to create powerful applications that automate workflows, improve customer interactions, and enhance software development processes. With Azure’s scalability, security, and developer-friendly APIs, harnessing AI for innovation has never been easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article dives into practical ways developers can leverage &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/azure-openai-getting-started-series-part-1&#34;&gt;Azure AI and GPT-4&lt;/a&gt;, featuring real-world use cases, actionable code examples, and best practices to unlock the full potential of AI in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;微软的 Azure AI 集成了 GPT-4，通过云提供先进的自然语言处理 (NLP) 功能。这种集成使开发人员能够创建功能强大的应用程序，实现工作流程自动化、改善客户交互并增强软件开发流程。凭借 Azure 的可扩展性、安全性和开发人员友好的 API，利用 AI 进行创新从未如此简单。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文深入探讨了开发人员利用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/azure-openai-getting-started-series-part-1&#34;&gt;Azure AI 和GPT-4&lt;/a&gt;，包含真实的用例、可操作的代码示例和最佳实践，以释放人工智能在云中的全部潜力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Router4j: A Free Alternative to Google Maps for Route and Distance Calculation】Router4j：用于路线和距离计算的 Google 地图的免费替代品</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/router4j-free-alternative-google-maps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Google Maps is probably the first thing that comes to mind when considering a routing and distance calculation solution. However, its pricing may discourage its use in open-source projects or projects with severe budget constraints. This article will present two alternatives encapsulated by a free library known as &lt;strong&gt;router4j&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Geospatial APIs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As stated by its developer, Ryan McCaffery, the Geospatial API or simply &lt;a href=&#34;https://geo.dev/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;geo.dev&lt;/a&gt; is:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在考虑路线和距离计算解决方案时，首先想到的可能是 Google 地图。然而，其定价可能会阻碍其在开源项目或预算严格的项目中的使用。本文将介绍由名为 &lt;strong&gt;router4j&lt;/strong&gt; 的免费库封装的两种替代方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;地理空间 API&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正如其开发者 Ryan McCaffery 所说，Geospatial API 或简称为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://geo.dev/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;geo.dev&lt;/a&gt;是：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Art of the Possible】可能性的艺术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/art-of-possible</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Last November, I got to spend more time with my 8-year-old nephew. Since we last met, he had added another box of Legos, lots of pencils, markers, and pastels to his collection. Soon, he began showing off his home creations and schoolbook contributions with that excitement only a child can feel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every Lego structure, every drawing, and every little craft project came with its own enthusiastic explanation. Lego instructions? Who needs them? He followed his instincts, building and creating in ways that felt right to him, unconstrained by rules or expectations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;去年 11 月，我有更多时间陪伴我 8 岁的侄子。自从我们上次见面以来，他又在他的收藏中添加了另一盒乐高积木、大量铅笔、记号笔和蜡笔。很快，他开始展示他的家庭创作和教科书贡献，带着只有孩子才能感受到的兴奋。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个乐高结构、每张图纸和每个小工艺项目都有自己热情的解释。乐高说明？谁需要它们？他遵循自己的直觉，以他认为正确的方式构建和创造，不受规则或期望的约束。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding DNS Records: What They Are and Why They Matter】了解 DNS 记录：它们是什么以及它们为何重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-dns-records</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The internet functions seamlessly because of a behind-the-scenes process many take for granted — DNS records. These records are critical for how websites, emails, and other online services operate. If you’ve ever wondered how your browser finds the right website or how email gets delivered, it’s all thanks to DNS records. Let’s break it down and explore what they are, how they work, and how to manage them effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Are DNS Records?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DNS (Domain Name System) records are key components of the internet&#39;s infrastructure. They serve as instructions that let computers know how to handle requests associated with a domain name. Think of DNS records as the phonebook of the web, mapping user-friendly domain names (like &lt;code&gt;example.com&lt;/code&gt;) to their corresponding machine-readable IP addresses. Without them, you’d need to remember long strings of numbers instead of simple URLs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;互联网之所以能够无缝运行，是因为有一个许多人认为理所当然的幕后过程——DNS 记录。这些记录对于网站、电子邮件和其他在线服务的运行至关重要。如果您曾经想知道浏览器如何找到正确的网站或如何发送电子邮件，这都要归功于 DNS 记录。让我们对其进行分解并探讨它们是什么、它们如何工作以及如何有效地管理它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是 DNS 记录？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DNS（域名系统）记录是互联网基础设施的关键组成部分。它们充当指令，让计算机知道如何处理与域名相关的请求。将 DNS 记录视为网络电话簿，将用户友好的域名（如 &lt;code&gt;example.com&lt;/code&gt;）映射到相应的机器可读 IP 地址。如果没有它们，您将需要记住长串数字而不是简单的 URL。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Sequential: Why Rust&#39;s Threading Model Changed How I Think About Concurrent Programming】超越顺序：为什么 Rust 的线程模型改变了我对并发编程的看法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rust-threading-concurrent-programming</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Threading is a fundamental concept in modern programming that allows applications to perform multiple operations concurrently. Rust, with its focus on memory safety and zero-cost abstractions, provides powerful tools for handling concurrent operations. In this article, we&#39;ll explore how threading works in Rust through practical examples.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction to Threading in Rust&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rust-programming-language-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;Rust&#39;s&lt;/a&gt; threading model is designed with safety in mind. The language&#39;s ownership and type systems help prevent common concurrent programming mistakes like data races at compile time. This approach makes &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-concurrency-and-multi-threading&#34;&gt;concurrent programming&lt;/a&gt; more reliable and easier to reason about.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;线程是现代编程中的一个基本概念，它允许应用程序同时执行多个操作。 Rust 专注于内存安全和零成本抽象，为处理并发操作提供了强大的工具。在本文中，我们将通过实际示例探讨线程在 Rust 中的工作原理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Rust 中的线程简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rust-programming-language-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;Rust 的&lt;/a&gt;线程模型在设计时就考虑到了安全性。该语言的所有权和类型系统有助于防止常见的并发编程错误，例如编译时的数据争用。这种方法使&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-concurrency-and-multi-threading&#34;&gt;并发编程&lt;/a&gt;更加可靠且更易于推理。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS Nitro Enclaves: Enhancing Security With Isolated Compute Environments】AWS Nitro Enclaves：通过隔离计算环境增强安全性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-nitro-enclaves-enhances-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Data breaches cost organizations an average of $4.45 million in 2023. This shows how secure data processing is becoming more crucial by the day, and the challenge grows more complex with sensitive information in cloud environments. AWS enclave technology solves this biggest problem by creating isolated compute environments that protect sensitive data and applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS Nitro Enclaves provides a robust solution to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/will-open-source-sdks-improve-the-adoption-of-conf&#34;&gt;confidential computing&lt;/a&gt;. It lets you process sensitive data with improved security guarantees. These isolated compute environments run among EC2 instances but stay separate from the host and other applications. This article will cover how these enclaves work, the implementation of secure workload processing, and the best ways to deploy them in production environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;到 2023 年，数据泄露平均会给组织造成 445 万美元的损失。这表明安全数据处理变得越来越重要，而云环境中的敏感信息带来的挑战也变得更加复杂。 AWS enclave 技术通过创建隔离的计算环境来保护敏感数据和应用程序，解决了这一最大的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS Nitro Enclaves 为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/will-open-source-sdks-improve-the-adoption-of-conf&#34;&gt;提供了强大的解决方案机密计算&lt;/a&gt;。它使您可以通过改进的安全保证来处理敏感数据。这些隔离的计算环境在 EC2 实例之间运行，但与主机和其他应用程序保持分离。本文将介绍这些 enclave 的工作原理、安全工作负载处理的实现以及在生产环境中部署它们的最佳方法。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Importance of AI System Memory】AI系统内存的重要性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/importance-of-ai-system-memory</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence (AI) has made tremendous strides in recent years, transforming from basic pattern recognition systems to complex, interactive entities capable of understanding and generating human-like responses. A crucial component in this evolution is the concept of memory in AI systems. Just as memory is essential for human cognition, enabling learning and the application of past experiences to new situations, memory in AI systems is foundational for their ability to function intelligently and adaptively.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The journey of AI memory has been nothing short of transformative, evolving from basic systems with short-term recall capabilities to sophisticated models capable of long-term insights. This evolution mirrors the growth of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;AI as a field&lt;/a&gt;, where early stages were focused on functionality and efficiency, and later stages have increasingly prioritized deep learning, adaptation, and context-based understanding.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;近年来，人工智能 (AI) 取得了巨大进步，从基本的模式识别系统转变为能够理解并生成类人响应的复杂交互式实体。这一演变的一个关键组成部分是人工智能系统中的内存概念。正如记忆对于人类认知至关重要，能够学习并将过去的经验应用于新情况，人工智能系统中的记忆也是其智能和自适应功能的基础。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;AI 记忆的历程堪称变革，从具有短期记忆能力的基本系统发展到具有长期洞察力的复杂模型。这种演变反映了&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;人工智能作为一个领域&lt;/a&gt;的发展，其中早期阶段侧重于功能和效率，后期阶段越来越优先考虑深度学习、适应和基于情境的理解。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Developer&#39;s Guide to Modern Queue Patterns】现代队列模式开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/modern-queue-patterns-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today’s distributed systems, queues serve as the backbone of reliable, scalable architectures. They’re not just simple data structures — they’re powerful tools that help manage system load, ensure reliability, and maintain data consistency across complex distributed applications. This comprehensive guide explores the most important queue patterns that solve real-world problems in modern software architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Basics: What’s a Queue?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Think of a queue like a line at a coffee shop. People join the line at one end and get served at the other end, following the First-In-First-Out (FIFO) principle. In software, queues work the same way - they store messages or tasks that need to be processed in order. However, modern queue implementations go far beyond this simple concept, offering sophisticated features for handling complex scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的分布式系统中，队列是可靠、可扩展架构的支柱。它们不仅仅是简单的数据结构，它们还是强大的工具，可以帮助管理系统负载、确保可靠性并维护复杂分布式应用程序中的数据一致性。本综合指南探讨了解决现代软件架构中实际问题的最重要的队列模式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;基础知识：什么是队列？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将队列想象成咖啡店里的队伍。人们在一端排队，并在另一端得到服务，遵循先进先出 (FIFO) 原则。在软件中，队列的工作方式相同——它们存储需要按顺序处理的消息或任务。然而，现代队列实现远远超出了这个简单的概念，提供了处理复杂场景的复杂功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Rise Of Reasoner Models: Scaling Test-Time Compute】Reasoner 模型的兴起：扩展测试时间计算</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/reasoner-models-test-time-compute</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A new kind of LLM has recently been popping out everywhere: &lt;strong&gt;Reasoner models&lt;/strong&gt;. Kickstarted by OpenAI&#39;s o1 and o3, these models are a bit different from the rest. These models particularly shine when dealing with mathematical problems and coding challenges, where success depends on following precise, logical steps to reach a correct solution. On the other hand, these models take much longer to answer than any conventional model.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The approach to problem-solving used by these models mirrors a well-known distinction in human cognition: System 1 versus System 2 thinking. Traditional LLMs operate much like System 1 thinking — quick, intuitive, and based on pattern recognition. They generate responses rapidly based on their trained neural networks. In contrast, Reasoner models embody System 2 thinking — deliberate, methodical, and self-correcting. They can pause, reflect on their reasoning, and even backtrack when they detect potential errors in their logic.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;一种新型的 LLM 最近随处可见：&lt;strong&gt;Reasoner 模型&lt;/strong&gt;。这些模型由 OpenAI 的 o1 和 o3 启动，与其他模型有点不同。这些模型在处理数学问题和编码挑战时尤其出色，成功取决于遵循精确、逻辑的步骤来得出正确的解决方案。另一方面，这些模型比任何传统模型需要更长的时间来回答。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些模型使用的解决问题的方法反映了人类认知中众所周知的区别：系统 1 与系统 2 思维。传统法学硕士的运作方式与系统 1 思维非常相似——快速、直观且基于模式识别。他们根据训练有素的神经网络快速生成响应。相比之下，Reasoner 模型体现了系统 2 思维——深思熟虑、有条不紊和自我纠正。他们可以暂停，反思自己的推理，甚至在发现逻辑中存在潜在错误时回溯。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Java Applications for AWS Lambda】为 AWS Lambda 优化 Java 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-apps-aws-lambda</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Java has long been a trusted language for enterprise applications due to its versatility and ability to run seamlessly across various platforms, but as serverless platforms like AWS Lambda gain momentum, deploying Java applications in serverless platforms presents unique challenges, notably due to bloated packages and time to get initialized.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This led to an increase in the popularity and adoption of languages such as Go, Node.js, and Python for applications that are traditionally built on Java. When we take a deeper look to understand the inherent struggles that JVM-based applications have, the prominent ones are slow cold starts, high memory consumption, and runtime inefficiencies, making lighter runtimes more attractive in cloud-native environments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Java 长期以来一直是企业应用程序值得信赖的语言，因为它具有多功能性和跨各种平台无缝运行的能力，但随着 AWS Lambda 等无服务器平台的发展势头，在无服务器平台中部署 Java 应用程序面临着独特的挑战，特别是由于臃肿的包和初始化时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;这使得 Go、Node.js 和 Python 等语言在传统上基于 Java 构建的应用程序中越来越流行和采用。当我们深入了解基于 JVM 的应用程序所面临的固有问题时，会发现最突出的问题是冷启动速度慢、内存消耗高和运行时效率低下，这使得更轻的运行时在云原生环境中更具吸引力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>