<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding AI Agent Types:Guide to 8 Modern AI Architectures】了解 AI 代理类型：8 种现代 AI 架构指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-ai-agent-types-ai-architectures</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will discuss eight major AI agent types: LCM, HRM, LAM, SLM, VLM, LRM, MOE, and GPT, optimized for specific problem domains, technological implementations, and practical applications. By understanding the strengths and limitations of each architecture, practitioners can make informed decisions when designing AI systems for production environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The landscape of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-ai-in-dotnet&#34;&gt;AI agents&lt;/a&gt; has transformed dramatically over the past five years. Rather than developing single models to address all problems, the industry has converged on specialized architectures, each tailored to specific computational and reasoning requirements. This article provides practitioners, researchers, and decision-makers with a detailed roadmap of eight foundational agent types, complete with technological stacks and implementation guidance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将讨论八种主要的人工智能代理类型：LCM、HRM、LAM、SLM、VLM、LRM、MOE 和 GPT，针对特定问题领域、技术实现和实际应用进行了优化。通过了解每种架构的优势和局限性，从业者可以在为生产环境设计人工智能系统时做出明智的决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去五年中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-ai-in-dotnet&#34;&gt;人工智能代理&lt;/a&gt;的格局发生了巨大变化。该行业并没有开发单一模型来解决所有问题，而是集中在专门的架构上，每个架构都根据特定的计算和推理要求进行定制。本文为从业者、研究人员和决策者提供了八种基本代理类型的详细路线图，并附有技术堆栈和实施指南。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Modern Full-Stack Python Applications: MVC Architecture Meets Enterprise-Ready Python】构建现代全栈 Python 应用程序：MVC 架构与企业级 Python 的结合</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-modern-full-stack-python-applications-mvc</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;The Model-View-Controller (MVC) architecture has been a cornerstone of software development for decades, but its relevance extends far beyond traditional web applications. &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;As I was developing a curriculum for a free course on Industry Projects with Python aimed at college students, I realized that enterprise use of Python had changed dramatically in the last year, driven by Python&#39;s dominance in AI and data science.&lt;/span&gt; As Python continues its meteoric rise in AI backends and enterprise development, developers are building full-stack applications using Python across both frontend and backend layers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;This article explores how MVC principles apply across diverse software projects, examines Python&#39;s growth in AI development, discusses the emerging trend of unified Python language stacks (beyond just TypeScript/Node.js), and highlights modern tooling that makes Python a first-class enterprise language.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;模型-视图-控制器 (MVC) 架构几十年来一直是软件开发的基石，但其相关性远远超出了传统的 Web 应用程序。 &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;当我为面向大学生的 Python 行业项目免费课程开发课程时，我意识到，在 Python 在 AI 和数据科学领域的主导地位的推动下，去年企业对 Python 的使用发生了巨大变化。&lt;/span&gt;随着 Python 在 AI 后端和企业开发中的持续迅速崛起，开发人员正在使用 Python 跨前端和后端层构建全栈应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;本文探讨了 MVC 原则如何应用于不同的软件项目，研究了 Python 在 AI 开发中的增长，讨论了统一 Python 语言堆栈（不仅仅是 TypeScript/Node.js）的新兴趋势，并重点介绍了使 Python 成为一流企业语言的现代工具。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enabling Single-Sign-On in SaaS Application】在 SaaS 应用程序中启用单点登录</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enabling-single-sign-on-in-saas-application</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction of SSO&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Single sign-on (SSO) allows users to log in to enterprise applications using central organizational credentials, which can be used across multiple internal applications without re-entering them. There will be a central Identity Provider that manages the same credentials across multiple applications. Once credentials are provided, they will remain in session for a set number of hours (6 or 8, as per organizational policy). Once credentials expire, the user has to re-enter them when they try to log in to any application, and again, there will be no login requirement for up to 8 hours. The Identity Provider handles authentication, authorization, and identity management across most aspects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why SSO Is Important&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a multinational organization, there are multiple applications for different purposes. Users of those applications need to maintain separate credentials for each application, which is hard to track, and maintaining safe password requirements across all the applications is hard for users.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;单点登录简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;单点登录 (SSO) 允许用户使用中央组织凭据登录企业应用程序，这些凭据可以在多个内部应用程序之间使用，而无需重新输入。将有一个中央身份提供商来管理多个应用程序中的相同凭据。提供凭据后，他们将在会话中保留一定的小时数（6 小时或 8 小时，根据组织政策）。一旦凭据过期，用户在尝试登录任何应用程序时都必须重新输入凭据，并且最多 8 小时内不需要登录。身份提供者处理大多数方面的身份验证、授权和身份管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么单点登录很重要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在跨国组织中，有多种用于不同目的的应用程序。这些应用程序的用户需要为每个应用程序维护单独的凭据，这很难跟踪，并且在所有应用程序中维护安全密码要求对于用户来说也很困难。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Real Cost of DevOps Backup Scripts】DevOps 备份脚本的实际成本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-real-cost-of-devops-backup-scripts</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;477&#34; data-start=&#34;168&#34;&gt;Organizations rely on different methods for data backup, depending on factors such as data criticality. There are several options, ranging from DIY scripts to third-party backup vendors. The effectiveness of these approaches depends on how well they protect data and support timely recovery after an incident.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;610&#34; data-start=&#34;479&#34;&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devsecops-strategic-imperative-modern-devops&#34;&gt;DevSecOps&lt;/a&gt;, data resilience is key, which puts backup and disaster recovery at the center of any effective security architecture.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;477&#34; data-start=&#34;168&#34;&gt;组织依赖不同的数据备份方法，具体取决于数据重要性等因素。有多种选择，从 DIY 脚本到第三方备份供应商。这些方法的有效性取决于它们保护数据和支持事件后及时恢复的程度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;610&#34; data-start=&#34;479&#34;&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devsecops-strategic-imperative-modern-devops&#34;&gt;DevSecOps&lt;/a&gt;中，数据弹性是关键，它将备份和灾难恢复置于任何有效安全架构的中心。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Self-Healing Directory: Architecting AI-Driven Security for Active Directory】自我修复目录：为 Active Directory 构建 AI 驱动的安全性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/self-healing-directory-ai-driven-security-for-ad</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;504&#34; data-start=&#34;217&#34;&gt;For over two decades, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/managing-aws-managed-microsoft-active-directory-objects&#34;&gt;Active Directory (AD)&lt;/a&gt; has been the “central nervous system” of enterprise IT. It manages who gets in, what they can access, and when. Because of this centrality, it is the single most valuable target for an attacker. If you control AD, you control the organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;855&#34; data-start=&#34;506&#34;&gt;The traditional security architecture for AD — SIEM logs, manual audits, and rule-based alerts — is broken. It generates too much noise (alert fatigue) and reacts too slowly (long dwell times). Modern attacks like Kerberoasting or “living off the land” use legitimate tools (such as PowerShell) to blend in, making signature-based detection ineffective.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;504&#34; data-start=&#34;217&#34;&gt;二十多年来，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/managing-aws-management-microsoft-active-directory-objects&#34;&gt;Active Directory (AD)&lt;/a&gt; 一直是企业 IT 的“中枢神经系统”。它管理谁可以进入、他们可以访问什么以及何时访问。由于这种中心性，它是攻击者最有价值的目标。如果您控制了 AD，您就控制了组织。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;855&#34; data-start=&#34;506&#34;&gt;传统的 AD 安全架构（SIEM 日志、手动审核和基于规则的警报）已被打破。它产生太多噪音（警报疲劳）并且反应太慢（停留时间长）。 Kerberoasting 或“living off the land”等现代攻击使用合法工具（例如 PowerShell）进行混合，使得基于签名的检测无效。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hybrid Vector Graph with AI Agents for Software Test Case Creation】用于软件测试用例创建的人工智能代理的混合矢量图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/hybrid-vector-graph-with-ai-agents-for-software-te</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;307&#34; data-start=&#34;252&#34;&gt;The Problem: Manual Test Case Creation Doesn’t Scale&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;590&#34; data-start=&#34;309&#34;&gt;Modern software development faces a critical bottleneck in test case creation. As applications become increasingly complex — with microservices architectures, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/api-driven-integration-is-a-revolutionary-game-changer&#34;&gt;API integrations&lt;/a&gt;, and distributed systems — manually creating comprehensive test cases becomes time-intensive and error-prone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;615&#34; data-start=&#34;592&#34;&gt;Key challenges include:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;307&#34; data-start=&#34;252&#34;&gt;问题：手动创建测试用例无法扩展&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;590&#34; data-start=&#34;309&#34;&gt;现代软件开发在测试用例创建方面面临着关键瓶颈。随着应用程序变得越来越复杂（微服务架构、API 集成和分布式系统），手动创建全面的测试用例变得非常耗时且容易出错。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;615&#34; data-start=&#34;592&#34;&gt;主要挑战包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Best Java GUI Frameworks for Modern Applications】适用于现代应用程序的最佳 Java GUI 框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/best-java-gui-frameworks-for-modern-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;504&#34; data-start=&#34;194&#34;&gt;Java has become one of the world’s most versatile programming languages, chosen for its adaptability, stability, and platform independence. Its extensive ecosystem encompasses virtually every application type, from web development to enterprise solutions, game design, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-internet-of-things-revolution&#34;&gt;Internet of Things (IoT)&lt;/a&gt;, and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;679&#34; data-start=&#34;506&#34;&gt;With an estimated &lt;a href=&#34;https://stratoflow.com/why-is-java-so-popular/&#34;&gt;51 billion active&lt;/a&gt; Java Virtual Machines (JVMs) globally, it goes without question that Java powers a substantial portion of modern software infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;504&#34; data-start=&#34;194&#34;&gt;Java 已成为世界上最通用的编程语言之一，因其适应性、稳定性和平台独立性而被选中。其广泛的生态系统几乎涵盖所有应用程序类型，从 Web 开发到企业解决方案、游戏设计、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-internet-of-things-revolution&#34;&gt;物联网 (IoT)&lt;/a&gt; 等等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;679&#34; data-start=&#34;506&#34;&gt;据估计，全球&lt;a href=&#34;https://stratoflow.com/why-is-java-so-popular/&#34;&gt;有 510 亿个活跃&lt;/a&gt; Java 虚拟机 (JVM)，毫无疑问，Java 为现代软件基础设施的很大一部分提供了支持。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ITSM Uncovered: How IT Teams Keep Businesses Running Smoothly】ITSM 揭秘：IT 团队如何保持业务平稳运行</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/itsm-uncovered-how-it-teams-keep-businesses-runnin</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;576&#34; data-start=&#34;161&#34;&gt;In today’s digital environment, incidents can have an immediate impact on revenue, customer trust, and team productivity. Traditional &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/evolving-landscape-of-itsm-through-ai&#34;&gt;IT Service Management (ITSM)&lt;/a&gt; approaches often struggle to keep pace with cloud-native, distributed, and AI-driven ecosystems. Organizations are now rethinking ITSM not as a process-heavy function, but as an adaptive platform that blends automation, collaboration, and intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;778&#34; data-start=&#34;578&#34;&gt;As organizations modernize, ITSM isn’t disappearing — it’s evolving from ticket queues into intelligent automation platforms that bridge the gap between development, operations, and business continuity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;576&#34; data-start=&#34;161&#34;&gt;在当今的数字环境中，事件可能会对收入、客户信任和团队生产力产生直接影响。传统的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/evolving-landscape-of-itsm-through-ai&#34;&gt;IT 服务管理 (ITSM)&lt;/a&gt; 方法往往难以跟上云原生、分布式和人工智能驱动的生态系统的步伐。组织现在正在重新思考 ITSM，不再将其视为流程繁重的功能，而是将其视为融合自动化、协作和智能的自适应平台。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;778&#34; data-start=&#34;578&#34;&gt;随着组织的现代化，ITSM 并没有消失 - 它正在从工单队列演变为智能自动化平台，以弥合开发、运营和业务连续性之间的差距。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Achieve More Accurate Data Extraction From Invoices】如何实现更准确的发票数据提取</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/accurate-invoice-data-extraction</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Extracting structured data from invoices looks straightforward until you run it at scale. Invoices arrive as PDFs, scans, and photos; they follow different layouts, languages, and fonts, and many contain tables, stamps, handwritten notes, or low-quality images. Even when the information is present, it is often split across lines, repeated in multiple places, or labeled inconsistently, which makes simple pattern matching unreliable. Moreover, we can face issues in numeric and alphanumeric fields, such as VINs and invoice numbers, which are especially error-prone because visually similar characters get swapped, for example, o and 0, w and v, 5 and s, or i and l.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The hardest part is that small errors are costly. A single misread character in an invoice number, a swapped decimal separator in a total amount, or a billing address confused with a shipping address can break downstream automation and trigger manual review. A robust solution usually combines several layers: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/search-basic-document-retrieval-to-answer-generation&#34;&gt;document ingestion&lt;/a&gt; and preprocessing, classic OCR and PDF text extraction, rule-based parsing for predictable patterns, business validation rules such as total consistency and identifier checks, and a workflow that routes low-confidence cases to human review.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;从发票中提取结构化数据看起来很简单，除非您大规模运行它。发票以 PDF、扫描件和照片形式送达；它们遵循不同的布局、语言和字体，并且许多包含表格、图章、手写笔记或低质量图像。即使信息存在，它也经常被跨行分割、在多个地方重复或标记不一致，这使得简单的模式匹配不可靠。此外，我们可能会面临数字和字母数字字段的问题，例如 VIN 和发票号码，这些问题特别容易出错，因为视觉上相似的字符会被交换，例如 o 和 0、w 和 v、5 和 s、i 和 l。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;最困难的部分是小错误会带来高昂的代价。发票号码中的单个误读字符、总额中小数点分隔符的交换或帐单地址与送货地址混淆都可能会破坏下游自动化并触发手动审核。强大的解决方案通常结合多个层：&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/search-basic-document-retrieval-to-answer- Generation&#34;&gt;文档提取&lt;/a&gt;和预处理、经典 OCR 和 PDF 文本提取、基于规则的可预测模式解析、业务验证规则（例如总体一致性和标识符检查）以及将低置信度案例路由至人工审核的工作流程。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Architecting Immutable Data Integrity with Amazon QLDB and Blockchain】使用 Amazon QLDB 和区块链构建不可变的数据完整性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/immutable-data-integrity-with-qldb-and-blockchain</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;472&#34; data-start=&#34;193&#34;&gt;In the current landscape of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-automatically-detect-multiple-cybersecurity&#34;&gt;ransomware and sophisticated SQL injection attacks&lt;/a&gt;, standard database security is no longer sufficient. We rely heavily on cryptographic hashes (such as SHA-256) to verify data integrity. The logic is simple: if the hash changes, the data was altered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;719&#34; data-start=&#34;474&#34;&gt;But there is a flaw in this logic. If an attacker gains administrative access to your database, they can modify the data and the stored hash simultaneously. The “seal” is broken, and you have no way of proving the original state of the document.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;472&#34; data-start=&#34;193&#34;&gt;在当前&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-automatically-detect-multiple-cybersecurity&#34;&gt;勒索软件和复杂的 SQL 注入攻击&lt;/a&gt;的情况下，标准的数据库安全已不再足够。我们严重依赖加密哈希（例如 SHA-256）来验证数据完整性。逻辑很简单：如果哈希值发生变化，数据就会被更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;719&#34; data-start=&#34;474&#34;&gt;但是这个逻辑有一个缺陷。如果攻击者获得对数据库的管理访问权限，他们可以同时修改数据和存储的哈希值。 “封印”被打破，你无法证明文件的原始状态。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>