<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Implement Linked Lists in Go】如何在GO中实现链接列表</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/go-linked-lists</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Linked lists are one of the most common data structures used for dynamic memory allocation. Here, a list of a finite set of elements is created, which contains at least two memory locations: one for the data element and another for the pointer that links the next set of elements. This tutorial explains how different linked lists can be implemented using pointers and structure types in Go.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Data Structures in Go&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The random access memory (RAM) can be visualized as a table, a matrix, or a grid of addressable locations. In order to store values in the table, Go programmers need to designate it into &lt;em&gt;locatable structures&lt;/em&gt;. These locatable structures are given a convenient name called &lt;em&gt;variable name&lt;/em&gt;. Understand that a name given to a variable is only for the convenience of the programmer; once the program is compiled, the variable name is replaced with a &lt;em&gt;reference&lt;/em&gt; (or memory address, such as &lt;strong&gt;0x78BAC&lt;/strong&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;链接列表是用于动态内存分配的最常见数据结构之一。在这里，创建了一组有限元素的列表，其中包含至少两个内存位置：一个用于数据元素，另一个用于链接下一组元素的指针。本教程解释了如何使用指针和结构类型在GO中实现不同的链接列表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; GO &lt;/h2&gt;中的数据结构&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随机访问存储器（RAM）可以可视化为表，矩阵或可寻址位置的网格。为了将值存储在表格中，GO程序员需要将其指定为可置处的结构&lt;/em&gt;。这些可定点的结构被给出了一个方便的名称，称为&lt;em&gt;变量名称&lt;/em&gt;。理解给变量的名称仅是为了方便程序员；一旦编译了程序，变量名称将替换为A &lt;em&gt;参考&lt;/em&gt;（或内存地址，例如&lt;strong&gt; 0x78bac &lt;/strong&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fixing OutOfMemoryErrors in Java Applications】在Java应用程序中修复OutofMemoryErrors</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fixing-outofmemoryerrors-in-java-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In one of my earlier posts, we discussed &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-heap-dumps-to-find-memory-leaks&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;how to best find memory leaks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;and the reasons behind them. It&#39;s best to use a focused and modern tool like HeapHero to detect OutOfMemory errors and many other performance bottlenecks, as it can pinpoint the real culprits and suggest ways to optimize the usage of computing resources. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;fr-inner&#34; contenteditable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;Above, you can see that there are a few thousand objects of&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;code&gt;byte[]&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;String&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;int[]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; etc. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在我之前的一篇文章中，我们讨论了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/using-heap-dumps-dumps-dumps-to-find-memory-leaks” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;如何最佳地找到记忆泄漏&lt;/a&gt;和其他原因&lt;/a&gt;和其他原因。最好使用Heaphero（例如Heaphero）的重点和现代工具来检测OutofMemory错误和许多其他性能瓶颈，因为它可以确定真正的罪魁祸首，并提出了优化计算资源使用的方法的方法。   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class =“ fr-inner” contenteaditable =“ true”&gt;&#xA; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;span style =“ background-color：透明;”&gt;上面，您可以看到&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;code&gt; byte [] &lt;/code&gt;，&lt;/code&gt; string&gt; string &lt;/code&gt; int []</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Doris and Hive Work Together to Maximize Data Analysis Efficiency】多丽丝和蜂巢如何一起工作以最大化数据分析效率</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/doris-hive-data-analysis-efficiency</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;At 3 a.m., the office is filled only with the dim glow of the computer screens. Data engineer Xiao Ming is struggling with two &#34;heavyweights&#34; — Doris and Hive. &#34;Export, clean, import...&#34; He mechanically repeats these steps between different components, his eyes starting to see stars.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;This scene is all too common in data teams, making one wonder: Do we really have to manually shuffle data for the rest of our lives? Just then, Doris extended an &#34;olive branch&#34; to Hive — the Hive Catalog made its dazzling debut! It&#39;s like arranging a perfect marriage for this &#34;data couple,&#34; allowing Doris to directly read and write Hive data, enabling the two systems to &#34;fly together.&#34; Whether it&#39;s HDFS or object storage, simple queries or complex analyses, one Catalog can handle it all!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;凌晨3点，办公室只充满了计算机屏幕的昏暗光芒。数据工程师小敏正在与两个“重量级”  - 多丽丝和蜂巢中挣扎。 “出口，干净，进口……”他机械地重复了不同组件之间的这些步骤，他的眼睛开始看到星星。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个场景在数据团队中非常普遍，使一个奇迹令人惊讶：我们真的必须在余生中手动洗牌吗？就在这时，多丽丝（Doris）向蜂巢（Hive）延伸了一个“橄榄树”（Olive Branch） -  Hive Catalog首次亮相！这就像为这对“数据夫妇”安排完美的婚姻，允许多丽丝直接读取和编写蜂巢数据，从而使两个系统可以“一起飞行”。无论是HDFS还是对象存储，简单的查询或复杂的分析，一个目录都可以处理所有目录！ &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 20:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Driven RAG Systems: Practical Implementation With LangChain】AI驱动的抹布系统：Langchain的实际实施</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-driven-rag-systems-langchain</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) is revolutionizing artificial intelligence by combining powerful generative AI models with sophisticated information retrieval systems. This comprehensive guide explores foundational concepts essential for understanding RAG, including information retrieval, generative AI models, embeddings, and vector databases, followed by a detailed, practical step-by-step implementation using LangChain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understanding these fundamentals and their practical application through &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-langchain-and-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LangChain&lt;/a&gt; allows developers and businesses to deploy effective, scalable, and context-aware AI solutions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;检索功能增强的生成（RAG）正在通过将强大的生成AI模型与复杂的信息检索系统相结合，从而彻底改变了人工智能。该综合指南探讨了理解破布至关重要的基础概念，包括信息检索，生成AI模型，嵌入和矢量数据库，然后使用Langchain进行了详细的，实用的逐步实现。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-langchain-and-lange-langue-models”&gt; langchain &lt;/a&gt;使开发人员和企业可以在有效，可扩展的AI解决方案。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Setting Up Your First Event-Driven Automation With Ansible】使用Ansible设置您的第一个事件驱动的自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/event-driven-automation-with-ansible</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Event-Driven Ansible enables real-time automation by automatically reacting to system events, logs, or alerts without manual intervention. This guide provides a step-by-step approach to setting up basic event-driven automation using Ansible Rulebooks and &lt;code&gt;ansible.eda.range&lt;/code&gt; module.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By the end of this tutorial, you will have created your first event-driven playbook that prints a hello message using &lt;code&gt;ansible.eda.hello&lt;/code&gt; module.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;事件驱动的Ansible通过自动对系统事件，日志或警报自动反应而无需手动干预，可以实现实时自动化。本指南提供了一种逐步的方法，可以使用Ansible规则手册和&lt;code&gt; ansible.eda.range &lt;/code&gt;模块来设置基本事件驱动的自动化。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本教程的末尾，您将创建第一个由事件驱动的剧本，该剧本使用&lt;code&gt; ansible.eda.hello &lt;/code&gt; Module打印Hello消息。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dynamic Web Forms In React For Enterprise Platforms】企业平台的React中的动态Web表单</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dynamic-web-forms-react-enterprise-platforms</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Forms are some of the easiest things to build in React, thanks to the useForm hook. For simple forms such as login, contact us, and newsletter signup forms, hard coding works just fine. But, when you have apps that require frequent updates to their forms, for example, surveys or product configuration tools, hard coding becomes cumbersome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The same goes for forms that require consistent validation or forms in apps that use micro frontends. For these types of forms, you need to build them dynamically. Fortunately, JSON and APIs provide a straightforward way to define and render these types of forms dynamically.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;表单是借助useform钩子在react中最简单的东西。有关登录，与我们联系和新闻通讯注册表单等简单表格，硬编码效果很好。但是，当您拥有需要频繁更新其表单的应用程序（例如调查或产品配置工具）时，硬编码会变得繁琐。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在使用微观前端的应用中需要一致的验证或表单的表单也是如此。对于这些类型的形式，您需要动态构建它们。幸运的是，JSON和API提供了一种直接的方式来定义和渲染这些类型的形式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker vs Kubernetes: Which to Use and When?】Docker vs Kubernetes：使用哪个以及何时？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-vs-kubernetes-showdown</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Containerization has changed the script of software development and deployment, significantly increasing the efficiency and portability. The two technologies at the forefront of this are Docker and Kubernetes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Docker is leading in container creation, while Kubernetes leads the orchestration, which is used for managing containers at scale. For developers, DevOps pros, and tech leaders, picking the right tool or a combination can make or break projects. In this article, we take a deep dive into the world of Docker and Kubernetes, discussing their strengths and helping you decide when to deploy each one.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;容器化改变了软件开发和部署的脚本，大大提高了效率和便携性。这两种技术处于最前沿的是Docker和Kubernetes。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Docker在创建容器中处于领先地位，而Kubernetes则领导编排，该编排用于规模管理容器。对于开发人员，DevOps专业人士和技术领导者，选择合适的工具或组合可以制作或打破项目。在本文中，我们深入研究了Docker和Kubernetes的世界，讨论他们的优势并帮助您决定何时部署每个人。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Achieving Zero Trust and Air-Gapped IaC in IBM Cloud With Schematics】使用原理图实现零信任和IAC的IAC IAC</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/achieving-zero-trust-and-air-gapped-iac-deployment</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;As modern enterprises continue their journey toward cloud-native infrastructure, security and automation aren’t just nice to have; they’re absolutely essential. Particularly in regulated industries like finance, government, and healthcare, there&#39;s a growing need to deploy Infrastructure as Code (IaC) within isolated (air-gapped) environments while also embracing zero-trust principles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In this blog, we’ll walk through how &lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.ibm.com/docs/schematics?topic=schematics-getting-started&amp;amp;interface=ui&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IBM Cloud Schematics&lt;/a&gt; can help you tackle these challenges head-on. We’ll explore how to securely provision IaC in isolated environments — while automating deployment and enforcing policy every step of the way. From air-gapped setups to zero trust enforcement, we’ve got you covered.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;随着现代企业继续朝着云本地基础架构，安全性和自动化的旅程不仅仅是很高兴；它们绝对是必不可少的。特别是在金融，政府和医疗保健等受管制行业中，越来越需要将基础设施作为代码（IAC）在孤立的（气动）环境中，同时也包含零信任原则。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;在此博客中，我们将介绍&lt;a a href =“ https：//cloud.ibm.com/docs/docs/schematics?topic = schematics-getting-start--getting＆getting＆interface = ui” 脑袋上。我们将探讨如何在孤立的环境中安全地提供IAC，同时在每个步骤中自动化部署和执行政策。从空防设置到零信托执行，我们已为您提供覆盖。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Doris Connects to Multiple Databases for Federated Analytics and Data Migration】多丽丝（Doris）如何连接到联合分析和数据迁移的多个数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/doris-jdbc-catalog-data-migration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Apache Doris is a high-performance real-time analytical database that supports multiple methods for connecting to external data sources. Among these, JDBC Catalog is a key feature that enables Doris to integrate with various mainstream databases, facilitating federated analysis and data migration.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article provides a detailed guide on how Doris connects to multiple databases via JDBC Catalog, lists the supported database types, and outlines the usage instructions to help users get started quickly. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Apache Doris是一个高性能的实时分析数据库，它支持多种连接到外部数据源的方法。其中，JDBC目录是一个关键功能，它使Doris能够与各种主流数据库集成，从而促进联合分析和数据迁移。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文提供了有关多丽丝如何通过JDBC目录连接到多个数据库的详细指南，列出了支持的数据库类型，并概述了用法说明以帮助用户快速启动。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Cost-Effective ELK Stack for Centralized Logging】建立一个具有成本效益的麋鹿堆栈，用于集中伐木</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/open-source-logging-with-elk-stack</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;27&#34; data-start=&#34;0&#34;&gt;If your company has budget constraints, purchasing licensed products like Splunk for logging infrastructure may not be feasible. Fortunately, a powerful open-source alternative exists: ELK (Elasticsearch, Logstash, and Kibana). ELK offers robust logging and visualization capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;27&#34; data-start=&#34;0&#34;&gt;At a startup where I worked, cost minimization was a priority, so I implemented ELK for logging.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 27” data-start =“ 0”&gt;如果您的公司有预算限制，则购买许可的产品（例如Splunk来伐木基础架构）可能是不可行的。幸运的是，存在强大的开源替代方案：Elk（Elasticsearch，Logstash和Kibana）。麋鹿提供了强大的记录和可视化功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 27” data-start =“ 0”&gt;在我工作的启动时，成本最小化是优先的，因此我实施了麋鹿的记录。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>