<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Testing DeepSeek-R1 Locally Using Ollama】使用Ollama在本地测试DeepSeek-R1</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/testing-deepseek-locally-using-ollama</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;DeepSeek-R1 has made a significant impact since its release. A number of cloud-based providers offer the ability to use DeepSeek-R1. It is also possible to use DeepSeek-R1 locally using Ollama. In this article, we&#39;ll test the smallest DeepSeek-R1 model, using Ollama, with a number of different tasks and evaluate its response.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The notebook file used in this article is available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/ollama-deepseek-demo/blob/main/ollama_deepseek_demo.ipynb&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; DeepSeek-R1自发布以来产生了重大影响。许多基于云的提供商提供了使用DeepSeek-R1的能力。也可以使用Ollama在本地使用DeepSeek-R1。在本文中，我们将使用Ollama进行许多不同的任务测试最小的DeepSeek-R1模型并评估其响应。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文中使用的笔记本文件可在&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/veryfatboy/ollama-deepseek-demo/blob/blob/main/main/main/main/olama_deepseek_demo.ipynb”中</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Safeguarding Sensitive Data: Content Detection Technologies in DLP】保护敏感数据：DLP中的内容检测技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/safeguarding-sensitive-data-content-detection-tech</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The 2024 IBM Cost of a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibm.com/reports/data-breach&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Data Breach Report&lt;/a&gt; found that data breaches cost organizations an average of $4.88 million per incident globally. Many of these breaches were caused by accidental or intentional mishandling of sensitive information. As businesses rely more on cloud collaboration tools, SaaS applications, and global data sharing, Data Loss Prevention (DLP) solutions have become essential to cybersecurity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Content detection technologies are the core of DLP tools. They identify and protect confidential data at rest, in motion, and in use. This article explores the key content detection technologies, their applications in various industries, and the best practices for effective deployment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.ibm.com/reports/reports/data-breach” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;数据违规报告&lt;/a&gt;数据破坏了全球范围4.8亿美元的组织成本。这些违规中的许多是由意外或故意对敏感信息的不当行为引起的。随着企业更多地依赖云协作工具，SaaS应用程序和全球数据共享，数据损失预防（DLP）解决方案已成为网络安全至关重要的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;内容检测技术是DLP工具的核心。他们在休息，运动和使用中识别并保护机密数据。本文探讨了关键内容检测技术，它们在各个行业中的应用以及有效部署的最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Predicting Ad Viewability With XGBoost Regressor Algorithm】使用XGBoost回归算法预测广告可视性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/predicting-ad-viewability-xgboost-regressor</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Extracting insights from data and leveraging them in decision-making processes is becoming increasingly prevalent. Today, this approach enables impactful actions across various domains, including digital advertising. In the world of digital advertising, interactions between users exposed to ads and the platforms displaying those ads hold critical importance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Matches between advertisers and publishers are facilitated by auctions conducted within milliseconds on demand-side platforms (DSPs) and supply-side platforms (SSPs). Accurate matching is vital for both user satisfaction and revenue management. One of the most important KPIs in this regard is the &lt;strong&gt;ad viewability rate&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;从数据中提取见解并在决策过程中利用它们的洞察力变得越来越普遍。如今，这种方法可以在包括数字广告在内的各个领域进行有影响力的动作。在数字广告的世界中，暴露于广告的用户与显示这些广告的平台之间的交互至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;广告客户与出版商之间的匹配是通过在需求端平台（DSP）和供应方平台（SSP）进行的拍卖来促进的。准确的匹配对于用户满意度和收入管理至关重要。在这方面，最重要的KPI之一是&lt;strong&gt; AD可见度率&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Generative AI in Agile: A Strategic Career Decision】敏捷的生成AI：战略职业决定</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-in-agile-a-strategic-career-decision</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR: A Harvard Study of Procter and Gamble Shows the Way&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recent research shows AI isn’t just another tool — it’s a “cybernetic teammate” that enhances agile work. A &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=5188231&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;The Cybernetic Teammate: A Field Experiment on Generative AI Reshaping Teamwork and Expertise&#34;&gt;Harvard Business School study of 776 professionals&lt;/a&gt; found individuals using AI matched the performance of human teams, broke down expertise silos, and experienced more positive emotions during work.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For agile practitioners, the choice isn’t between humans or AI but between being AI-augmented or falling behind those who are. The cost of experimentation is low; the potential career advantage, on the other side, is substantial. A reason to embrace generative AI in Agile?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt; tl; DR：哈佛对宝洁和赌博的研究显示了&lt;/h2&gt;的方式&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近的研究表明，AI不仅是另一种工具，而且是一种“控制论队友”，可以增强敏捷工作。 A &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=5188231&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;The Cyber​​netic Teammate: A Field Experiment on Generative AI Reshaping Teamwork and Expertise&#34;&gt;Harvard Business School study of 776 professionals&lt;/a&gt; found individuals using AI matched the performance of human团队，打破了专业知识孤岛，并在工作期间经历了更多积极的情绪。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于敏捷的从业者来说，选择不是人类或人工智能之间的选择，而是在被a-ai-aigment或落后于那些人之间。实验的成本很低；另一方面，潜在的职业优势是巨大的。在敏捷中拥抱生成AI的理由？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Testing AI Is the First Step to Using AI】测试AI是使用AI的第一步</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/testing-ai-is-the-first-step-to-using-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Sales and marketing professionals in high tech are being told — daily, loudly, and from every direction — that they should be using AI. And while it&#39;s absolutely true that AI has real potential to boost productivity and unlock new insights, there&#39;s a crucial first step that often gets skipped: testing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article is the result of testing AI with data from a large developer community with over 2,800 registered users, almost 800 unique organizations, and nine years of cumulative data from 41 countries. It&#39;s simply too much data for a marketing team to realistically try to analyze, too much information for working in a spreadsheet or a series of spreadsheets.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;高科技领域的销售和营销专业人员每天，大声和每个方向都被告知他们应该使用AI。尽管AI具有提高生产力并解锁新见解的真正潜力是绝对的确，但通常会跳过至关重要的第一步：测试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;本文是通过来自一个大型开发人员社区的数据测试AI的结果，该社区拥有超过2,800个注册用户，近800个独特的组织以及来自41个国家 /地区的9年累积数据。营销团队实际上试图分析的数据太多了，对于在电子表格或一系列电子表格中工作的信息太多。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build a New API Quickly Using Spring Boot and Maven】如何使用Spring Boot和Maven快速构建新的API</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-api-with-spring-boot-and-maven</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In my &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduce-new-api-spring-boot-gradle&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;last post&lt;/a&gt;, I wrote about how quick and easy it is to turn an idea into reality. I built a Spring Boot API service using Gradle as my build management tool and then deployed it to Heroku.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But what about my readers who have Maven in their toolchain?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在我的&lt;a a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduce-new-api-spring-boot-gradle-- boot-gradle” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;上一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;我写了如何快速而容易地将一个事实变成现实。我使用Gradle作为我的构建管理工具构建了Spring Boot API服务，然后将其部署到Heroku。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;但是我的读者在工具链中有毛刺呢？ &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 19:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Scalable Data Lake Using AWS】使用AWS构建可扩展数据湖</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-scalable-data-lake-using-aws</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Data lakes are centralized repositories that facilitate flexible and economical data management, and businesses are using them to store, process, and analyze this data effectively. AWS offers a strong ecosystem for creating a safe and scalable data lake with services like Lake Formation AWS Glue and Amazon S3.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Along with best practices for implementation, this article examines the essential elements of an AWS &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-lakes-all-you-need-to-know&#34;&gt;Data Lake architecture&lt;/a&gt;, including ingestion storage processing and analytics.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;数据湖是促进灵活和经济数据管理的集中存储库，并且企业正在使用它们来有效地存储，处理和分析这些数据。 AWS提供了一个强大的生态系统，用于创建一个安全可扩展的数据湖，并提供诸如Lake Formation AWS Glue和Amazon S3之类的服务。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;除了实施实施的最佳实践外，本文研究了AWS &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/data-lakes-lakes-alk-lakes-allakes-allakes-allakes-allakes-ally-you-need-to-know”&gt; data Lake架构</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding SQL Server Query Store: A Comprehensive Guide】了解SQL Server查询商店：综合指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-sql-server-query-store</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;SQL Server Query Store is an essential feature introduced in SQL Server 2016, designed to provide insights into query performance by storing a history of executed queries, query plans, and runtime statistics. Acting as a flight recorder for your database, Query Store simplifies performance troubleshooting and helps DBAs optimize database workloads efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will explore what Query Store is, its benefits, scenarios for its use, and steps to implement it with examples.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; SQL Server查询商店是SQL Server 2016中介绍的重要功能，旨在通过存储执行的查询，查询计划和运行时统计信息来提供有关查询性能的见解。查询商店充当数据库的飞行记录器，简化了性能故障排除，并帮助DBA有效地优化了数据库工作负载。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨哪些查询商店是什么，其好处，使用情况以及用示例实施的步骤。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cost-Aware Resilience: Implementing Chaos Engineering Without Breaking the Budget】成本感知的弹性：实施混乱工程而不打破预算</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/chaos-engineering-cost-awareness</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Modern distributed systems, like microservices and cloud-native architectures, are built to be scalable and reliable. However, their complexity can lead to unexpected failures. Chaos engineering is a useful way to test and improve system resilience by intentionally creating controlled failures. However, it can be costly due to resource usage, monitoring needs, and testing in production-like environments. This article explores ways to make chaos engineering more cost-effective while maintaining its quality and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding Chaos Engineering Costs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resource Utilization:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Running chaos experiments often requires extra resources, like more compute instances or virtual machines.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring Overheads&lt;/strong&gt;: Better monitoring is needed to track how the system behaves during experiments, which can increase costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Production-Like Environments&lt;/strong&gt;: Testing in environments similar to production can be expensive because of the high infrastructure costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Downtime Risks&lt;/strong&gt;: Inadequately planned experiments can cause unexpected outages.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Importance of Cost-Aware Chaos Engineering:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Cost-Aware chaos engineering makes sure testing resilience doesn&#39;t become too expensive. By using resources wisely and relying on existing tools, organizations can include chaos engineering in their work without going over budget or affecting their goals.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;现代分布式系统（如微服务和云本地体系结构）都是可扩展可靠的。但是，它们的复杂性可能导致意外的失败。混乱工程是一种有用的方法，可以通过有意创造受控故障来测试和提高系统弹性。但是，由于资源使用，监视需求和类似生产的环境的测试，这可能是昂贵的。本文探讨了使混乱工程在保持其质量和可靠性的同时更具成本效益的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;了解混乱工程成本&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;资源利用率：&lt;/strong&gt;运行混乱实验通常需要额外的资源，例如更多的计算实例或虚拟机。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li style =“ text-align：左;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;监视开销&lt;/strong&gt;：需要更好的监视以跟踪系统在实验过程中的行为，这可以增加成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;类似生产的环境&lt;/strong&gt;：在类似生产的环境中进行测试可能很昂贵，因为基础设施成本很高。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;停机风险&lt;/strong&gt;：计划不足的实验可能会导致意外的中断。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;成本感知混乱工程的重要性：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;成本吸引的混乱工程确保测试弹性不会变得太昂贵。通过明智地使用资源并依靠现有工具，组织可以在工作中包括混乱工程，而无需超越预算或影响其目标。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating a Web Project: Refactoring】创建网络项目：重构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-a-web-project-refactoring</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/creating-a-web-project-key-steps-to-identify-issue&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;the previous article&lt;/a&gt;, we spoke about hunting bugs. But a time will come when your hunters’ ‘trophy collection’ grows to a scary size. More and more ‘targets’ will be coming as if it were a zombie apocalypse. There will be red lamps flashing across your metrics dashboard. If (or rather when) that happens, it would mean it’s time for a bigger change than just routine debugging and streamlining your codebase. Today, I am going to talk you into refactoring, which is basically digging into and altering the very foundations of your project. Don’t take anything for granted, check everything yourself and think twice before diving into this work. It’s just as easy as swapping an engine in a flying airplane. But that’s exactly what you will have to do. Let’s get started!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Monsters Beneath the Surface&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the troubleshooting guide, I already mentioned how important it was to create and closely watch the metrics of your project. System metrics — like response time, memory consumption, etc. — and product metrics — like user acquisitions and engagement — are equally important (you watch and log your metrics, right?). It may happen that the problems you see with these instruments keep mounting up. Solving them consumes more and more time and resources, and you become short of both for growth and development. This is the worst symptom that your project needs refactoring. Ideally, you should be alert before skyfall gets at your doorstep. But for a lot of people, &#34;If it ain&#39;t broke, don&#39;t fix it&#34; is a motto for stability. Well, it doesn’t really work that way. You will actually save more if you start refactoring your project before real trouble hits you.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; in &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/creating-a-web-project-project-project-key-steps-teps-to-sideify-issue-sissue” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt;上一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;，我们说明了&lt;/a&gt;，我们说明了huningting bugs。但是，当您的猎人的“奖杯收藏”增长到可怕的大小时，将会到来的时间。越来越多的“目标”即将到来，好像是僵尸启示录。您的指标仪表板将有红灯闪烁。如果发生这种情况（或者是什么时候），那意味着现在该进行更大的变化了，而不仅仅是例行调试和简化您的代码库。今天，我将与您交谈进行重构，这基本上是在研究和改变您项目的基础。不要把任何事情都视为理所当然，请自己检查一切，然后三思而后行，然后再研究这项工作。这就像在飞机上换引擎一样容易。但这正是您要做的。让我们开始！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;表面下方的怪物&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在“故障排除指南”中，我已经提到了创建和密切关注项目指标的重要性。系统指标（例如响应时间，内存消耗等）以及产品指标（例如用户获取和参与度）同样重要（您观看和记录指标，对吗？）。您可能会遇到这些乐器的问题不断增加。解决它们会消耗越来越多的时间和资源，而您将不足以增长和发展。这是您项目需要重构的最严重症状。理想情况下，您应该在Skyfall驶入家门之前保持警惕。但是对于很多人来说，“如果没有破产，请不要修复它”是稳定的座右铭。好吧，它并没有这种方式。如果您在真正的麻烦袭来之前开始重构项目，则实际上将节省更多。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>