<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Storybook: A Developer’s Secret Weapon】故事书：开发人员的秘密武器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/storybook-a-developers-secret-weapon</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In my experience, Storybook has been a game-changer as a front-end developer who has mainly relied on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/jest-tutorial-for-selenium-javascript-testing-with&#34;&gt;Jest&lt;/a&gt;, Mocha, and Chai to get the basic testing working for the components I&#39;ve built — learning about Storybook has been an eye-opener. It&#39;s one of those tools that once you&#39;ve used you wonder how you managed without it. The ability to visualize components in isolation has streamlined our development process, making collaboration between devs and designers seamless.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;That said, I’ve seen some developers shy away from Storybook, citing the extra setup and maintenance as a downside. But here’s why I disagree: once you get past the initial integration, the time saved outweighs the setup cost in the long run. In this article, I would like to shed some light on the integration process and showcase some features that are most beneficial when using Storybook.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;根据我的经验，对于主要依赖 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/jest-tutorial-for 的前端开发人员来说，Storybook 已经改变了游戏规则-selenium-javascript-testing-with&#34;&gt;Jest&lt;/a&gt;、Mocha 和 Chai 对我构建的组件进行基本测试 - 了解 Storybook 让人大开眼界。它是一种工具，一旦您使用过，您就会想知道如果没有它，您将如何管理。独立可视化组件的能力简化了我们的开发流程，使开发人员和设计人员之间的协作变得无缝。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;也就是说，我看到一些开发人员回避 Storybook，认为额外的设置和维护是一个缺点。但我不同意的原因是：一旦完成了最初的集成，从长远来看，节省的时间超过了设置成本。在本文中，我想阐明集成过程并展示使用 Storybook 时最有用的一些功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using SingleStore and WebAssembly for Sentiment Analysis of Stack Overflow Comments】使用 SingleStore 和 WebAssembly 对 Stack Overflow 评论进行情感分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/singlestore-and-webassembly-for-sentiment-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll see how to use SingleStore and WebAssembly to perform sentiment analysis of Stack Overflow comments. We&#39;ll use some existing WebAssembly code that has already been prepared and hosted in a cloud environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The notebook file used in this article is available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/sentiment-analysis-demo&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将了解如何使用 SingleStore 和 WebAssembly 对 Stack Overflow 评论进行情感分析。我们将使用一些已在云环境中准备并托管的现有 WebAssembly 代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文中使用的笔记本文件可在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/sentiment-analysis-demo&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; 上找到。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Time Data Streaming on Cloud Platforms: Leveraging Cloud Features for Real-Time Insights】云平台上的实时数据流：利用云功能进行实时洞察</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-data-streaming-on-cloud-platforms</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-data-engineering-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Data Engineering: Enriching Data Pipelines, Expanding AI, and Expediting Analytics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Businesses today rely significantly on data to drive customer engagement, make well-informed decisions, and optimize operations in the fast-paced digital world. For this reason, real-time data and analytics are becoming increasingly more necessary as the volume of data continues to grow. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/real-time-data-architecture-patterns&#34;&gt;Real-time data&lt;/a&gt; enables businesses to respond instantly to changing market conditions, providing a competitive edge in various industries. Because of their robust infrastructure, scalability, and flexibility, cloud data platforms have become the best option for managing and analyzing real-time data streams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-data-engineering-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;数据工程：丰富数据管道，扩展数据管道人工智能和加速分析&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;当今的企业严重依赖数据来推动客户参与、做出明智的决策并在快节奏的数字世界中优化运营。因此，随着数据量的不断增长，实时数据和分析变得越来越必要。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/real-time-data-architecture-patterns&#34;&gt;实时数据&lt;/a&gt;使企业能够立即响应不断变化的市场状况，从而在各种领域提供竞争优势行业。由于其强大的基础设施、可扩展性和灵活性，云数据平台已成为管理和分析实时数据流的最佳选择。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Read JSON Files in Java Using the Google Gson Library】如何使用 Google Gson 库在 Java 中读取 JSON 文件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-read-json-files-in-java-using-google-gson-l</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;JSON files are commonly used these days for sending data to applications. Be it a web application, an API, or a mobile application, JSON is used by almost every team as it is lightweight and self-describing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Due to its high popularity and wide usage, it is important to understand and know what JSON is, its features, its different data types, file formats, etc. In this blog, we will be learning about JSON, its features, data types, and file formats. We will then continue to learn to read JSON files in Java using the Google Gson library.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;如今，JSON 文件通常用于向应用程序发送数据。无论是 Web 应用程序、API 还是移动应用程序，几乎每个团队都使用 JSON，因为它是轻量级且自描述的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;由于其高流行度和广泛使用，了解和了解 JSON 是什么、它的特性、它的不同数据类型、文件格式等非常重要。在本博客中，我们将了解 JSON 及其功能、数据类型和文件格式。然后我们将继续学习使用 Google Gson 库在 Java 中读取 JSON 文件。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Jakarta WebSocket Essentials: A Guide to Full-Duplex Communication in Java】Jakarta WebSocket Essentials：Java 全双工通信指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/jakarta-websocket-essentials</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Have you ever wondered what happens when you send a message to friends or family over the Internet? It’s not just magic — there’s a fascinating technology at work behind the scenes called &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-the-heck-are-websockets&#34;&gt;WebSocket&lt;/a&gt;. This powerful protocol enables real-time communication, allowing messages to flow seamlessly between users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Join us as we dive deeper into the world of WebSocket! We’ll explore how this technology operates and even create a simple application together to see it in action. Get ready to unlock the potential of real-time communication!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;您有没有想过当您通过互联网向朋友或家人发送消息时会发生什么？这不仅仅是魔法，还有一种令人着迷的技术在幕后工作，称为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-the-heck-are-websockets&#34;&gt;WebSocket&lt;/a&gt;。这种强大的协议支持实时通信，允许消息在用户之间无缝流动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;加入我们，深入探索 WebSocket 的世界！我们将探索这项技术的运作方式，甚至一起创建一个简单的应用程序来查看它的实际效果。准备好释放实时通信的潜力！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 22:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Licenses With Daily Time Fencing】每日时间围栏许可证</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/licenses-with-daily-time-fencing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Despite useful features offered by software, sometimes software pricing and packaging repel consumers and demotivate them to even take the first step of evaluation. Rarely, we have seen software/hardware used for the full 24 hours of a day but still, as a consumer, I am paying for the 24 hours of the day. At the same time, as a cloud software vendor, I know my customer is not using cloud applications for 24 hours but still, I am paying the infrastructure provider for 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the 23rd of July, 2024, we brainstormed about the problem and identified a solution. License with daily time fencing can help consumers by offering them a cheaper license and can also help ISV in infrastructure demand forecasting and implementing eco-design.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;尽管软件提供了有用的功能，但有时软件的定价和包装会令消费者望而却步，甚至阻碍他们迈出评估的第一步。我们很少看到软件/硬件全天 24 小时都在使用，但作为消费者，我仍然为全天 24 小时付费。同时，作为云软件供应商，我知道我的客户不是 24 小时使用云应用程序，但我仍然向基础设施提供商支付 24 小时费用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2024 年 7 月 23 日，我们针对该问题进行了集思广益并确定了解决方案。具有每日时间限制的许可证可以通过为消费者提供更便宜的许可证来帮助他们，还可以帮助 ISV 进行基础设施需求预测和实施生态设计。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) With Milvus】使用 Milvus 构建检索增强生成 (RAG)</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-rag-with-milvus</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;It&#39;s no secret that traditional &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;large language models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; often hallucinate — generate incorrect or nonsensical information — when asked knowledge-intensive questions requiring up-to-date information, business, or domain knowledge. This limitation is primarily because most LLMs are trained on publicly available information, not your organization&#39;s internal knowledge base or proprietary custom data. This is where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-generative-ai-with-retrieval-augmented&#34;&gt;retrieval-augmented generation (RAG)&lt;/a&gt;, a model introduced by&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2005.11401&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;Meta AI researchers&lt;/a&gt;, comes in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;RAG addresses an LLM&#39;s limitation of over-relying on pre-trained data for output generation by combining parametric memory with non-parametric memory through vector-based information retrieval techniques. Depending on the scale, this vector-based information retrieval technique often works with vector databases to enable fast, personalized, and accurate similarity searches. In this guide, you&#39;ll learn how to build a retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) with Milvus.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;传统的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/a 已不是什么秘密&gt; 当被问到需要最新信息、业务或领域知识的知识密集型问题时，经常产生幻觉——生成不正确或无意义的信息。这种限制主要是因为大多数法学硕士接受的是公开信息的培训，而不是您组织的内部知识库或专有的自定义数据。这就是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-generative-ai-with-retrieval-augmented&#34;&gt;检索增强生成(RAG)&lt;/a&gt;，这是&lt;a href引入的模型=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2005.11401&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;元人工智能研究人员&lt;/a&gt;进来了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;RAG 通过基于向量的信息检索技术将参数内存与非参数内存相结合，解决了法学硕士过度依赖预训练数据来生成输出的限制。根据规模的不同，这种基于矢量的信息检索技术通常与矢量数据库配合使用，以实现快速、个性化和准确的相似性搜索。在本指南中，您将学习如何使用 Milvus 构建检索增强生成 (RAG)。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Harnessing GenAI for Enhanced Agility and Efficiency During Planning Phase】利用 GenAI 增强规划阶段的敏捷性和效率</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/genai-for-enhanced-agility-and-efficiency</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Project planning is one of the first steps involved in any form of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-guide-to-project-management-life-cycle&#34;&gt;project management&lt;/a&gt;. In this &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-agile-methodology-dzone&#34;&gt;Agile&lt;/a&gt; era, whatever flavor of Agile it may be, programs and projects undergo a cadence for planning on the set-up of intentions for the next phase of delivering value to customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this generation of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;GenAI&lt;/a&gt;, there is an opportunity to catalyze productivity not just by reducing routine tasks through manual intervention, but also by providing key insights from analyzing the performance of previous delivery cycles and real-time progress tracking.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;项目规划是任何形式的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-guide-to-project-management-life- 涉及的首要步骤之一周期“项目管理”。在这个&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-agile-methodology-dzone&#34;&gt;敏捷&lt;/a&gt;时代，无论敏捷的风格是什么，程序和项目都会经历一种节奏：规划下一阶段为客户提供价值的意图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这一代&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;GenAI&lt;/a&gt;中，有机会提高生产力，而不仅仅是通过减少通过手动干预来执行日常任务，还可以通过分析先前交付周期的绩效和实时进度跟踪来提供关键见解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cost Optimization Strategies for Managing Large-Scale Open-Source Databases】管理大规模开源数据库的成本优化策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cost-optimization-large-scale-open-source-dbs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In today’s world where data drives everything, managing large-scale databases and their security is both a necessity and a challenge. A few factors that organizations consider when choosing databases are primary are its cost, flexibility, and support from hosting providers. An &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-trends-driving-open-source-database-pro&#34;&gt;open-source database&lt;/a&gt; is your best bet for many reasons. As organizations are looking for more and more open-source products to run their enterprise business, this gives them greater flexibility and cost-effectiveness. Achieving lower costs while maintaining high-performance databases is critical. Most organizations are now adopting open-source databases for some projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;There are multiple factors that one should consider when picking an open-source database. Below are some options that can be adapted to achieve effective management of large-scale open-source databases while keeping the costs in control.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在数据驱动一切的当今世界，管理大型数据库及其安全既是必要的，也是挑战。组织在选择数据库时考虑的几个主要因素是其成本、灵活性和托管提供商的支持。出于多种原因，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-trends-driven-open-source-database-pro&#34;&gt;开源数据库&lt;/a&gt;是您的最佳选择。随着组织正在寻找越来越多的开源产品来运行其企业业务，这为他们提供了更大的灵活性和成本效益。在维持高性能数据库的同时降低成本至关重要。大多数组织现在都在某些项目中采用开源数据库。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;选择开源数据库时应考虑多种因素。以下是一些可用于实现大规模开源数据库的有效管理，同时控制成本的选项。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 21:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging Apache Flink Dashboard for Real-Time Data Processing in AWS Apache Flink Managed Service】利用 Apache Flink 仪表板在 AWS Apache Flink 托管服务中进行实时数据处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/apache-flink-dashboard-for-real-time-data-processing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Apache Flink Managed Service in AWS, offered through Amazon Kinesis data analytics for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/apache-flink-101-a-guide-for-developers&#34;&gt;Apache Flink&lt;/a&gt;, allows developers to run Flink-based stream processing applications without the complexities of managing the underlying infrastructure. This fully managed service simplifies the deployment, scaling, and operation of real-time data processing pipelines, enabling users to concentrate on building applications rather than handling cluster setup and maintenance. With seamless integration into AWS services such as Kinesis and S3, it provides automatic scaling, monitoring, and fault tolerance, making it ideal for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-real-time-analytics&#34;&gt;real-time analytics&lt;/a&gt;, event-driven applications, and large-scale data processing in the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This guide talks about how to use the Apache Flink dashboard for monitoring and managing real-time data processing applications within AWS-managed services, ensuring efficient and reliable stream processing.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS 中的 Apache Flink 托管服务，通过 Amazon Kinesis 数据分析提供 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/apache-flink-101-a-guide-for-开发人员&#34;&gt;Apache Flink&lt;/a&gt;，允许开发人员运行基于 Flink 的流处理应用程序，而无需管理底层基础设施的复杂性。这种完全托管的服务简化了实时数据处理管道的部署、扩展和操作，使用户能够专注于构建应用程序，而不是处理集群设置和维护。通过与 Kinesis 和 S3 等 AWS 服务无缝集成，它提供自动扩展、监控和容错能力，使其成为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-real- time-analytics&#34;&gt;实时分析&lt;/a&gt;、事件驱动的应用程序以及云中的大规模数据处理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本指南介绍如何使用 Apache Flink 仪表板监控和管理 AWS 托管服务中的实时数据处理应用程序，确保高效可靠的流处理。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 14:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>