<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Quick Scrum Gains】快速 Scrum 收益</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/quick-scrum-gains</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Quick Scrum Gains&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Suppose you are a Scrum Master or Agile Coach. Have you recently been asked to explain your contribution to the organization’s value creation? In other words, does management want to know whether you are pulling your weight or if your salary is an expendable expenditure? This article points to ten quick Scrum gains you can pull off without asking for permission or budget to prove your contribution to your organization’s survival in these challenging times.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Ten Quick Scrum Gains You Can Start Tomorrow&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few years ago, when money was cheap, valuations high, and profits more than decent, no one questioned the necessity of a Scrum Master or Agile Coach.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR：快速 Scrum 收益&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设您是 Scrum Master 或敏捷教练。您最近是否被要求解释您对组织价值创造的贡献？换句话说，管理层是否想知道你是否尽职尽责，或者你的薪水是否属于消耗性支出？本文指出了十个无需请求许可或预算即可快速实现的 Scrum 收益，以证明您对组织在这个充满挑战的时代生存的贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;明天就可以开始的十个快速 Scrum 收获&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;几年前，当资金便宜、估值高、利润高的时候，没有人质疑 Scrum Master 或敏捷教练的必要性。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why You Should Use Buildpacks Over Docker】为什么你应该使用 Buildpack 而不是 Docker</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-you-should-use-buildpacks-over-docker</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docker.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; is the obvious choice for building containers, but there is a catch: writing optimized and secure Dockerfiles and managing a library of them at scale can be a real challenge. In this article, I will explain why you may want to use Cloud Native &lt;a href=&#34;https://buildpacks.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Buildpacks&lt;/a&gt; instead of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Common Issue Using Docker&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;When a company begins using Docker, it typically starts with a simple &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-dockerfile&#34;&gt;Dockerfile&lt;/a&gt;. However, as more projects require Dockerfiles, the following problematic situation often comes up:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docker.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a &gt; 是构建容器的明显选择，但有一个问题：编写优化且安全的 Dockerfile 并大规模管理它们的库可能是一个真正的挑战。在本文中，我将解释为什么您可能想要使用云原生 &lt;a href=&#34;https://buildpacks.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Buildpacks&lt;/a&gt; 而不是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker。&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;使用 Docker 的常见问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;当一家公司开始使用 Docker 时，通常会从一个简单的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-dockerfile&#34; 开始&gt;Dockerfile&lt;/a&gt;。然而，随着越来越多的项目需要Dockerfile，经常会出现以下问题：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【JMeter Plugin HTTP Simple Table Server (STS) In-Depth】JMeter 插件 HTTP 简单表服务器 (STS) 深入研究</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/jmeter-plugin-http-simple-table-server</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;The Need for the Creation of the STS Plugin&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;From a Web Application in Tomcat&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea of having a server to manage the dataset was born during the performance tests of the income tax declaration application of the French Ministry of Public Finance in 2012. The dataset consisted of millions of lines to simulate tens of thousands of people who filled out their income tax return form per hour and there were a dozen injectors to distribute the injection load of a performance shot. The dataset was consumed, that is to say, once the line with the person&#39;s information was read or consumed, we could no longer take the person&#39;s information again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The management of the dataset in a centralized way had been implemented with a Java web application (war) running in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-tomcat&#34;&gt;Tomcat&lt;/a&gt;. Injectors requesting a row of the dataset from the web application.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;创建STS插件的必要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;来自 Tomcat 中的 Web 应用程序&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用服务器来管理数据集的想法诞生于2012年法国财政部所得税申报应用程序的性能测试期间。该数据集由数百万行组成，可以模拟数万人的数据他们每小时填写一次所得税申报表，还有十几个注射器来分配表演镜头的注射量。数据集被消耗了，也就是说，一旦读取或消耗了包含该人信息的行，我们就无法再获取该人的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-tomcat&#34; 中运行的 Java Web 应用程序 (war) 实现数据集的集中管理&gt;雄猫&lt;/a&gt;。注入器从 Web 应用程序请求一行数据集。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Harnessing DevOps Potential: Why Backup Is a Missing Piece】发挥 DevOps 潜力：为何备份是缺失的一环</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/harnessing-devops-potential</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We often hear about the importance of developers and the role they play in the success of a business. After all, they are those craftsmen who create the software and apps that make businesses run smoothly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, there is one key element of development that is still overlooked – backup. Why? DevOps is constantly focused on delivering the best user experience and making sure the apps they build are bug-free. Yet what if something goes wrong one day or another? Let’s move on step-by-step.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们经常听说开发人员的重要性以及他们在企业成功中所扮演的角色。毕竟，他们是那些创造使企业顺利运营的软件和应用程序的工匠。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，开发的一个关键要素仍然被忽视——备份。为什么？ DevOps 始终致力于提供最佳的用户体验并确保他们构建的应用程序没有错误。但万一有一天出了问题怎么办？让我们一步一步地继续。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What Is &#34;Progressive Disclosure&#34; and How Does It Impact Developer Portals?】什么是“渐进式披露”以及它如何影响开发者门户？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-progressive-disclosure</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-hook=&#34;rcv-block3&#34; type=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Progressive disclosure is a UX design pattern that reduces cognitive load by gradually revealing more complex information or features as the user progresses through the UI of a digital product (such as a portal).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div data-breakout=&#34;normal&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Why Should Platform Engineers Care?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div data-hook=&#34;rcv-block6&#34; type=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;I&#39;ve encountered the term a few times, but its value really hit home in July during two panels I participated in. First, in the LeadDev panel &#34;&lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gMBDstc1P5g&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;How to implement platform engineering at scale&lt;/a&gt;,&#34; &lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/smrutirp/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Smruti Patel&lt;/a&gt; mentioned this. Then, in a panel that I hosted with &lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/abbybangser/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Abby Bangser&lt;/a&gt;, &#34;&lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://youtu.be/k87wukNGo70&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;When Terraform Met Backstage&lt;/a&gt;,&#34; our guest, &lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sevedkim/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Seve Kim&lt;/a&gt;, also mentioned progressive disclosure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-hook=&#34;rcv-block3&#34; type=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;渐进式披露是一种用户体验设计模式，当用户在数字产品（例如门户）的 UI 中进行操作时，它会逐渐显示更复杂的信息或功能，从而减少认知负荷。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div data-breakout=&#34;正常&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;为什么平台工程师应该关心？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div data-hook=&#34;rcv-block6&#34; type=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;我曾多次遇到过这个术语，但在 7 月份我参加的两次小组讨论中，它的价值才真正体现出来。首先，在 LeadDev 小组中“&lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href =&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gMBDstc1P5g&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;如何大规模实施平台工程&lt;/a&gt;,&#34; &lt;a data-hook=&#34; WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/smrutirp/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Smruti Patel&lt;/a&gt; 提到了这一点。然后，在我用 &lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/abbybangser/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Abby Bangser 主持的小组中&lt;/a&gt;, &#34;&lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://youtu.be/k87wukNGo70&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;当 Terraform 遇见后台&lt;/a&gt;,&#34;我们的客人，&lt;a data-hook=&#34;WebLink&#34; href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sevedkim/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Seve Kim&lt;/a&gt;，也提到渐进式披露。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building an LLM-Powered Product To Learn the AI Stack: Part 1】构建 LLM 支持的产品来学习 AI 堆栈：第 1 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-an-llm-powered-product-to-learn-the-ai-stack-pt1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Forget what you think you know about AI. It&#39;s not just for tech giants and universities with deep pockets and armies of engineers and grad students. &amp;nbsp;The power to build useful intelligent systems is within your reach. Thanks to incredible advancements in&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt; Large Language Models &lt;/a&gt;(LLMs) – like the ones powering Gemini and ChatGPT – you can create AI-driven products that used to require a team of engineers. In this series, we&#39;ll demystify the process of building LLM-powered applications, starting with a delicious use case: creating a personalized AI meal planner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Our Use Case&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As an example use case for our journey, we&#39;re going to be building a meal-planning app. There’s no shortage of meal plans available online, including those customized for different needs (varying goals, underlying health conditions, etc.). The problem is that it’s often difficult (sometimes impossible) to find guidance tailored specifically for you without hiring a health professional.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;忘记你认为自己对人工智能了解多少。这不仅仅适用于财力雄厚、工程师和研究生大军的科技巨头和大学。  构建有用的智能系统的能力触手可及。得益于&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;大型语言模型&lt;/a&gt;（LLM）取得的令人难以置信的进步 - 就像那些为 Gemini 和ChatGPT – 您可以创建过去需要工程师团队的人工智能驱动产品。在本系列中，我们将从一个美味的用例开始，揭秘构建由法学硕士支持的应用程序的过程：创建个性化的人工智能膳食计划。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我们的用例&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;作为我们旅程的一个示例用例，我们将构建一个膳食计划应用程序。网上不乏膳食计划，包括根据不同需求（不同的目标、潜在的健康状况等）定制的膳食计划。问题是，如果不聘请健康专业人士，通常很难（有时是不可能）找到专门为您量身定制的指导。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Handling Schema Versioning and Updates in Event Streaming Platforms Without Schema Registries】在没有架构注册表的情况下处理事件流平台中的架构版本控制和更新</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/handling-schema-versioning-and-updates</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In real life, change is constant. As businesses evolve, the technology systems supporting them must also evolve. In many &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-an-event-driven-architecture-using-kafka&#34;&gt;event-driven systems&lt;/a&gt; today, event streaming platforms like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/apache-kafka&#34;&gt;Kafka&lt;/a&gt;, Kinesis, and Event Hubs are crucial components facilitating communication between different technology systems and services. As these systems and services change, the schema of event streaming platform messages needs to be updated. The most common way to address this problem is by using schema registries like Confluent Schema Registry, AWS Glue Schema Registry, and Azure Schema Registry. However, in this article, I am going to discuss a simple solution that does not use any of these schema registries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Although I will use Kafka as an example in this article, this strategy can be applied to any other event streaming platform or messaging queue.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在现实生活中，变化是永恒的。随着业务的发展，支持业务的技术系统也必须不断发展。如今，在许多&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-an-event-driven-architecture-using-kafka&#34;&gt;事件驱动系统&lt;/a&gt;中，诸如&lt;a href= &#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/apache-kafka&#34;&gt;Kafka&lt;/a&gt;、Kinesis 和事件中心是促进不同技术系统和服务之间通信的关键组件。随着这些系统和服务的变化，事件流平台消息的架构需要更新。解决此问题的最常见方法是使用架构注册表，例如 Confluence Schema Registry、AWS Glue Schema Registry 和 Azure Schema Registry。不过，在本文中，我将讨论一个不使用任何这些架构注册表的简单解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然我将在本文中使用 Kafka 作为示例，但此策略可以应用于任何其他事件流平台或消息队列。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Not All MFA Is Equal: Lessons From MFA Bypass Attacks】并非所有 MFA 都是一样的：MFA 绕过攻击的教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/not-all-mfa-is-equal</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;One-time passwords are one of the most relied-on forms of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/role-based-multi-factor-authentication&#34;&gt;multi-factor authentication (MFA)&lt;/a&gt;. They’re also failing miserably at keeping simple attacks at bay. Any shared secret a user can unknowingly hand over is a target for cybercriminals, even short-lived &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-security-with-two-factor-authentication&#34;&gt;TOTPs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Consider this: What if the multi-factor authentication your users rely on couldn’t save your organization from a large-scale account takeover? That’s what happened to an organization using SMS one-time passwords to secure customer accounts. We’ll call the affected organization “Example Company,” or EC for short.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;一次性密码是最可靠的形式之一&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/role-based -multi-factor-authentication&#34;&gt;多重身份验证 (MFA)&lt;/a&gt;。他们在阻止简单攻击方面也惨遭失败。用户在不知情的情况下泄露的任何共享秘密都会成为网络犯罪分子的目标，甚至是短暂的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-security-with-two-factor-authentication&#34;&gt;TOTP&lt;/一个&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;考虑一下：如果您的用户所依赖的多重身份验证无法使您的组织免遭大规模帐户接管怎么办？这就是一个使用短信一次性密码来保护客户帐户的组织所发生的情况。我们将受影响的组织称为“示例公司”，简称 EC。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Oracle: Migrate PDB to Another Database】Oracle：将 PDB 迁移到另一个数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/oracle-migrate-pdb-to-another-database-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you want to migrate or relocate the PDB from one database to another, there are multiple options available in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/oracle-advanced-queue-a-guide&#34;&gt;Oracle&lt;/a&gt;. Here, we will discuss a few of them. The source and target database can be in a standalone database, RAC, cloud, or autonomous database. After verifying the PDB is on the target, open it for customer access and remove it from the source database based on company policy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;The target database version should same or higher than the source database.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;The source database should be accessible from the target.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;The degree of parallelism should be calculated properly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Aware of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reflections-from-a-dba&#34;&gt;DBA &lt;/a&gt;privileged username/password on the source to create DB link&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;The encryption key is different from the user password. Must have access to the encryption key - it may be either database or tablespace or table level&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;The user in the remote database that the database link connects to, must have the &lt;code&gt;CREATE PLUGGABLE DATABASE&lt;/code&gt; privilege.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;The character set on source and target should be compatible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Known Issues&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-check-oracle-database-tablespace&#34;&gt;Tablespace&lt;/a&gt; may be in a big file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Tablespace may be encrypted.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Using a database link, the target database should be able to access the source database. Create an Access Control List (ACL) or whitelist the IP address and port if required.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;To access the DB link, either enter the source database information in &lt;strong&gt;TNSnames.ora&lt;/strong&gt; or give a full connection string.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Stable network connectivity between source and target&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;RMAN jobs may interfere with refreshable cloning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Port from source to target should be opened to copy the files or to access the DB&amp;nbsp;link&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Remote CDB uses local undo mode. Otherwise, remote PDB may be opened in read-only mode.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Copy/cloning/synchronization between source and target may vary by network traffic and speed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few of the approaches are as follows:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您想要将 PDB 从一个数据库迁移或重新定位到另一个数据库，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/oracle-advanced-queue-a-guide&#34;&gt; 中提供了多个选项甲骨文&lt;/a&gt;。在这里，我们将讨论其中的一些。源数据库和目标数据库可以位于独立数据库、RAC、云或自治数据库中。验证 PDB 位于目标上后，将其打开以供客户访问，并根据公司策略将其从源数据库中删除。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;先决条件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;目标数据库版本应与源数据库相同或更高。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;源数据库应可从目标访问。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;要合理计算并行度。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;了解&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reflections-from-a-dba&#34;&gt;DBA&lt;/a&gt;源上用于创建数据库链接的特权用户名/密码&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;加密密钥与用户密码不同。必须有权访问加密密钥 - 它可以是数据库、表空间或表级别&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;数据库链接连接到的远程数据库中的用户必须具有&lt;code&gt;CREATE PLUGGABLE DATABASE&lt;/code&gt; 权限。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;源和目标上的字符集应兼容。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;已知问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-check-oracle-database-tablespace&#34;&gt;表空间&lt;/a&gt;可能位于一个大文件中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;表空间可能已加密。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;使用数据库链接，目标数据库应该能够访问源数据库。如果需要，创建访问控制列表 (ACL) 或将 IP 地址和端口列入白名单。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;要访问数据库链接，请在 &lt;strong&gt;TNSnames.ora&lt;/strong&gt; 中输入源数据库信息或提供完整的连接字符串。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;源与目标之间稳定的网络连接&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;RMAN 作业可能会干扰可刷新克隆。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;应打开从源到目标的端口以复制文件或访问数据库链接&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;远程CDB使用本地undo模式。否则，远程 PDB 可能会以只读模式打开。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;源和目标之间的复制/克隆/同步可能会因网络流量和速度而异。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一些方法如下：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Solve OutOfMemoryError: Java Heap Space】如何解决 OutOfMemoryError：Java 堆空间</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-solve-outofmemoryerror-java-heap-space</link>
      <description>【&lt;header&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;There are &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heaphero.io/types-of-outofmemoryerror/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;9 types of java.lang.OutOfMemoryError&lt;/a&gt;, each signaling a unique memory-related issue within Java applications. Among these, &lt;code&gt;java.lang.OutOfMemoryError: Java heap space&lt;/code&gt; stands out as one of the most prevalent and challenging errors developers encounter. In this post, we’ll delve into the root causes behind this error, explore potential solutions, and discuss effective diagnostic methods to troubleshoot this problem. Let’s equip ourselves with the knowledge and tools to conquer this common adversary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;JVM Memory Regions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To better understand &lt;code&gt;OutOfMemoryError&lt;/code&gt;, we first need to understand different JVM Memory regions (see &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P3gFfPIN3sw&amp;amp;t=1s&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;this video clip&lt;/a&gt; that gives a good introduction to different JVM memory regions). But in a nutshell, JVM has the following memory regions:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;标题&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;有&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.heaphero.io/types-of-outofmemoryerror/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;9种java.lang.OutOfMemoryError&lt;/a &gt;，每个信号都表明 Java 应用程序中存在一个独特的内存相关问题。其中，&lt;code&gt;java.lang.OutOfMemoryError: Java heap space&lt;/code&gt; 是开发人员遇到的最常见和最具挑战性的错误之一。在这篇文章中，我们将深入研究此错误背后的根本原因，探索潜在的解决方案，并讨论解决此问题的有效诊断方法。让我们用知识和工具武装自己来战胜这个共同的对手。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;JVM 内存区域&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了更好地理解 &lt;code&gt;OutOfMemoryError&lt;/code&gt;，我们首先需要了解不同的 JVM 内存区域（请参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P3gFfPIN3sw&amp;t=1s&#34; rel =&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;这个视频剪辑&lt;/a&gt;很好地介绍了不同的 JVM 内存区域）。但概括地说，JVM 有以下内存区域：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>