<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Data at Rest Encryption: Protecting Stored Data】静态数据加密：保护存储的数据</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-different-methods-of-data-at-rest-encryp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Securing sensitive information is more critical than ever. One of the key defenses in data protection is data at rest encryption, a method that safeguards information stored on devices such as hard drives, databases, and servers. Unlike data in transit, which is actively moving through networks, data at rest is idle, yet just as vulnerable to breaches. From personal devices to enterprise storage systems, encryption ensures that even if unauthorized access occurs, the data remains unreadable without the appropriate decryption keys.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;An alarming &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.varonis.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;53% of companies left more than 1,000&lt;/a&gt; sensitive files and folders unencrypted, accessible to all employees. This article explores the various methods of encrypting data at rest, helping you understand the strengths and limitations of each approach to better protect your stored information.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;保护敏感信息比以往任何时候都更加重要。数据保护的关键防御之一是静态数据加密，这是一种保护存储在硬盘驱动器、数据库和服务器等设备上的信息的方法。与在网络中主动移动的传输中的数据不同，静态数据是闲置的，但同样容易受到破坏。从个人设备到企业存储系统，加密可确保即使发生未经授权的访问，如果没有适当的解密密钥，数据仍然无法读取。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;令人震惊的&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.varonis.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;53% 的公司离开了 1,000 多家&lt;/a&gt;敏感文件和文件夹未加密，所有员工都可以访问。本文探讨了静态加密数据的各种方法，帮助您了解每种方法的优点和局限性，以更好地保护您存储的信息。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Oracle CloudWorld 2024: Key Takeaways for Developers, Engineers and Architects】Oracle CloudWorld 2024：开发人员、工程师和架构师的主要收获</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/oracle-cloudworld-key-takeaways</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Oracle CloudWorld 2024 showcased a range of innovations and strategic shifts that will significantly impact the work of developers, engineers, and architects across industries. From AI integrations to multi-cloud strategies, Oracle is positioning itself as a key enabler of digital transformation. Here are the most important takeaways for technical professionals:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;1. AI Integration Across the Stack&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence was undoubtedly the star of CloudWorld 2024, with Oracle emphasizing its integration throughout its product suite. For developers and engineers, this means having access to powerful AI capabilities without building them from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Oracle CloudWorld 2024 展示了一系列创新和战略转变，这些创新和战略转变将对各行业开发人员、工程师和架构师的工作产生重大影响。从人工智能集成到多云战略，甲骨文将自己定位为数字化转型的关键推动者。以下是技术专业人员最重要的要点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;1.跨堆栈的人工智能集成&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能无疑是 CloudWorld 2024 的明星，Oracle 强调其在整个产品套件中的集成。对于开发人员和工程师来说，这意味着无需从头开始构建即可获得强大的人工智能功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 14:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【VACUUM In Postgres Demystified】Postgres 中的 VACUUM 揭秘</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vacuum-in-postgres-demystified</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Let’s see what is VACUUM in PostgreSQL, how it’s useful, and how to improve your database performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Storage Basics&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before diving into vacuuming, it&#39;s important to first understand the fundamentals of data storage in PostgreSQL. While we’ll explain how data is represented internally, we won’t cover every aspect of storage, such as shared memory or buffer pools.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;让我们看看 PostgreSQL 中的 VACUUM 是什么、它有什么用处以及如何提高数据库性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;存储基础知识&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在深入研究清理之前，首先了解 PostgreSQL 中数据存储的基础知识非常重要。虽然我们将解释数据如何在内部表示，但我们不会涵盖存储的每个方面，例如共享内存或缓冲池。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Strategies for Enhanced Language Model Performance】增强语言模型性能的人工智能策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-the-potential-of-ai-in-enterprise-mobile</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) and language models are transforming various fields, including natural language processing, automated customer support, and data analysis. A critical challenge that these models face is the ability to perform compositional reasoning — an essential skill for understanding and combining different pieces of information to solve complex problems. This article explores the concept of compositionality, the challenges associated with it, and advanced strategies to improve language models&#39; ability to reason compositionally.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding Compositionality in AI&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Compositionality refers to the ability of AI models to combine simple concepts to form complex ideas or solutions. For instance, answering a question like &#34;Who was the U.S. President when the Eiffel Tower was completed?&#34; requires understanding separate facts and combining them to arrive at the answer. While language models have made significant progress in understanding individual facts, they often struggle with tasks that require them to combine these facts in a coherent manner.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能 (AI) 和语言模型正在改变各个领域，包括自然语言处理、自动化客户支持和数据分析。这些模型面临的一个关键挑战是执行组合推理的能力——这是理解和组合不同信息以解决复杂问题的基本技能。本文探讨了组合性的概念、与之相关的挑战以及提高语言模型组合推理能力的高级策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;理解人工智能中的组合性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;组合性是指人工智能模型将简单概念组合起来形成复杂想法或解决方案的能力。例如，回答“埃菲尔铁塔竣工时谁是美国总统？”之类的问题。需要理解不同的事实并将它们结合起来才能得出答案。虽然语言模型在理解单个事实方面取得了重大进展，但它们常常难以完成需要以连贯方式组合这些事实的任务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Vector Search: The Hottest Topic in Information Retrieval】矢量搜索：信息检索中最热门的话题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vector-search-hottest-topic-in-information-retrieval</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;My name is Bohdan Snisar. With 13 years in the software industry, I’ve transitioned from a software engineer to a software architect, gaining a deep understanding of the software development lifecycle and honing my problem-solving skills. My expertise spans Java, Go, Big Data pipelines, vector-based search, machine learning, relational databases, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-distributed-systems-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;distributed systems&lt;/a&gt;, with significant contributions at companies like Revolut and Wix.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;At Revolut, I played a pivotal role in developing infrastructure for Bloomberg integration, creating a transparent and traceable interface for trading terminals that became a vital data source. This experience highlighted the growing need for advanced data handling and retrieval techniques, leading me to explore the potential of vector search.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我叫博赫丹·斯尼萨尔。在软件行业工作了 13 年，我已经从软件工程师转变为软件架构师，对软件开发生命周期有了深入的了解，并磨练了解决问题的能力。我的专业知识涵盖 Java、Go、大数据管道、基于向量的搜索、机器学习、关系数据库和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-distributed-systems-a-beginners-guide&#34; &gt;分布式系统&lt;/a&gt;，在 Revolut 和 Wix 等公司做出了重大贡献。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在 Revolut，我在开发 Bloomberg 集成基础设施、为成为重要数据源的交易终端创建透明且可追踪的界面方面发挥了关键作用。这次经历凸显了对高级数据处理和检索技术日益增长的需求，促使我探索矢量搜索的潜力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Domain-Driven Design: Manage Data With Jakarta Data and JNoSQL】领域驱动设计：使用 Jakarta Data 和 JNoSQL 管理数据</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-domain-driven-design-with-jakarta-data-a</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Managing data access in Domain-Driven Design (DDD) applications can be challenging, especially when working with different database types, like relational and NoSQL. This article explores how leveraging tools like JNoSQL and Jakarta Data helps simplify data access, making it easier to implement domain-focused repositories, integrate ubiquitous language, and naturally align business semantics with your code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-line-end=&#34;5&#34; data-line-start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Understanding DDD vs. DAO&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before diving into the practical implementation details, it&#39;s essential to clarify the distinction between Domain-Driven Design (DDD) and the Data Access Object (DAO) pattern. Understanding this difference will help recognize the value of domain-focused repositories in DDD applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;管理领域驱动设计 (DDD) 应用程序中的数据访问可能具有挑战性，尤其是在使用不同的数据库类型（例如关系数据库和 NoSQL）时。本文探讨了如何利用 JNoSQL 和 Jakarta Data 等工具帮助简化数据访问，从而更轻松地实现以领域为中心的存储库、集成通用语言以及自然地将业务语义与代码保持一致。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-line-end=&#34;5&#34; data-line-start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;了解 DDD 与 DAO&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在深入研究实际实现细节之前，有必要澄清域驱动设计 (DDD) 和数据访问对象 (DAO) 模式之间的区别。了解这种差异将有助于认识 DDD 应用程序中以领域为中心的存储库的价值。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Acting Like We Care About Security】表现得像我们关心安全一样</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/acting-like-we-care-about-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This will be my last entry on the topic for a while. For context, I introduced the idea that folks don’t care about security, they care about outcomes &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/nobody-cares-about-security&#34;&gt;in this post&lt;/a&gt;; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/starting-to-care-about-security&#34;&gt;then I began exploring ways&lt;/a&gt; we, as IT practitioners, can shift the focus to the results and therefore contextualize the actions needed as something other than “security for the sake of security.” In this post, I’m continuing with that line of discussion. What can we DO to make our environments more secure, and how can we get our colleagues to understand and want to do it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Focus on Actual Risks and Realistic Outcomes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(or: Don’t let “perfect” be the enemy of “good”)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这将是我一段时间内关于该主题的最后一篇文章。作为背景，我在这篇文章中介绍了这样一个想法：人们并不关心安全，他们关心的是结果&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/nobody-cares-about-security&#34;&gt;&lt;/a &gt;; &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/starting-to-care-about-security&#34;&gt;然后我开始探索&lt;/a&gt;我们作为 IT 从业者可以将重点转移到结果和因此，将所需的行动视为“为了安全而安全”之外的其他事情。在这篇文章中，我将继续这一讨论。我们可以做些什么来使我们的环境更加安全，我们如何才能让我们的同事理解并愿意这样做？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;关注实际风险和现实结果&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;（或者：不要让“完美”成为“良好”的敌人）&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transforming Customer Feedback With Automation of Summaries and Labels Using TAG and RAG】使用 TAG 和 RAG 实现摘要和标签自动化，从而转变客户反馈</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-customer-feedback-with-tag-and-rag</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today’s data-driven landscape, businesses encounter a vast influx of customer feedback through reviews, surveys, and social media interactions. While this information can yield invaluable insights, it also presents a significant challenge: how to distill meaningful data from an overwhelming amount of information. Advanced analytics techniques are revolutionizing our approach to understanding customer sentiment. Among the most innovative are Table-Augmented Generation (TAG) and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-generative-ai-with-retrieval-augmented&#34;&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)&lt;/a&gt;, which enable businesses to derive complex insights from thousands of reviews simultaneously using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-translation-the-power-of-context-in-n-1&#34;&gt;natural language processing &lt;/a&gt;(NLP).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article delves into the workings of TAG and RAG, their implications for data labeling and Text-to-SQL generation, and their practical applications in real-world scenarios. By providing concrete examples, we illustrate how these technologies can enhance data analysis and facilitate informed decision-making, catering to both seasoned data scientists and newcomers to the field.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今数据驱动的环境中，企业通过评论、调查和社交媒体互动收到大量客户反馈。虽然这些信息可以产生宝贵的见解，但它也提出了一个重大挑战：如何从大量信息中提取有意义的数据。先进的分析技术正在彻底改变我们理解客户情绪的方法。其中最具创新性的是表增强生成 (TAG) 和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-generative-ai-with-retrieval-augmented&#34;&gt;检索增强生成 (RAG)&lt;/ a&gt;，使企业能够使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-translation-the-power-of-context-in-n-1&#34;&gt; 同时从数千条评论中获得复杂的见解自然语言处理（NLP）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文深入探讨了 TAG 和 RAG 的工作原理、它们对数据标记和文本到 SQL 生成的影响，以及它们在现实场景中的实际应用。通过提供具体示例，我们说明这些技术如何增强数据分析并促进明智的决策，从而满足经验丰富的数据科学家和该领域的新手的需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Date-Time APIs: Challenges With Java&#39;s Calendar and JDK Date/Time APIs】掌握日期/时间 API：Java 日历和 JDK 日期/时间 API 的挑战</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-date-time-apis-challenges-with-javas</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll address four problems covering different date-time topics. These problems are mainly focused on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/finding-a-time-to-meet-via-the-google-calendar-api&#34;&gt;Calendar API&lt;/a&gt; and on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/deeper-look-java-8-date-and&#34;&gt;JDK Date/Time API&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: This article is an abstract from my recent book&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://packt.link/wpywI&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Java Coding Problems, Second Edition&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将解决涉及不同日期时间主题的四个问题。这些问题主要集中在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/finding-a-time-to-meet-via-the-google-calendar-api&#34;&gt;Calendar API&lt;/a&gt; 和在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/deeper-look-java-8-date-and&#34;&gt;JDK 日期/时间 API&lt;/a&gt; 上。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;免责声明：本文是我最近出版的一本书的摘要&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://packt.link/wpywI&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt; &gt;Java 编码问题，第二版&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 21:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Simplify Complex Conditions With Python&#39;s Match Statement】如何使用 Python 的 Match 语句简化复杂条件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/simplify-complex-conditions-python-match-statement</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Pattern matching is a programming technique that involves comparing a value against a pattern and extracting information from the value if it matches the pattern. Instead of writing lengthy code, conditional checks, pattern matching enables a concise and readable way to identify the value matching the pattern. While pattern matching is rooted in functional programming, it can be used both functional and non-functional styles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Benefits of pattern matching include:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;模式匹配是一种编程技术，涉及将值与模式进行比较，如果值与模式匹配，则从值中提取信息。模式匹配无需编写冗长的代码，而是通过条件检查，以简洁且可读的方式来识别与模式匹配的值。虽然模式匹配植根于函数式编程，但它可以用于函数式和非函数式风格。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;模式匹配的好处包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 19:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>