<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling in Practice: Caching and Rate-Limiting With Redis and Next.js】在实践中扩展：用redis和next.js缓存和限制速率</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/caching-rate-limiting-redis-nextjs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As someone who loves shipping products and tools for people to experiment with and use, it was only a matter of time before scalability issues caught up with me. I always knew what scaling meant and how to scale in theory. I was familiar with vertical and horizontal scaling, and the intricacies of each, but again, in theory. I had actually never needed to implement any of them, as my user base was usually modest.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is until I built a faucet that exceeded my expectations in terms of usage. But this massive traction came with its own set of issues. The TL;DR of the issue was that even though I restricted the frequency with which a wallet address could claim funds to once a day, a user could simply spin up new addresses and keep claiming. This resulted in my faucet being drained frequently.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为一个喜欢运输产品和工具供人们实验和使用的工具的人，这只是时间问题，直到可伸缩性问题吸引了我。我一直都知道缩放的含义以及如何在理论上扩展。我熟悉垂直和水平缩放以及每个缩放的复杂性，但从理论上讲。我实际上永远不需要实施其中的任何一个，因为我的用户群通常是适度的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是直到我建立了一个超出我的使用期望的水龙头。但是，这种巨大的牵引力带来了自己的一系列问题。问题的TL; DR是，即使我限制了钱包地址每天要求资金一次的频率，但用户可以简单地旋转新的地址并继续索赔。这导致我的水龙头经常被排干。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scalability 101: How to Build, Measure, and Improve It】可伸缩性101：如何构建，测量和改进它</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-measure-improve-scalability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this post, I&#39;d like to talk a little about scalability from a system design perspective. In the following paragraphs, I&#39;ll cover multiple concepts related to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-for-success-why-scalability-is-the-forefro&#34;&gt;scalability&lt;/a&gt;—from defining what it is, to the tools and approaches that help make the system more scalable, and finally, to the signs that show whether a system is scaling well or not.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-what-is-scalability-&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is Scalability?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First things first: I’m pretty sure you know what scalability is, but let’s have a brief look at the definition just to be safe.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我想从系统设计的角度谈论可扩展性。在以下段落中，我将介绍与&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-for-success-why-scalobility-isscalibality-is-the-forro”&gt;可伸缩性&lt;/a&gt;的多个概念。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“  - 什么 -  s量表 - ”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是可扩展性？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第一件事首先：我敢肯定您知道什么是可扩展性，但是让我们简要介绍一下以安全的定义。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java&#39;s Quiet Revolution: Thriving in the Serverless Kubernetes Era】爪哇的安静革命：在无服务的Kubernetes时代蓬勃发展</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/javas-quiet-revolution-thriving-in-the-serverless</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Along with the rise of Kubernetes, there is another shift that is happening under the hood - the rise of serverless architecture, which is quietly rewriting the way we deploy and scale applications, with Java taking a lead. Java, which is usually associated with legacy code and monolithic enterprise applications, has been slowly but steadily evolving into a microservices architecture and is now evolving into a leaner, serverless-ready world.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the availability of tools like Knative and frameworks like Quarkus, Java has been transforming from a heavyweight language into a zero-management, Kubernetes-ready ready. In this article, we will reflect on this promising transformation in Java and where it can take us in 2025 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着Kubernetes的兴起，引擎盖下正在发生另一种变化 - 无服务器体系结构的兴起，该架构正在悄悄地重写我们部署和扩展应用程序的方式，Java率先。 Java通常与旧版代码和整体企业应用程序相关联，它一直在缓慢但稳步发展为微服务体系结构，现在已经演变成一个更精简，无服务器就绪的世界。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用knative和Quarkus等工具的可用性，Java已从重量级语言转变为零管理的kubernetes准备就绪。在本文中，我们将思考Java的这种有希望的转型，并在2025年及以后带我们。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Clean Up Event Data in Ansible Event-Driven Automation】清理Ansible事件驱动的自动化中的事件数据</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ansible-eda-clean-up-event-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the past few articles, we explored how to use different event sources in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/simulating-events-in-ansible-eda&#34;&gt;Ansible Event-Driven Automation (EDA)&lt;/a&gt;. In this demo, we&#39;ll focus on how event filters can help clean up and simplify event data, making automation easier to manage. Specifically, we&#39;ll explore the&lt;code&gt;&amp;nbsp;ansible.eda.dashes_to_underscores&lt;/code&gt; event filter and how it works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When using Ansible EDA with tools like webhooks, Prometheus, or cloud services, events often come in as JSON data. These JSON payloads usually have keys with dashes in their names, like alert-name or instance-id. While this is fine in JSON, it becomes a problem in Ansible because variable names with dashes can&#39;t be used directly in playbooks or Jinja2 templates. The &lt;code&gt;dashes_to_underscores&lt;/code&gt; filter helps solve this issue by converting those dashed keys into names that &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/monitoring-journald-logs-with-ansible-eda&#34;&gt;Ansible&lt;/a&gt; can work with more easily.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在过去的几篇文章中，我们探索了如何在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/simulating-events-in--ansible-eeda”中使用不同的事件源。在此演示中，我们将重点介绍事件过滤器如何帮助清理和简化事件数据，从而使自动化更易于管理。具体来说，我们将探索&lt;code&gt; ansible.eda.dashes_to_underscores &lt;/code&gt;事件过滤器及其工作方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在使用Webhooks，Prometheus或Cloud Services等工具使用Ansible EDA时，事件通常会作为JSON数据。这些JSON有效载荷通常具有名称中带有破折号的键，例如Alert-Name或Instance-ID。尽管在JSON中这很好，但它在Ansible中成为一个问题，因为带有破折号的变量名称不能直接在Playbooks或Jinja2模板中使用。 &lt;code&gt; dashes_to_underscores &lt;/code&gt;过滤器通过将那些虚线的键转换为&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/monitoring-journald-logs-with-ansible-sible-ible--ansible--asible-eeda”&gt; Ansible &lt;/a&gt;可以更轻松地使用的名称来帮助解决此问题。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 1: Introduction and Power BI Authoring Overview】Power BI嵌入式分析 - 第1部分：简介和Power BI创作概述</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-power-bi-authoring-overview</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: This is a multi-part series exploring Power BI Embedded Analytics. The other parts of the series are listed below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-part-11-powerbi-authori&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Part 1.1: Power BI Authoring Data Federation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-2-powerbi-a&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Part 2: Power BI Embedded Overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-3-powerbi-e&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Part 3: Power BI Embedded Demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Analytics&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Analytics is all about making sense of data — finding patterns, uncovering insights, and using that information to make smarter decisions. It involves various techniques and tools to interpret data, create visualisations, and simplify complex information. Whether it’s businesses optimizing operations or researchers making discoveries, analytics is crucial in improving efficiency, productivity, and competitiveness.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;：这是一个探索功率BI嵌入分析的多部分系列。该系列的其他部分如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-part-11-powerbi-authori” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt;第1.1部分：第1.1部分&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-part-part-part-2-powerbi-a” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” noopener noreferrer“ target =” _ black&#39;&gt;第2部分&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-part-3-powerbi-e”&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Analytics &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Analytics就是要理解数据 - 查找模式，发现见解以及使用这些信息来做出更明智的决策。它涉及各种技术和工具来解释数据，创建可视化并简化复杂信息。无论是企业优化运营还是研究人员发现，分析对于提高效率，生产力和竞争力至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Role of Functional Programming in Modern Software Development】功能编程在现代软件开发中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/role-of-functional-programming</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Functional programming is one approach used in modern software development due to technological advancements. It enables developers to write code that is clean, efficient, and easy to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In addition, programming methods that are focused on pure functions, immutability, and declarative style make it easy for developers to create applications. This article analyzes the major principles of functional programming and their importance in modern software development.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;功能编程是由于技术进步而在现代软件开发中使用的一种方法。它使开发人员能够编写干净，高效且易于维护的代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;此外，专注于纯函数，不变性和声明风格的编程方法使开发人员可以轻松创建应用程序。本文分析了功能编程的主要原则及其在现代软件开发中的重要性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Analyzing “java.lang.OutOfMemoryError: Failed to create a thread” Error】分析“ java.lang.outofmemoryerror：无法创建线程”错误</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-outofmemoryerror-failed-to-create-thread</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding the Error &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OutOfMemoryError thrown appears not because of insufficient heap memory but due to the following reasons:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excessive Thread Creation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the application creates too many threads, it may reach a limit where no more threads can be created. In such cases, it is crucial to investigate the stack trace thrown with the error and reduce the number of thread creations at the application code level.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;了解错误&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;抛出的OutofMemoryError似乎不是因为堆内存不足，而是由于以下原因：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3&gt; &lt;strong&gt;过多的线程创建&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果应用程序创建太多线程，则可能达到无法创建线程的限制。在这种情况下，至关重要的是要研究错误的堆栈跟踪并减少应用程序代码级别的线程创建数量。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build the Right Infrastructure for AI in Your Private Cloud】如何在私有云中为AI建立正确的基础架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-right-infrastructure-ai-private-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;853&#34; data-start=&#34;540&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;569&#34; data-start=&#34;540&#34;&gt;AI is no longer optional&lt;/strong&gt;. From fraud detection to predictive maintenance, businesses everywhere are investing in machine learning and deep learning models. But training and running these models isn&#39;t light work. They require high-performance hardware, massive storage, fast networking, and serious automation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1102&#34; data-start=&#34;855&#34;&gt;Public clouds like AWS and Azure offer AI-ready infrastructure, but not every company wants to go that route. Whether it&#39;s for compliance, cost control, or pure performance, many teams are building AI stacks in their &lt;strong data-end=&#34;1088&#34; data-start=&#34;1071&#34;&gt;private cloud&lt;/strong&gt; environments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 853” data-start =“ 540”&gt; &lt;strong data-end =“ 569” data-start =“ 540”&gt; ai不再是可选的&lt;/strong&gt;。从欺诈检测到预测性维护，各地的企业都投资于机器学习和深度学习模型。但是培训和运行这些模型不是轻便的工作。他们需要高性能的硬件，大量存储，快速的网络和严重的自动化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1102” data-start =“ 855”&gt;像AWS和Azure这样的公共云提供AI-Ready基础架构，但并不是每个公司都想走这条路。无论是为了合规，成本控制还是纯表现，许多团队都在其&lt;strong data-end =“ 1088” data-start =“ 1071”&gt;私有云&lt;/strong&gt;环境中构建AI堆栈。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thermometer Continuation in Scala】Scala中的温度计延续</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/thermometer-continuation-in-scala</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A continuation represents the control state of computation at a given point during evaluation. &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Delimited_continuation&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Delimited Continuations&lt;/a&gt; is a programming mechanism that can be used to implement various control flow constructs. Thermometer continuations implement delimited continuation using exceptions and state, particularly focused on saving and resuming interactive or concurrent computations at specific points; they often require additional context or constructs to be fully realized.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In a 2018 paper, “&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1710.10385&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Capturing the Future by Replaying the Past&lt;/a&gt;,” Koppel et al. showed that in any language with exception and state, thermometer continuations can be used. This allows most of the languages to implement thermometer continuations. Koppel provided Java, OCaml and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jkoppel/thermometer-continuations&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SML reference implementations&lt;/a&gt; as part of the paper; Python implementation is available &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/calwoo/delimited&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, where the author devised a way to overcome &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/modern-python-patterns-features-and-strategies&#34;&gt;python generator&lt;/a&gt;’s inability to run the continuation multiple times.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; a延续表示评估过程中给定点处的计算状态。 &lt;a href =“ https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/delimited_continuation” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;界定延续&lt;/a&gt;是一种可以用于实施各种控制流动流的程序机制。温度计延续使用例外和状态实施界定延续，特别是在特定点上节省和恢复交互式或并发计算；他们通常需要完全实现其他上下文或构造。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在2018年论文中，“ &lt;a href =” https://arxiv.org/pdf/1710.10385“ rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;通过重播过去的&lt;/a&gt; koppel等来捕捉未来。表明在任何语言中，都可以使用温度计连续。这允许大多数语言实施温度计连续性。 Koppel提供了Java，Ocaml和&lt;a Href =“ https://github.com/jkoppel/thermmeter-continuations” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; sml参考实现&lt;/a&gt;作为论文的一部分； Python实现可用&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/calwoo/delimited” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;在这里&lt;/a&gt;，作者在其中设计了一种克服&lt;a的方法href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/modern-python-patterns-features-and-strategies”&gt; Python Generator &lt;/a&gt;无法多次运行延续。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SQL Server Index Optimization Strategies: Best Practices with Ola Hallengren’s Scripts】SQL Server索引优化策略：Ola Hallengren脚本的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sql-server-index-optimization-ola-hallengren</link>
      <description>【&lt;div dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div data-radix-scroll-area-viewport=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;main&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;article data-message-id=&#34;693de536-8613-4a1e-a6e6-ae8513aa2eb7&#34;&gt;&#xA;     &lt;p&gt;Index maintenance is a critical component of database administration as it helps ensure the ongoing efficiency and performance of a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-sql-server-query-store&#34;&gt;Structured Query Language (SQL) Server&lt;/a&gt; environment. Over time, as data is added, updated, and deleted, index fragmentation can occur, where the logical and physical ordering of index pages becomes misaligned. This fragmentation can lead to increased disk I/O, decreased query performance, and overall system inefficiency. Running index maintenance jobs, such as those provided by the Ola Hallengren SQL Server Maintenance Solution, allows DBAs to proactively address this fragmentation and optimize the indexes for better performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/article&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/main&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By regularly monitoring index fragmentation levels and executing maintenance operations like index reorganizations and rebuilds, DBAs can keep their databases running at peak efficiency. This is especially important for large, mission-critical databases, where any degradation in performance can have a significant business impact. Maintaining optimal index health helps ensure fast, reliable data access, reduced resource consumption, and an overall improvement in the user experience. Consequently, implementing a well-designed index maintenance strategy is a crucial responsibility for any DBA managing a complex &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sql-server-from-zero-to-advanced-level&#34;&gt;SQL Server&lt;/a&gt; environment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div dir =“ ltr”&gt;&#xA; &lt;div div data-radix-scroll-area-viewport =“”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;ain&gt;&#xA;   &lt;div tabindex =“ 0”&gt;&#xA;    &lt;文章data-message-id =“ 693DE536-8613-4A1E-A6E6E6-AE8513AA2EB7”&gt;&#xA;     &lt;p&gt;索引维护是数据库管理的关键组成部分，因为它有助于确保a &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-sql-server-query-store”&gt;结构化查询语言（sql）服务器的持续效率和性能。随着时间的流逝，随着数据的添加，更新和删除，可能会发生索引碎片，其中索引页的逻辑和物理排序被错误对准。这种分裂会导致磁盘I/O增加，查询性能降低以及整体系统效率低下。运行索引维护作业，例如Ola Hallengren SQL Server维护解决方案提供的索引维护作业，允许DBA主动解决此片段并优化索引以获得更好的性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/agets&gt;&#xA;   &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/main&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过定期监视索引碎片水平并执行索引重组和重建等维护操作，DBA可以使其数据库保持在峰值效率上。这对于大型，关键任务数据库尤其重要，在这种数据库中，任何绩效的退化都可能产生重大业务影响。保持最佳指数健康有助于确保快速，可靠的数据访问，减少资源消耗以及用户体验的总体改进。因此，实施精心设计的索引维护策略对于管理复杂的任何DBA是至关重要的责任，管理复杂的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/sql-server-server-server-from-zerer-zere-to-advanced-levanc--levanc--level-level-sql Server”&gt; sql Server&gt; sql Server &lt;/a&gt;环境。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>