<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【10 Best Practices for Managing Kubernetes at Scale】大规模管理Kubernetes的10种最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-managing-kubernetes-at-scale</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;As organizations use microservices and cloud-native architectures, Kubernetes is becoming the norm for container orchestration. As much as Kubernetes simplifies deploying and managing containers, workloads at scale make life complex, and robust practices are necessary.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;In this article, I will cover technical strategies and best practices for workload management at scale in Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;作为组织使用微服务和云本地体系结构，Kubernetes已成为容器编排的规范。尽管Kubernetes简化了部署和管理容器，但大规模的工作量使生活变得复杂，并且必须进行健全的实践。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;在本文中，我将涵盖Kubernetes大规模工作负载管理的技术策略和最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Ransomware Attacks】AI驱动的勒索软件攻击</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-ransomware-attacks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The improvement of artificial brainpower (artificial intelligence) has improved many fields, including digital protection. Notwithstanding, this mechanical improvement is a two-sided deal. While computerized reasoning brings many advantages, it also empowers cybercriminals to send off progressively complex and disastrous assaults.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most upsetting viewpoints is using AI in ransomware assaults. These AI-controlled assaults are robotized at different levels and find unpretentious procedures to make them greener, more complex, and more impressive. Most importantly, the danger scene quickly develops, creating more difficulties for people and associations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;改善人造脑力（人工智能）已改善了许多领域，包括数字保护。尽管如此，这种机械改进是双面交易。尽管计算机推理带来了许多优势，但它也使网络犯罪分子逐渐发出逐渐复杂和灾难性的攻击。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最令人沮丧的观点之一是在勒索软件攻击中使用AI。这些AI控制的攻击在不同层面上被机器人进行了机器人，并找到了朴实的程序，使它们更加绿色，更复杂，更令人印象深刻。最重要的是，危险场景迅速发展，给人们和协会带来了更多困难。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Banking Fraud Prevention With DeepSeek AI and AI Explainability】DeepSeek AI和AI的解释性预防银行欺诈性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/banking-fraud-prevention-deepseek-ai-ai-explainability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Fraud detection in banking has significantly advanced with artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML). However, a persistent challenge is the explainability of fraud decisions — how do we justify why a particular transaction was flagged as fraudulent?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores how DeepSeek AI enhances fraud prevention through:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在人工智能（AI）和机器学习（ML）中，银行业中的欺诈检测已大大提高。但是，持续的挑战是欺诈决定的解释性 - 我们如何证明为什么特定交易被标记为欺诈性？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了DeepSeek AI如何通过以下方式增强欺诈预防：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Annotating Data at Scale in Real Time】实时对数据进行大规模注释</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/annotating-data-at-scale-in-real-time</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As enterprises deal with large datasets, the demand for high-quality annotations has increased exponentially. Annotating data at a petabyte scale and in real time introduces unique challenges that require creative solutions. This article discusses the architecture for real-time annotation pipelines, leveraging LLMs, feedback loops, and active learning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Challenges in Scaling Data Annotation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Volume&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Petabyte-scale datasets often involve millions of entries spanning diverse modalities, including text, images, and videos. Efficiently handling this scale requires:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;当企业处理大型数据集时，对高质量注释的需求呈指数增长。以PB量表和实时进行注释数据引入了需要创造性解决方案的独特挑战。本文讨论了实时注释管道，利用LLM，反馈循环和主动学习的体系结构。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;缩放数据注释&lt;/h2&gt;的挑战&#xA;&lt;h3 dir =“ ltr”&gt;音量&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Petabyte尺度数据集通常涉及数百万个条目，这些条目包括文本，图像和视频。有效处理此量表需要：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Step-by-Step Guide to Write a System Design Document】编写系统设计文档的分步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-write-a-system-design-document</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Have you ever wondered how large-scale systems handle millions of requests seamlessly while ensuring speed, reliability, and scalability? Behind every high-performing application — whether it’s a search engine, an e-commerce platform, or a real-time messaging service — lies a well-thought-out system design. Without it, applications would struggle with bottlenecks, downtimes, and an overall poor user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-system-design-a-comprehensive-guide-to-s&#34;&gt;System design&lt;/a&gt; is more than just structuring components; it&#39;s about anticipating future needs, balancing trade-offs, and building a solution that can scale gracefully under heavy loads. In this blog, we’ll explore a structured approach to system design using a proven template that can help engineers, architects, and teams craft efficient, high-performing systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;您是否曾经想过如何无缝处理数百万个请求，同时确保速度，可靠性和可伸缩性？在每个高性能的应用程序（无论是搜索引擎，电子商务平台还是实时消息服务）的背后都是经过深思熟虑的系统设计。没有它，应用程序将在瓶颈，下降和整体用户体验中困难。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-system-design-a-comprehens-guide-to-s-guide-to-s”&gt;系统设计&lt;/a&gt;不仅仅是构建组件；这是关于预期未来需求，平衡权衡取舍，并建立一个可以在重负荷下优雅扩展的解决方案。在此博客中，我们将使用经过验证的模板探索一种结构化的系统设计方法，该模板可以帮助工程师，建筑师和团队制定高效，高性能的系统。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Scale Elasticsearch to Solve Your Scalability Issues】如何扩展Elasticsearch解决您的可伸缩性问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-scale-elasticsearch-to-solve-scalability-issues</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the evolution of modern applications serving increasing needs for real-time data processing and retrieval, scalability does, too. One such open-source, distributed search and analytics engine is Elasticsearch, which is very efficient at handling data in large sets and high-velocity queries. However, the process for effectively scaling Elasticsearch can be nuanced, since one needs a proper understanding of the architecture behind it and of performance tradeoffs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;While Elasticsearch’s distributed nature lets it scale horizontally, that also introduces more complexities in how data is spread and queries served. One of the theoretical challenges associated with scaling Elasticsearch is its inherently distributed nature. In most practical scenarios, reads on a standalone node will always outperform reads in a sharded cluster. This is because, in a sharded cluster, data ownership is spread across multiple nodes. That means every query may have to shoot multiple requests to different nodes, aggregate the results back at the coordinating node, and return the result. This extra network overhead will easily result in increased latency compared to a single-node architecture where data access is straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;随着现代应用的演变，可以满足实时数据处理和检索需求的增长，可伸缩性也是如此。 Elasticsearch是一种这样的开源，分布式搜索和分析引擎，它在处理大型集和高速查询的数据方面非常有效。但是，有效扩展Elasticsearch的过程可能会细微，因为人们需要正确理解其背后的体系结构和性能折衷。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;虽然Elasticsearch的分布式性质可以水平扩展，但它也引入了更复杂的数据传播和查询。与扩展弹性搜索相关的理论挑战之一是它的本质分布性质。在大多数实用的情况下，独立节点上的读取总是以碎片群的读取。这是因为，在碎片集群中，数据所有权分布在多个节点之间。这意味着每个查询可能都必须向不同的节点发送多个请求，将结果汇总在协调节点上，然后返回结果。与数据访问直接的单个节点体系结构相比，此额外的网络开销很容易增加延迟。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Platform-Agnostic Approach in Cloud Security】云安全性中的平台无知方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/platform-agnostic-approach-in-cloud-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Companies are now turning to data as one of the most important assets in their businesses, and data engineers are in the midst of managing and improving this asset and its effectiveness. In addition, the integration of data engineering with the use of cloud computing offers scalability, accessibility, and reduced expenses. However, there are security challenges that come with this integration that need to be solved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is essential to know the rates and causes of cloud security incidents in order to identify the vulnerabilities of the cloud systems. The cost of security incidents in businesses has shockingly&lt;a href=&#34;https://engage.checkpoint.com/2024-cloud-security-report?ref=hackernoon.com&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer ugc&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://engage.checkpoint.com/2024-cloud-security-report?ref=hackernoon.com&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer ugc&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;increased to 61% in 2024&lt;/a&gt; from the previous year’s 24%.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;公司现在正在将数据作为其业务中最重要的资产之一，数据工程师正在管理和改善该资产及其有效性。此外，使用云计算的数据工程集成提供可伸缩性，可访问性和降低的费用。但是，这种集成需要解决的安全挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;必须了解云安全事件的速率和原因，以确定云系统的漏洞。企业中安全事件的成本令人震惊地令人震惊地&lt;a href =“ https://engage.checkpoint.com/2024-cloud-security-report?ref=hackernoon.com” rel =“ noopener noreferrer ugc ugc” href =“ https://engage.checkpoint.com/2024-cloud-security-report?ref=hackernoon.com” rel =“ noopener noreferrer ugc” target =“ _ blank”&gt;上一年的24％。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Professor Rating Assistant With RAG and Pinecone】AI驱动的教授评级助理抹布和Pinecone</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-an-ai-powered-professor-rating-assistant</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence is transforming how people interact with information, and retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) is at the forefront of this innovation. RAG enhances large language models by enabling access to external knowledge bases, providing highly accurate and context-aware answers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, I’ll guide you through building an AI-powered assistant using RAG to create a smarter, more informed system for rating professors. Using tools like Next.js, React, Pinecone, and OpenAI’s API, this project is designed to be approachable for all, whether you’re just starting or already have experience in AI.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能正在改变人们与信息互动的方式，而检索演出的一代（RAG）处于这项创新的最前沿。 RAG通过允许访问外部知识库，提供高度准确和上下文感知的答案来增强大型语言模型。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本教程中，我将指导您建立一个使用AI的助手使用抹布来创建一个更智能，更明智的评级教授系统。使用Next.js，React，Pinecone和OpenAI的API之类的工具，该项目旨在为所有人而言，无论您只是刚开始还是已经在AI中都有经验。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Identity and Access Management Solution to Safeguard LLMs】确保LLMS的身份和访问管理解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llm-security-and-principles-of-identity-and-access</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the era of artificial intelligence, the use of large language models (LLMs) is increasing rapidly. These models offer amazing opportunities but also introduce new privacy and security challenges. One of the essential security measures to address these challenges involves securing access to the LLMs so that only authorized individuals have access to data and permissions to perform any action. This can be achieved using identity and access management (IAM).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-iam-basics-identity-and-access-management&#34;&gt;Identity and access management&lt;/a&gt; act as a security guard for critical data and systems. This approach operates just like a physical security guard who controls who can enter a building and who has access to security camera footage. When entering a building, security guards can ask for your identity, where you live, etc. They can also keep an eye on your activity around or inside the building if they see something suspicious. Similarly, identity and access management ensure that only authorized individuals can enter and access large language models. IAM also keeps a log of user activities to identify suspicious behavior.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在人工智能时代，大型语言模型（LLM）的使用正在迅速增加。这些模型提供了惊人的机会，但也引入了新的隐私和安全挑战。应对这些挑战的基本安全措施之一是确保访问LLMS，以便只有授权的个人才能访问数据和权限以执行任何行动。这可以使用身份和访问管理（IAM）来实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/aws-iam-basics-indistity-andisity-and-access-management”&gt;身份和访问管理&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;充当关键数据和系统的保安。这种方法就像一个身体保安人员一样运行，他控制谁可以进入建筑物并可以访问安全摄像机镜头。进入建筑物时，保安人员可以要求您的身份，您的住所等。同样，身份和访问管理确保只有授权的个人才能输入和访问大型语言模型。 IAM还保留用户活动的日志以识别可疑行为。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PostgreSQL 12 End of Life: What to Know and How to Prepare】Postgresql 12生命的结束：知道什么以及如何准备</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-12-end-of-life-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL-compatible edition major version 12.x and Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL 12 reach the end of standard support on February 28, 2025. Higher database versions introduce new features, enhancing operational efficiency and cost-effectiveness.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Identifying qualified databases and upgrading them promptly is crucial. As the end of standard support is approaching, it&#39;s crucial for database administrators and developers to understand the implications and plan for the future. This article discusses PostgreSQL 12&#39;s end-of-standard support for Aurora and RDS PostgreSQL 12, Amazon RDS extended support, upgrade options, and the benefits of moving to PostgreSQL 16.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Amazon Aurora Postgresql兼容版本的专业版本12.x和Amazon RDS for Postgresql 12在2025年2月28日达到标准支持的结束。高等数据库版本引入了新功能，提高操作效率和成本效益。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;识别合格的数据库并及时升级它们至关重要。随着标准支持的终结即将到来，对于数据库管理员和开发人员来说，了解未来的含义和计划至关重要。本文讨论了PostgreSQL 12对Aurora和RDS PostgreSQL 12，Amazon RDS扩展支持，升级选项以及迁移到PostgreSQL 16的好处。&lt;/p&gt;的好处。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>