<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Point-In-Time Recovery (PITR) in PostgreSQL】PostgreSQL 中的时间点恢复 (PITR)</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/point-in-time-recovery-pitr-in-postgresql</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Point-in-time recovery (PITR) is a robust feature in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/essential-postgresql&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt; that has become even more efficient and user-friendly with the advent of PostgreSQL. It enables administrators to restore a PostgreSQL database to a specific moment in the past. This is particularly useful if you manage disaster recovery for a large-scale system with a large transaction load.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This blog will explore PITR and equip you with knowledge about potential pitfalls and their solutions, ensuring a smooth and successful implementation. We&#39;ll also share its key benefits and detail a step-by-step implementation of PostgreSQL.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;时间点恢复 (PITR) 是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/essential-postgresql&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt; 中的一项强大功能，现已成为随着 PostgreSQL 的出现，它变得更加高效和用户友好。它使管理员能够将 PostgreSQL 数据库恢复到过去的特定时刻。如果您管理具有大量事务负载的大型系统的灾难恢复，这尤其有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本博客将探讨 PITR 并为您提供有关潜在陷阱及其解决方案的知识，确保顺利成功实施。我们还将分享其主要优势并详细介绍 PostgreSQL 的逐步实施。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java 21 Features: A Detailed Look at the Most Important Changes in the New LTS Release】Java 21 功能：详细了解新 LTS 版本中最重要的变化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-21-features-a-detailed-look</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Since the Java platform adopted a six-month release cycle, we&#39;ve moved past the perennial questions such as &#34;Will Java die this year?&#34; or &#34;Is it worth migrating to the new version?&#34;. Despite 28 years since its first release, Java continues to thrive and remains a popular choice as the primary programming language for many new projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java 17 was a significant milestone, but Java 21 has now taken 17’s place as the next long-term support release (LTS). It&#39;s essential for Java developers to stay informed about the changes and new features this version brings. Inspired by my colleague Darek, who detailed &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretius.com/blog/java-17-features/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Java 17 features&lt;/a&gt; in his article, I&#39;ve decided to discuss JDK 21 in a similar fashion (I&#39;ve also analyzed &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretius.com/blog/java-23-features/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Java 23 features&lt;/a&gt; in a follow-up piece, so check it out too).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;自从 Java 平台采用了六个月的发布周期以来，我们已经摆脱了诸如“Java 今年会消亡吗？”之类的长期问题。或“是否值得迁移到新版本？”。尽管自首次发布以来已有 28 年，Java 仍在蓬勃发展，并且仍然是许多新项目的主要编程语言的流行选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java 17 是一个重要的里程碑，但 Java 21 现已取代 17 成为下一个长期支持版本 (LTS)。 Java 开发人员必须随时了解此版本带来的更改和新功能。受到我的同事 Darek 的启发，他在他的文章中详细介绍了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretius.com/blog/java-17-features/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Java 17 功能&lt;/a&gt;文章中，我决定以类似的方式讨论 JDK 21（我还分析了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretius.com/blog/java-23-features/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Java 23 功能&lt;/a&gt; 在后续文章中，所以也请查看）。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Tic Tac Toe Game Using React】使用 React 构建 Tic Tac Toe 游戏</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-tic-tac-toe-game-using-react</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my version of the classic &lt;strong&gt;Tic Tac Toe&lt;/strong&gt; game! I created a Tic Tac Toe game using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/reactjs-essentials&#34;&gt;React&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-of-scss&#34;&gt;SCSS&lt;/a&gt;, completing it in around 6 hours. The game features single-player mode against the computer, a winner announcement popup, and win counters for both players. While the grid is customizable to &lt;code&gt;n x n&lt;/code&gt;, the current winning logic supports only &lt;code&gt;3 x 3&lt;/code&gt;. Future improvements include smarter computer moves and real-time multiplayer functionality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total development time needed:&lt;/strong&gt; ~6 hours&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technologies used:&lt;/strong&gt; JavaScript (React) + SCSS&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Game Rules&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Objective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The goal of the game is to align three of your symbols (X or O) in a horizontal, vertical, or diagonal row on a &lt;code&gt;3 x 3&lt;/code&gt; grid.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;欢迎来到我的经典&lt;strong&gt;井字棋&lt;/strong&gt;游戏版本！我使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/reactjs-essentials&#34;&gt;React&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction 创建了一个 Tic Tac Toe 游戏-of-scss&#34;&gt;SCSS&lt;/a&gt;，大约 6 小时内完成。该游戏具有与计算机对抗的单人游戏模式、获胜者公告弹出窗口以及双方玩家的获胜计数器。虽然网格可自定义为 &lt;code&gt;n x n&lt;/code&gt;，但当前获胜逻辑仅支持 &lt;code&gt;3 x 3&lt;/code&gt;。未来的改进包括更智能的计算机移动和实时多人游戏功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;所需总开发时间：&lt;/strong&gt; ~6 小时&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用的技术：&lt;/strong&gt; JavaScript (React) + SCSS&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;游戏规则&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1。目标&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;游戏的目标是将三个符号（X 或 O）排列在 &lt;code&gt;3 x 3&lt;/code&gt; 网格上的水平、垂直或对角行中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Art of Prompt Engineering in Incident Response】事件响应中的快速工程艺术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-art-of-prompt-engineering-in-incident-response</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the rapidly evolving field of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/surviving-the-incident&#34;&gt;Incident Response (IR),&lt;/a&gt; prompt engineering has become an essential skill that leverages AI to streamline processes, enhance response times, and provide deeper insights into threats. By creating precise and targeted prompts, IR teams can effectively utilize AI to triage alerts, assess threats, and even simulate incident scenarios, bringing significant value to cybersecurity operations. This article explores the foundations, benefits, and best practices for mastering prompt engineering in Incident Response, shedding light on how this practice is reshaping the field.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is Prompt Engineering in Incident Response?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Prompt engineering in the context of IR is the art and science of crafting highly specific, structured instructions for AI systems to guide them through various stages of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-primer-on-the-history-and-evolution-of-incident&#34;&gt;incident management&lt;/a&gt;, from detection and assessment to remediation and post-incident analysis. Unlike conventional IR processes that rely on human input alone, prompt engineering allows IR teams to harness AI’s analytical power to accelerate workflows and provide more data-driven responses to threats.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在快速发展的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/surviving-the-incident&#34;&gt;事件响应 (IR) 领域&lt;/a&gt;，快速工程已成为这是一项利用人工智能简化流程、缩短响应时间并提供对威胁更深入洞察的基本技能。通过创建精确且有针对性的提示，IR 团队可以有效地利用人工智能来分类警报、评估威胁，甚至模拟事件场景，为网络安全运营带来巨大价值。本文探讨了掌握事件响应中的即时工程的基础、好处和最佳实践，阐明了这种实践如何重塑该领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是事件响应中的即时工程？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;IR 背景下的即时工程是一门艺术和科学，为人工智能系统制定高度具体的结构化指令，以指导它们完成&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ articles/a-primer-on-the-history-and-evolution-of-incident&#34;&gt;事件管理&lt;/a&gt;，从检测和评估到补救和事件后分析。与仅依赖于人工输入的传统 IR 流程不同，即时工程允许 IR 团队利用 AI 的分析能力来加速工作流程并提供更多数据驱动的威胁响应。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Motivations for Creating Filter and Merge Plugins for Apache JMeter With Use Cases】使用案例为 Apache JMeter 创建过滤器和合并插件的动机</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-filter-and-merge-plugins-jmeter</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Use Cases for Filters&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Results Filter Plugin&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The standard &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-jmeter&#34;&gt;JMeter&lt;/a&gt; tool does not have a filter on the overall performance load test results.&lt;br&gt;&#xA; Filters exist for some standard graphs and also when generating the HTML report, but it lacks a powerful global results filter tool.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is often necessary to filter results to show only the pages and not all the URLs that make up the page. There are also &#34;debug&#34; or &#34;JSR223 Groovy&#34; samplers for intermediate calculations that are not pages and which are interesting to filter.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;过滤器的用例&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;结果过滤器插件&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;标准的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-jmeter&#34;&gt;JMeter&lt;/a&gt;工具没有对整体性能负载测试结果的过滤器。 &lt;br&gt;&#xA; 一些标准图表以及生成 HTML 报告时都存在过滤器，但它缺乏强大的全局结果过滤工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通常需要过滤结果以仅显示页面而不是组成页面的所有 URL。还有用于中间计算的“调试”或“JSR223 Groovy”采样器，这些采样器不是页面，并且有利于过滤。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Natural Language Processing (NLP) for Voice-Controlled Frontend Applications: Architectures, Advancements, and Future Direction】用于语音控制前端应用的自然语言处理 (NLP)：架构、进步和未来方向</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/natural-language-processing-nlp-for-voice-controll</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Voice-controlled frontend applications have gained immense traction due to the rising popularity of smart devices, virtual assistants, and hands-free interfaces. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-translation-the-power-of-context-in-n-1&#34;&gt;Natural Language Processing (NLP)&lt;/a&gt; lies at the heart of these systems, enabling human-like understanding and generation of speech. This white paper presents an in-depth examination of NLP methodologies for voice-controlled frontend applications, reviewing the state-of-the-art in speech recognition, natural language understanding, and generation techniques, as well as their architectural integration into modern web frontends. It also discusses relevant use cases, technical challenges, ethical considerations, and emerging directions such as multimodal interaction and zero-shot learning. By synthesizing recent research, best practices, and open challenges, this paper aims to guide developers, researchers, and industry professionals in leveraging NLP for inclusive, responsive, and efficient voice-controlled frontend applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The shift from traditional graphical interfaces to more natural, intuitive methods of human-computer interaction has accelerated over the past decade. Voice-controlled frontend applications — encompassing virtual assistants, voice-enabled search, and smart home interfaces — are at the forefront of this transformation. These applications promise hands-free, eyes-free interaction, dramatically expanding accessibility for users with disabilities and delivering more streamlined user experiences in scenarios where visual attention is limited (e.g., driving, cooking).&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;由于智能设备、虚拟助手和免提界面的日益普及，语音控制的前端应用程序获得了巨大的吸引力。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-translation-the-power-of-context-in-n-1&#34;&gt;自然语言处理 (NLP)&lt;/a&gt; 是这些技术的核心系统，能够实现类似人类的理解和语音生成。本白皮书深入研究了语音控制前端应用程序的 NLP 方法，回顾了语音识别、自然语言理解和生成技术的最新技术，以及它们与现代 Web 前端的架构集成。它还讨论了相关用例、技术挑战、道德考虑以及多模式交互和零样本学习等新兴方向。通过综合最新研究、最佳实践和开放挑战，本文旨在指导开发人员、研究人员和行业专业人士利用 NLP 实现包容性、响应式和高效的语音控制前端应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去十年，从传统图形界面向更自然、直观的人机交互方法的转变加速了。语音控制的前端应用程序（包括虚拟助手、语音搜索和智能家居界面）处于这一转型的最前沿。这些应用程序承诺免提、免眼交互，极大地扩展了残障用户的可访问性，并在视觉注意力有限的场景（例如驾驶、烹饪）中提供更简化的用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thoughts On the Software Crisis】对软件危机的思考</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/thoughts-on-the-software-crisis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you’re an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-stay-happy-and-relevant-as-a-java-developer&#34;&gt;experienced developer&lt;/a&gt; or a seasoned computer user, you might recall a time when having 128MB of RAM was considered a luxury. For those who don’t know, are too young, or started using computers more recently, let me put this into perspective: the original Max Payne video game required just 128MB of RAM, as did GTA: Vice City. This meant that a computer needed only this amount of memory to run the game alongside all other programs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But that’s not the point. The point is that these games were, and still are, considered significant milestones in gaming. Yes, their graphics are now dated. Yes, they don’t offer the same level of immersion or the rich gameplay mechanics found in modern titles. However, from an algorithmic perspective, they are not fundamentally different from modern games like Assassin’s Creed or Red Dead Redemption.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您是一位&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-stay-happy-and-relevant-as-a-java-developer&#34;&gt;经验丰富的开发人员&lt;/a&gt;或者是一位经验丰富的计算机用户，您可能还记得曾经拥有 128MB RAM 被认为是一种奢侈。对于那些不知道、太年轻或最近才开始使用电脑的人，让我来客观地阐述一下：最初的《马克思佩恩》视频游戏只需要 128MB RAM，《GTA：罪恶都市》也是如此。这意味着计算机只需要这个量的内存就可以与所有其他程序一起运行游戏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但这不是重点。重点是，这些游戏曾经并且仍然被认为是游戏领域的重要里程碑。是的，他们的图形现在已经过时了。是的，它们无法提供现代游戏中相同水平的沉浸感或丰富的游戏机制。然而，从算法的角度来看，它们与《刺客信条》或《荒野大镖客》等现代游戏并没有本质上的不同。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【RAG From a Beginner to Advanced: Introduction [Video]】RAG 从初级到高级：简介 [视频]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rag-from-a-beginner-to-advance-introduction</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In this blog post, we’ll explore:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Problems with traditional LLMs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;What is Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;How RAG works&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Real-world implementations of RAG&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Problems With Traditional LLMs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While LLMS have revolutionized the way we interact with technology, they come with some significant limitations:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;在这篇博文中，我们将探讨：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;传统法学硕士的问题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;什么是检索增强生成 (RAG)？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;RAG 的工作原理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;RAG 的实际实现&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;传统法学硕士的问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 LLMS 彻底改变了我们与技术交互的方式，但它们也存在一些重大局限性：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Privacy and Security: A Developer&#39;s Guide to Handling Sensitive Data With DuckDB】数据隐私和安全：使用 DuckDB 处理敏感数据的开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-handling-sensitive-data-with-duckdb</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Understanding DuckDB for Data Privacy and Security&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-privacy-and-security&#34;&gt;Data privacy and security&lt;/a&gt; have become critical for all organizations across the globe. Organizations often need to identify, mask, or remove sensitive information from their datasets while maintaining data utility. This article explores how to leverage DuckDB, an in-process analytical database, for efficient sensitive data remediation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why DuckDB? (And Why Should You Care?)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Think of DuckDB as &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-sqlite-database-works&#34;&gt;SQLite&lt;/a&gt;&#39;s analytically gifted cousin. It&#39;s an embedded database that runs right in your process, but it&#39;s specifically designed for handling analytical workloads. What makes it perfect for data remediation? Well, imagine being able to process large datasets with lightning speed, without setting up a complicated database server. Sounds good, right?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;了解 DuckDB 的数据隐私和安全性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-privacy-and-security&#34;&gt;数据隐私和安全&lt;/a&gt;对于全球所有组织都至关重要。组织通常需要从数据集中识别、屏蔽或删除敏感信息，同时保持数据实用性。本文探讨了如何利用 DuckDB（一种进程内分析数据库）来进行高效的敏感数据修复。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么选择 DuckDB？ （你为什么要关心？）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将 DuckDB 视为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-sqlite-database-works&#34;&gt;SQLite&lt;/a&gt; 具有分析天赋的表弟。它是一个直接在您的流程中运行的嵌入式数据库，但它是专门为处理分析工作负载而设计的。是什么使它非常适合数据修复？好吧，想象一下能够以闪电般的速度处理大型数据集，而无需设置复杂的数据库服务器。听起来不错，对吧？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Root Causes of Out of Memory (OOM) Issues in Java Containers】了解 Java 容器中内存不足 (OOM) 问题的根本原因</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/root-causes-of-OOM-issues-in-Java-containers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Out-of-memory errors in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/java-containerization&#34;&gt;containerized Java applications&lt;/a&gt; can be very frustrating, especially when happening in a production environment. These errors can happen for various reasons. Understanding the Java Memory Pool model and different types of OOM errors can significantly help us in identifying and resolving them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Java Memory Pool Model&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Java Heap&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-out-of-memory-heap-analysis&#34;&gt;Java heap&lt;/a&gt; is the region where memory is allocated by JVM for storing Objects and dynamic data at runtime. It is divided into specific areas for efficient memory management (Young Gen, Old Gen, etc.). Reclamation of memory is managed by the Java GC process.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/java-containerization&#34;&gt;容器化 Java 应用程序&lt;/a&gt;中的内存不足错误可能非常严重令人沮丧，尤其是在生产环境中发生时。发生这些错误的原因有多种。了解Java内存池模型和不同类型的OOM错误可以极大地帮助我们识别和解决它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Java内存池模型&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Java 堆&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;目的&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-out-of-memory-heap-analysis&#34;&gt;Java 堆&lt;/a&gt; 是区域其中内存由 JVM 分配，用于在运行时存储对象和动态数据。它被划分为特定的区域以进​​行高效的内存管理（Young Gen、Old Gen 等）。内存回收由Java GC 进程管理。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>