<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【From Zero to Scale With AWS Serverless】从零到AWS无服务器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/from-zero-to-scale-with-aws-serverless</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In recent years, cloud-native applications have become the go-to standard for many businesses to build scalable applications. Among the many advancements in cloud technologies, serverless architectures stand out as a transformative approach. Ease-of-use and efficiency are the two most desirable properties for modern application development, and serverless architectures offer these. This has made serverless the game changer for both the cloud providers and the consumers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;For companies that are looking to build applications with this approach, major cloud providers offer several serverless solutions. In this article, we will explore the features, benefits, and challenges of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-serverless-architecture&#34;&gt;this architecture&lt;/a&gt;, along with use cases. In this article, I used AWS as an example to explore the concepts, but the same concepts are applicable across all major cloud providers.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;近年来，云本地应用程序已成为许多企业构建可扩展应用程序的首选标准。在云技术的许多进步中，无服务器体系结构是一种变革性的方法。易用性和效率是现代应用程序开发的两个最理想的属性，而无服务器体系结构为这些提供了这些属性。这使云提供商和消费者的游戏改变者都无服务器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;对于希望通过这种方法构建应用程序的公司，主要的云提供商提供了多种无服务器解决方案。在本文中，我们将探讨&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-cus-serverless-architecture”&gt;此架构的功能，好处和挑战&lt;/a&gt;用例。在本文中，我以AWS为例探索了这些概念，但是相同的概念适用于所有主要的云提供商。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SQL as the Backbone of Big Data and AI Powerhouses】SQL作为大数据和人工智能的骨干</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sql-the-backbone-of-big-data-and-ai-powerhouses</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The term &#34;big data&#34; often conjures images of massive unstructured datasets, real-time streams, and machine learning algorithms. Amid this buzz, some may question whether SQL, the language of traditional relational databases, still holds its ground. Spoiler alert: SQL is not only relevant but is a cornerstone of modern data warehousing, big data platforms, and AI-driven insights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores how SQL, far from being a relic, remains the backbone of big data and AI ecosystems, thriving in the context of data warehousing and cloud-native technologies like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/bigquery-data-frames-in-python-1&#34;&gt;Google BigQuery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;术语“大数据”通常会想到大量非结构化数据集，实时流和机器学习算法的图像。在这种嗡嗡声中，有些人可能会质疑SQL（传统关系数据库的语言）是否仍然持有基础。扰流板警报：SQL不仅相关，而且是现代数据仓库，大数据平台和AI驱动的见解的基石。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了SQL远非遗物，还是大数据和AI生态系统的骨干，在数据仓库和云本地技术的背景下蓬勃发展，例如&lt;a href =” https:///dzone.com /文章/bigquery-data-frames in-python-1“&gt; Google bigquery &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【System Design of an Audio Streaming Service】音频流服务的系统设计</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/system-design-of-an-audio-streaming-system</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The system design of an audio streaming app is unique in how it deals with idiosyncratic business needs. Typically, audio streaming requires a large amount of data to be transferred within the limited bandwidth of the network communication channel.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A successful audio streaming service must handle millions of active users and thousands of content providers from various geographical locations. Different devices and platforms (smartphone, desktop, smart speaker) may support different audio formats &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-convert-mp4-to-mp3-in-java&#34;&gt;such as MP3&lt;/a&gt;, FLAC, ALAC, and so on.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;音频流应用程序的系统设计在处理特质业务需求方面是独一无二的。通常，音频流需要大量数据在网络通信渠道的有限带宽中传输。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成功的音频流服务必须处理来自各个地理位置的数百万活跃用户和成千上万的内容提供商。不同的设备和平台（智能手机，桌面，智能扬声器）可能支持不同的音频格式&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-conto-conterver-conterv-mp4-to-mp4-to-mp4-to-mp3-in-java，如mp3 &lt;/a&gt;，Flac，Alac等。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top 5 GRC Certifications for Cybersecurity Professionals】网络安全专业人员的前5名GRC认证</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-5-grc-certifications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Governance, Risk, and Compliance (GRC) certifications have become crucial for professionals keen on securing cybersecurity and risk management roles. These certifications validate one&#39;s skills and expertise, opening the door to new career opportunities in a dynamically changing environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the increase in the demand for skilled &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/3-compliance-management-solutions-for-technology-d&#34;&gt;GRC professionals&lt;/a&gt;, choosing the proper certification that aligns with your career goals and ambitions is crucial. This article explores the growing demand for GRC certifications and their key benefits and compares the top five certifications to help you make an informed decision. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;治理，风险和合规性（GRC）认证对于热衷于确保网络安全和风险管理角色的专业人员至关重要。这些认证证明了自己的技能和专业知识，在动态不断变化的环境中为新的职业机会打开了大门。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;随着对熟练的需求的增加&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/3-compliance-management-management-mmanagement-solutions-foror-technology-d”&gt; grc专业人员&lt;/&gt; a&gt;，选择与您的职业目标和野心保持一致的适当认证至关重要。本文探讨了对GRC认证及其主要收益的需求不断增长，并比较了前五名认证，以帮助您做出明智的决定。    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Chat Completion Models vs OpenAI Assistants API】聊天完成型号与Openai助手API</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/chat-completion-models-vs-openai-assitance-api</link>
      <description>【&lt;section name=&#34;5ece&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;6700&#34;&gt;In this blog, we are going to explore some key differences between chat completion models (like those provided via the Chat Completions endpoint) and the more advanced OpenAI Assistants API. We will break down how these two approaches handle messages, conversation history, large documents, coding tasks, context window limits, and more. We will also look at how the Assistants API provides additional tools — such as code interpreters, document retrieval, and function calling — that overcome many limitations of chat completions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 name=&#34;60c2&#34;&gt;Understanding Chat Completion Models&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;figure name=&#34;60c2&#34;&gt;&#xA;  Chat completion models, such as GPT‑4 or GPT‑4o, typically expect a sequence of messages as input. The usual process is simple:&#xA; &lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;section name=&#34;8f2a&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;90e7&#34;&gt;You send a list of messages to the model.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;343a&#34;&gt;The model generates a response.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;b2d8&#34;&gt;You receive the response as output.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;h3 name=&#34;22e5&#34;&gt;Example Flow of Chat Completions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;1c9f&#34;&gt;You ask: &lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What’s the capital of Japan&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;部分名称=“ 5EC”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name =“ 6700”&gt;在此博客中，我们将探讨聊天完成模型之间的一些关键差异（例如通过聊天完成端点提供的聊天模型）和更高级的OpenAI助手API。我们将分解这两种方法如何处理消息，对话历史记录，大量文档，编码任务，上下文窗口限制等等。我们还将研究助手API如何提供其他工具（例如代码解释器，文档检索和功能调用），从而克服了聊天完成的许多局限性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 name =“ 60c2”&gt;了解聊天完成模型&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;fige name =“ 60c2”&gt;&#xA;  聊天完成模型，例如GPT -4或GPT -4O，通常会期望一系列消息作为输入。通常的过程很简单：&#xA; &lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;部分名称=“ 8f2a”&gt;&#xA; &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name =“ 90E7”&gt;您将消息列表发送到模型。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name =“ 343a”&gt;该模型会生成一个响应。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name =“ b2d8”&gt;您收到响应作为输出。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;h3 name =“ 22e5”&gt;聊天完成的示例&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name =“ 1c9f”&gt;您问：&lt;em&gt;“ &lt;/em&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;日本的首都&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Secrets Security Is the Most Important Issue For Mobile Apps】秘密安全是移动应用程序最重要的问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secrets-security-important-issue-mobile-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Recently, the Open Worldwide Application Security Project (OWASP) updated its Top 10 Risks for Mobile Applications for the first time since 2016. The security risk at the top this time? &#34;&lt;strong&gt;Improper credential usage&lt;/strong&gt;.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a wake-up call to mobile app providers about the danger of hardcoded credentials and bad secrets hygiene in general.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;最近，自2016年以来，全球开放式应用程序安全项目（OWASP）首次更新了其移动应用程序的十大风险。这次的安全风险是最高的？ “ &lt;strong&gt;凭证使用不当&lt;/strong&gt;。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是向移动应用程序提供商呼唤的关于硬编码证书和坏秘密卫生危险的呼吁。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding AWS Karpenter for Kubernetes Auto-Scaling】了解kubernetes自动缩放的AWS karpenter</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-karpenter-kubernetes-auto-scaling</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In cloud computing, staying ahead requires keeping pace with the latest technologies and mastering them to derive strategic advantage. Today, I delve into AWS Karpenter, a revolutionary auto-scaling solution that promises to transform the efficiency and agility of your cloud architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloud architectures are the backbone of modern digital enterprises, enabling flexibility, scalability, and resilience. However, managing cloud resources, especially in a dynamic and scalable environment, can be challenging. Traditional auto-scaling solutions, while effective, often come with limitations in responsiveness and resource optimization. AWS Karpenter is a next-generation auto-scaling tool designed to address these challenges head-on.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在云计算中，保持领先地位需要与最新技术保持同步并掌握它们以获得战略优势。今天，我深入研究AWS Karpenter，这是一种革命性的自动缩放解决方案，有望改变您的云体系结构的效率和敏捷性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;云体系结构是现代数字企业的骨干，具有灵活性，可扩展性和弹性。但是，管理云资源，尤其是在动态和可扩展的环境中，可能具有挑战性。传统的自动缩放解决方案虽然有效，但通常会限制响应能力和资源优化。 AWS Karpenter是下一代自动缩放工具，旨在正面解决这些挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Perfecting CRUD Functionality in NextJS】完善NextJS中的CRUD功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-crud-with-nextjs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;CRUD operations are fundamental building blocks and crucial for managing data. They are ubiquitous in virtually every application, from simple websites to complex enterprise solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;NestJS Boilerplate users have already been able to evaluate and use a powerful new tool — CLI, which allows you to automatically create resources and their properties. With this tool, you can make all CRUD operations and add the necessary fields to them without writing a single line of code manually. Let’s now explore CRUD operations from the frontend perspective.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; CRUD操作是基本的构建块，对于管理数据至关重要。从简单的网站到复杂的企业解决方案，它们几乎无处不在。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Nestjs样板用户已经能够评估和使用功能强大的新工具 -  CLI，该工具使您可以自动创建资源及其属性。使用此工具，您可以在不手动编写一行代码的情况下向其添加所有CRUD操作，并将必要的字段添加到它们。现在，让我们从前端的角度探索Crud操作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OpenCV Integration With Live 360 Video for Robotics】OPENCV与Live 360​​视频机器人集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/opencv-integration-live-video-for-robotics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As artificial intelligence gets more advanced, robots are increasingly used to free humans from the risks of inspecting dangerous locations or the drudgery of routine visual surveillance. To provide some degree of autonomous decision, the robot often has cameras connected to an onboard Linux computer such as an NVIDIA Jetson or x86 single-board computer (SBC).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the application benefits from live 360-degree video, there are two approaches. The first, more difficult approach is to use multiple cameras and stitch the video together on the computer or process each video feed separately. The number of cameras used depends on the field of view of each camera. If the robot uses two fisheye lenses that can show more than 180 degrees, only two cameras are needed. It&#39;s common to use three or four cameras.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着人工智能变得更加先进，机器人越来越多地用来使人类摆脱检查危险位置或常规视觉监视的繁琐的风险。为了提供一定程度的自主决定，机器人通常将相机连接到板上Linux计算机，例如NVIDIA JETSON或X86单板计算机（SBC）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果该应用程序受益于实时360度视频，则有两种方法。首先，更困难的方法是使用多个摄像头并将视频拼接在一起，或分别处理每个视频供稿。所使用的相机数量取决于每个相机的视场。如果机器人使用两个可以显示超过180度的鱼眼镜头，则只需要两个摄像头。使用三到四个摄像机是常见的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Logfire: Uncomplicated Observability for Python Applications】logfire：Python应用程序的简单可观察性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/logfire-uncomplicated-observability-for-python-app</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In my previous article on Pydantic, I introduced you to Logfire in one of the code examples as an observability platform designed to provide developers with insights into Python applications. In this article, you will get a deep dive into Logfire and its capabilities that will eventually simplify your Observability journey from tracing to debugging to logging.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logfire is an innovative observability platform developed by the creators of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-pydantic-1&#34;&gt;Pydantic&lt;/a&gt;, designed to provide developers with powerful insights into their Python applications. Built on the same principles that made Pydantic a success, Logfire aims to make observability easy to implement and understand while offering deep insights into application behavior.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我的上一篇关于Pydantic的文章中，我向您介绍了其中一个代码示例中的logfire，作为一个可观察性平台，旨在为开发人员提供对Python应用程序的见解。在本文中，您将深入了解logfire及其功能，最终将简化从跟踪到调试再到伐木的可观察性旅程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; logFire是一个创新的可观察性平台，由&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-is-pydantic-1”&gt; pydantic开发的创建者开发洞悉其Python应用程序。 LogFire建立在使Pydantic取得成功的相同原则上，旨在使可观察性易于实施和理解，同时深入了解应用程序行为。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>