<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking the Power of Reflection in Mobile Development】释放移动开发中反思的力量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/reflection-mobile-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This article explores the concept of &lt;strong data-end=&#34;212&#34; data-start=&#34;198&#34;&gt;reflection&lt;/strong&gt; in software development, with a particular focus on mobile platforms like iOS (Swift) and Android (Kotlin/Java). Reflection allows code to inspect and interact with objects, types, and properties at runtime, offering a way to make applications more dynamic and adaptable.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Reflection in Mobile Development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In software development, reflection gives us the ability to inspect and interact with objects, types, and members at runtime, without knowing their specifics at compile time. While it’s often overlooked, reflection can be a powerful tool when used correctly, offering flexibility and adaptability in situations where static code might otherwise be limiting.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了软件开发中的&lt;strong data-end=&#34;212&#34; data-start=&#34;198&#34;&gt;反射&lt;/strong&gt;概念，特别关注 iOS (Swift) 和 Android (Kotlin/Java) 等移动平台。反射允许代码在运行时检查对象、类型和属性并与之交互，从而提供了一种使应用程序更具动态性和适应性的方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;移动开发反思&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在软件开发中，反射使我们能够在运行时检查对象、类型和成员并与之交互，而无需在编译时了解它们的具体信息。尽管经常被忽视，但如果正确使用反射，它可以成为一个强大的工具，在静态代码可能受到限制的情况下提供灵活性和适应性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Penetration Testing Strategy: How to Make Your Tests Practical, Repeatable, and Risk-Reducing】渗透测试策略：如何使您的测试实用、可重复且降低风险</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/penetration-testing-strategy-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Penetration testing — “pentesting” — still surprises teams. Some treat it as a checkbox before launch; others expect it to magically find every vulnerability. The truth sits in the middle: a well-planned penetration testing strategy turns a point-in-time assessment into a practical tool that reduces business risk, informs engineering priorities, and improves resilience over time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article walks through how to build a penetration testing strategy that’s repeatable, cost-effective, and aligned with your business goals. It’s written for security leaders, engineering managers, and CISOs who want tests that do more than produce reports — they change behavior and reduce real risk.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;渗透测试——“渗透测试”——仍然让团队感到惊讶。有些人将其视为启动前的复选框；有些人则将其视为启动前的复选框。其他人则期望它能够神奇地找到每一个漏洞。真相位于中间：精心策划的渗透测试策略将时间点评估转变为实用工具，可以降低业务风险，告知工程优先级，并随着时间的推移提高弹性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文将介绍如何构建可重复、经济高效且与您的业务目标保持一致的渗透测试策略。它是为安全领导者、工程经理和 CISO 编写的，他们希望测试不仅仅能生成报告，还能改变行为并降低实际风险。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Modeling: From ERwin to the Cloud】数据建模：从 ERwin 到云</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-modeling-from-erwin-to-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Data modeling has transformed beyond recognition. We have moved from a simple entity-relationship diagram to sophisticated cloud architectures, and honestly, it is not just about shinier technology — it is a complete rethink of how we handle data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I learned the basics of ERwin back when it ruled the enterprise world. All industries used it, including banks, hospitals, and government agencies. The tool did wonders to standardize and document, which made CFOs and compliance officers happy [1]. The vast database designs across massive organizations could be counted on. Though I will admit, the licensing costs were brutal — especially for smaller teams who just needed basic modeling capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据建模已经发生了翻天覆地的变化。我们已经从简单的实体关系图转向复杂的云架构，老实说，这不仅仅是更先进的技术，而是对我们处理数据方式的彻底重新思考。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当 ERwin 统治企业世界时，我就了解了它的基础知识。所有行业都使用它，包括银行、医院和政府机构。该工具在标准化和记录方面创造了奇迹，这让 CFO 和合规官员感到高兴 [1]。跨大型组织的庞大数据库设计值得信赖。尽管我承认，许可成本非常高，尤其是对于只需要基本建模功能的小型团队而言。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【JavaScript Data Grid Comparison: 8 Popular Options Reviewed】JavaScript 数据网格比较：回顾 8 个流行选项</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/javascript-data-grids-top-options</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Why does choosing the right JavaScript Data Grid still matter in 2026? Data grids remain a cornerstone of web applications: dashboards, admin panels, CRMs, analytics, and enterprise systems all rely on them. The choice of the right grid still defines performance, customization flexibility, accessibility, and cost.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;To find which grid fits your needs, I reviewed eight top JavaScript data grids and compared them by performance, customization, accessibility, cost, integration, and devX.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为什么选择正确的 JavaScript 数据网格在 2026 年仍然很重要？数据网格仍然是 Web 应用程序的基石：仪表板、管理面板、CRM、分析和企业系统都依赖于它们。选择正确的网格仍然决定着性能、定制灵活性、可访问性和成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为了找到适合您需求的网格，我回顾了八个顶级 JavaScript 数据网格，并从性能、定制、可访问性、成本、集成和 devX 方面对它们进行了比较。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Expose Any MCP Server as a Web API】将任何 MCP 服务器公开为 Web API</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/expose-mcp-server-as-web-api</link>
      <description>【&lt;section name=&#34;7185&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;4055&#34;&gt;Transform your MCP server into an HTTP API that anyone can access from anywhere&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/section&gt;&#xA;&lt;section name=&#34;92c5&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 name=&#34;ea28&#34;&gt;The Goal&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;3b82&#34;&gt;You have an MCP server running locally. You want others to use it via HTTP calls.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;部分名称=“7185”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;4055&#34;&gt;将您的 MCP 服务器转换为任何人都可以从任何地方访问的 HTTP API&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/节&gt;&#xA;&lt;节名称=“92c5”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 name=&#34;ea28&#34;&gt;目标&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;3b82&#34;&gt;您有一个本地运行的 MCP 服务器。您希望其他人通过 HTTP 调用使用它。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Automated Validation and Anomaly Detection】实施自动验证和异常检测</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automated-data-validation-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Ensuring data quality has become much harder because contemporary systems generate data at high volume, high velocity, and high variety. Ensuring data consistency, completeness, and accuracy is harder as large-scale data pipelines often pull data from different sources in different formats. Traditional manual review processes simply can&#39;t keep up as the datasets are constantly being expanded and updated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Manual checks not only cause delays but also rely heavily on human judgment, and when the workload is either too big or too fast, the checks are usually no longer applicable. This situation in large-scale environments results in a lack of anomaly identification, inconsistent validation, and increased operational risk.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;由于当代系统生成的数据量大、速度快且种类繁多，因此确保数据质量变得更加困难。确保数据一致性、完整性和准确性更加困难，因为大规模数据管道通常以不同格式从不同来源提取数据。由于数据集不断扩展和更新，传统的手动审核流程根本无法跟上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工检查不仅造成延误，而且严重依赖人的判断，当工作量太大或太快时，检查通常不再适用。这种情况在大规模环境中会导致缺乏异常识别、验证不一致以及增加操作风险。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Atomic Writes in NoSQL: A Multi-Cloud Deep Dive】NoSQL 中的原子写入：多云深入探讨</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/atomic-writes-in-nosql-databases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-path-to-node=&#34;2,0&#34;&gt;Atomic writes used to be one of the important reasons we stuck with relational databases. The rule was simple: &lt;strong&gt;either all your updates succeed&lt;/strong&gt;, or &lt;strong&gt;they all fail&lt;/strong&gt;. But as we moved to NoSQL databases in distributed systems, we often traded that safety for scale. Now, the pendulum is swinging back. Developers building microservices and server-less apps are realizing that writing manual &lt;strong&gt;undo&lt;/strong&gt; logic (compensating transactions) is a nightmare, and they want their NoSQL databases to handle that heavy lifting again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-path-to-node=&#34;2,1&#34;&gt;However, &lt;strong&gt;atomicity&lt;/strong&gt; isn&#39;t standard across the cloud. AWS, Azure, GCP, and Alibaba all offer transaction capabilities, but they have wildly different rules regarding locking, limits, idempotency, and consistency guarantees.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-path-to-node=&#34;2,0&#34;&gt;原子写入曾经是我们坚持使用关系数据库的重要原因之一。规则很简单：&lt;strong&gt;要么所有更新都成功&lt;/strong&gt;，要么&lt;strong&gt;全部失败&lt;/strong&gt;。但当我们转向分布式系统中的 NoSQL 数据库时，我们经常用安全性来换取规模。现在，钟摆又摆回来了。构建微服务和无服务器应用程序的开发人员意识到，编写手动&lt;strong&gt;撤消&lt;/strong&gt;逻辑（补偿事务）是一场噩梦，他们希望自己的 NoSQL 数据库能够再次处理这项繁重的工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-path-to-node=&#34;2,1&#34;&gt;但是，&lt;strong&gt;原子性&lt;/strong&gt;并不是整个云的标准。 AWS、Azure、GCP 和阿里巴巴都提供事务功能，但它们在锁定、限制、幂等性和一致性保证方面有截然不同的规则。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Blockchain + AI Integration: The Architecture Nobody&#39;s Talking About】区块链+人工智能集成：无人谈论的架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/blockchain-ai-integration-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Walk into any tech conference today, and you&#39;ll hear buzzwords flying: AI this, blockchain that. But ask anyone about the actual architecture required to integrate these technologies, and you&#39;ll mostly get hand-waving. That&#39;s because while everyone talks about the potential of combining blockchain&#39;s trustless verification with AI&#39;s decision-making capabilities, very few teams have solved the architectural nightmares that come with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s the uncomfortable truth: these technologies weren&#39;t designed to work together. Blockchain prioritizes transparency, immutability, and deterministic execution. AI thrives on opacity, continuous learning, and probabilistic outputs. Forcing them into the same system is like trying to merge a public ledger with a black box — and expecting both to play nice.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;今天走进任何技术会议，您都会听到流行语飞扬：人工智能这个，区块链那个。但如果问任何人集成这些技术所需的实际架构，大多数人都会表示不解。这是因为，虽然每个人都在谈论将区块链的去信任验证与人工智能决策能力相结合的潜力，但很少有团队解决了随之而来的架构噩梦。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一个令人不安的事实：这些技术并不是为了协同工作而设计的。区块链优先考虑透明度、不变性和确定性执行。人工智能的蓬勃发展依赖于不透明性、持续学习和概率输出。强迫它们进入同一个系统就像试图将公共分类账与黑匣子合并一样 - 并期望两者都能很好地发挥作用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bridging the Gap Between Data Lakes and Warehouses】弥合数据湖和仓库之间的差距</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-lakehouse-bridging-lake-warehouse-gap</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the current analytics landscape, companies rely heavily on data lakes and data warehouses as their primary sources for data storage and analysis. On the one hand, data lakes allow easy storage of a variety of raw and non-processed data, and on the other hand, data warehouses support formatting, storage, and processing of data in a manner that suits reporting and analytics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Figure 1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;: Evolution from data lakes and warehouses to the lakehouse model&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当前的分析环境中，公司严重依赖数据湖和数据仓库作为数据存储和分析的主要来源。一方面，数据湖可以轻松存储各种原始和未处理的数据，另一方面，数据仓库支持以适合报告和分析的方式格式化、存储和处理数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;图 1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;：从数据湖和数据仓库到 Lakehouse 模型的演变&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Practical Guide to Blocking Cyber Threats】阻止网络威胁的实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/nonprofits-least-privilege-cybersecurity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As cyberthreats dominate the news headlines day after day, it is important for large multinational organizations and nonprofits to take immediate notice of such events. Nonprofits often work under stark resource constraints, such as minimal IT staff and limited access control methods — yet the critical information they carry, from donor to staff information, must always be protected. As cyberattacks on nonprofits are rising faster than ever, the limitations that nonprofits have often put in place make them an ideal target for phishing, account takeover, and insider misuse.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the critical and initial methods nonprofits can implement to protect their assets is the Principle of Least Privilege. The principle is based on the simple idea that bare minimum access to the appropriate resource should be provided to the subject, and no more than what is required for them to do their job. In general, there are basically no blanket permissions and no “admin for convenience.” It is a highly practical and actionable approach to fortify their defenses — without requiring a major personnel or technical overhaul. The principle — when implemented correctly — reduces the attack surface area for nonprofits and prevents such attacks from happening in the first place.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着网络威胁日复一日地占据新闻头条，大型跨国组织和非营利组织必须立即注意到此类事件。非营利组织通常在严格的资源限制下开展工作，例如最少的 IT 人员和有限的访问控制方法，但它们携带的关键信息（从捐赠者信息到员工信息）必须始终受到保护。由于针对非营利组织的网络攻击比以往任何时候都增长得更快，非营利组织经常设置的限制使其成为网络钓鱼、帐户接管和内部滥用的理想目标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;非营利组织可以实施的保护其资产的关键和初步方法之一是最小特权原则。该原则基于一个简单的想法，即应向主体提供对适当资源的最低限度的访问权限，并且不超过他们完成工作所需的权限。一般来说，基本上没有一揽子权限，也没有“方便管理”。这是一种非常实用且可操作的加强防御的方法，而不需要进行重大的人员或技术改革。该原则如果正确实施，可以减少非营利组织的攻击面，并从一开始就防止此类攻击的发生。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>