<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes Deployments With DMZ Clusters: An Essential Guide】使用 DMZ 集群进行 Kubernetes 部署：基本指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-deployments-with-dmz-clusters</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;As organizations increasingly adopt Kubernetes for managing microservices and containerized workloads, securing these deployments becomes paramount. A&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Demilitarized Zone (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;DMZ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;cluster, a proven security architecture that isolates public-facing services from sensitive internal resources, ensures robust protection against external threats. In this article, we’ll explore the concept of DMZ clusters in Kubernetes, their importance, and how to implement these robust security measures effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is a DMZ Cluster in Kubernetes?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A DMZ is a network boundary that exposes specific services to external traffic while safeguarding the internal network. In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-introduction-to-kubernetes-an-orchestra&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;, this architecture is implemented by creating separate clusters for public-facing applications and internal workloads, ensuring limited and tightly controlled communication between them.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;随着组织越来越多地采用 Kubernetes 来管理微服务和容器化工作负载，保护这些部署变得至关重要。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;非军事区 (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;DMZ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver- space=&#34;true&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; 集群是一种经过验证的安全架构，可将面向公众的服务与敏感的内部资源隔离开来，确保针对外部威胁提供强大的保护。在本文中，我们将探讨 Kubernetes 中 DMZ 集群的概念、其重要性以及如何有效实施这些强大的安全措施。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes 中的 DMZ 集群是什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DMZ 是一个网络边界，它将特定服务暴露给外部流量，同时保护内部网络。在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-introduction-to-kubernetes-an-orchestra&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; 中，这种架构是通过为面向公众的应用程序创建单独的集群来实现的和内部工作负载，确保它们之间的通信受到有限且严格控制。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Incremental Jobs and Data Quality Are On a Collision Course】增量工作和数据质量正在发生冲突</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/incremental-jobs-and-data-quality-are-on-a-collision-course</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If you keep an eye on the data space ecosystem like I do, then you’ll be aware of the rise of DuckDB and its &lt;a href=&#34;https://motherduck.com/blog/big-data-is-dead/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;message that big data is dead&lt;/a&gt;. The idea comes from two industry papers (and associated data sets), one from the Redshift team (&lt;a href=&#34;https://assets.amazon.science/24/3b/04b31ef64c83acf98fe3fdca9107/why-tpc-is-not-enough-an-analysis-of-the-amazon-redshift-fleet.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/amazon-science/redset&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;dataset&lt;/a&gt;) and one from Snowflake (&lt;a href=&#34;https://event.cwi.nl/lsde/papers/p215-dageville-snowflake.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/resource-disaggregation/snowset&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;dataset&lt;/a&gt;). Each paper analyzed the queries run on their platforms, and some surprising conclusions were drawn — one being that most queries were run over quite small data. The conclusion (of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-to-duckdb-optimization&#34;&gt;DuckDB&lt;/a&gt;) was that big data was dead, and you could use simpler query engines rather than a data warehouse. It’s far more nuanced than that, but data shows that most queries are run over smaller datasets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果您像我一样关注数据空间生态系统，那么您就会意识到 DuckDB 及其&lt;a href=&#34;https://motherduck.com/blog/ 的崛起big-data-is-dead/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;大数据已死的消息&lt;/a&gt;。这个想法来自两篇行业论文（以及相关数据集），其中一篇来自 Redshift 团队 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://assets.amazon.science/24/3b/04b31ef64c83acf98fe3fdca9107/why-tpc-is-not-enough -an-analysis-of-the-amazon-redshift-fleet.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;论文&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/amazon-science/redset&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;数据集&lt;/a&gt;）和来自 Snowflake 的一份 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://event.cwi.nl/lsde/papers/p215-dageville-snowflake.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;论文&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/resource-disaggregation/snowset&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;数据集&lt;/a&gt;）。每篇论文都分析了在其平台上运行的查询，并得出了一些令人惊讶的结论——其中之一是大多数查询都是在相当小的数据上运行的。结论（&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/developers-guide-to-duckdb-optimization&#34;&gt;DuckDB&lt;/a&gt;）是大数据已死，您可以使用更简单的查询引擎而不是数据仓库。它比这要微妙得多，但数据显示大多数查询都是在较小的数据集上运行的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为什么？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Avoiding If-Else: Advanced Approaches and Alternatives】避免 If-Else：高级方法和替代方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/avoiding-if-else-advanced-approaches-and-alternatives</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Mostly, developers make use of if-else statements to cater to differing circumstances. Even so, this could prove itself quite troublesome especially when more conditions arise. Putting additional business needs into these chains might cause errors while making the code more complicated than necessary. It is advisable that we anticipate eventually creating solutions that could change or grow without being difficultly updated in order not only to ensure the robustness of one’s system but also to enable its adaptation within unforeseen circumstances. Our codes will then remain potent and readily adaptable to the needs ahead us in this case.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In this article, we’ll delve into methods for managing functions in a calculator using Java in all examples. The aim is to enhance the processing of operations (such as addition, subtraction, multiplication, and division) in our coding. We’ll incorporate techniques by using a sample calculator that receives a request with an operation type and two values, including if-else statements, switch cases, and the strategy design pattern. The main focus will be on describing the concepts and benefits of each method.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;大多数情况下，开发人员会使用 if-else 语句来满足不同的情况。即便如此，这可能会带来相当大的麻烦，尤其是当出现更多情况时。将额外的业务需求放入这些链中可能会导致错误，同时使代码变得不必要的复杂。建议我们最终创建可以更改或增长而无需困难更新的解决方案，以便不仅确保系统的稳健性，而且能够在不可预见的情况下进行适应。在这种情况下，我们的代码将保持有效并随时适应我们面临的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将深入研究在所有示例中使用 Java 管理计算器中的函数的方法。目的是增强编码中的运算处理（例如加法、减法、乘法和除法）。我们将通过使用示例计算器来整合技术，该计算器接收带有操作类型和两个值的请求，包括 if-else 语句、switch 案例和策略设计模式。主要重点是描述每种方法的概念和优点。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing GitHub Access Management for Enterprises: Enhancing Security, Scalability, and Continuity with Jenkins GitHub App Authentication and Load Balancing】优化企业的 GitHub 访问管理：使用 Jenkins GitHub 应用程序身份验证和负载平衡增强安全性、可扩展性和连续性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-github-access-management-for-enterprises</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As enterprises expand their software development practices and scale their DevOps pipelines, effective management of continuous integration (CI) and continuous deployment (CD) processes becomes increasingly important. GitHub, as one of the most widely used source control platforms, plays a central role in modern development workflows. It is critical for managing code repositories, automating tasks, and enabling collaboration among development teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;To streamline CI/CD activities and ensure smoother operations, many organizations implement a centralized GitHub admin account that oversees repository management, integrations, and automation. This method helps maintain control and consistency across development environments. However, such an approach can introduce security vulnerabilities, scalability challenges, and operational risks, particularly when it comes to handling increasing complexity and ensuring high availability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着企业扩展其软件开发实践并扩展其 DevOps 管道，持续集成 (CI) 和持续部署 (CD) 流程的有效管理变得越来越重要。 GitHub 作为最广泛使用的源代码控制平台之一，在现代开发工作流程中发挥着核心作用。它对于管理代码存储库、自动化任务以及实现开发团队之间的协作至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为了简化 CI/CD 活动并确保操作更顺畅，许多组织实施了集中式 GitHub 管理员帐户来监督存储库管理、集成和自动化。此方法有助于保持跨开发环境的控制和一致性。然而，这种方法可能会带来安全漏洞、可扩展性挑战和操作风险，特别是在处理日益增加的复杂性和确保高可用性时。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Lighthouse Test Automation Into Your CI/CD Pipeline】将 Lighthouse 测试自动化集成到您的 CI/CD 管道中</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-lighthouse-test-automation-into-your-ci-cd-pipeline</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Web performance can make or break your digital presence. While developers constantly push new features and updates, maintaining consistent quality across deployments remains a challenge. Lighthouse test automation has emerged as a powerful solution, transforming how development teams approach quality assurance and performance optimization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding Lighthouse Test Automation Fundamentals&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lighthouse test automation serves as the foundation for comprehensive performance testing. When integrated into continuous integration workflows, Google Lighthouse&amp;nbsp;provides consistent, objective measurements of web application performance. This integration enables teams to catch performance regressions before they impact users.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;网络性能可以成就或毁掉您的数字形象。尽管开发人员不断推出新功能和更新，但在部署中保持一致的质量仍然是一个挑战。 Lighthouse 测试自动化已成为一种强大的解决方案，改变了开发团队实现质量保证和性能优化的方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解 Lighthouse 测试自动化基础知识&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lighthouse 测试自动化是全面性能测试的基础。当集成到持续集成工作流程中时，Google Lighthouse 可以提供一致、客观的 Web 应用程序性能测量。这种集成使团队能够在性能下降影响用户之前捕获它们。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Troubleshooting Kubernetes Pod Crashes: Common Causes and Effective Solutions】排除 Kubernetes Pod 崩溃问题：常见原因和有效解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/troubleshooting-kubernetes-pod-crashes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Kubernetes has become the de facto standard for container orchestration, offering scalability, resilience, and ease of deployment. However, managing Kubernetes environments is not without challenges. One common issue faced by administrators and developers is pod crashes. In this article, we will explore the reasons behind pod crashes and outline effective strategies to diagnose and resolve these issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Common Causes of Kubernetes Pod Crashes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Out-of-Memory (OOM) Errors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cause&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/root-causes-of-OOM-issues-in-Java-containers&#34;&gt;Insufficient memory allocation&lt;/a&gt; in resource limits. Containers often consume more memory than initially estimated, leading to termination.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 已成为容器编排的事实上的标准，提供可扩展性、弹性和易于部署。然而，管理 Kubernetes 环境并非没有挑战。管理员和开发人员面临的一个常见问题是 Pod 崩溃。在本文中，我们将探讨 Pod 崩溃背后的原因，并概述诊断和解决这些问题的有效策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Pod 崩溃的常见原因&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1。内存不足 (OOM) 错误&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;原因&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/root-causes-of-OOM-issues-in-Java-containers&#34;&gt;资源限制中内存分配不足&lt;/a&gt;。容器消耗的内存通常比最初估计的要多，从而导致终止。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software Development Trends to Follow in 2025】2025 年软件开发趋势</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-development-trends-to-follow-in-2025</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;2025 is knocking on the door, and software development is changing at a rapid pace due to advanced technologies. Tech advancements like AI have transformed how developers create, deploy, and scale software. To stay ahead of the curve, developers need to stay on top of the latest software development trends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I am going to shed light on software development trends you need to watch in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;2025 年即将到来，由于先进技术，软件开发正在快速变化。人工智能等技术进步改变了开发人员创建、部署和扩展软件的方式。为了保持领先地位，开发人员需要掌握最新的软件开发趋势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇博文中，我将阐明 2025 年您需要关注的软件开发趋势。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Decoding the Role of a Delivery Manager: Ensuring Smooth Operations Across the Software Development Lifecycle】解读交付经理的角色：确保整个软件开发生命周期的顺利运营</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-the-role-of-a-delivery-manager</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In software development, the term “delivery” often sparks a range of interpretations. Ask ten people what it means, and you might receive ten distinct answers. Yet, despite these varied perspectives, one thing remains constant: the role of a delivery manager is pivotal in turning ideas into reality. They are the glue that holds projects together, ensuring every step of the journey — from concept to launch — unfolds as smoothly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article explores the delivery manager’s responsibilities, their role within a team, and the profound impact they have on ensuring project success.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在软件开发中，“交付”一词经常引发一系列的解释。问十个人这意味着什么，你可能会得到十个不同的答案。然而，尽管观点各异，但有一件事始终不变：交付经理的角色对于将想法变为现实至关重要。它们是将项目粘合在一起的粘合剂，确保从概念到发布的每一步都尽可能顺利地展开。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;本文探讨了交付经理的职责、他们在团队中的角色以及他们对确保项目成功的深远影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Stop Being Afraid of Databases】不要再害怕数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/stop-being-afraid-of-databases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Ensuring database reliability can be difficult. Our goal is to speed up development and minimize rollbacks. We want developers to be able to work efficiently while taking ownership of their databases. Achieving this becomes much simpler when robust database observability is in place. Let’s explore how.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Do Not Wait With Checks&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Teams aim to maintain continuous database reliability, focusing on ensuring their designs perform well in production, scale effectively, and allow for safe code deployments. To achieve this level of quality, they rely on a range of practices, including thorough testing, code reviews, automated &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-cicd-pipeline&#34;&gt;CI/CD pipelines&lt;/a&gt;, and component monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;确保数据库可靠性可能很困难。我们的目标是加快开发速度并最大限度地减少回滚。我们希望开发人员能够在拥有数据库的同时高效工作。当强大的数据库可观察性到位时，实现这一点变得更加简单。让我们探讨一下如何实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;不要等待支票&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;团队的目标是保持数据库的持续可靠性，重点是确保他们的设计在生产中表现良好、有效扩展并允许安全的代码部署。为了达到这种质量水平，他们依靠一系列实践，包括彻底的测试、代码审查、自动化&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-cicd-pipeline&#34;&gt;CI /CD 管道&lt;/a&gt;和组件监控。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Performance in Azure Cosmos DB: Best Practices and Tips】优化 Azure Cosmos DB 的性能：最佳实践和技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-performance-in-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When we are working with a database, optimization is crucial and key in terms of application performance and efficiency. Likewise, in Azure Cosmos DB, optimization is crucial for maximizing efficiency, minimizing costs, and ensuring that your application scales effectively. Below are some of the best practices with coding examples to optimize performance in Azure Cosmos DB.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Selection of Right Partition Key&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Choosing an appropriate partition key is vital for distributed databases like&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/tips-on-performance-optimization-of-cosmos-db&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cosmos DB&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. A good partition key ensures that data is evenly distributed across partitions, reducing hot spots&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;and improving performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;当我们使用数据库时，优化对于应用程序性能和效率至关重要。同样，在 Azure Cosmos DB 中，优化对于最大限度地提高效率、最大限度地降低成本并确保应用程序有效扩展至关重要。以下是优化 Azure Cosmos DB 性能的一些最佳实践和编码示例。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;1。选择正确的分区键&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;选择合适的分区键对于分布式数据库（如 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/tips-on-performance-optimization-of-cosmos-db&#34;）至关重要&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cosmos DB&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;。良好的分区键可确保数据在分区之间均匀分布，从而减少热点&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;并提高性能。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>