<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Data Storage: Challenges, Capabilities, and Comparative Analysis】人工智能数据存储：挑战、能力和比较分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-data-storage-challenges-capabilities-comparison</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The explosion in the popularity of ChatGPT has once again ignited a surge of excitement in the AI world. Over the past five years, AI has advanced rapidly and has found applications in a wide range of industries. As a storage company, we’ve had a front-row seat to this expansion, watching more and more AI startups and established players emerge across fields like autonomous driving, protein structure prediction, and quantitative investment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI scenarios have introduced new challenges to the field of data storage. Existing storage solutions are often inadequate to fully meet these demands. In this article, we’ll deep dive into the storage challenges in AI scenarios, critical storage capabilities, and comparative analysis of storage products. I hope this post will help you make informed choices in AI and data storage.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;ChatGPT 的爆发式流行再次点燃了 AI 世界的热潮。五年来，人工智能发展迅速，在各行各业得到广泛应用。作为一家存储公司，我们在这一扩张中处于领先地位，看到越来越多的人工智能初创公司和老牌企业在自动驾驶、蛋白质结构预测和量化投资等领域涌现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI场景给数据存储领域带来了新的挑战。现有的存储解决方案通常不足以完全满足这些需求。在本文中，我们将深入探讨AI场景下的存储挑战、关键存储能力以及存储产品的对比分析。我希望这篇文章能帮助您在人工智能和数据存储方面做出明智的选择。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streaming vs In-Memory DataWeave: Designing for 1M+ Records Without Crashing】流式传输与内存中 DataWeave：设计 100 万条以上记录而不崩溃</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/streaming-vs-in-memory-dataweave-large-datasets</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;648&#34; data-start=&#34;603&#34;&gt;The Real Problem With Scaling DataWeave&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;935&#34; data-start=&#34;649&#34;&gt;MuleSoft is built to handle enterprise integrations — but most developers test with small payloads. Everything looks fine in dev, until one day a real file with 1 million records hits your flow. Suddenly, your worker crashes with an &lt;code&gt;OutOfMemoryError&lt;/code&gt;, and the job fails halfway through.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1066&#34; data-start=&#34;937&#34;&gt;The truth is, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/dataweave-the-map-function-explained&#34;&gt;DataWeave&lt;/a&gt; by default works in-memory. That’s acceptable for small datasets, but in production, we often deal with:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;648&#34; data-start=&#34;603&#34;&gt;扩展 DataWeave 的真正问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;935&#34; data-start=&#34;649&#34;&gt;MuleSoft 旨在处理企业集成 - 但大多数开发人员都使用较小的有效负载进行测试。开发中一切看起来都很好，直到有一天，一个包含 100 万条记录的真实文件出现在您的流程中。突然，您的工作线程因 &lt;code&gt;OutOfMemoryError&lt;/code&gt; 崩溃，作业中途失败。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1066&#34; data-start=&#34;937&#34;&gt;事实是，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/dataweave-the-map-function-explained&#34;&gt;DataWeave&lt;/a&gt; 默认情况下在内存中工作。这对于小型数据集来说是可以接受的，但在生产中，我们经常处理：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Escaping the &#34;Excel Trap&#34;: Building an AI-Assisted ETL Pipeline Without a Data Team】逃离“Excel陷阱”：在没有数据团队的情况下构建人工智能辅助的ETL管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/escaping-the-excel-trap-building-an-ai-assisted-et</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Business data often lives in hundreds of disconnected Excel files, making it invisible to decision-makers. Here is a pattern for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.computerweekly.com/blog/CW-Developer-Network/Data-engineering-SAS-The-install-rise-of-the-citizen-data-engineer&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Citizen Data Engineering&lt;/a&gt; using Python, GitHub Copilot, and Qlik Sense to unify data silos without writing a single line of manual code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the enterprise world, the most common database isn&#39;t Oracle or PostgreSQL — it’s &lt;strong&gt;Excel&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;业务数据通常存在于数百个互不关联的 Excel 文件中，决策者看不到这些数据。以下是&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.computerweekly.com/blog/CW-Developer-Network/Data-engineering-SAS-The-install-rise-of-the-citizen-data-engineer&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;公民数据工程&lt;/a&gt;的模式，使用 Python、GitHub Copilot 和 Qlik Sense 来统一数据孤岛，而无需编写任何手动代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在企业界，最常见的数据库不是 Oracle 或 PostgreSQL，而是 &lt;strong&gt;Excel&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DZone&#39;s 2025 Community Survey】DZone 2025 年社区调查</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/2025-dzone-community-survey</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Another year passed right under our noses, and software development trends moved along with it. The steady rise of AI, the introduction of vibe coding — these are just among the many impactful shifts, and you&#39;ve helped us understand them better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, as we move on to another exciting year, we would like to continue to learn more about you as software developers, your tech habits and preferences, and the topics you wish to know more about. With that comes our annual community survey — a great opportunity for you to give us more insights into your interests and priorities. We ask this because we want DZone to work for &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;又一年在我们眼皮子底下过去了，软件开发趋势也随之发生变化。人工智能的稳步崛起、振动编码的引入——这些只是众多影响深远的转变中的一部分，您帮助我们更好地理解了它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，随着我们进入另一个激动人心的一年，我们希望继续更多地了解您作为软件开发人员、您的技术习惯和偏好，以及您希望更多了解的主题。随之而来的是我们的年度社区调查——这是您让我们更深入地了解您的兴趣和优先事项的绝佳机会。我们提出这个问题是因为我们希望 DZone 为您服务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Metrics to Action: Adding AI Recommendations to Your SaaS App】从指标到行动：将 AI 建议添加到您的 SaaS 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/saas-ai-actionable-recommendations</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;You log into your DevOps portal, pinched to think about 300 different metrics: CPU, latency, errors, all lighting up red on your dashboard. But what to prioritize? It’s what an AI-based recommendation tool could resolve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every SaaS platform managing cloud operations records an incredible amount of telemetry data. Most products, however, simply provide visualization: interesting graphics, yet no actionable information. What if your product could provide automated suggestions for config, scaling, or alerts based on tenant behavior?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您登录到 DevOps 门户，需要思考 300 个不同的指标：CPU、延迟、错误，所有指标都在仪表板上亮起红色。但要优先考虑什么？这就是基于人工智能的推荐工具可以解决的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个管理云运营的 SaaS 平台都会记录大量遥测数据。然而，大多数产品只是提供可视化：有趣的图形，但没有可操作的信息。如果您的产品可以根据租户行为自动提供配置、扩展或警报建议，结果会怎样？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【2026 IaC Predictions: The Year Infrastructure Finally Grows Up】2026 年 IaC 预测：基础设施最终成长的一年</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/iac-predictions-infrastructure-grows-up</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The industry spent the last decade racing to automate the cloud, and 2026 will be the year we find out what happens when automation actually wins.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI is writing Terraform and OpenTofu faster than teams can review it. Cloud providers are shipping higher-level services every month. Business units want new environments on demand. The IaC footprint inside large enterprises is exploding.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;业界在过去十年里一直在竞相实现云自动化，而 2026 年我们将看到自动化真正获胜时会发生什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI 编写 Terraform 和 OpenTofu 的速度比团队审查的速度还要快。云提供商每个月都在提供更高级别的服务。业务部门希望按需提供新的环境。大型企业内部的 IaC 足迹正在呈爆炸式增长。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Containers: Docker-First Mobile Build Pipelines (Android and iOS) — End-to-End from Code to Artifact】超越容器：Docker 优先的移动构建管道（Android 和 iOS）——从代码到工件的端到端</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/beyond-containers-docker-first-mobile-build-pipeli</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In many mobile app shops, builds are still done locally (on dev laptops) or through fragile CI scripts. This leads to inconsistent builds, wasted hours onboarding developers, or debugging “but it worked on my machine” issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Using Docker — already popular for backend and microservices — mobile teams can also build a &lt;strong&gt;reproducible, scalable, and version-controlled pipeline&lt;/strong&gt; for both Android and iOS (to the extent possible), which speeds up development, reduces “works on my machine” issues, and enables hybrid mobile/web-backend synergy.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在许多移动应用商店中，构建仍然在本地（在开发笔记本电脑上）或通过脆弱的 CI 脚本完成。这会导致构建不一致、浪费时间帮助开发人员或调试“但它在我的机器上运行”问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用 Docker（在后端和微服务中已经很流行），移动团队还可以为 Android 和 iOS（尽可能）构建一个&lt;strong&gt;可重复、可扩展和版本控制的管道&lt;/strong&gt;，从而加快开发速度，减少“在我的机器上运行”问题，并实现混合移动/Web 后端协同。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Agent Trap: Why AI&#39;s Autonomous Future Might Be Its Biggest Liability】代理陷阱：为什么人工智能的自主未来可能是其最大的责任</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-ai-autonomous-future-might-be-its-liability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve been covering enterprise AI deployments since Watson was still pretending to revolutionize healthcare, and I&#39;ve learned to distinguish genuine paradigm shifts from rebranded hype cycles. What&#39;s happening with agentic AI in 2025 feels uncomfortably like both.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The pitch is seductive: autonomous software agents that plan, reason, and execute complex tasks without constant human supervision. Instead of asking a chatbot for information, you delegate an entire workflow — &#34;book my travel to the conference in Austin, find a hotel near the venue, block my calendar, and brief me on attendees I should meet.&#34; The agent figures out the rest.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;自从沃森仍然假装要彻底改变医疗保健以来，我就一直在报道企业人工智能部署，并且我学会了区分真正的范式转变和重新命名的炒作周期。 2025 年代理人工智能所发生的事情让人感觉两者都令人不安。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个宣传很诱人：自主软件代理可以在没有持续人工监督的情况下计划、推理和执行复杂的任务。您无需向聊天机器人询问信息，而是委托整个工作流程 - “预订前往奥斯汀会议的行程，找到会场附近的酒店，锁定我的日历，并向我介绍我应该会见的与会者。”代理会计算出剩下的内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ambient Agentic Systems – A New Era Begins】环境代理系统——新时代的开始</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ambient-agentic-systems-a-new-era-begins</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In recent years, the field of generative artificial intelligence (gen AI) has transformed sectors like healthcare, manufacturing, automobiles &amp;amp; finance. GPT-4, Claude, and Gemini have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in language understanding, content creation, and reasoning.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, these significant strides have brought forth their fair share of challenges, like maintaining performance, efficiency, and adaptability as they scale. Finetuning and deploying sophisticated gen AI models require significant computational power, which can be costly and infrastructure-intensive. This has meant that only large organizations with deep pockets could leverage gen AI at scale.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;近年来，生成人工智能 (gen AI) 领域已经改变了医疗保健、制造、汽车和金融等行业。 GPT-4、Claude 和 Gemini 在语言理解、内容创作和推理方面表现出了卓越的能力。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，这些重大进步也带来了相当大的挑战，例如在扩展时保持性能、效率和适应性。微调和部署复杂的新一代人工智能模型需要大量的计算能力，这可能成本高昂且基础设施密集。这意味着只有财力雄厚的大型组织才能大规模利用人工智能。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Virtual Threads in JDK 21: Revolutionizing Java Multithreading】JDK 21 中的虚拟线程：彻底改变 Java 多线程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/virtual-threads-in-jdk-21-revolutionize-java-multithreading</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;What is Virtual Thread&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multi-threading is a widely used feature across the industry for developing Java-based applications. It allows us to run operations in parallel, enabling faster task execution. The number of threads created by any Java application is limited by the number of parallel operations the OS can handle; in other words, the number of threads in a Java application is equal to the number of OS threads. Until now, this limitation has created a bottleneck on further scaling any application, considering the current fast-paced ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To overcome this limitation, Java has introduced the concept of Virtual Thread in JDK21. A Java application creates a Virtual Thread and is not associated with any OS thread. It means every Virtual Thread does not need to be dependent on a Platform Thread (aka OS thread). Virtual Thread will work on any task independently and will acquire a Platform Thread only when it needs to perform any I/O operation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;什么是虚拟线程&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多线程是业界广泛使用的用于开发基于 Java 的应用程序的功能。它允许我们并行运行操作，从而实现更快的任务执行。任何 Java 应用程序创建的线程数量都受到操作系统可以处理的并行操作数量的限制；换句话说，Java 应用程序中的线程数等于操作系统线程数。到目前为止，考虑到当前快节奏的生态系统，这种限制已经成为进一步扩展任何应用程序的瓶颈。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了克服这个限制，Java在JDK21中引入了虚拟线程的概念。 Java 应用程序创建一个虚拟线程，并且不与任何操作系统线程关联。这意味着每个虚拟线程不需要依赖于平台线程（也称为操作系统线程）。虚拟线程将独立地处理任何任务，并且仅当需要执行任何I/O操作时才会获取平台线程。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>