<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a 300 Channel Video Encoding Server】搭建300路视频编码服务器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-300-channel-video-encoding-server</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Snapshot&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organization&lt;/strong&gt;: NETINT, Supermicro, and Ampere® Computing&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Problem&lt;/strong&gt;: The demand for high-quality live video streaming has surged, putting pressure on operational costs and user expectations. Legacy x86 processors struggle to handle the intensive video processing tasks required for modern streaming.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;快照&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;组织&lt;/strong&gt;：NETINT、Supermicro 和 Ampere® 计算&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;问题&lt;/strong&gt;：对高质量直播视频流的需求激增，给运营成本和用户期望带来压力。传统 x86 处理器难以处理现代流媒体所需的密集视频处理任务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Spring Boot Concurrency: Virtual Threads in Practice】AI 支持的 Spring Boot 并发：虚拟线程实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-spring-boot-concurrency-virtual-threads</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern microservices face a common challenge: managing multiple tasks simultaneously without putting too much pressure on the systems that follow. Adjusting traditional thread pools often involves a lot of guesswork, which usually doesn&#39;t hold up in real-world situations. However, with the arrival of virtual threads in Java 21 and the growth of AI-powered engineering tools, we can create smart concurrency adapters that scale in a safe and intelligent way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article provides a step-by-step guide to a practical proof-of-concept using Spring Boot that employs AI (OpenAI/Gemini) to assist in runtime concurrency decisions. It also integrates virtual threads and bulkheads to ensure a good balance between throughput and the safety of downstream systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代微服务面临一个共同的挑战：同时管理多个任务，而不会给后续系统带来太大压力。调整传统线程池通常涉及大量猜测，这通常在现实情况下不成立。然而，随着 Java 21 中虚拟线程的到来以及人工智能驱动的工程工具的发展，我们可以创建以安全、智能的方式扩展的智能并发适配器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文提供了使用 Spring Boot 进行实用概念验证的分步指南，该指南利用 AI (OpenAI/Gemini) 来协助运行时并发决策。它还集成了虚拟线程和舱壁，以确保吞吐量和下游系统安全性之间的良好平衡。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Verify Domain Ownership: A Technical Deep Dive】如何验证域名所有权：技术深入探讨</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-verify-domain-ownership-technical-deep-dive</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;616&#34; data-start=&#34;322&#34;&gt;Domain ownership verification is a fundamental security mechanism that proves you control a specific domain. Whether you&#39;re setting up email authentication, SSL certificates, or integrating third-party services, understanding domain verification methods is essential for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/revolutionizing-the-web-emerging-trends-and-innova&#34;&gt;modern web development&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;927&#34; data-start=&#34;618&#34;&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll explore the three most common verification methods, their trade-offs, and practical implementation patterns. I recently built domain verification for &lt;strong data-end=&#34;813&#34; data-start=&#34;791&#34;&gt;allscreenshots.com&lt;/strong&gt;, a screenshot API I work on, to enable automatic OG image generation — and I’ll share what I learned along the way.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;616&#34; data-start=&#34;322&#34;&gt;域所有权验证是一种基本安全机制，可证明您控制特定域。无论您是设置电子邮件身份验证、SSL 证书还是集成第三方服务，了解域验证方法对于&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/revolutionizing-the-web-emerging-trends-and-innova&#34;&gt;现代 Web 开发&lt;/a&gt;都至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;927&#34; data-start=&#34;618&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨三种最常见的验证方法、它们的权衡以及实际的实施模式。我最近为 &lt;strong data-end=&#34;813&#34; data-start=&#34;791&#34;&gt;allscreenshots.com&lt;/strong&gt;（我正在开发的一个屏幕截图 API）构建了域验证，以实现自动 OG 图像生成 - 我将分享我在此过程中学到的知识。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Rapid Prototyping for Multimodal AI Agents in Enterprise Collaboration】企业协作中多模式人工智能代理的快速原型设计</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rapid-prototyping-multimodal-ai-agents-enterprise</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Gartner&#39;s latest research paints a striking picture: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2025-08-26-gartner-predicts-40-percent-of-enterprise-apps-will-feature-task-specific-ai-agents-by-2026-up-from-less-than-5-percent-in-2025&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;40% of enterprise applications will have task-specific AI agents by 2026&lt;/a&gt;. Right now, we&#39;re at 5%. That&#39;s not gradual adoption. That&#39;s a landslide. And yet &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/quantumblack/our-insights/the-state-of-ai&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;McKinsey found&lt;/a&gt; that while 88% of enterprises have AI running somewhere in their operations, only 6% are seeing real financial returns across the business. Everyone&#39;s adopting. Almost no one&#39;s scaling. The bottleneck isn&#39;t technology anymore. It&#39;s figuring out whether what you&#39;re building actually works for the people who have to use it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Validation Gap Nobody Talks About&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The pitch sounds great: AI that joins your meetings, transcribes everything, writes up the recap, and flags who owes what to whom. Some of these tools even jump in when the conversation stalls. Technically, it&#39;s remarkable work. But here&#39;s what gets glossed over in product demos: this isn&#39;t software that behaves the way software usually behaves. You can ask the same thing twice and get different answers both times. That&#39;s not a bug. That&#39;s how language models function.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Gartner 的最新研究描绘了一幅引人注目的图景：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2025-08-26-gartner-predicts-40-percent-of-enterprise-apps-will-feature-task-specific-ai-agents-by-2026-up-from-less-than-5-percent-in-2025&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;40%到 2026 年，80% 的企业应用程序将拥有特定于任务的人工智能代理&lt;/a&gt;。现在，我们的比例是 5%。这不是逐步采用。那是山崩地裂。然而，麦肯锡发现，尽管 88% 的企业在其运营中的某个地方运行了人工智能，但只有 6% 的企业在整个企业中看到了真正的财务回报。大家都在领养。几乎没有人在缩放。瓶颈不再是技术。它正在弄清楚您正在构建的内容是否真正适合必须使用它的人。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;没人谈论的验证差距&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;这个宣传听起来很棒：人工智能会加入您的会议，转录所有内容，写下摘要，并标记谁欠谁什么。其中一些工具甚至会在对话停止时介入。从技术上来说，这是一项了不起的工作。但产品演示中掩盖了这一点：这不是软件，其行为方式与软件通常的行为方式不同。你可以问同一件事两次，但两次都会得到不同的答案。这不是一个错误。这就是语言模型的运作方式。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Distributed Task Queue With Python asyncio + Redis (A Celery Replacement)】使用 Python asyncio + Redis 的分布式任务队列（Celery 替代品）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/distributed-task-queue-python-asyncio-redis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Celery has been the de facto standard for background task processing in Python for over a decade. It’s powerful, battle-tested, and feature-rich, but it also comes with significant complexity: brokers, result backends, worker pools, configuration overhead, serialization quirks, and sometimes opaque debugging. With the rise of asyncio, high-performance Redis clients, and modern Python runtimes, many teams are asking a simple question:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do we really need Celery for every background job use case?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;十多年来，Celery 一直是 Python 后台任务处理的事实上的标准。它功能强大、经过实战检验且功能丰富，但也具有显着的复杂性：代理、结果后端、工作池、配置开销、序列化怪癖以及有时不透明的调试。随着 asyncio、高性能 Redis 客户端和现代 Python 运行时的兴起，许多团队都在问一个简单的问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们真的需要 Celery 来满足每个后台作业用例吗？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Resilient Industrial AI: A Developer’s Guide to Multi-ERP RAG】构建有弹性的工业人工智能：多 ERP RAG 开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-resilient-industrial-ai-multi-erp-rag</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;The Integration Reality&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When someone says &#34;AI agent for supply chain,&#34; it’s tempting to think first about prompts and setting windows. But in real enterprises, the hard part isn’t generating text — it’s surviving the desegregation reality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Engineers in manufacturing inherit many systems with multiple issues: ERP sprawl across regions, unstructured truth hidden in emails, text files, spreadsheets, and notes, and complex data lineage where SKUs vary by region.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;集成现实&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当有人说“供应链的人工智能代理”时，人们很容易首先想到提示和设置窗口。但在真正的企业中，困难的部分不是生成文本，而是在废除种族隔离的现实中生存下来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;制造业工程师继承的许多系统存在多个问题：ERP 跨地区蔓延，电子邮件、文本文件、电子表格和注释中隐藏着非结构化事实，以及 SKU 因地区而异的复杂数据沿袭。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Token-Efficient RAG: Using Query Intent to Reduce Cost Without Losing Accuracy】令牌高效的 RAG：使用查询意图来降低成本而不损失准确性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/token-efficient-rag-using-query-intent-to-reduce-cost</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;605&#34; data-start=&#34;345&#34;&gt;In this article, we will examine the RAG optimization technique to reduce the number of tokens required to generate a response while maintaining response accuracy. Before we dig deeper into RAG, let us review a few basic terms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;648&#34; data-start=&#34;607&#34;&gt;What Is an LLM (Large Language Model)?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;910&#34; data-start=&#34;650&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-the-llm-landscape-a-comparative-analysi&#34;&gt;Large language models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; are very large deep learning models that are pre-trained on vast amounts of data. They are capable of performing tasks ranging from simple to complex, such as content generation, text classification, text mining, and summarization.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;605&#34; data-start=&#34;345&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将研究 RAG 优化技术，以减少生成响应所需的令牌数量，同时保持响应准确性。在深入研究 RAG 之前，让我们先回顾一下一些基本术语。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;648&#34; data-start=&#34;607&#34;&gt;什么是 LLM（大型语言模型）？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;910&#34; data-start=&#34;650&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-the-llm-landscape-a-comparative-analysi&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/a&gt; 是基于大量数据进行预训练的超大型深度学习模型。它们能够执行从简单到复杂的任务，例如内容生成、文本分类、文本挖掘和摘要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building SRE Error Budgets for AI/ML Workloads: A Practical Framework】为 AI/ML 工作负载构建 SRE 错误预算：实用框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-sre-error-budgets-for-ai-ml-workloads</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Here&#39;s a problem I&#39;ve seen happen far too often: your recommendation system is functioning, spitting out results in milliseconds, and meeting all its infrastructure SLAs. Everything is looking rosy in the dashboard world. Yet engagement has plummeted by 40% because your model has been pointless for several weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;On behalf of your traditional error budget? You&#39;re golden. According to your product team? The system is broken.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;这是我经常看到的一个问题：您的推荐系统正在运行，在几毫秒内给出结果，并满足其所有基础设施 SLA。仪表板世界中的一切看起来都很美好。然而，参与度却骤降了 40%，因为您的模型在几周内毫无意义。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;代表您传统的错误预算？你是金色的。根据您的产品团队的说法？系统坏了。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Global Payment Processors like Stripe and PayPal Use Apache Kafka and Flink to Scale】Stripe 和 PayPal 等全球支付处理器如何使用 Apache Kafka 和 Flink 进行扩展</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-global-payment-processors-use-apache</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;601&#34; data-start=&#34;228&#34;&gt;The recent announcement that Global Payments will acquire Worldpay for $22.7 billion has once again put the spotlight on the payment processing space. This move consolidates two giants and signals the growing importance of real-time, global payment infrastructure. But behind this shift is something deeper: data streaming has become the backbone of modern payment systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1021&#34; data-start=&#34;603&#34;&gt;From Stripe’s 99.9999% Kafka availability to PayPal streaming over a trillion events per day, and Payoneer replacing its existing message broker with data streaming, the world’s leading payment processors are redesigning their core systems around streaming technologies. Even companies like Worldline, which developed its own Apache Kafka management platform, have made Kafka central to their financial infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;601&#34; data-start=&#34;228&#34;&gt;最近宣布 Global Payments 将以 227 亿美元收购 Worldpay，再次让支付处理领域成为焦点。此举整合了两大巨头，标志着实时全球支付基础设施的重要性日益增长。但这种转变背后还有更深层次的原因：数据流已成为现代支付系统的支柱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1021&#34; data-start=&#34;603&#34;&gt;从 Stripe 99.9999% 的 Kafka 可用性到 PayPal 每天流式处理超过一万亿个事件，以及 Payoneer 用数据流取代其现有消息代理，全球领先的支付处理商正在围绕流技术重新设计其核心系统。即使是像 Worldline 这样开发了自己的 Apache Kafka 管理平台的公司，也将 Kafka 作为其金融基础设施的核心。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agentic Commerce: A Developer&#39;s Guide to Google&#39;s Universal Commerce Protocol (UCP)】代理商务：Google 通用商务协议 (UCP) 开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-commerce-arrives-a-developers-guide-to-goo</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;761&#34; data-start=&#34;225&#34;&gt;Online shopping just got its biggest upgrade in years. On January 11, 2026, Google CEO Sundar Pichai announced the Universal Commerce Protocol (UCP) at the National Retail Federation conference — a new open standard co-developed with Shopify, Walmart, Etsy, Target, Wayfair, and others (with endorsements from Stripe, Visa, Mastercard, and more). UCP is designed for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/your-next-customer-is-a-bot?fromrel=true&#34;&gt;era of agentic commerce&lt;/a&gt;, where AI agents handle the full shopping journey: discovery, comparison, cart management, discounts, checkout, and even post-purchase support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1135&#34; data-start=&#34;763&#34;&gt;No more humans clicking through tabs, managing carts, or entering payment details. Instead, AI agents act as trusted proxies, communicating directly with merchant systems via a standardized protocol. For developers and architects building e-commerce backends, integrations, or AI tools, this shift means rethinking how you expose data — not for human eyes, but for machines.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;761&#34; data-start=&#34;225&#34;&gt;在线购物刚刚经历了多年来最大的升级。 2026 年 1 月 11 日，Google 首席执行官 Sundar Pichai 在全国零售联合会会议上宣布了通用商业协议 (UCP)，这是与 Shopify、沃尔玛、Etsy、Target、Wayfair 等公司共同开发的新开放标准（得到了 Stripe、Visa、Mastercard 等公司的认可）。 UCP 专为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/your-next-customer-is-a-bot?fromrel=true&#34;&gt;代理商务时代&lt;/a&gt;而设计，其中人工智能代理处理完整的购物流程：发现、比较、购物车管理、折扣、结账，甚至购买后支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1135&#34; data-start=&#34;763&#34;&gt;不再需要人工点击标签、管理购物车或输入付款详细信息。相反，人工智能代理充当可信代理，通过标准化协议直接与商家系统通信。对于构建电子商务后端、集成或人工智能工具的开发人员和架构师来说，这种转变意味着重新思考如何公开数据——不是针对人眼，而是针对机器。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>