<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS Cloud Security: Key Components, Common Vulnerabilities, and Best Practices】AWS 云安全：关键组件、常见漏洞和最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cloud-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With organizations shifting at a rapid pace to the cloud, securing the infrastructure is of paramount importance in their list of priorities. Even though AWS provides a varied set of tools and services related to security and compliance. There are various other factors beyond security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Security is not just about tools but about strategy, vigilance, continuous improvement, and conformity to the industry &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-developers-guide-to-saas-compliance&#34;&gt;compliance standards for secure environments&lt;/a&gt;, including GDPR, HIPAA, and PCI DSS.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着组织快速转向云，保护基础设施在其优先事项中至关重要。尽管 AWS 提供了一系列与安全性和合规性相关的工具和服务。除了安全之外，还有各种其他因素。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;安全不仅仅与工具有关，还与策略、警惕性、持续改进和行业合规性有关 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-developers-guide-to-saas-compliance&#34; &gt;安全环境的合规标准&lt;/a&gt;，包括 GDPR、HIPAA 和 PCI DSS。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Efficient Artificial Intelligence: Training to Production】高效人工智能：培训到生产</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/efficient-artificial-intelligence</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the advancements in artificial intelligence (AI), the models are getting increasingly complex, resulting in increased size and latency, leading to difficulties in shipping models to production. Maintaining a balance between performance and efficiency is often a challenging task, and the faster and more lightweight you make your models, the further along they can be deployed into production. Training models on massive datasets with over a billion parameters results in high latency and is impractical for real-world use.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, we will be delving into techniques that can help make your model more efficient. These methods focus on reducing the models’ size and latency and making them ready for deployment without any significant degradation in performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着人工智能 (AI) 的进步，模型变得越来越复杂，导致尺寸和延迟增加，从而导致将模型交付生产变得困难。保持性能和效率之间的平衡通常是一项具有挑战性的任务，模型制作得越快、越轻量，它们就越能部署到生产中。在具有超过十亿个参数的海量数据集上训练模型会导致高延迟，并且对于实际使用来说是不切实际的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将深入研究有助于提高模型效率的技术。这些方法的重点是减少模型的大小和延迟，并使它们做好部署准备，而不会显着降低性能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【API and Security: From IT to Cyber】API 和安全：从 IT 到网络</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/api-amp-security-from-it-to-cyber</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The primary inspiration for this article was my feeling that unfortunately, IT and Cyber too often work in silos — with security constraints often poorly addressed or insufficiently shared. It was also inspired by meetings with people working in Cyber, who may recognize each other.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, on the IT side, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/api-security-patterns&#34;&gt;API security&lt;/a&gt; is often perceived as a subject that is covered as long as authentication and rights are properly managed and an API Gateway is used. Of course, this is necessary. But thinking about API security, in terms of what it involves, means thinking about a large part of the security of your IT.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本文的主要灵感来自于我的感觉，不幸的是，IT 和网络经常各自为政 — 安全限制往往得不到很好的解决或共享不足。它还受到与网络工作人员的会面的启发，他们可能会认识彼此。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;事实上，在 IT 方面，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/api-security-patterns&#34;&gt;API 安全性&lt;/a&gt;通常被视为只要满足以下条件即可涵盖的主题：身份验证和权限得到正确管理，并使用 API 网关。当然，这是必要的。但是，考虑 API 安全性（就其涉及的内容而言）意味着考虑 IT 安全性的很大一部分。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When (Tech Service) Relationships Don’t Work Out】当（技术服务）关系不成功时</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/when-tech-service-relationships-dont-work-out</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Think back to those days when you met the love of your life. The feeling was mutual. The world seemed like a better place, and you were on an exciting journey with your significant other. You were both “all-in” as you made plans for a life together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Life was amazing... until it wasn’t.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;回想一下您遇到一生挚爱的那些日子。这种感觉是相互的。世界似乎变得更加美好，你和你的另一半正在经历一段激动人心的旅程。当你们为共同的生活制定计划时，你们都“全力以赴”。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;生活本来就很精彩……直到它不再精彩。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Event-Driven Business Architecture】事件驱动的业务架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/event-driven-business-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&#34;Event-driven business architecture&#34; is the idea of a software architecture that centers business applications on events and processes. In the following, I will explain its core concepts and describe how building business applications around events can enhance architectural flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is an Event?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When we talk about &#34;event-driven business architecture,&#34; one of the first questions that naturally arises is: what exactly is an event? Let’s examine the characteristics of an event in detail.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;“事件驱动的业务架构”是一种以事件和流程为中心的业务应用程序的软件架构理念。下面我将解释其核心概念，并描述围绕事件构建业务应用程序如何增强架构灵活性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是事件？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们谈论“事件驱动的业务架构”时，自然出现的第一个问题是：事件到底是什么？让我们详细研究一下事件的特征。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visualizing the Air Quality Index (AQI) Across Punjab, Pakistan, and India】旁遮普邦、巴基斯坦和印度的空气质量指数 (AQI) 可视化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/visualizing-aqi-across-punjab</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Air pollution has become a pressing issue in South Asia with recent reports from major news outlets, such as the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cm20k76d5xno&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;BBC&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://edition.cnn.com/2024/11/11/asia/pakistan-punjab-pollution-satellite-images-climate-intl-hnk/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CNN&lt;/a&gt;, highlighting Lahore in Pakistan as a city struggling with critically poor air quality. Using open data from IQAir, this article plots the Air Quality Index (AQI) for Lahore and expands the analysis to include other locations within Punjab, covering cities in both Pakistan and India. By visualizing AQI levels across these areas, we can shed light on the air pollution crisis, its implications, and potential areas for environmental intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The notebook file used in this article is available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/iqair-demo&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;空气污染已成为南亚的一个紧迫问题，主要新闻媒体最近进行了报道，例如&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cm20k76d5xno&#34; target=&#34; _blank&#34;&gt;BBC&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://edition.cnn.com/2024/11/11/asia/pakistan-punjab-pollution-satellite-images-climate-intl-hnk/index.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CNN&lt;/ a&gt;，强调巴基斯坦的拉合尔是一个空气质量极差的城市。本文使用 IQAir 的开放数据绘制了拉合尔的空气质量指数 (AQI)，并将分析范围扩展到旁遮普省的其他地点，涵盖巴基斯坦和印度的城市。通过可视化这些地区的 AQI 水平，我们可以揭示空气污染危机、其影响以及环境干预的潜在领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文中使用的笔记本文件可在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/iqair-demo&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; 上找到。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scholcast: Generating Academic Paper Summaries With AI-Driven Audio】Scholcast：使用人工智能驱动的音频生成学术论文摘要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generating-academic-paper-summaries-with-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Keeping up with the latest research is a critical part of the job for most data scientists. Faced with this challenge myself, I often struggled to maintain a consistent habit of reading academic papers and wondered if I could design a system that would lower the barrier to exploring new research making it easier to engage with developments in my field without the need for extensive time commitments. Given my long commute to work and an innate lack of motivation to perform weekend chores, an audio playlist that I could listen to while doing both sounded like the obvious option.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This led me to build Scholcast, a simple &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-python&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; package that creates detailed audio summaries of academic papers. While I had previously built versions using language models, the recent advancements in expanded context lengths for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-transformer-algorithm-data-and-attention&#34;&gt;Transformers&lt;/a&gt; and improved vocalization finally aligned with all my requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;跟上最新研究的步伐对于大多数数据科学家来说是工作的重要组成部分。面对这一挑战，我经常努力保持阅读学术论文的一贯习惯，并想知道我是否可以设计一个系统来降低探索新研究的障碍，从而更容易地参与我的领域的发展，而不需要广泛的研究时间承诺。考虑到我上班的时间很长，而且天生缺乏做周末家务的动力，所以我可以在做这两件事的同时听音频播放列表，这听起来是显而易见的选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;这促使我构建了 Scholcast，这是一个简单的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-python&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; 包，可以创建详细的学术音频摘要文件。虽然我之前使用语言模型构建了版本，但最近在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-transformer-algorithm-data-and-attention&#34;&gt;Transformer&lt;/a 扩展上下文长度方面取得了进展&gt; 改进的发声终于符合我的所有要求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top 5 Key Features of Apache Iceberg for Modern Data Lakes】适用于现代数据湖的 Apache Iceberg 的 5 大主要功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/key-features-of-apache-iceberg-for-data-lakes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Big data has significantly evolved since its inception in the late 2000s. Many organizations quickly adapted to the trend and built their big data platforms using open-source tools like Apache Hadoop. Later, these companies started facing trouble managing the rapidly evolving data processing needs. They have faced challenges handling schema level changes, partition scheme evolution, and going back in time to look at the data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I faced similar challenges while designing large-scale &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolution-of-distributed-systems&#34;&gt;distributed systems back in the 2010s&lt;/a&gt; for a big tech company and a healthcare customer. Some industries need these capabilities to adhere to banking, finance, and healthcare regulations. Heavy data-driven companies like Netflix faced similar challenges as well. They invented a table format called &#34;Iceberg,&#34; which sits on top of the existing data files and delivers key features by leveraging its architecture. This has quickly become the top ASF project as it gained rapid interest in the data community. I will explore the top 5 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-iceberg&#34;&gt;Apache Iceberg&lt;/a&gt; key features in this article with examples and diagrams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大数据自 2000 年代末诞生以来已经发生了显着的发展。许多组织迅速适应了这一趋势，并使用 Apache Hadoop 等开源工具构建了自己的大数据平台。后来，这些公司开始在管理快速变化的数据处理需求方面遇到困难。他们面临着处理架构级别更改、分区方案演变以及及时返回查看数据的挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;早在 2010 年代，我在设计大型&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolution-of-distributed-systems&#34;&gt;分布式系统&lt;/a&gt;时就遇到了类似的挑战大型科技公司和医疗保健客户。一些行业需要这些功能来遵守银行、金融和医疗保健法规。像 Netflix 这样的重数据驱动型公司也面临着类似的挑战。他们发明了一种名为“Iceberg”的表格格式，它位于现有数据文件之上，并通过利用其架构提供关键功能。由于它在数据社区中引起了快速兴趣，它已迅速成为 ASF 的顶级项目。我将通过示例和图表探索本文中 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-iceberg&#34;&gt;Apache Iceberg&lt;/a&gt; 的 5 个主要功能。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating AWS Infrastructure Testing With Terratest】使用 Terratest 自动化 AWS 基础设施测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/terratest-for-aws</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Organizations adopting Infrastructure as Code (IaC) on AWS often struggle with ensuring that their infrastructure is not only correctly provisioned but also functioning as intended once deployed. Even minor misconfigurations can lead to costly downtime, security vulnerabilities, or performance issues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional testing methods — such as manually inspecting resources or relying solely on static code analysis — do not provide sufficient confidence for production environments. There is a pressing need for an automated, reliable way to validate &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/API-Gateway-using-cloudformation-template&#34;&gt;AWS infrastructure&lt;/a&gt; changes before they go live.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在 AWS 上采用基础设施即代码 (IaC) 的组织常常难以确保其基础设施不仅能够正确配置，而且在部署后也能按预期运行。即使是轻微的配置错误也可能导致代价高昂的停机、安全漏洞或性能问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统的测试方法（例如手动检查资源或仅依赖静态代码分析）无法为生产环境提供足够的信心。迫切需要一种自动化、可靠的方法来在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/API-Gateway-using-cloudformation-template&#34;&gt;AWS 基础设施&lt;/a&gt;更改上线之前对其进行验证.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dev Home and Dev Boxes: Revolutionizing Developer Environments】开发主页和开发盒：彻底改变开发人员环境</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dev-home-and-dev-boxes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The efficiency and productivity of developers greatly depend on the tools and environments they use. Creating traditional development environments has been a time-consuming process, which results in errors due to inconsistencies across teams and projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, with the introduction of Dev Home and Dev Boxes, developers can now have solutions that simplify the setup and management of development environments quickly. This article delves into the concept of Dev Home and Dev Boxes, their advantages, and how they could revolutionize how developers work.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;开发人员的效率和生产力很大程度上取决于他们使用的工具和环境。创建传统的开发环境是一个耗时的过程，并且由于团队和项目之间的不一致而导致错误。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，随着 Dev Home 和 Dev Boxes 的推出，开发人员现在可以拥有快速简化开发环境设置和管理的解决方案。本文深入探讨了 Dev Home 和 Dev Boxes 的概念、它们的优势以及它们如何彻底改变开发人员的工作方式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>