<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Enabling Risk Management With AI/ML Powered by Cloud Native Data Architecture】用云原生数据体系结构提供的AI/ML启用风险管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/risk-management-ai-ml-cloud-native-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Financial crimes are a persistent threat to financial institutions. Financial institutions have to build risk management systems that can detect and prevent malicious activities. The evolution of cloud computing has enabled leveraging computing power for machine learning in risk management functions like anti-money laundering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Risk management in financial institutions will primarily focus on identifying, assessing, maintaining, and monitoring various risks. This is very important to ensure compliance with regulatory requirements and stability of the institution to maintain investor confidence. Each institution will have its own structure and process to define adherence to different types of risk functions. Most of the risk functions will involve the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;金融犯罪是对金融机构的持续威胁。金融机构必须建立可以检测和防止恶意活动的风险管理系统。云计算的演变使在风险管理功能中利用计算能力，例如反洗钱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;金融机构的风险管理主要集中在识别，评估，维护和监视各种风险上。这对于确保遵守机构维持投资者信心的监管要求和稳定性非常重要。每个机构将拥有自己的结构和过程，以定义遵守不同类型的风险功能。大多数风险功能将涉及以下步骤：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multi-Cloud Infrastructure Challenges and Solutions】多云基础架构挑战和解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/multi-cloud-infrastructure-challenges-solutions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The cloud landscape has changed so much, with companies moving to multi-cloud.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://info.flexera.com/CM-REPORT-State-of-the-Cloud&#34;&gt;According to Flexera’s 2024 State of the Cloud Report&lt;/a&gt;, 87% of companies are using multiple cloud providers for resilience, cost optimization, and vendor independence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But managing infrastructure across AWS, Azure, Google Cloud, and other providers brings configuration drift, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-security-vulnerabilities-a-first-ste&#34;&gt;security vulnerabilities&lt;/a&gt;, and cost overruns that can overwhelm IT teams.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;云景观发生了很大变化，公司转向多云。 &lt;a href =“ https://info.flexera.com/cm-report-state-of-the-cloud”&gt;根据Flexera的2024年2024年云报告&lt;/a&gt;，有87％的公司在使用多个云提供者来进行弹性，成本优化，并优化供应商。&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;但在AWS，Azure，Google Cloud和其他提供商跨管理基础架构会带来配置漂移，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/artecting-security-security-vulnerability-vulnerabilities-a-firnerabilities-a-firste-first-ste--first-s-first--firste”</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 12:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Big Data to Agents: My Decade Building Systems】从大数据到代理：我的十年建筑系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/big-data-to-agents-decade-building-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;When a Simple Scraper Changed Everything&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My first “real” task wasn’t glamorous: &lt;strong&gt;scrape some data&lt;/strong&gt;. We all start at the bottom, and scraping is a rite of passage for data engineers — turning unstructured sources into structured signals. That first job taught me a lesson I’ve carried since 2014/15: access to the right data beats cleverness — and the right pattern beats the shiniest tool.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking back at that moment — and the path since — this article traces how I entered the data world and what changed up to today’s AI revolution.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;当简单的刮板更改一切&lt;/h2&gt;时&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我的第一个“真实”任务并不迷人：&lt;strong&gt;刮擦一些数据&lt;/strong&gt;。我们都从底部开始，刮擦是数据工程师的通道 - 将非结构化源变成结构化信号。这份工作教会了我自2014/15年以来上课的一堂课：访问正确的数据胜过聪明 - 正确的模式击败了最明亮的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;回顾那一刻 - 以及以来的道路 - 这篇文章追溯了我进入数据世界的方式以及变为今天的AI革命的原因。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing the Model Context Protocol (MCP): New AI Security Risks in Agentic Workflows】确保模型上下文协议（MCP）：代理工作流程中的新AI安全风险</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mcp-ai-security-risks-agentic-workflows</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;, introduced in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;late 2024&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, is a significant move forward towards transforming&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;the agentic AI&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;revolution by providing a mechanism for them to connect with enterprise tools, APIs, and databases.&lt;/span&gt; The protocol presents a standardized way &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;for large&lt;/span&gt; language models (LLMs) and business workflows to communicate with business systems, databases, APIs, and even development environments. Just as Open Database Connectivity (ODBC) standardized access to databases, MCP offers a standard way for AI agents to interact with data and applications across an enterprise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, as &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/model-context-protocol-mcp-guide-architecture-uses-implementation&#34;&gt;MCP is adopted across organizations&lt;/a&gt;, we are also seeing the introduction of new types of security risks that did not exist before. The same abilities that make MCP so powerful, such as bidirectional communication, agentic features, tool descriptions, etc., all introduce a new threat landscape that cybersecurity professionals may not be ready for.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;模型上下文协议（MCP）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;，在&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; 2024年末&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;中引入的&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt;，是向转换&lt;/span&gt;转换&lt;/span&gt;通过为它们提供与企业工具相关的机制来转换&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; pastect &lt;/span&gt;的范围&lt;/span&gt; paste &lt;/span sandent apis and span =/span apen span &lt;/span &lt;/span &lt;/span &lt;/span &lt;/ 0px;填充：0px;“&gt;对于大型语言模型（LLM）和业务工作流程，以与业务系统，数据库，API甚至开发环境进行通信。就像开放数据库连接（ODBC）对数据库的标准化访问一样，MCP也为AI代理与跨企业进行与数据和应用程序进行交互的标准方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，如&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/model-context-protocol-mcp-guide-architecture-restecture-uss-implementation”&gt; MCP在整个组织中都采用了MCP &lt;/a&gt;，我们还看到了以前不存在的新型安全风险的引入。同样的能力使MCP如此强大，例如双向交流，代理功能，工具描述等，都引入了一个新的威胁景观，网络安全专业人员可能无法做好准备。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Testing Updates in Insert-Only Ledger Tables and Understanding Updates in Updatable Ledger Tables】在仅插入分类帐中的测试更新，并了解更新的分类帐表中的更新</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sql-server-ledger-table-updates-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In SQL Server, ledger tables offer powerful tamper-evident functionality, which is essential for systems that require high levels of trust and auditability. Two distinct types serve different needs: &lt;strong&gt;insert-only ledger tables&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;updatable ledger tables&lt;/strong&gt;. Insert-only tables enforce strict immutability, allowing data to be added but never altered or deleted, making them ideal for transaction logs or event sourcing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, updatable ledger tables permit modifications and deletions while meticulously maintaining a cryptographically verifiable history of all changes, much like a blockchain. This article provides a hands-on demonstration of these principles. We will test update operations against insert-only tables to confirm their constraints and then explore how updates are seamlessly and transparently managed in updatable ledger tables, complete with practical examples.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在SQL Server中，分类帐桌提供了功能强大的篡改功能，这对于需要高水平的信任和可审核性的系统至关重要。两种不同的类型满足不同的需求：&lt;strong&gt;仅插入分类账表&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;可更新的分类帐表&lt;/strong&gt;。仅插入表可执行严格的不可超数性，允许添加数据但从未更改或删除数据，使其非常适合交易日志或事件采购。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;相反，可更新的分类账表可以修改和删除，同时精心维护所有更改的密码可验证的历史记录，就像区块链一样。本文提供了这些原则的动手演示。我们将针对仅插入表测试更新操作，以确认其约束，然后探索如何在可更新的分类帐表中无缝和透明地管理更新，并提供实际示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Infrastructure Guide: Tools, Frameworks, and Architecture Flows】AI基础设施指南：工具，框架和架构流动</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-infrastructure-guide-tools-frameworks-and-archi</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Building robust AI infrastructure requires understanding both the theoretical foundations and practical implementation details across multiple layers of technology. This comprehensive guide provides the definitive resource for architecting, deploying, and managing AI systems at any scale — from experimental prototypes to enterprise-grade production deployments serving millions of users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern AI applications demand sophisticated infrastructure that can handle the computational intensity of large language models, the complexity of multi-agent systems, and the real-time requirements of interactive applications. The challenge lies not just in selecting the right tools, but in understanding how they integrate across the entire technology stack to deliver reliable, scalable, and cost-effective solutions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;构建强大的AI基础架构需要了解多层技术层的理论基础和实际实施细节。该综合指南为架构，部署和管理AI系统提供了确定的资源 - 从实验原型到为数百万用户提供服务的企业级生产部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代AI应用程序需要复杂的基础架构，该基础架构可以处理大型语言模型的计算强度，多代理系统的复杂性以及交互式应用程序的实时要求。挑战不仅在于选择正确的工具，还在于了解它们如何在整个技术堆栈中集成以提供可靠，可扩展和成本效益的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building ML Platforms for Real-Time Integrity】构建实时完整性的ML平台</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ml-platforms-for-real-time-integrity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Large-scale social networks face a universal challenge: maintaining safe and reliable environments as user traffic grows exponentially. Manual processes often break under load, while ad-hoc machine learning models frequently fail to generalize. This article explores how a large-scale platform could address the challenge by developing a comprehensive machine learning infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Single filters or stand-alone models rarely survive long at scale.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;大规模的社交网络面临一个普遍的挑战：随着用户流量的成倍增长，保持安全可靠的环境。手动过程通常会在负载下破裂，而临时机器学习模型通常无法概括。本文探讨了大型平台如何通过开发全面的机器学习基础架构来应对挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;单个过滤器或独立模型很少在大规模生存。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Scalable and Reliable Marketing Data Stack on GCP】在GCP上构建可扩展可靠的营销数据堆栈</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scalable-reliable-marketing-data-stack-gcp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Creative campaigns are no longer modern marketing; data is. And not any data: clean, contextual, and timely data that fuels specific, personalised experiences that enable quantifiable outcomes. If you have dozens (or hundreds) of campaigns running across platforms such as Google Ads, Meta, and programmatic DSPs, the infrastructure that enables this orchestration is just as important as the insights themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today, scaling a marketing data stack is not about selecting a BI tool or lifting a few datasets to the cloud. It’s about architecting a resilient foundation on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-iam-in-google-cloud-platform-gcp&#34;&gt;GCP&lt;/a&gt; that can ingest campaign data from multiple sources, support time-zone distributed teams, and power real-time dashboards, all while maintaining governance and operational reliability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;创意活动不再是现代营销；数据是。而不是任何数据：清洁，上下文和及时的数据，这些数据为可以量化的结果提供了特定的个性化体验。如果您在Google广告，元和程序化DSP等平台上进行了数十个（或数百个）广告系列，那么使该编排的基础架构与见解本身一样重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;今天，缩放营销数据堆栈并不是要选择BI工具或将几个数据集提升到云。这是关于在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to--iam-in------------------------platform-gcp-&gt; gcp”&gt; gcp &lt;/a&gt;上可以从多个来源中吸收活动数据，在支持时间Zone的分布式dashboards and/containity plational collance &lt;/a&gt; gcp &lt;/a&gt;上，在&lt;a href =“</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Infrastructure as Code (IaC) in a Multi-Cloud Environment: Consistency and Security Issues】在多云环境中作为代码（IAC）的基础架构：一致性和安全问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/iac-multi-cloud-consistency-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevance of the Study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Modern organizations are increasingly turning to cloud technologies to improve the flexibility, scalability, and efficiency of their IT infrastructure. One important tool in this process is Infrastructure as Code (IaC), which allows organizations to describe their infrastructure using code, automate the deployment process, reduce the risk of human error, and ensure consistency across different stages of the application lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, there is a trend towards multi-cloud architectures, where companies use multiple cloud providers to spread the load, improve fault tolerance, and comply with security and data localization regulations. This approach allows organizations to take advantage of the benefits of different cloud providers while minimizing the risks associated with a single provider.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;研究的相关性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现代组织越来越多地转向云技术，以提高其IT基础架构的灵活性，可扩展性和效率。此过程中的一个重要工具是基础架构作为代码（IAC），它允许组织使用代码来描述其基础架构，自动化部署过程，减少人为错误的风险，并确保应用程序生命周期的不同阶段的一致性。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，多云体系结构有一种趋势，在该架构中，公司使用多个云提供商来扩大负载，提高容错的承受能力，并遵守安全性和数据本地化规定。这种方法使组织可以利用不同云提供商的好处，同时最大程度地减少与单个提供商相关的风险。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unpack IPTables: Its Inner Workings With Commands and Demos】打开iptables：它的内部运作，带有命令和演示</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unpack-iptables-inner-workings-commands-demos</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We all know that the internet works by sending and receiving small chunks of data called &lt;strong&gt;packets&lt;/strong&gt;. Back in the early days, when the internet was still in its infancy, packets were allowed to transfer freely across a connected world, however small that world was. Anyone could send packets to your system, and you could send packets to other connected systems. All services running on systems were exposed by default.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the internet started to grow, problems started to emerge, problems related to security. There are worms, viruses, unauthorized access, denial-of-service (DoS) attacks, IP spoofing, etc. Iptables is an attempt to deal with some of these problems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们都知道，互联网是通过发送和接收&lt;strong&gt;数据包&lt;/strong&gt;的少量数据来工作的。早期，当互联网仍处于起步阶段时，允许包装包在一个连接的世界中自由转移，无论世界多么小。任何人都可以将数据包发送到您的系统，您可以将数据包发送到其他连接的系统。默认情况下，所有在系统上运行的服务均已公开。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着互联网开始增长，问题开始出现，与安全有关。有蠕虫，病毒，未经授权的访问，拒绝服务（DOS）攻击，IP欺骗等。Iptables是一种尝试处理其中一些问题的尝试。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>