<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Successful Companies Don&#39;t Have DBAs】为什么成功的公司没有 DBA</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-successful-companies-dont-have-dbas</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Database administrators play a crucial role in our organizations. They manage databases, monitor performance, and address issues as they arise. However, consider the possibility that their current role may be problematic and that we need to rethink how they operate and integrate within our organizations. Successful companies do not have DBAs. Continue reading to find out why.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;DBAs Make Teamwork Harder&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the problems with having a separate team of DBAs is that it can unintentionally push other teams into silos and kill all the teamwork. Let&#39;s explore why this happens.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;数据库管理员在我们的组织中发挥着至关重要的作用。他们管理数据库、监控性能并解决出现的问题。然而，请考虑他们当前的角色可能存在问题的可能性，我们需要重新考虑他们如何在我们的组织中运作和整合。成功的公司没有DBA。继续阅读以找出原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;DBA 让团队合作变得更加困难&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;拥有一个单独的 DBA 团队的问题之一是，它可能会无意中将其他团队推入孤岛并破坏所有团队合作。让我们探讨一下为什么会发生这种情况。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Globalization Testing: The Key to Reaching Users Around the World】全球化测试：接触全球用户的关键</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/globalization-testing-reaching-users-around-the-world</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Imagine launching your cutting-edge app, only to see it falter in a key international market due to unreadable characters or culturally insensitive visuals. Frustrating, right? Now, every tech company dreams of becoming a global fan favorite.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While a big part of this is having a top-notch software product, it also demands understanding and meeting the unique expectations of users across diverse geographies.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;想象一下，推出您的尖端应用程序，却发现它由于难以阅读的字符或对文化不敏感的视觉效果而在关键的国际市场上举步维艰。令人沮丧，对吧？现在，每家科技公司都梦想成为全球粉丝的最爱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然其中很大一部分是拥有一流的软件产品，但它也需要了解并满足不同地区用户的独特期望。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Evolution of Adaptive Frameworks】自适应框架的演变</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-evolution-of-adaptive-frameworks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;3:1-3:405&#34;&gt;Collaboration tools are rapidly evolving to meet modern demands. Adaptive frameworks stand out by delivering real-time, personalized updates tailored to individual users. These frameworks overcome the rigidity of traditional systems, enhancing efficiency, fostering innovation, and transforming industries like healthcare, education, and remote work. This paper delves into their technical principles, practical applications, and future potential, illustrating how adaptive frameworks redefine collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The inefficiencies of traditional collaboration tools — static interfaces, impersonal workflows, and delayed updates — have long hindered productivity in critical scenarios. Imagine a teacher unable to adapt lesson plans in real time or a healthcare team relying on outdated patient data during an emergency. These limitations disrupt workflows and stifle innovation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;3:1-3:405&#34;&gt;协作工具正在迅速发展以满足现代需求。自适应框架通过提供针对个人用户量身定制的实时、个性化更新而脱颖而出。这些框架克服了传统系统的僵化，提高了效率，促进了创新，并改变了医疗保健、教育和远程工作等行业。本文深入探讨了它们的技术原理、实际应用和未来潜力，说明了自适应框架如何重新定义协作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简介&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统协作工具的低效率（静态界面、非个性化工作流程和延迟更新）长期以来一直阻碍着关键场景中的生产力。想象一下，教师无法实时调整课程计划，或者医疗团队在紧急情况下依赖过时的患者数据。这些限制扰乱了工作流程并扼杀了创新。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python Automation Testing With Examples】Python 自动化测试示例</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-automation-testing-with-examples</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When it comes to automating front-end tests, choosing the ideal programming language becomes extremely crucial. Python is one such language that tops the list, owing to ease of use and extensive community support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-tutorial-for-beginners-a-comprehensive-guid&#34;&gt;Python automation testing&lt;/a&gt; lets you harness the capabilities offered by popular libraries and frameworks like Selenium, pytest, and Robot, amongst others. Using Selenium with Python helps in making the most of Selenium’s powerful browser automation capabilities and Python’s simplicity and extensibility. Overall, Python automation testing is widely used by QAs all over, especially with Selenium WebDriver.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当谈到自动化前端测试时，选择理想的编程语言变得极其重要。 Python 是一种位居榜首的语言，因为它易于使用且具有广泛的社区支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-tutorial-for-beginners-a-compressive-guid&#34;&gt;Python 自动化测试&lt;/a&gt;可让您利用流行的工具提供的功能Selenium、pytest 和 Robot 等库和框架。将 Selenium 与 Python 结合使用有助于充分利用 Selenium 强大的浏览器自动化功能以及 Python 的简单性和可扩展性。总体而言，Python 自动化测试被各地的 QA 广泛使用，尤其是 Selenium WebDriver。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Rust Command Line Interface to Chat With Llama 3.2】构建 Rust 命令行界面来与 Llama 3.2 聊天</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-a-rust-command-line-interface-to-chat-with-llama-32</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As a developer learning Rust, I wanted to build a practical project to apply my new skills. With the rise of large language models like Anthropic&#39;s Llama 3.2, I thought it would be interesting to create a Rust command line interface (CLI) to interact with the model.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In just a couple of minutes, I was able to put together a working CLI using the Ollama Rust library. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/secrets-at-the-command-line-cheat-sheet-included&#34;&gt;CLI&lt;/a&gt;, which I call &#34;Jarvis,&#34; allows you to chat with Llama 3.2, as well as perform some basic commands like checking the time, date, and listing directory contents.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为一名学习 Rust 的开发人员，我想构建一个实用的项目来应用我的新技能。随着像 Anthropic 的 Llama 3.2 这样的大型语言模型的兴起，我认为创建一个 Rust 命令行界面 (CLI) 来与模型交互会很有趣。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在短短几分钟内，我就能够使用 Ollama Rust 库构建一个可工作的 CLI。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/secrets-at-the-command-line-cheat-sheet-included&#34;&gt;CLI&lt;/a&gt;（我称之为“Jarvis”）允许您聊天使用 Llama 3.2，以及执行一些基本命令，例如检查时间、日期和列出目录内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Emerging Mobile Threats and Defensive Strategies for Developers】新兴的移动威胁和开发人员的防御策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mobile-threats-and-defensive-strategies-for-developers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Mobile applications have become indispensable across industries, from banking to healthcare. However, their rapid growth has led to an equally fast increase in security threats. The problem lies in the increasing sophistication of attacks on mobile platforms, the rising volume of data breaches, and the inadequate implementation of security measures during app development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Supporting Data&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Mobile Malware&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;According to Statista, the number of unique mobile malware files detected globally increased from 8.5 million in 2019 to 11.5 million in 2022.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Over 60% of mobile users reportedly fall victim to phishing scams annually.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financial Impact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The 2024 Cybersecurity Ventures Report predicts cybercrime damages could reach $10.5 trillion annually by 2025, with mobile threats constituting a significant portion.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;移动应用程序已成为从银行到医疗保健等各个行业不可或缺的一部分。然而，它们的快速增长导致安全威胁同样快速增加。问题在于移动平台的攻击日益复杂、数据泄露数量不断增加以及应用开发过程中安全措施落实不到位。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;支持数据&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;全球移动恶意软件&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;根据 Statista 的数据，全球检测到的独特移动恶意软件文件数量从 2019 年的 850 万个增加到 2022 年的 1150 万个。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;据报道，每年有超过 60% 的移动用户成为网络钓鱼诈骗的受害者。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;财务影响&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li 目录=“ltr”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;2024 年网络安全风险报告预测，到 2025 年，网络犯罪每年造成的损失可能达到 10.5 万亿美元，其中移动威胁占很大一部分。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Kubernetes Workload Rightsizing With StormForge】使用 StormForge 自动调整 Kubernetes 工作负载大小</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-kubernetes-workload-rightsizing-with-stormforge</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As Kubernetes workloads grow in complexity, ensuring optimal resource utilization while maintaining performance becomes a significant challenge. Over-provisioning leads to wasted costs, while under-provisioning can degrade application performance. StormForge offers a machine learning-driven approach to automate workload rightsizing, helping teams strike the perfect balance between cost and performance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article provides a comprehensive guide to implementing StormForge for Kubernetes workload optimization.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着 Kubernetes 工作负载复杂性的增加，在保持性能的同时确保最佳资源利用率成为一项重大挑战。过度配置会导致成本浪费，而配置不足则会降低应用程序性能。 StormForge 提供了一种机器学习驱动的方法来自动调整工作负载，帮助团队在成本和性能之间取得完美平衡。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文提供了实施 StormForge 来优化 Kubernetes 工作负载的综合指南。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Achieving Security and Trust in a Data Fabric: The Role of Zero Trust Architecture】在 Data Fabric 中实现安全性和信任：零信任架构的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/achieving-security-and-trust-in-a-data-fabric-zta</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Organizations face the growing challenge of managing, protecting, and governing data across diverse environments. As data flows through hybrid cloud systems, multi-cloud environments, and on-premises infrastructures, maintaining a cohesive, secure data ecosystem has become a complicated and daunting affair.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A promising solution to this challenge is &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-data-fabric-architecture-a-comprehens&#34;&gt;the concept of a data fabric&lt;/a&gt; — a unified, integrated layer that provides seamless access, management, and governance across disparate data sources. However, ensuring the security and integrity of data within this unconventional framework requires an equally unconventional approach to security. In this article, I’d like to discuss how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/harnessing-security-by-adopting-zero-trust-archite&#34;&gt;Zero Trust Architecture (ZTA)&lt;/a&gt; can provide a solid foundation for achieving security and trust in a data fabric.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;组织面临着跨不同环境管理、保护和治理数据的日益严峻的挑战。随着数据流经混合云系统、多云环境和本地基础设施，维护一个有凝聚力、安全的数据生态系统已成为一件复杂而艰巨的事情。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;应对这一挑战的一个有希望的解决方案是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-data-fabric-architecture-a-comprehens&#34;&gt;数据结构的概念&lt; /a&gt; — 一个统一的集成层，提供跨不同数据源的无缝访问、管理和治理。然而，在这个非常规框架内确保数据的安全性和完整性需要同样非常规的安全方法。在本文中，我想讨论如何&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/harnessing-security-by-adopting-zero-trust-archite&#34;&gt;零信任架构 (ZTA)&lt;/a &gt; 可以为实现数据结构的安全性和信任提供坚实的基础。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Efficiently Processing Billions of Rows Daily With Presto】使用 Presto 每天高效处理数十亿行</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/processing-billions-of-rows-daily-with-presto</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In a world where companies rely heavily on data for insights about their performance, potential issues, and areas for improvement, logging comprehensively is crucial, but it comes at a cost. If not stored properly it can become cumbersome to maintain, query, and overall expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Logging detailed user activities like time spent on various apps, which interface where they are active, navigation path, app start-up times, crash reports, country of login, etc. could be vital in understanding user behaviors — but we can easily end up with billions of rows of data, which can quickly become an issue if scalable solutions are not implemented at the time of logging.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在一个公司严重依赖数据来了解其绩效、潜在问题和需要改进的领域的世界中，全面的日志记录至关重要，但这是有代价的。如果存储不当，维护、查询可能会变得很麻烦，而且总体成本高昂。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;记录详细的用户活动，例如在各种应用程序上花费的时间、它们处于活动状态的界面、导航路径、应用程序启动时间、崩溃报告、登录国家/地区等对于了解用户至关重要行为 - 但我们很容易最终得到数十亿行数据，如果在日志记录时未实施可扩展的解决方案，这很快就会成为一个问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Setting Up Local Kafka Container for Spring Boot Application】为 Spring Boot 应用程序设置本地 Kafka 容器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/setting-up-local-kafka-container-for-spring-boot-application</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s microservices and event-driven architecture, Apache Kafka is the de facto for streaming applications. However, setting up Kafka for local development in conjunction with your Spring Boot application can be tricky, especially when configuring it to run locally.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-framework-tutorials&#34;&gt;Spring Boot application&lt;/a&gt; provides support for Kafka integration through the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;spring-kafka&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; maven package. To work with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;spring-kafka&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, we need to connect to the Kafka instance. Typically, during development, we would just run a local Kafka instance and build against it. But with Docker Desktop and containers, things are much easier to set up than running a local Kafka instance. This article guides us through the steps for setting up the local Kafka container with the Spring Boot application. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的微服务和事件驱动架构中，Apache Kafka 是流应用程序的事实。然而，设置 Kafka 与 Spring Boot 应用程序结合进行本地开发可能会很棘手，特别是在将其配置为本地运行时。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-framework-tutorials&#34;&gt;Spring Boot 应用程序&lt;/a&gt;通过&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;spring-kafka 提供对 Kafka 集成的支持&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; maven 包。要使用 &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;spring-kafka&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;，我们需要连接到 Kafka 实例。通常，在开发过程中，我们只会运行一个本地 Kafka 实例并针对它进行构建。但使用 Docker Desktop 和容器，设置比运行本地 Kafka 实例要容易得多。本文指导我们完成使用 Spring Boot 应用程序设置本地 Kafka 容器的步骤。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>