<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Self-Compassion in Tech Teams: Building Strength and Teamwork】技术团队的自我同情心：增强力量和团队合作</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/self-compassion-in-technical-teams</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Tech teams have a hard job. They deal with tight deadlines and tough problems. This can cause stress and self-criticism. But being kind to yourself can help. Self-compassion makes you feel better. It also helps the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-improve-team-performance-11-effective-ways&#34;&gt;team work better&lt;/a&gt; together. This guide will explain what self-compassion is. It will also show why it’s good for tech teams and how to use it at work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Self-Compassion for Tech Teams&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Self-compassion is like being your own supportive friend. When things go wrong or you make mistakes, instead of being hard on yourself, treat yourself kindly. For tech teams, this means understanding hard tasks and handling mistakes gently. It helps you stay calm and focused. Dr. Kristin Neff talks about three parts of self-compassion:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;技术团队的工作很艰巨。他们要处理紧迫的期限和棘手的问题。这可能会导致压力和自我批评。但善待自己会有帮助。自我同情会让你感觉更好。它还有助于&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-improve-team-performance-11- effective-ways&#34;&gt;团队更好地合作&lt;/a&gt;。本指南将解释什么是自我同情。它还将展示为什么它对技术团队有好处以及如何在工作中使用它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;技术团队的自我同情心&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自我同情就像成为你自己支持的朋友一样。当事情出错或犯错误时，不要对自己太苛刻，而是善待自己。对于技术团队来说，这意味着理解艰巨的任务并温和地处理错误。它可以帮助您保持冷静和专注。克里斯汀·内夫博士谈论了自我慈悲的三个部分：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Interference in A/B Tests】A/B 测试中的干扰</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/interference-in-ab-tests</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A/B testing is the gold standard for online experimentation used by most companies to test out their product features. Whereas A/B test experimentation works just fine in most settings, it is particularly susceptible to interference bias, particularly in the case of online marketplaces or social networks. In this article, we aim to look at the situations with interference bias and some potential ways to mitigate its effect on evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;SUTVA, the Fundamental Assumption of A/B Testing and Its Violations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;One of the fundamental assumptions of A/B Testing is SUTVA — Stable Unit Treatment Value Assumption. The potential outcome of treatment in the randomization unit depends only on the treatment they receive and not on the treatments assigned to other subjects.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A/B 测试是大多数公司用来测试其产品功能的在线实验的黄金标准。尽管 A/B 测试实验在大多数情况下效果都很好，但它特别容易受到干扰偏差的影响，尤其是在在线市场或社交网络的情况下。在本文中，我们旨在研究存在干扰偏差的情况以及减轻其对评估影响的一些潜在方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;SUTVA，A/B 测试的基本假设及其违规&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A/B 测试的基本假设之一是 SUTVA — 稳定单位处理值假设。随机化单元中治疗的潜在结果仅取决于他们接受的治疗，而不取决于分配给其他受试者的治疗。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ensuring Data Integrity Through Anomaly Detection: Essential Tools for Data Engineers】通过异常检测确保数据完整性：数据工程师的基本工具</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-integrity-through-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the trending landscape of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt; and AI, companies are tirelessly innovating to deliver cutting-edge solutions for their customers. However, amidst this rapid evolution, ensuring a robust data universe characterized by high quality and integrity is indispensable. While much emphasis is often placed on refining AI models, the significance of pristine datasets can sometimes be overshadowed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article sets out to explore some of the essential tools required by organizations in the domain of data engineering to efficiently improve &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/strategies-for-governing-data-quality-accuracy-and&#34;&gt;data quality&lt;/a&gt; and triage/analyze data for effective business-centric machine learning analytics, reporting, and anomaly detection. To illustrate these tools/frameworks and their importance, let us consider a scenario within the fintech industry.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习&lt;/a&gt;和人工智能的趋势中，公司正在孜孜不倦地创新，为以下领域提供尖端解决方案：他们的客户。然而，在这种快速发展的过程中，确保以高质量和完整性为特征的强大数据世界是必不可少的。虽然人们通常非常重视改进人工智能模型，但原始数据集的重要性有时可能会被掩盖。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文旨在探讨数据工程领域组织有效提高&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/strategies-for-governing-data-quality”所需的一些基本工具-准确性和&#34;&gt;数据质量&lt;/a&gt;和分类/分析数据，以实现有效的以业务为中心的机器学习分析、报告和异常检测。为了说明这些工具/框架及其重要性，让我们考虑金融科技行业内的一个场景。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SingleStore Kai Support for MongoDB $vectorSearch】SingleStore Kai 支持 MongoDB $vectorSearch</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/singlestore-kai-support-for-mongodb-vectorsearch</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;SingleStore is a high-performance distributed SQL database and through SingleStore Kai extends its compatibility to MongoDB&#39;s vector search capabilities. By supporting MongoDB&#39;s &lt;code&gt;$vectorSearch&lt;/code&gt; operator, SingleStore Kai provides efficient querying and indexing of vector data, such as embeddings used in ML and AI applications. Users can benefit from SingleStore&#39;s optimized data handling and Kai&#39;s vector search capabilities to perform similarity searches across large datasets. In this article, we&#39;ll see an example of how to use SingleStore Kai with vector data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The notebook file used in this article is available on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/singlestore-kai-vectorsearch-example&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;SingleStore 是一个高性能分布式 SQL 数据库，通过 SingleStore Kai 扩展了其对 MongoDB 向量搜索功能的兼容性。通过支持 MongoDB 的 &lt;code&gt;$vectorSearch&lt;/code&gt; 运算符，SingleStore Kai 提供了矢量数据的高效查询和索引，例如 ML 和 AI 应用程序中使用的嵌入。用户可以受益于 SingleStore 的优化数据处理和 Kai 的矢量搜索功能，以跨大型数据集执行相似性搜索。在本文中，我们将看到如何将 SingleStore Kai 与矢量数据结合使用的示例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文中使用的笔记本文件可在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VeryFatBoy/singlestore-kai-vectorsearch-example&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt; /a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multimodal Search in AI Apps With PostgreSQL pgvector】使用 PostgreSQL pgvector 在 AI 应用程序中进行多模式搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/multimodal-search-in-ai-apps-with-postgresql-pgvector</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Large language models (LLMs) have significantly evolved beyond generating text responses to text prompts. These models are now trained to possess advanced capabilities like interpreting images and providing detailed descriptions from visual inputs. This gives users an even greater search capacity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, I’ll demonstrate how to build an application with multimodal search functionality. Users of this application can upload an image or provide text input that allows them to search a database of Indian recipes. The application is built to work with multiple LLM providers, allowing users to choose between OpenAI, or a model running locally with &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ollama&lt;/a&gt;. Text embeddings are then stored and queried in PostgreSQL using pgvector.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM) 的发展已经超越了对文本提示生成文本响应的范围。这些模型现在经过训练，拥有先进的功能，例如解释图像和根据视觉输入提供详细描述。这为用户提供了更大的搜索能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我将演示如何构建具有多模式搜索功能的应用程序。该应用程序的用户可以上传图像或提供文本输入，以便搜索印度食谱数据库。该应用程序旨在与多个 LLM 提供商合作，允许用户在 OpenAI 或使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; 本地运行的模型之间进行选择奥拉马&lt;/a&gt;。然后使用 pgvector 在 PostgreSQL 中存储和查询文本嵌入。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Common CSS Breakpoints for Media Queries】媒体查询的常见 CSS 断点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/common-css-breakpoints-for-media-queries</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As technology is growing every day, the diversification in the types of electronic devices is also expanding. In the present time, a wide range of electronic devices exist, including tablets, laptops, desktops, smartphones, and even smartwatches.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tech giants are spending millions of dollars in their research and development to introduce new and improved electronic devices daily in the market. This has resulted in the daily continuous increase in the catalog of electronic devices.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着科技日新月异，电子设备的种类也在不断扩大。目前，存在各种各样的电子设备，包括平板电脑、笔记本电脑、台式机、智能手机，甚至智能手表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;科技巨头每天花费数百万美元进行研发，在市场上推出新的和改进的电子设备。这导致电子设备的目录每天都在不断增加。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Two-Tower Model for Fraud Detection: A Comprehensive Guide】欺诈检测的两塔模型：综合指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-the-two-tower-model-for-fraud-detection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Fraud detection is a very important task in most industries, especially in finance and e-commerce. The classic &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; models struggle to handle the subtlety and complexity of patterns rooted in fraudulent behavior. The dual-tower or Siamese network model provides a powerful architecture to handle the complex tasks of parallel processing with two different sets of inputs, thus helping capture the intricate relationships between them. This article presents how to apply the two-tower model to fraud detection, with detailed explanations, code snippets, and practical illustrations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Is a Two-Tower Model?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;It is an architecture that comprises two independent &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/Neural-Network-Representations&#34;&gt;neural networks&lt;/a&gt;: one dealing with one type of input data and the second dealing with another. These two towers may work independently, although their output results are combined to make a single unified prediction. This architecture works very nicely in tasks involving finding relationships or similarities between two diverse sources of data.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;欺诈检测在大多数行业中都是一项非常重要的任务，尤其是在金融和电子商务领域。经典的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习&lt;/a&gt;模型很难处理源于欺诈行为的模式的微妙性和复杂性。双塔或暹罗网络模型提供了强大的架构来处理具有两组不同输入的并行处理的复杂任务，从而有助于捕获它们之间复杂的关系。本文介绍了如何将两塔模型应用于欺诈检测，并配有详细解释、代码片段和实际插图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;什么是两塔模型？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;它是一种由两个独立的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/Neural-Network-Representations&#34;&gt;神经网络&lt;/a&gt;组成的架构：一个处理一种类型处理输入数据，第二个处理另一个。这两个塔可以独立工作，尽管它们的输出结果被组合起来做出单一的统一预测。这种架构在涉及查找两个不同数据源之间的关系或相似性的任务中非常有效。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Merge Multiple PDFs in MuleSoft】在 MuleSoft 中合并多个 PDF</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/merge-multiple-pdfs-in-mulesoft</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Suppose there is a scenario where you have to merge multiple PDFs into one PDF and send the merged PDF as a response back to the source system or store the merged PDF in a file location. In this article, you will learn how to do this. There is no such &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/custom-icon-for-mule-4-custom-connector&#34;&gt;connector in MuleSoft&lt;/a&gt; that you can use to merge the PDFs. You will have to use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; library &lt;strong&gt;org.apache.pdfbox.multipdf&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;to merge the PDFs. It contains all necessary Java libraries for merging multiple PDFs into one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Implementation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Step 1&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Add the dependency as shown below in &lt;strong&gt;pom.xml:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;假设有一种情况，您必须将多个 PDF 合并为一个 PDF，并将合并的 PDF 作为响应发送回源系统或将合并的 PDF 存储在文件位置。在本文中，您将学习如何执行此操作。 MuleSoft 中没有可用于合并 PDF 的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/custom-icon-for-mule-4-custom-connector&#34;&gt;连接器&lt;/a&gt;。您必须使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 库&lt;strong&gt;org.apache.pdfbox.multipdf &lt;/strong&gt;来合并 PDF 。它包含将多个 PDF 合并为一个所需的所有 Java 库。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;实施&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;步骤 1&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;strong&gt;pom.xml中添加如下所示的依赖项：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Plot Your REST Endpoints Using grafana-infinity-datasource】使用 grafana-infinity-datasource 绘制您的 REST 端点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/plot-rest-endpoints-using-grafana-infinity-datasource</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When it comes to observability &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.com/&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; is the go-to tool for visualization. A Grafana dashboard consists of various forms of visualizations which are usually backed by a database.&lt;a href=&#34;https://egkatzioura.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/grafana.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;img data-permalink=&#34;https://egkatzioura.com/?attachment_id=2493&#34; data-orig-size=&#34;216,233&#34; data-image-meta=&#34;{&amp;quot;aperture&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;credit&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;camera&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;caption&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;created_timestamp&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;copyright&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;focal_length&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;iso&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shutter_speed&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;title&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;orientation&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;0&amp;quot;}&#34; data-image-description=&#34;&#34; data-medium-file=&#34;https://egkatzioura.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/grafana.jpeg?w=216&#34; tabindex=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;Grafana logo&#34; width=&#34;216&#34; height=&#34;233&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;42.4 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1721996413897&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;07/26/2024 12:20 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17816564-1721996413434.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;42351&#34; data-name=&#34;1721996413434.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17816564&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17816564-1721996413434.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; This is not always the case. Sometimes instead of pushing the data from the database as is, you might want to refine the data. This cannot always be achieved through the functionalities the DB provides. For example, you might want to fetch results from a proprietary API. This is where the &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/yesoreyeram-infinity-datasource/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;grafana-infinity-datasource&lt;/a&gt; plugin kicks in. With grafana-infinity-datasource, you can create visualizations based on JSON, XML, CSV, etc. You can issue an HTTP request to a REST API and plot the received data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Tutorial&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s assume we have an eShop application. We will create a simple Python API using FastAPI to manage the items of the eShop and the purchase volume.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;说到可观察性，&lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.com/&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; 是可视化的首选工具。 Grafana 仪表板由各种形式的可视化效果组成，这些可视化效果通常由数据库支持。&lt;a href=&#34;https://egkatzioura.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/grafana.jpeg&#34;&gt;&lt;img data-permalink =&#34;https://egkatzioura.com/?attachment_id=2493&#34; data-orig-size=&#34;216,233&#34; data-image-meta=&#34;{&#34;光圈&#34;:&#34;0&#34;,&#34;信用&#34;:&#34;&#34;,&#34;相机&#34; ：“”，“标题”：“”，“created_timestamp”：“0”，“版权”：“”，“focal_length”：“0”，“iso”：“0”，“shutter_speed”：“0”， &#34;标题&#34;:&#34;&#34;,&#34;方向&#34;:&#34;0&#34;}&#34; data-image-description=&#34;&#34; data-medium-file=&#34;https://egkatzioura.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/grafana .jpeg?w=216&#34; tabindex=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;Grafana 徽标&#34; width=&#34;216&#34; height=&#34;233&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new= “假”data-sizeformatted =“42.4 kB”data-mimetype =“image / png”data-creationdate =“1721996413897”data-creationdateformatted =“07/26/2024 12:20 PM”data-type =“临时”数据-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17816564-1721996413434.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;42351&#34; data-name=&#34;1721996413434.png&#34; data-id =&#34;17816564&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17816564-1721996413434.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA; 这并非总是如此。有时，您可能不想按原样从数据库推送数据，而是希望优化数据。这并不总是可以通过数据库提供的功能来实现。例如，您可能想要从专有 API 获取结果。这是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.com/grafana/plugins/yesoreyeram-infinity-datasource/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;grafana-infinity-datasource&lt;/a&gt; 插件的位置开始使用。使用 grafana-infinity-datasource，您可以基于 JSON、XML、CSV 等创建可视化。您可以向 REST API 发出 HTTP 请求并绘制接收到的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;教程&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设我们有一个 eShop 应用程序。我们将使用 FastAPI 创建一个简单的 Python API 来管理 eShop 的商品和购买量。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software Engineering Grief】软件工程悲伤</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-engineering-grief</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Human beings resist change. &amp;nbsp;This is not personal opinion, it&#39;s our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.peopleproductive.com/blog/do-people-really-resist-change&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;defense mechanism against uncertainty&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;nbsp;If you narrow your target to software engineers and technologists - who, in &lt;em&gt;almost&lt;/em&gt; all cases, are humans - the defense mechanism can become a survival mechanism.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Woman grieving&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;240.9 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1722260654200&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;07/29/2024 01:44 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17823194-1722260654879.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;240908&#34; data-name=&#34;1722260654879.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17823194&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17823194-1722260654879.png&#34;&gt;Successful companies rarely rest on their laurels and assume the money will flow in unimpeded by change. Instead, companies constantly analyze the current to define their vision for the future:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;How do economic and market conditions affect our ability to sell?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;    Would new features or product offerings attract new customers while retaining existing customers?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;    Could we more efficiently increase market share through acquisitions rather than internal product development?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;    Are there partner opportunities beneficial to us?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;   How can we expand the industries in which are products are sold?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人类抵制改变。  这不是个人意见，而是我们的&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.peopleproductive.com/blog/do-people-really-resist-change&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;防御机制不确定性。  如果您将目标缩小到软件工程师和技术人员（在&lt;em&gt;几乎&lt;/em&gt;所有情况下，他们都是人类），防御机制就可以成为一种生存机制。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;悲伤的女人“class =“fr-fic fr-dib lazyload”data-image =“true”data-new =“false”data-sizeformatted =“240.9 kB”data-mimetype =“image / png”data-creationdate =“1722260654200” data-creationdateformatted=&#34;07/29/2024 01:44 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17823194-1722260654879.png&#34; data-modificationdate =&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;240908&#34; data-name=&#34;1722260654879.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17823194&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17823194-1722260654879. png&#34;&gt;成功的公司很少满足于现状，并认为资金会不受变革阻碍地流入。相反，公司不断分析当前情况来定义未来愿景：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA; &lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;经济和市场状况如何影响我们的销售能力？&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;    新功能或产品能否在保留现有客户的同时吸引新客户？&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;    我们能否通过收购而不是内部产品开发更有效地增加市场份额？&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;    有对我们有利的合作伙伴机会吗？&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;   如何扩大产品销售的行业？&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>