<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Stream Data Processing With Snow Pipe, Cortex AI, and Snow Park】使用 Snow Pipe、Cortex AI 和 Snow Park 增强流数据处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-stream-data-processing-with-snow-pipe</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Why Snowflake?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-snowflake-is-powering-the-future-of-big-data&#34;&gt;Snowflake&lt;/a&gt; is a cloud-based data platform that provides a fully managed service for handling data-driven engagements. It is scalable and is enabled on multiple cloud tenants of AWS, Azure, and GCP.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Snowflake has a unique architecture that separates the storage, compute, and service layers which enables scalable and elastic data processing. This architecture enables us to use resources of storage, compute, and services independently and pay as per the usage.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;为什么是雪花？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-snowflake-is-powering-the-future-of-big-data&#34;&gt;Snowflake&lt;/a&gt; 是一个基于云的数据平台，提供完全托管的服务来处理数据驱动的业务。它具有可扩展性，并且在 AWS、Azure 和 GCP 的多个云租户上启用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Snowflake 拥有独特的架构，将存储、计算和服务层分开，从而实现可扩展和弹性的数据处理。这种架构使我们能够独立使用存储、计算和服务资源，并按用量付费。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitOps: ArgoCD vs FluxCD】GitOps：ArgoCD 与 FluxCD</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/gitops-argocd-vs-fluxcd</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Getting Started With GitOps&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Most organizations are always looking for ways to streamline their processes and improve efficiency by implementing automation. In recent years, software deployment has been done multiple times in a day rather than weeks or months. Organizations have moved from the waterfall models to hyper-agile methodologies and particularly due to the adoption of microservices architecture, teams are releasing their software much faster. To make this possible, GitOps implements a &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/architecture/controller/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;control-loop&lt;/a&gt; pattern more often seen in Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;GitOps offers a more consistent and reliable way to handle infrastructure and deployment. In this blog, we&#39;ll explore what GitOps is and why it&#39;s becoming increasingly popular among DevOps teams. We will also walk through popular GitOps tools like Argo CD and Flux CD.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;GitOps 入门&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;大多数组织一直在寻找通过实施自动化来简化流程并提高效率的方法。近年来，软件部署已在一天内完成多次，而不是几周或几个月。组织已经从瀑布模型转向超敏捷方法，特别是由于微服务架构的采用，团队发布软件的速度要快得多。为了实现这一点，GitOps 实现了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/architecture/controller/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;control-loop&lt;/a&gt; 模式在 Kubernetes 中更常见。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;GitOps 提供了一种更一致、更可靠的方式来处理基础架构和部署。在本博客中，我们将探讨 GitOps 是什么以及它为何在 DevOps 团队中变得越来越受欢迎。我们还将介绍流行的 GitOps 工具，例如 Argo CD 和 Flux CD。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Time Anomaly Detection Using Large Language Models】使用大型语言模型进行实时异常检测</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/realtime-anomaly-detection-using-large-language</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The capability to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/anomaly-detection-survey&#34;&gt;detect anomalies&lt;/a&gt; becomes important in the data-driven world of today and is a key component for various industries such as finance, healthcare, cybersecurity, and manufacturing. Anomalies can be a sign of fraud, system failings, security incidents, or other important events that require immediate attention. The volume, velocity, and variety of streaming data are difficult for traditional anomaly detection techniques to handle. On the other hand, recent developments in Large Language Models (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/task-specific-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLMs&lt;/a&gt;) provide a new path to perform real-time anomaly detection. In this blog post, we discuss how LLMs can be used for anomaly detection on streaming data in detail with some examples.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Anomaly Detection&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anomalies are patterns in your data that do not conform to a well-defined notion of normal behavior.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/anomaly-detection-survey&#34;&gt;检测异常&lt;/a&gt;的能力在当今数据驱动的世界中变得非常重要，并且是金融、医疗保健、网络安全和制造等各个行业。异常可能是欺诈、系统故障、安全事件或其他需要立即关注的重要事件的迹象。传统的异常检测技术难以处理流数据的数量、速度和种类。另一方面，大型语言模型（&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/task-specific-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLM&lt;/a&gt;）的最新发展提供了一条新的执行路径实时异常检测。在这篇博文中，我们通过一些示例详细讨论了如何使用 LLM 来对流数据进行异常检测。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;异常检测&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;异常是数据中不符合明确定义的正常行为概念的模式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Apache Iceberg Table Management】Apache Iceberg 表管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/apache-iceberg-table-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;1. What Are Iceberg and Table Layout for Iceberg?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-short-introduction-to-apache-iceberg&#34;&gt;Apache Iceberg&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;is a high-performance table format for large analytic datasets. It&#39;s designed to handle petabyte-scale data lakes with the reliability and efficiency needed for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-data-analytics-understanding-data-analytic&#34;&gt;data analytics&lt;/a&gt; and big data workflows. Iceberg tables organize data into a consistent format that simplifies querying, updating, and managing data at scale. One of the main advantages of Iceberg table format is schema evolution, which allows updating the table schema without re-writing the data. However, all these advantages come at the cost of maintaining table metadata disjoint from data in metadata files which are updated for each table ops in a transaction while maintaining concurrency. A typical Iceberg table layout has:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manifest files:&lt;/strong&gt; Store metadata about data files in the table, including their locations, sizes, and statistics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Snapshot files:&lt;/strong&gt; Represent the state of the table at a given point in time. Each snapshot includes references to manifest files and data files.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data files:&lt;/strong&gt; Contain the actual data in the table, typically stored in columnar formats like Parquet or ORC.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metadata files:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Store global metadata about the table, such as schema, partitioning information, and properties.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CRUD &amp;nbsp;operations on table leads to generation of multiple snapshot files, manifest files, data files etc which can consume storage making the table operations inefficient.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;1。 Iceberg 和 Iceberg 的表格布局是什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-short-introduction-to-apache-iceberg&#34;&gt;Apache Iceberg&lt;/a&gt;是一种适用于大型分析数据集的高性能表格格式。它旨在处理 PB 级数据湖，并提供&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-data-analytics-understanding-data-analytic&#34;&gt;数据分析&lt;/ a&gt; 和大数据工作流程。 Iceberg 表将数据组织成一致的格式，从而简化了大规模数据的查询、更新和管理。 Iceberg 表格式的主要优点之一是模式演化，它允许更新表模式而无需重新写入数据。然而，所有这些优点都是以维护表元数据与元数据文件中的数据不相交为代价的，这些元数据文件是在事务中为每个表操作更新的，同时保持并发性。典型的 Iceberg 表布局具有：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;清单文件&lt;/strong&gt;：存储有关表中数据文件的元数据，包括其位置、大小和统计信息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;快照文件&lt;/strong&gt;：表示表在给定时间点的状态。每个快照都包含对清单文件和数据文件的引用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据文件：&lt;/strong&gt;包含表中的实际数据，通常以列式格式存储，例如 Parquet 或 ORC。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;元数据文件：&lt;/strong&gt;存储有关表的全局元数据，例如架构、分区信息和属性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;表上的 CRUD 操作会导致生成多个快照文件、清单文件、数据文件等，这些文件会消耗存储空间，从而导致表操作效率低下。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Run Apache Spark on Kubernetes in Less Than 5 Minutes】如何在 5 分钟内在 Kubernetes 上运行 Apache Spark</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/run-apache-spark-on-k8s-in-less-than-5-mins</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Tools like Ilum will go a long way in simplifying the process of installing Apache Spark on Kubernetes. This guide will take you step-by-step through how to run Spark well on your Kubernetes cluster. With Ilum, deploying, managing, and scaling Apache Spark clusters is easily and naturally done.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we will showcase how to get up and running with Apache Spark on K8s. There are many ways to do that, but most are complex and require several configurations. We will use &lt;a href=&#34;https://ilum.cloud/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ilum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; since that will do all the cluster setup for us. In the next blog post, we will compare the usage with the Spark operator.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;像 Ilum 这样的工具将大大简化在 Kubernetes 上安装 Apache Spark 的过程。本指南将逐步指导您如何在 Kubernetes 集群上良好地运行 Spark。借助 Ilum，可以轻松、自然地完成部署、管理和扩展 Apache Spark 集群。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们将展示如何在 K8s 上启动并运行 Apache Spark。有很多方法可以做到这一点，但大多数都很复杂并且需要多种配置。我们将使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ilum.cloud/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ilum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;将为我们完成所有集群设置。在下一篇博文中，我们将与Spark算子进行使用比较。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Hands-On Guide to OpenTelemetry: Better Tracing With Automatic Instrumentation】OpenTelemetry 实践指南：使用自动仪器更好地进行跟踪</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-hands-on-guide-to-opentelemetry-better-tracing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to start your journey on the road to collecting telemetry data from your applications? Great observability begins with great instrumentation!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this series, you&#39;ll explore how to adopt &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; and how to instrument an application to collect tracing telemetry. You&#39;ll learn how to leverage out-of-the-box automatic instrumentation tools and understand when it&#39;s necessary to explore more advanced manual instrumentation for your applications. By the end of this series, you&#39;ll have an understanding of how telemetry travels from your applications to the OpenTelemetry Collector, and be ready to bring OpenTelemetry to your future projects. Everything discussed here is supported by &lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a hands-on, self-paced workshop&lt;/a&gt; authored &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.paigerduty.com/about/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;by Paige Cruz&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您准备好开始从应用程序收集遥测数据的旅程了吗？出色的可观测性始于出色的仪器！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本系列中，您将探索如何采用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; 以及如何检测一个应用程序来收集跟踪遥测数据。您将学习如何利用开箱即用的自动仪表工具，并了解何时需要为您的应用探索更高级的手动仪表。在本系列结束时，您将了解遥测如何从应用程序传输到 OpenTelemetry Collector，并准备好将 OpenTelemetry 引入您未来的项目。这里讨论的所有内容均由&lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;动手、自定进度的研讨会&lt;/ a&gt; 作者：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.paigerduty.com/about/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;由 Paige Cruz&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Multi-Level Caching in Java With NCache】使用 NCache 在 Java 中实现多级缓存</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-multi-level-caching-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/architectural-insights-designing-efficient-multi-l&#34;&gt;Multi-level caching&lt;/a&gt; is a technique used to improve the performance of applications by storing frequently accessed data in different cache layers. The cache layers generally lie at various levels of the application stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is a common practice to use a distributed cache like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.alachisoft.com/ncache/&#34;&gt;NCache&lt;/a&gt; to implement multi-level caching in applications. NCache provides a scalable and high-performance caching solution that can store data in memory across multiple servers. In addition to this, NCache provides a feature to enable local caching in client nodes to offer even faster data access.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/architectural-insights-designing-efficient-multi-l&#34;&gt;多级缓存&lt;/a&gt;是一种通过以下方式提高应用程序性能的技术：将经常访问的数据存储在不同的缓存层中。缓存层通常位于应用程序堆栈的各个级别。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用分布式缓存（例如&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.alachisoft.com/ncache/&#34;&gt;NCache&lt;/a&gt;）在应用程序中实现多级缓存是一种常见的做法。 NCache 提供了可扩展且高性能的缓存解决方案，可以跨多个服务器将数据存储在内存中。除此之外，NCache 还提供了一项功能，可以在客户端节点中启用本地缓存，从而提供更快的数据访问。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Step-By-Step Guide To Creating a Calculator App With HTML and JS (With Factor Calculator Example)】使用 HTML 和 JS 创建计算器应用程序的分步指南（包含因子计算器示例）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/step-by-step-guide-to-creating-a-calculator-app</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Creating a calculator app is a great way to practice and understand the basics of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/html-layout-1&#34;&gt;HTML&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/practical-example-of-using-css-layer&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/12-ways-to-optimize-your-javascript-journey&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt;. This guide will walk you through the steps to build a simple yet functional calculator. By the end of this tutorial, you will have a fully operational calculator that can perform basic arithmetic operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Calculators are essential tools, and building one is an excellent project for learning web development. This guide will cover the following:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;创建计算器应用程序是练习和理解 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/html-layout-1&#34;&gt;HTML&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href= 基础知识的好方法“https://dzone.com/articles/practical-example-of-using-css-layer&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/12-ways- to-optimize-your-javascript-journey&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt;。本指南将引导您完成构建简单但实用的计算器的步骤。在本教程结束时，您将拥有一个可以执行基本算术运算的功能齐全的计算器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;计算器是必不可少的工具，构建一个计算器是学习 Web 开发的绝佳项目。本指南将涵盖以下内容：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Generate Flame Graphs in Java】如何用 Java 生成火焰图</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-generate-flame-graphs-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Flame graphs became the de facto standard for investigating issues in today&#39;s applications (not only written in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;). The flame graphs can provide a lot of interesting insights and can give developers valuable hints to improve the execution of their applications. However, still, a lot of developers don&#39;t use them, even if generating flame graphs is easier than ever before.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will demonstrate a couple of examples of how easy it is in Java to get started with the investigation of your applications. If you don&#39;t know the details about flame graph visualization, please, visit a great article &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.brendangregg.com/flamegraphs.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;about flame graphs&lt;/a&gt; from Brendan Gregg.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;火焰图成为调查当今应用程序中问题的事实上的标准（不仅仅是用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 编写的）。火焰图可以提供许多有趣的见解，并可以为开发人员提供宝贵的提示，以改进其应用程序的执行。然而，尽管生成火焰图比以前更容易，但许多开发人员仍然不使用它们。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将演示几个示例，说明在 Java 中开始研究应用程序是多么容易。如果您不了解有关火焰图可视化的详细信息，请访问一篇精彩文章 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.brendangregg.com/flamegraphs.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;关于 Brendan Gregg 的火焰图&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Pivoting Database Systems Practices to AI: Create Efficient Development and Maintenance Practices With Generative AI】将数据库系统实践转向人工智能：利用生成式人工智能创建高效的开发和维护实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/pivoting-database-systems-practices-to-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-database-systems-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Database Systems: Modernization for Data-Driven Architectures&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Modern database practices enhance performance, scalability, and flexibility while ensuring data integrity, consistency, and security. Some key practices include leveraging distributed databases for scalability and reliability, using cloud databases for on-demand scalability and maintenance, and implementing NoSQL databases for handling unstructured data. Additionally, data lakes store vast amounts of raw data for advanced analytics, and in-memory databases speed up data retrieval by storing data in main memory. The advent of artificial intelligence (AI) is rapidly transforming database development and maintenance by automating complex tasks, enhancing efficiency, and ensuring system robustness.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-database-systems-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;数据库系统：数据驱动架构的现代化&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。 p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;现代数据库实践增强了性能、可扩展性和灵活性，同时确保数据完整性、一致性和安全性。一些关键实践包括利用分布式数据库实现可扩展性和可靠性、使用云数据库实现按需可扩展性和维护，以及实施 NoSQL 数据库来处理非结构化数据。此外，数据湖存储大量原始数据用于高级分析，内存数据库通过将数据存储在主内存中来加速数据检索。人工智能 (AI) 的出现通过自动化复杂任务、提高效率并确保系统稳健性，正在迅速改变数据库开发和维护。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>