<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Certificate Authorities: The Keystone of Digital Trust】证书机构：数字信托的基石</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/certificate-authorities-trust-transparency</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TLDR:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-certificate-authority-ca-server-for-you&#34;&gt;Certificate Authorities&lt;/a&gt; (CAs) are the ultimate trust brokers online, issuing the digital certificates that make secure web browsing, e-commerce, and confidential communications possible. This article breaks down what CAs do, the nuances of public and private trust, role of browsers and global forums and how they enforce compliance, and why recent security incidents underline the critical responsibility of every CA.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ll explore &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-ssl-certificate-troubleshooting-windows&#34;&gt;Certificate Transparency&lt;/a&gt; (CT), &amp;nbsp;leading CAs and CT log providers, review high-profile failures, and explain where CA technology is headed next.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TLDR:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-certificate-authority-ca-server-for-you&#34;&gt;Certificate Authorities&lt;/a&gt; (CAs) are the ultimate trust brokers online, issuing the digital certificates that make secure web browsing, e-commerce, and confidential communications possible.本文打破了CAS的工作，公共和私人信任的细微差别，浏览器和全球论坛的作用以及它们如何执行合规性以及为什么最近的安全事件为何强调每个CA的关键责任。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将探索&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-ssl-certificate-certificate-troubleshooting-windows--证书透明度&lt;/a&gt;（CT）（CT），领先的Cas和CT日志提供者，查看高调失败，并解释CA技术的位置。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From History to the Future of AI Communication—IPC to MCP and A2A】从历史到AI通信的未来 -  IPC到MCP和A2A</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a2a-mcp-agent-ai-communication-evolution</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Google has explicitly positioned its &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.googleblog.com/en/a2a-a-new-era-of-agent-interoperability/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A2A protocol&lt;/a&gt; as complementary to Anthropic&#39;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://modelcontextprotocol.io/introduction&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MCP&lt;/a&gt;, aiming to address different yet related aspects of building sophisticated agentic systems. The core distinction lies in the layer of interaction each protocol standardizes. MCP focuses on the connection between a single AI agent and its external resources (tools and data), while A2A focuses on the communication and collaboration among distinct AI agents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Architecturally, they operate at different levels. MCP governs the agent-to-resource interface, while A2A governs the agent-to-agent interface. In a typical multi-agent workflow, one agent (the client) might use A2A to request assistance from another specialized agent (the server). This server agent might then use MCP to interact with various tools or data sources required to fulfill the task requested via A2A, before sending the result back using A2A.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Google已明确定位其&lt;a href =“ https://developers.googleblog.com/en/a2a-a2a-a-new-a-new-era-era-ovent-interoperability/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” tart href =“ https://modelcontextprotocol.io/introduction” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; mcp &lt;/a&gt;，旨在解决构建复杂的代理系统的不同方面。核心区别在于每个协议标准化的相互作用层。 MCP专注于单个AI代理及其外部资源（工具和数据）之间的联系，而A2A专注于不同的AI代理之间的沟通和协作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在架构上，它们在不同级别上运行。 MCP控制代理到资源界面，而A2A控制代理到代理接口。在典型的多代理工作流中，一个代理（客户端）可以使用A2A向另一个专业代理（服务器）请求帮助。然后，该服务器代理可能会使用MCP与完成A2A请求的任务所需的各种工具或数据源进行交互，然后再向使用A2A发送结果。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SHAP-Based Explainable AI (XAI) Integration With .Net Application】基于形状的可解释的AI（XAI）与.NET应用程序集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-shap-xai-methods-dotnet-integration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Think of&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-7-tools-and-techniques-for-model&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Explainable AI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;(XAI) as your friendly guide to a complex machine’s secret thoughts. Instead of leaving you guessing why an algorithm made a certain call, XAI opens the door, points out the important clues, and speaks plainly about what drove its decision. Explainable AI builds trust on the ML decision since it speaks how the decision made, makes the human to believe and to catch and fix the mistakes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Explanation from Explainable AI:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I have started at 0%—yet to know the prediction. Spotting that dog’s snout boosted my confidence by 45%, seeing its upright ears added 30%, the fluffy fur another 10%, and the collar a small 7%. A hint of grass slightly pulled me down by 5%. This is a dog and I&#39;m 87% sure about this.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p lang =“ en-us”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;想想&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/explainable--ai--ai--ai--ai--ai-ai-ai-ai-ai-ai--ai--ai--ai--ai----------------ai--ai-----------------------er-techniques-for-model-for-model--------- ai &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;（xai）作为复杂机器秘密思想的友好指南。 Xai并没有让您猜测为什么算法打电话打开门，而是指出了重要的线索，并清楚地说明了什么做出决定。可解释的AI建立了对ML决定的信任，因为它说明了决定的做出，使人相信并捕获和解决错误。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {” 134233117“：false，” 134233118“：false，” 201341983“：0，” 335551550 “：6，” 335551620“：6，” 335559738“：0，” 335559739“：160，” 335559740“：276}：276}”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 lang =“ en-us”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;从可解释的AI：&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span的解释data-ccp-props =“ {” 134233117“：false，” 134233118：false，“ 201341983”：0，“ 335551550” ：0，“ 335551620”：0，“ 335559738”：0，“ 335559739”：160，“ 335559740”：276}：276}&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p lang =“ en-us”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我开始时为0％，但要知道预测。确定。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {” 134233117“：false，” 134233118“：false，” 201341983“：0，” 335551550”：0，”：0，” 335551620“：0，” 335559738“：0，” 335559739“：160，” 3355559740“：276}”&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Time Model Inference With Apache Kafka and Flink for Predictive AI and GenAI】使用Apache Kafka和Flink进行实时模型推断，用于预测AI和Genai</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/model-inference-kafka-flink-predictive-genai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Artificial intelligence (AI) and machine Learning (ML) are transforming business operations by enabling systems to learn from data and make intelligent decisions for predictive and generative AI use cases. Two essential components of AI/ML are model training and inference. Models are developed and refined using historical data. Model inference is the process of using trained machine learning models to make predictions or generate outputs based on new, unseen data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This blog post covers the basics of model inference, comparing different approaches like remote and embedded inference. It also explores how data streaming with Apache Kafka and Flink enhances the performance and reliability of these predictions. Whether for real-time fraud detection, &amp;nbsp;smart customer service applications, or predictive maintenance, understanding the value of data streaming for model inference is crucial for leveraging AI/ML effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能（AI）和机器学习（ML）正在通过使系统从数据中学习并为预测性和生成性AI用例做出明智的决策来改变业务运营。 AI/ML的两个基本组成部分是模型培训和推理。使用历史数据开发和完善模型。模型推断是使用训练有素的机器学习模型进行预测或基于新的，看不见的数据生成输出的过程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本博客文章涵盖了模型推理的基础知识，比较了远程和嵌入式推理等不同方法。它还探讨了使用Apache Kafka和Flink的数据流如何增强这些预测的性能和可靠性。无论是用于实时欺诈检测，智能客户服务应用程序还是预测性维护，了解模型推理数据流的价值对于有效利用AI/ML至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Lake, Warehouse, or Lakehouse? Rethinking the Future of Data Architecture】数据湖，仓库还是湖泊？重新思考数据架构的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-lake-warehouse-or-lakehouse</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px; text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-data-engineering-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Data Engineering: Scaling Intelligence With the Modern Data Stack&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the age of AI and ubiquitous data, the lines between traditional data architectures are blurring. Data lakes, warehouses, and lakehouses are no longer isolated strategies but are increasingly converging into unified, intelligent platforms. This article explores how modern data architectures are evolving to meet new demands for real-time insights, agility, and a single source of truth.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ font-size：17px; text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;编辑器注：以下是为Dzone的2025年2025年趋势报告编写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https:///dzone.com/dzone.com/link/link/link/link/2025-tr-data-tr-data-tr-data-gendata-gendata-gencineering-contributor-contributor-conter--conter--roreernerernerernerernerernerernerernerernerernerernerernerer n =” target =“ _ blank”&gt; &lt;em&gt;数据工程：使用现代数据堆栈缩放智能&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在AI和无处不在的数据中，传统数据架构之间的界线模糊。数据湖，仓库和湖泊不再是孤立的策略，而是越来越多地聚集成统一的智能平台。本文探讨了现代数据体系结构如何发展以满足实时见解，敏捷性和单一真理来源的新需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Deep Dive into Behavior-Driven Development】深入研究行为驱动的发展</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/behavior-driven-development-deep-dive</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-bdd-a-complete-guide&#34;&gt;Behavior-Driven Development (BDD)&lt;/a&gt; fosters integration between developers, testers, product owners, and business analysts. Scenario participation ensures a common understanding of system functionality among all participants. In this article, we focus on BDD, its definition, importance, and strategies for implementing it in current projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding the Problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In software engineering, fulfilling both a product&#39;s technical requirements and the business objectives is essential.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-bdd-a-complete-guide”&gt;行为 - 驱动开发（BDD）&lt;/a&gt;促进开发人员，测试者，产品所有者和业务分析师之间的整合。场景参与确保了对所有参与者系统功能的共同理解。在本文中，我们关注BDD，其定义，重要性和在当前项目中实施它的策略。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;了解问题&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在软件工程中，满足产品的技术要求和业务目标至关重要。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python Async/Sync: Advanced Blocking Detection and Best Practices (Part 2)】python async/sync：高级阻止检测和最佳实践（第2部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-asyncsync-advanced-blocking-detection-and-b</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re new to the challenges of mixing asynchronous and synchronous Python code, you might find it helpful to first read &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/solving-async-blocking&#34;&gt;the first part&lt;/a&gt;, which focuses on understanding and solving asynchronous blocking and covers the foundational problems and initial solutions. This part will delve into advanced techniques for identifying and mitigating performance pitfalls.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Detect Blocking Sync Code in Async&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Proactively identifying these hidden blockers is crucial for maintaining high-performance asyncio applications. Here are battle-tested methodologies:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;re new to the challenges of mixing asynchronous and synchronous Python code, you might find it helpful to first read &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/solving-async-blocking&#34;&gt;the first part&lt;/a&gt;, which focuses on understanding and solving asynchronous blocking and covers the foundational problems and initial solutions.该部分将深入研究高级技术，以识别和减轻性能陷阱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;如何检测异步中的阻止同步代码&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主动识别这些隐藏的阻滞剂对于维持高性能异步应用至关重要。这是经过战斗的方法：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Storage: The Foundation for Scalable Analytics】数据存储：可扩展分析的基础</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-storage-scalable-analytics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;606&#34; data-start=&#34;242&#34;&gt;In the last few years, cloud storage has become so inexpensive that most teams barely think about it. Services like S3 can store petabytes for pennies, and Glacier can archive data for less than the price of a coffee each month. We know how easy it is to spin up buckets and push data in, and it’s no wonder storage often gets treated as an afterthought.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;962&#34; data-start=&#34;608&#34;&gt;But here’s the catch: cheap doesn’t mean unimportant. With the rise of digital transformation, every company is turning into a data company, with its data volumes skyrocketing. For example, e-commerce sites track every click by customers, manufacturers stream IoT sensor feeds, storing every log, and banks store every transaction for years for audit and compliance reasons.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 606” data-start =“ 242”&gt;在过去几年中，云存储变得如此便宜，以至于大多数团队几乎没有考虑它。 S3之类的服务可以存储便士的pbot，冰川可以以每月的价格归档数据少于咖啡的价格。我们知道旋转存储桶和推入数据是多么容易，难怪存储通常会被视为事后的想法。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 962” data-start =“ 608”&gt;，但这是收获：便宜并不意味着不重要。随着数字化转型的兴起，每个公司都将变成数据公司，其数据量飙升。例如，电子商务网站跟踪客户的每次点击，制造商流媒体IoT传感器供稿，存储每个日志，而银行为了审计和合规性原因存储每笔交易。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Create Ansible Users and Add Passwords】如何创建Ansible用户并添加密码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/create-ansible-users-add-passwords</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Managing users efficiently is a key part of automating system administration with Ansible. In this guide, you’ll learn how to create users, set passwords, add users to groups, and configure remote access using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ansible-security-and-testing-tools-for-automation&#34;&gt;Ansible’s powerful tools&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What is the Ansible User Module?&lt;a href=&#34;https://spacelift.io/blog/ansible-create-user#what-is-the-ansible-user-module&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Ansible &lt;code&gt;user&lt;/code&gt; module is used to manage user accounts on Linux and UNIX-like operating systems on target systems. It can set user properties such as UID, home directory, login shell, and password hash. Ansible tasks are idempotent, so re-running the task will not create duplicate users.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;有效地管理用户是与Ansible自动化系统管理的关键部分。在本指南中，您将学习如何创建用户，设置密码，将用户添加到组中，并使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/aseible-security-security-andible-and-testing-testing-tools-for-automation”&gt; Ansible的强大工具&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是Ansible用户模块？&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Ansible &lt;code&gt;用户&lt;/code&gt;模块用于在目标系统上管理Linux和Unix样操作系统上的用户帐户。它可以设置用户属性，例如UID，主目录，登录外壳和密码哈希。 Ansible任务是掌握的，因此重新运行该任务不会创建重复的用户。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Toward Explainable AI (Part I): Bridging Theory and Practice—Why AI Needs to Be Explainable】迈向可解释的AI（第一部分）：桥接理论和实践 - 为什么AI需要解释</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-part-1-why-it-matters</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Series reminder: This series explores how explainability in AI helps build trust, ensure accountability, and align with real-world needs, from foundational principles to practical use cases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;In this Part: We lay the groundwork for explainable AI: what it means, why it matters, and what’s at stake when AI systems remain opaque.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;em&gt;系列提醒：本系列探讨了AI中的解释性如何帮助建立信任，确保问责制并与现实世界需求保持一致，从基本原理到实际用例。&lt;br&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;em&gt;在这一部分：我们为Audyable AI奠定了基础：它的含义，为什么重要以及当AI系统保持不透明时的危险。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>