<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【LangGraph Orchestrator Agents: Streamlining AI Workflow Automation】Langgraph编排代理：简化AI工作流程自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/langgraph-orchestrator-agents</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;In AI-driven applications, complex tasks often require breaking down into multiple subtasks. However, the exact subtasks cannot be predetermined in many real-world scenarios. For instance, in automated code generation, the number of files to be modified and the specific changes needed depend entirely on the given request. Traditional parallelized workflows struggle unpredictably, requiring tasks to be predefined upfront. This rigidity limits the adaptability&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;of AI systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;However, the Orchestrator-Workers Workflow Agents in LangGraph introduce a more flexible and intelligent approach to address this challenge. Instead of relying on static task definitions, a&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle=&#34;Hyperlink&#34;&gt;central orchestrator&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle=&#34;Hyperlink&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;LLM dynamically analyses the input&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;, determines the required subtasks, and delegates them to specialized worker LLMs. The orchestrator then collects and synthesizes the outputs, ensuring a cohesive final result. These&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle=&#34;Hyperlink&#34;&gt;GenAI services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;enable real-time decision-making, adaptive task management, and higher accuracy, ensuring that complex workflows are handled with smarter agility and precision.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ in-in”&gt;在AI驱动的应用程序中，复杂的任务通常需要分解为多个子任务。但是，在许多实际情况下，确切的子任务不能预先确定。例如，在自动代码生成中，要修改的文件数和所需的特定更改完全取决于给定的请求。传统的并行工作流程不可预测，要求预先定义任务。这种刚度限制了适应性&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ in”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” auto“ auto” lang =“ inan&gt;” aisystems。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ in-in”&gt;但是，langgraph中的编目工人工作流代理引入了一种更灵活，更智能的方法来应对这一挑战。 A &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ in”&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-charstyle =“ hyperlink”&gt; central Orchestrator &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data data data data contrast =“ none&gt;输入&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ in-in”&gt;，确定所需的子任务，并将其委派给专业的工作Worker LLMS。然后，编排者收集并合成输出，确保最终结果。这些&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ in”&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-charstyle =“ hyperlink”&gt; genai services &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” auto“ lang =” in in in on in in in on in in in in of ofable实时决策，适应性的任务管理以及更高的准确性，并随身携带了复杂的工作，并且会使工作变得更加努力，并且要努力工作。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {” 335551550“：6，” 335551620“：6}”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agentic AI vs Traditional AI Agents: What Makes Them Autonomous?】代理AI与传统的AI代理：是什么使它们自主？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-vs-traditional-ai-autonomy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Artificial intelligence has developed, and the appearance of agentic artificial intelligence is a significant turning point. Unlike conventional AI agents, which depend too much on human cues, agentic AI systems (such as OpenAI’s Auto-GPT 3.0, Google’s Gemini Pro 1.5, and Meta’s LLaMA 3) demonstrate autonomy, initiative, and adaptive decision-making.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This blog post examines how agentic AI differs from traditional agents, what innovations are leading the transformation, and what this means for the world of automation and work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;人工智能已经发展出来，代理人工智能的出现是一个重要的转折点。与传统的AI代理不同，它过多地取决于人类提示，代理AI系统（例如OpenAI的自动GPT 3.0，Google的Google的Gemini Pro 1.5和Meta的Llama 3）展示了自治，主动性和自适应决策。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;此博客文章研究了代理AI与传统代理人的不同，哪些创新引起了转型以及这对自动化和工作的世界意味着什么。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【API Testing With Playwright: A Guide for QA Engineers and Developers】与剧作家一起测试的API测试：QA工程师和开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/playwright-api-testing-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;743&#34; data-start=&#34;376&#34;&gt;Ensuring the quality and reliability of backend services through &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-ultimate-guide-to-api-testing&#34;&gt;API testing&lt;/a&gt; is as crucial as testing the user interface. APIs act as the backbone for data exchange between different components and systems. Without robust API tests, defects can propagate unnoticed, leading to faulty features and unhappy users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1217&#34; data-start=&#34;745&#34;&gt;Playwright, widely acclaimed as a next-generation browser automation framework, extends its capabilities beyond UI testing to support comprehensive API testing. By leveraging Playwright for API testing, QA engineers and developers benefit from a unified framework that seamlessly integrates API and UI tests. This article explores how to effectively use Playwright for API testing—from basics to advanced techniques—while offering practical advice and real-world examples.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 743” data-start =“ 376”&gt;通过&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-yultimate-guide-to-api-testing”&gt; api测试&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;与用户接口相关。 API充当不同组件和系统之间数据交换的骨干。如果没有强大的API测试，缺陷可能会引起未注意的传播，导致功能错误和不愉快的用户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1217” data-start =“ 745”&gt;剧作家广受赞誉，作为下一代浏览器自动化框架，将其功能扩展到UI测试之外，以支持全面的API测试。通过利用剧作家进行API测试，QA工程师和开发人员从无缝集成API和UI测试的统一框架中受益。本文探讨了如何有效地将剧作家用于API测试（从基础知识到高级技术），同时提供实用建议和现实世界的示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing Secure APIs: A Developer’s Guide to Authentication, Rate Limiting, and Data Validation】设计安全API：开发人员的身份验证，速率限制和数据验证指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-apis-guide-to-authentication-rate-limiting-data-validation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;APIs have emerged as the cement of the contemporary application. APIs are at the heart of the movement of data, and the interaction of systems, whether in the form of mobile apps and web frontends or microservices and third-party integrations. However, along with this omnipresence there is exposure. Malicious actors will usually start with APIs to exploit low-security authentication, rate-limit bypass, and malicious payload injection. This article will examine some of the most important concepts that developers should use to create secure APIs; namely authentication, rate limiting, and input validation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Authentication: Controlling Access at the Door&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Authentication defines who can access your API and improper authentication is one of the most frequent reasons of data leakage. Although internal API use cases continue to use static API keys, newer systems are using tokens to provide more granular and scalable control, e.g. JWT (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/jwt-authentication-and-authorization-a-detailed-introduction&#34;&gt;JSON Web Tokens&lt;/a&gt;) or OAuth2.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; API已成为当代应用的水泥。 API是数据移动的核心，以及系统的相互作用，无论是移动应用程序和Web前端，微服务和第三方集成的形式。但是，随着这种无所不能的态度，还会有暴露。恶意演员通常会从API开始，以利用低安全性身份验证，速率限制旁路和恶意有效载荷注入。本文将研究开发人员应使用的一些最重要的概念来创建安全的API；即身份验证，速率限制和输入验证。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;身份验证：控制门上的访问&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;身份验证定义谁可以访问您的API，而身份验证不当是数据泄漏的最常见原因之一。尽管内部API用例继续使用静态API键，但较新的系统正在使用令牌来提供更详细和可扩展的控制，例如jwt（&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/jwt-authentication-and-authorization-a-detailed-indroduction”&gt; json web sokens &lt;/a&gt;）或oauth2。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Databricks DBRX vs OpenAI GPT-4o vs Claude 3: Which LLM Is Best for Enterprise Use Cases?】DataBricks DBRX与OpenAI GPT-4O vs Claude 3：哪个LLM最适合企业用例？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enterprise-ai-dbrx-gpt4o-claude3-comparison</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Enterprise AI has been shaped in new ways due to the fast development of large language models (LLMs). More companies are starting to use these models to enhance their approach to workflow, improve automated communication, make analyzing data easier, and develop smart applications. There are three leading language models in this fast-changing environment. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-llms-mixture-of-experts&#34;&gt;Databricks DBRX&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zapbot-building-a-chatbot-with-openai-and-gradio&#34;&gt;OpenAI’s GPT-4&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/use-anthropic-claude-3-models-to-build-generative&#34;&gt;Anthropic’s Claude 3&lt;/a&gt;. Every model offers a separate solution to the needs of enterprises with open-source flexibility, multi-modality, or ethical consideration.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Databricks DBRX: The Open-Source Powerhouse&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Databricks’ DBRX gives businesses a chance to manage and adapt their infrastructure more effectively. Only a part of its parameters are used for making inferences, so inference becomes quick and efficient. This is possible because of the design, which ensures it is very precise and smooth. DBRX has gained recognition for being open-source, giving users a chance to modify and edit the model they download for free. You may install the model in either the company’s private cloud or on their servers, which helps it to comply with their security protocols. Furthermore, using the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform allows companies to scale their use of LLM models easily and make sure they are properly managed and used. Those who have their data and systems internally can use DBRX to guarantee both transparency and excellent results.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Enterprise AI由于大型语言模型（LLMS）的快速发展而以新的方式形成。越来越多的公司开始使用这些模型来增强其工作流程的方法，改善自动通信，使分析数据更容易并开发智能应用程序。在这种快速变化的环境中，有三种领先的语言模型。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-llms-mixture-of-experts”&gt; databricks dbrx &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/articles/articles/articles/articles/Articles/Zapbot-building-a-apbot-building-a-chatbot-with-with-with-with-with-with-popenai- and obai and aboi and aboi and &lt;/aboit &lt;/aboi &lt;/abai and &lt;ai&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/use-anthropic-claude-3-models-to-build-generative”&gt; Anthropic的Claude 3 &lt;/a&gt;。每个模型都可以单独解决具有开源灵活性，多模式或道德考虑的企业需求的单独解决方案。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Databricks DBRX：开源PowerHouse &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Databricks的DBRX为企业提供了更有效地管理和调整其基础架构的机会。仅使用其参数的一部分来推断，因此推理变得快速有效。这是可能的，因为设计可确保它非常精确和光滑。 DBRX因开源而获得了认可，使用户有机会免费修改和编辑他们免费下载的模型。您可以在公司的私有云或服务器上安装模型，这有助于其遵守其安全协议。此外，使用Databricks Data Intelligence平台允许公司轻松扩展其对LLM模型的使用，并确保它们得到了正确的管理和使用。那些内部具有数据和系统的人可以使用DBRX来保证透明度和出色的结果。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Boosting Algorithms Demystified: A Deep Dive into XGBoost With Code and Explanation】增强算法脱颖而出：用代码和解释深入研究XGBoost</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/xgboost-deep-dive</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Boosting algorithms have become a staple in the machine learning world, particularly for structured/tabular data. Among these, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/predicting-ad-viewability-xgboost-regressor&#34;&gt;XGBoost&lt;/a&gt; (Extreme Gradient Boosting) stands out as one of the most widely used and effective techniques. From winning Kaggle competitions to production-level applications, XGBoost consistently delivers top-tier performance. This post aims to provide a comprehensive and technically detailed exploration of boosting, focusing specifically on XGBoost, complete with concepts, practical insights, and experimental strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Foundation: What Is Boosting?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/xgboost-a-deep-dive-into-boosting&#34;&gt;Boosting&lt;/a&gt; is an ensemble technique designed to convert a set of weak learners into a strong one. It builds models sequentially, each new model attempting to correct the errors made by the previous ones. The core idea is not just averaging predictions (like bagging) but optimizing the overall model by learning from residuals or gradients.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;增强算法已成为机器学习世界中的主食，尤其是对于结构化/表格数据。其中，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/predicting-ad-viewability-viewability-xgboost-regressor”&gt; xgboost &lt;/a&gt;（极端的梯度增强）脱颖而出，是最广泛使用和有效的技术之一。从赢得Kaggle比赛到生产级别的应用程序，Xgboost始终提供顶级性能。这篇文章旨在提供对提升的全面且技术详细的探索，专门针对Xgboost，包括概念，实践见解和实验策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;基础：什么是提升？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/xgboost-a-deep-dive-into-boosting”&gt;增强&lt;/a&gt;是一种合奏技术，旨在将一组弱小的学习者转换为强大的学习者。它依次构建模型，每个新模型都试图纠正以前的模型。核心思想不仅是平均预测（例如包装），而且是通过从残留物或梯度中学习来优化整体模型。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Adaptive Modular Monolith Concept】自适应模块化整体概念</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/adaptive-modular-monolith-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/microservices-vs-monoliths-choosing-the-right-architecture&#34;&gt;Modular Monolith&lt;/a&gt; architecture is reshaping how software systems are built and evolved. Although splitting modules into independent microservices typically requires significant efforts - such as repackaging, redeployment, and reconfiguration - an ideal architecture would allow modules to be spun off as independent services effortlessly, without these manual steps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This capability distinguishes the Adaptive Modular Monolith concept from both traditional monoliths and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/microservices&#34;&gt;microservices&lt;/a&gt;, providing a seamless, evolutionary path from simple development to scalable, flexible architectures on demand. It would enable starting with a unified, modular application and later extracting modules as standalone services with minimal overhead, combining the benefits of both monoliths and microservices in one system.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/microservices-vs-monoliths-choosing-choosing-the-right-architecture”&gt;模块化单片&lt;/a&gt;架构正在重塑软件系统的构建方式和进化。尽管将模块分成独立的微服务通常需要重大努力（例如重新包装，重新部署和重新配置），但理想的体系结构将允许模块毫不费力地将模块旋转为独立服务，而没有这些手动步骤。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种能力将自适应模块化整体概念与传统的整体概念区分开，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/microservices”&gt; microservices &lt;/a&gt;，提供了从简单开发到可伸缩的，可伸缩的，可伸缩的，可柔韧的体系图，提供了无缝的进化路径。它将从一个统一的模块化应用程序开始，然后将模块作为独立服务提取，并将模块作为最小开销，将整体和微服务的好处结合在一起。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【State Machines Behind the Scenes of Flight Booking and Payments】国家机器幕后预订和付款</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/saga-state-machine-flight-booking</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern flight booking and payment systems are composed of numerous steps spanning multiple services. For example, an airline booking might involve one service to &lt;strong&gt;reserve a seat&lt;/strong&gt;, another to &lt;strong&gt;process payment&lt;/strong&gt;, and a third to &lt;strong&gt;issue the ticket&lt;/strong&gt; (confirm the seat). All these steps must succeed to complete the booking; if any step fails, the prior steps’ effects should be undone to avoid inconsistencies. In a monolithic system, a single ACID transaction might handle this. But in a distributed microservices architecture, no single transaction can easily encompass seat inventory and payment across systems. As one article notes, &lt;em&gt;in a flight booking scenario, a seat-reservation microservice cannot acquire a lock on the payment database (often an external service), so a different approach to transaction management is required&lt;/em&gt; – one that embraces loose coupling and eventual consistency . This is where &lt;strong&gt;state machines&lt;/strong&gt; and the saga pattern come into play.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;state machine&lt;/strong&gt; models a process as a series of discrete &lt;strong&gt;states&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;transitions&lt;/strong&gt; in response to events. We can define states corresponding to each stage of booking (seat selection, fare held, payment processing, ticket issued, etc.) and transitions triggered by events like “payment successful” or “seat hold expired.” For example, a travel booking flow might have states such as &lt;em&gt;Booking Flight&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Booking Hotel&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Booking Car&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Confirmation&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Error&lt;/em&gt;. Events then drive transitions between these states: e.g. a &lt;strong&gt;Flight booked&lt;/strong&gt; event moves from &lt;em&gt;Booking Flight&lt;/em&gt; to the next state, whereas a &lt;strong&gt;Flight booking failed&lt;/strong&gt; event transitions to an &lt;em&gt;Error&lt;/em&gt; state. Time-based events like &lt;strong&gt;Fare hold timeout&lt;/strong&gt; are also part of the model . By enumerating all success and failure events (including timeouts), engineers can explicitly capture how the system should react at each step, ensuring no outcome is overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代的飞行预订和支付系统由跨越多个服务的许多步骤组成。例如，航空公司的预订可能涉及一项服务&lt;strong&gt;预留席位&lt;/strong&gt;，另一个用于&lt;strong&gt;流程付款&lt;/strong&gt;，第三到&lt;strong&gt;发行票证&lt;/strong&gt;（确认座位）。所有这些步骤必须成功完成预订；如果任何步骤失败，则应撤消先前的步骤的效果，以避免不一致。在整体系统中，单个酸性交易可能会处理这一点。但是在分布式微服务体系结构中，没有任何一笔交易可以轻松地包含跨系统的座位清单和付款。正如一篇文章所指出的那样，在飞行预订方案中，座位保留微服务无法在付款数据库中获得锁定（通常是外部服务），因此需要另一种交易管理方法&lt;/em&gt;  - 一种具有松散的coupling coupling和最终的一致性。这是&lt;strong&gt;状态机&lt;/strong&gt;和传奇图案发挥作用的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; a &lt;strong&gt;状态机&lt;/strong&gt;模拟一个过程作为一系列离散&lt;strong&gt;状态&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;过渡&lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt;响应事件。我们可以定义与预订的每个阶段相对应的州（座位选择，票价，付款处理，发行的票务等）以及由“付款成功”或“座位持有过期”等事件触发的过渡。例如，旅行预订流量可能具有&lt;em&gt;预订航班&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;em&gt;预订酒店&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;em&gt;预订汽车&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;em&gt;确认&lt;/em&gt;和&lt;em&gt;错误&lt;/em&gt;。事件然后驱动这些状态之间的过渡：例如&lt;strong&gt;航班预订&lt;/strong&gt;事件从预订航班&lt;/em&gt;移动到下一个状态，而&lt;strong&gt;飞行预订失败&lt;/strong&gt;事件过渡到&lt;em&gt; error &lt;/em&gt;状态。基于时间的事件，例如&lt;strong&gt;票价保留超时&lt;/strong&gt;也是模型的一部分。通过列举所有成功和故障事件（包括超时），工程师可以明确捕获系统在每个步骤中应如何反应，从而确保不忽略结果。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【CSS Hide and Seek: Choosing Between display: none and visibility: hidden】CSS隐藏和寻求：在显示之间选择：无与可见性：隐藏</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/css-display-none-vs-visibility-hidden</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;535&#34; data-start=&#34;516&#34;&gt;When it comes to hiding elements in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/corecss-part1&#34;&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;, developers often face a fundamental choice: should they use &lt;code&gt;display: none&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;visibility: hidden&lt;/code&gt;? While both properties can make elements disappear from view, they behave very differently under the hood. Understanding these differences is crucial for creating efficient, accessible, and maintainable web applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;535&#34; data-start=&#34;516&#34;&gt;The Core Difference&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The primary distinction between &lt;code&gt;display: none&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;visibility: hidden&lt;/code&gt; lies in how they affect the document flow and layout:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 535” data-start =“ 516”&gt;在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/corecss-part1”&gt; csss &lt;/a&gt;中隐藏元素时尽管这两种属性都可以使元素从视图中消失，但在引擎盖下它们的行为却大不相同。了解这些差异对于创建高效，可访问和可维护的Web应用程序至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end =“ 535” data-start =“ 516”&gt;核心差&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;code&gt;显示：无&lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt;可见性：隐藏&lt;/code&gt;在于它们如何影响文档流和布局：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【VB6 vs. C#: How to Migrate and Modernize Your Legacy Code】VB6与C＃：如何迁移和现代化您的旧版代码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vb6-vs-c-how-to-migrate-and-modernize-your-legacy</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Introduction to VB6 and C#: Why Modernization Matters&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Visual Basic 6 (VB6) was once a popular choice for Windows application development. However, as technology evolved, VB6 became outdated, with Microsoft officially ending support in 2008. Today, businesses relying on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/vb6-to-net-migration&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;VB6 applications&lt;/a&gt; face increasing security risks, compatibility issues, and maintenance challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In contrast, C#—a modern, object-oriented programming language developed by Microsoft—offers significant advantages, including enhanced security, cross-platform compatibility, and seamless integration with modern technologies like cloud computing and microservices.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt; VB6和C＃简介：为什么现代化重要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Visual Basic 6（VB6）曾经是Windows应用程序开发的流行选择。 However, as technology evolved, VB6 became outdated, with Microsoft officially ending support in 2008. Today, businesses relying on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/vb6-to-net-migration&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;VB6 applications&lt;/a&gt; face increasing security risks, compatibility issues, and maintenance挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;相比之下，C＃ - 一种由Microsoft开发的现代，面向对象的编程语言 - 取得了很大的优势，包括增强的安全性，跨平台兼容性以及与云计算和微服务等现代技术的无缝集成。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>