<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Tracing Stratoshark’s Roots: From Packet Capture to System Call Analysis】追踪Stratoshark的根源：从数据包捕获到系统呼叫分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/stratoshark-packet-capture-to-system-call-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;610&#34; data-start=&#34;138&#34;&gt;The journey that led to the creation of open-source &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/whitepapers/the-architecture-of-the-sysdig-container-intellige&#34;&gt;&lt;code data-end=&#34;198&#34; data-start=&#34;190&#34;&gt;Sysdig&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-falco-to-create-custom-identity-detections&#34;&gt;&lt;code data-end=&#34;210&#34; data-start=&#34;203&#34;&gt;Falco&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; traces its roots to packet capture—a domain where many of the original developers had honed their expertise over the years. This deep connection to network traffic analysis, combined with inspiration from technologies like &lt;code data-end=&#34;439&#34; data-start=&#34;434&#34;&gt;BPF&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code data-end=&#34;450&#34; data-start=&#34;441&#34;&gt;libpcap&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code data-end=&#34;461&#34; data-start=&#34;452&#34;&gt;tcpdump&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code data-end=&#34;474&#34; data-start=&#34;467&#34;&gt;Snort&lt;/code&gt;, laid the groundwork for innovations that extended packet capture principles into the evolving worlds of containers and cloud security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1194&#34; data-start=&#34;612&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/wireshark-amp-tcpdump-a-debugging-power-couple?fromrel=true&#34;&gt;&lt;code data-end=&#34;623&#34; data-start=&#34;612&#34;&gt;Wireshark&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a well-known network analysis tool that uses &lt;code data-end=&#34;681&#34; data-start=&#34;672&#34;&gt;libpcap&lt;/code&gt;, a user-level library for capturing and filtering packets. At its core, &lt;code data-end=&#34;765&#34; data-start=&#34;754&#34;&gt;Wireshark&lt;/code&gt; relies on &lt;code data-end=&#34;785&#34; data-start=&#34;776&#34;&gt;libpcap&lt;/code&gt;—a versatile library that manages live packet capture, filtering, and file handling. &lt;code data-end=&#34;879&#34; data-start=&#34;870&#34;&gt;Libpcap&lt;/code&gt; became a foundation for countless tools, providing a generic interface that could be extended to fit various needs. &lt;code data-end=&#34;1003&#34; data-is-only-node=&#34;&#34; data-start=&#34;996&#34;&gt;Snort&lt;/code&gt;, for instance, built a rule engine for network intrusion detection directly on top of &lt;code data-end=&#34;1099&#34; data-start=&#34;1090&#34;&gt;libpcap&lt;/code&gt;, leveraging its packet capture capabilities to detect and prevent suspicious network activity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 610” data-start =“ 138”&gt;导致创建开放式href =”的旅程href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/using-falco-to-to-to-to-to-custom-indistity-detections”&gt; &lt;code data-end =“ 210” data-start =“ 203”&gt; falco &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/a&gt;将其根源捕捉到包装捕获的范围 - 许多原始开发商的范围是许多原始开发商所赢得了他们的范围，以纪念他们的范围。 This deep connection to network traffic analysis, combined with inspiration from technologies like &lt;code data-end=&#34;439&#34; data-start=&#34;434&#34;&gt;BPF&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code data-end=&#34;450&#34; data-start=&#34;441&#34;&gt;libpcap&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code data-end=&#34;461&#34; data-start=&#34;452&#34;&gt;tcpdump&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code data-end =“ 474” data-start =“ 467”&gt; snort &lt;/code&gt;，为将数据包捕获原理扩展到不断发展的容器和云安全性的创新基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1194” data-start =“ 612”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/wireshark-amp-amp-tcpdump-tcpdump-a-debugging-power-power-power-power-couple?fromrel = fromrel = fromrel=true”&gt; &lt;代码data-end =“ 681” data-start =“ 672”&gt; libpcap &lt;/code&gt;，一个用于捕获和过滤数据包的用户级库。以&lt;code data-end =“ 765” data-start =“ 754”&gt; wireshark &lt;/code&gt;依赖于&lt;code data-end =“ 785” data-start =“ 776”&gt; libpcap &lt;/code&gt;  - 一个多功能库，它管理实时数据包捕获，过滤和文件处理。 &lt;Code Data-End =“ 879” data-start =“ 870”&gt; libpcap &lt;/code&gt;成为无数工具的基础，提供了可以扩展以适合各种需求的通用接口。 &lt;code data-end=&#34;1003&#34; data-is-only-node=&#34;&#34; data-start=&#34;996&#34;&gt;Snort&lt;/code&gt;, for instance, built a rule engine for network intrusion detection directly on top of &lt;code data-end=&#34;1099&#34; data-start=&#34;1090&#34;&gt;libpcap&lt;/code&gt;, leveraging its packet capture capabilities to detect and prevent suspicious network activity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Orchestrating Edge Computing with Kubernetes: Architectures, Challenges, and Emerging Solutions】使用Kubernetes编排边缘计算：建筑，挑战和新兴解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-edge-computing-architecture-challenges-solutions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;963&#34; data-start=&#34;282&#34;&gt;Edge computing has emerged as a transformative approach to handle data processing closer to the data source rather than relying on centralized cloud infrastructures. This is particularly important for real-time applications that demand low latency, higher bandwidth efficiency, and more autonomy in operations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;963&#34; data-start=&#34;282&#34;&gt;Kubernetes, an open-source container orchestration platform, has revolutionized how applications are deployed and managed across distributed systems. Its powerful orchestration capabilities make it an ideal solution for managing workloads in edge computing environments, where resources are often constrained, and the system architecture is highly decentralized.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 963” data-start =“ 282”&gt; Edge Computing已成为一种变革性的方法，可以将数据处理更接近数据源，而不是依靠集中式的云基础架构。这对于需要低潜伏期，更高的带宽效率和更多自主权的实时应用程序尤其重要。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 963” data-start =“ 282”&gt; kubernetes，一个开源容器编排平台，已彻底改变了如何在分布式系统中部署和管理应用程序的应用程序。它强大的编排功能使其成为管理在边缘计算环境中管理工作负载的理想解决方案，这些解决方案通常受到限制，并且系统体系结构高度分散。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding k-NN Search in Elasticsearch】在Elasticsearch中了解K-NN搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-k-nn-search-in-elasticsearch</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;205&#34; data-start=&#34;190&#34;&gt;Businesses are increasingly relying on intelligent search capabilities to enhance customer experience, automate insights, and unlock the potential of unstructured information. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-elasticsearch-1&#34;&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/a&gt;, a leading distributed search and analytics engine, is at the heart of many such systems. One of its powerful and lesser-known capabilities is support for k-nearest neighbors (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/primary-supervised-learning-algorithms-used-in-mac&#34;&gt;k-NN&lt;/a&gt;) search, a method particularly useful for similarity-based retrieval in domains such as semantic search, recommendation engines, and image recognition.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;937&#34; data-start=&#34;760&#34;&gt;This article delves into what Elasticsearch and k-NN search are, how the two are integrated, and how to configure and optimize k-NN in Elasticsearch for real-world applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 205” data-start =“ 190”&gt;企业越来越依赖智能搜索功能来增强客户体验，自动洞察并解锁非结构化信息的潜力。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-elasticsearch-1”&gt; Elasticsearch &lt;/a&gt;，是领先的分布式搜索和分析引擎，是许多此类系统的核心。 One of its powerful and lesser-known capabilities is support for k-nearest neighbors (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/primary-supervised-learning-algorithms-used-in-mac&#34;&gt;k-NN&lt;/a&gt;) search, a method particularly useful for similarity-based retrieval in domains such as semantic search, recommendation engines, and image recognition.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 937” data-start =“ 760”&gt;本文深入探讨了Elasticsearch和K-NN搜索的内容，两者的集成方式以及如何在elasticsearch中为真实世界应用程序配置和优化K-NN。&lt;/p&gt;&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build Your First Generative AI App With Langflow: A Step-by-Step Guide】如何使用langflow构建第一个生成AI应用程序：逐步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-genai-apps-with-langflow</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As you all know, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/trendreports/generative-ai&#34;&gt;Generative AI&lt;/a&gt; is reshaping how we build certain applications — but diving into &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/getting-started-with-langchain-for-beginners&#34;&gt;LangChain code&lt;/a&gt; or orchestrating complex pipelines can be intimidating for newcomers. That’s where I feel &lt;strong&gt;Langflow&lt;/strong&gt; comes in very handy for first-timers trying to explore and build such applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Langflow is a &lt;strong&gt;low-code, visual interface&lt;/strong&gt; that lets you prototype and deploy LLM-powered applications without writing a single line of backend code. Whether you&#39;re building a chatbot, a document summarizer, or a custom &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;retrieval-augmented generation (RAG)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; app — Langflow lets you do it &lt;strong&gt;visually and quickly&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;As you all know, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/trendreports/generative-ai&#34;&gt;Generative AI&lt;/a&gt; is reshaping how we build certain applications — but diving into &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/getting-started-with-langchain-for-beginners&#34;&gt;LangChain code&lt;/a&gt; or orchestrating对于新移民来说，复杂的管道可能令人生畏。这就是我感到&lt;strong&gt; langflow &lt;/strong&gt;对于试图探索和构建此类应用程序的初学者非常方便。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; langflow是&lt;strong&gt;低音，可视接口&lt;/strong&gt;，可让您在不编写单个后端代码的情况下进行原型和部署LLM驱动的应用程序。 Whether you&#39;re building a chatbot, a document summarizer, or a custom &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;retrieval-augmented generation (RAG)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; app — Langflow lets you do it &lt;strong&gt;visually and quickly&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Stop Building Monolithic AI Brains, Build a Specialist Team Instead】停止建造单片AI大脑，改为建立专业团队</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/multi-agent-ai-vs-monolithic</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;You’ve been there. You’ve got a killer app idea, and you want to sprinkle in some AI magic. The first instinct? Build a single, massive AI model—a &#34;genius brain&#34; that can handle anything a user throws at it. But let&#39;s be real, as soon as things get even a little complex, that approach starts to fall apart.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Your &#34;genius&#34; model becomes a jack-of-all-trades and a master of none. It gets confused, it becomes a massive bottleneck when traffic spikes, and trying to update one part of its knowledge is a complete nightmare. Sound familiar?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您去过那里。您有一个杀手级应用程序的想法，并且想撒一些AI魔术。第一个本能？构建一个单一的，庞大的AI模型 - 一种“天才大脑”，可以处理用户对其进行的任何操作。但是，让我们成为现实，一旦事情变得有些复杂，这种方法就会开始崩溃。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您的“天才”模型变成了全部贸易千斤顶，而无人的主人。它感到困惑，当交通峰值时，它变成了一个巨大的瓶颈，试图更新其知识的一部分是一场噩梦。听起来很熟悉？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Deploy Serverless Lambdas Confidently Using Canary】使用Canary自信地部署无服务器的Lambdas</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/canary-deployments-aws-lambda</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Releasing software quickly and safely is tough, but it’s becoming a basic expectation. The right setup can help teams deliver faster without losing reliability. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-ecs-vs-aws-lambda-top-5-main-differences&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AWS Lambda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;a popular serverless compute service, combined with continuous deployment practices and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-detailed-guide-to-canary-deployments-1&#34;&gt;canary release strategies&lt;/a&gt;, allows teams to deploy changes frequently while minimizing risk. This article explores the importance of continuous deployment, examines rolling vs. canary deployment strategies, and provides guidance on implementing canary releases for Lambda functions with best practices and pitfalls to avoid.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Importance of Continuous Deployment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Continuous deployment is the practice of releasing software updates in an automated, frequent manner. For businesses, this means new features and fixes get to users faster, enabling quicker feedback and adaptation to market needs. Frequent, small releases also reduce the risk associated with each deployment compared to large infrequent launches.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;快速，安全地发布软件是艰难的，但它已成为一个基本期望。正确的设置可以帮助团队更快地交付而不会失去可靠性。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/aws-ec-cs-vs-aws-aws-lambda-top-5-main-differences”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; aws lambda &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;grong&gt;，&lt;/strong&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a-detailed-guide-guide-to-canary-deployments-1”&gt;金丝雀释放策略&lt;/a&gt;，允许团队经常部署变化，而最小化风险。本文探讨了连续部署的重要性，检查滚动与加那利部署策略，并提供了针对Lambda功能的金丝雀发行的指导，并具有最佳实践和陷阱，以避免。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;连续部署的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;连续部署是以自动，频繁的方式释放软件更新的实践。对于企业而言，这意味着新功能和修复程序可以更快地吸引用户，从而更快地适应了市场需求。与大型发射相比</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Load Balancing Algorithms: Choosing the Right Strategy】最高负载平衡算法：选择正确的策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/load-balancing-algorithms-comparison</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern software applications need &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-load-balancers-optimizing-traffic-for-hi&#34;&gt;load balancing&lt;/a&gt; as an essential component when they expand across distributed systems and containerized environments and microservices architecture. The application system provides consistent user service through load balancing even when traffic increases or servers become unavailable. Different &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-system-design-a-comprehensive-guide-to-s&#34;&gt;load balancing strategies&lt;/a&gt; demonstrate varying levels of quality. The selection of a suitable load balancing &amp;nbsp;strategy depends on understanding system behavior during high loads and determining acceptable tradeoffs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This analysis examines the primary load balancing algorithms which divide into static and dynamic categories and examines the advantages and disadvantages of each approach together with recommendations for their appropriate deployment scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代软件应用程序需要&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-load-balancers-poptimizing-traffic-for-hi”&gt;负载平衡&lt;/a&gt;当它们跨分布式系统和集装环境和集装环境和MicroServices架构扩展时，它们是必不可少的组件。即使流量增加或无法使用，应用程序系统也通过负载平衡提供一致的用户服务。不同的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-system-design-a-comprehens-guide-guide-guide-to-s”&gt;负载平衡策略&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;表现出不同级别的质量。选择合适的负载平衡策略取决于在高负载和确定可接受的权衡期间了解系统行为。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此分析检查了主要负载平衡算法，该算法分为静态和动态类别，并检查每种方法的优点和缺点，以及针对其适当部署方案的建议。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Software Engineer’s Guide to Thrive in Gen AI Era: Master It or Fade Out】软件工程师在AI Gen Era中蓬勃发展的指南：掌握或淡出</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-software-engineers-guide-to-thrive-in-gen-ai-era</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/trendreports/generative-ai&#34;&gt;Gen AI&lt;/a&gt; is everywhere, seriously shaking things up in our world, and having expertise in this technology has become a critical skill for landing job interviews. According to this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2025-03-31-gartner-forecasts-worldwide-genai-spending-to-reach-644-billion-in-2025&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Gartner report&lt;/a&gt;, global spending on Gen AI is expected to reach $644 billion in 2025 (76.4% increase from 2024). It also notes that despite high failure rate for Gen AI PoCs (proof-of-concept), foundation model providers continue to pour billions of dollars annually to enhance model’s size, performance and reliability, signaling strong confidence in future.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;During the COVID-19 pandemic, software engineers were in high demand, commanding top salaries as companies scrambled to hire talent capable of tackling complex challenges. However, there was a market reset by 2022 where the industry &lt;a href=&#34;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/layoffs-techs-year-of-efficiency-continues-as-wall-street-cheers-on-silicon-valley-090030081.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;pivoted toward efficiency&lt;/a&gt;, and the arrival of ChatGPT marked a transformative shift, redefining roles and accelerating AI integration across the tech sector.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/trendreports/generative-ai”&gt; gen ai &lt;/a&gt;无处不在，在我们的世界中严重震撼了一切，并且在这项技术方面拥有专业知识已成为着陆工作面试的关键技能。根据此&lt;a href =“ https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2025-03-03-03-31-gartner-forecasts-worldwide-genai-genai-genai-genai-genai to-reach-64444444444444444444444444-billion-in-billion-in-2025 AI预计在2025年将达到6440亿美元（从2024年增长76.4％）。它还指出，尽管AI Gen POC（概念证明）的失败率很高，但基金会模型提供商每年继续倾注数十亿美元，以提高模型的规模，性能和可靠性，并对未来的强烈信心表示信心。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在COVID-19大流行期间，软件工程师的需求很高，随着公司争先恐后地雇用能够应对复杂挑战的人才，因此指挥了最高工资。但是，到2022年有一个市场重置，该行业&lt;a href =“ https://finance.yahoo.com/news/layoffs-techs-techs-techs-techs-techs-techs-continues-continues-continues-as-as-wall-cheeers-on-cheers-on-silicon-on-silicon-valley-valley-valley-090030081.html”效率&lt;/a&gt;，Chatgpt的到来标志着变革性的转变，重新定义了角色并加速了整个技术领域的AI集成。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Developers Are Driving Supply Chain Innovation With Modern Tech】开发人员如何通过现代技术推动供应链创新</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/redefining-supply-chains-through-tech-a-developers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern supply chains are under increasing pressure. The old models cannot keep up, from disrupted logistics during global crises to rising consumer expectations for speed and transparency. As a developer who has worked with logistics systems and enterprise software, I have seen firsthand where the cracks are and, more importantly, how to build smarter, leaner, and more responsive supply chains using technology. This blog is not a broad overview as it is a technical take on how developers and engineers can inject innovation directly into supply chain systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API-First Architecture to Break Silos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many supply chains still run on fragmented systems: separate platforms for procurement, inventory, logistics, and fulfillment. These silos slow everything down and make real-time decision-making nearly impossible. An API-first strategy is key to integrating these systems and enabling better data flows&amp;nbsp;across the board.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代供应链的压力正在增加。从全球危机期间的后勤工作到消费者对速度和透明度的期望不断提高，旧模型无法跟上。作为一名使用物流系统和企业软件合作的开发人员，我已经亲眼目睹了裂缝所在的地方，更重要的是，如何使用技术构建更智能，更精简和更响应式的供应链。该博客并不是广泛的概述，因为它是开发人员和工程师如何将创新直接注入供应链系统的技术性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; API-Fir-Fir-Fir-Fir-trake break slos &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多供应链仍在零散的系统上运行：采购，库存，物流和履行的单独平台。这些筒仓减慢一切，使实时决策几乎不可能。 API优先的策略是集成这些系统并实现更好的数据流的关键。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The QA Paradox: To Save Artificial Intelligence, We Must Stop Blindly Trusting Data—And Start Trusting Human Judgment】质量检查悖论：为了节省人工智能，我们必须停止盲目信任数据，并开始信任人类的判断</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/qa-paradox-human-judgment-in-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Artificial Intelligence is undoubtedly driving a generational shift in our current society. However, excessive reliance on data can threaten its credibility and introduce risks. Generative AI models produce convincingly erroneous information (Farid, 2024; NewsGuard, 2025), while biased algorithms perpetuate and amplify societal inequalities (AIMultiple, 2024; UN Women, 2025). This reliance on data—AI’s greatest strength—becomes its critical vulnerability. A flawed, incomplete, or unrepresentative dataset reflecting our diverse world adds further complexity to AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We need a fundamental shift in quality assurance (QA) approaches to extract AI&#39;s transformative potential while mitigating its inherent risks. Implicit trust in data-driven outputs is no longer tenable. Human QA professionals’ nuanced, contextual, and ethical judgment must be elevated as an essential corrective. This article advocates for rebalancing the equation: augmenting data-driven insights with irreplaceable human judgment to ensure AI serves humanity equitably and responsibly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能无疑是推动我们当前社会的世代转变。但是，过度依赖数据会威胁其信誉并引入风险。生成的AI模型产生了令人信服的错误信息（Farid，2024; Newsguard，2025），而偏见的算法使社会不平等永存和扩大（Aimultiph，2024； UN妇女，2025年）。这种对数据的依赖（ai是最大的优势）使其至关重要的脆弱性。反映我们多样化世界的有缺陷，不完整或不代表性的数据集为AI增添了复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们需要在质量保证（QA）方法上进行基本转变，以提取AI的变革潜力，同时减轻其固有的风险。对数据驱动的输出的隐性信任不再是可行的。人类质量保证专业人员的细微差别，背景和道德判断必须提升为基本纠正措施。本文主张重新平衡方程：以不可替代的人类判断来增强数据驱动的见解，以确保AI平等，负责任地为人类服务。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>