<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AI/ML Big Data-Driven Policy: Insights Into Governance and Social Welfare】AI/ML大数据驱动政策：对治理和社会福利的见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-driven-policy-insights-governance-social-welfare</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;clutterFree_existingDuplicate clutterFree_noIcon cf_div_theme_dark&#34; href=&#34;https://www.datatopolicy.org/navigator/turn-data-into-policy#:~:text=Data%2Ddriven%20policy%20actions%20help,than%20&#39;responsive&#39;%20decision%20making.&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Data-driven policy&lt;/a&gt; refers to the practice of using data, analytics, and empirical evidence to inform and guide government decision-making, moving beyond reliance on intuition or anecdotal information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Governments must be agile, transparent, and resilient in their decision-making. The convergence of big data, cloud computing, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-ml-and-data-science&#34;&gt;AI/ML&lt;/a&gt; is enabling a new era of data-driven policy, transforming how societies anticipate challenges and adapt to change. This article explores the impact of data-driven governance, illustrated with real-world examples, statistics, and diagrams.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a class =“ clutterfree_existingDuplate clutterfree_noicon cf_div_theme_dark” href =“ https://www.datatopolicy.org/navigator/turn-data-into-policy#:~:: text = data%2Ddriven%20policy%20policy%20Actions%20help,than%20&#39;Responsive&#39;Responsive&#39;Responsive&#39;pponsive&#39;pmponsive&#39;%20Decision 20making。” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt;数据驱动的策略&lt;/a&gt;是指使用数据，分析和经验证据的实践，以告知和指导政府的决策，超越对直觉或anecdotal信息的依赖。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;政府必须在决策中敏捷，透明和弹性。大数据，云计算和&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-ml-and-data-science”&gt; ai/ml &lt;/a&gt;的收敛性正在实现数据驱动的政策的新时代，从而改变了社会的预期挑战和挑战的方式。本文探讨了数据驱动治理的影响，并用现实世界的示例，统计和图表进行了说明。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unveiling Supply Chain Transformation: IIoT and Digital Twins】揭幕供应链转换：IIOT和Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/supply-chain-transformation-iiot-digital-twins</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Digital twins and IIoTs are evolving technologies that are transforming the digital landscape of supply chain transformation. The IIoT aims to connect to actual physical sensors and actuators. On the other hand, DTs are replica copies that virtually represent the physical components. The DTs are invaluable for testing and simulating design parameters instead of disrupting production elements. Still, the adoption of both technologies remains limited in real-world scenarios. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This article explains the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) and digital twins (DT) technologies, and how they transform business and the global environment to optimize supply chain ecosystems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;数字双胞胎和IIOT是不断发展的技术，这些技术正在改变供应链变换的数字景观。 IIOT旨在与实际的物理传感器和执行器联系起来。另一方面，DTS是几乎代表物理组件的复制副本。 DTS对于测试和模拟设计参数而不是破坏生产元素是无价的。尽管如此，在实际情况下，两种技术的采用仍然有限。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;本文解释了工业互联网（IIOT）和数字双胞胎（DT）技术，以及它们如何改变业务和全球环境以优化供应链生态系统。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Mobile App Performance Matters More Than You Think】为什么移动应用程序性能比您想象的重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-mobile-app-performance-matters</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Performance Is the Heartbeat of Mobile Apps&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Think about it, on average, a smartphone user spends about 4 hours each day interacting with mobile apps. Given this extensive usage, even minor performance issues, such as brief lags or occasional app crashes, can become instantly noticeable. More often than not, users won&#39;t raise complaints. Instead, they&#39;ll quietly uninstall the app and move on to a competitor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s competitive app market, you often don&#39;t get a second chance. Industry research emphasizes that the majority of users abandon digital experiences that take longer than 3 to 5 seconds to load, whether it&#39;s a mobile web page or a native application (&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.google/products/admanager/the-need-for-mobile-speed/?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;blog.google&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apmdigest.com/mobile-apps-launch-3-seconds?utm_source=chatgpt.com&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;apmdigest.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;). Sluggish performance isn&#39;t just a nuisance, but it&#39;s a silent killer of user retention and hence revenue.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;性能是移动应用的心跳&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;平均而言，智能手机用户每天花费大约4个小时与移动应用程序进行互动。鉴于这种广泛的用法，即使是短暂的滞后或偶尔的应用程序崩溃，甚至可能会立即引人注目。用户通常不会提出投诉。相反，他们会悄悄卸载该应用程序并继续访问竞争对手。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在当今竞争激烈的应用市场中，您通常不会获得第二次机会。行业研究强调，大多数用户放弃加载需要超过3到5秒钟的数字体验，无论是移动网页还是本机应用程序（&lt;a href =“ https://blog..google/products/admanager/the--need-need-for-for-mobile-mobile-mobile-mobile-mobile-mobile-mobile-mobile-speed/----------------------- target =“ _ blank”&gt; &lt;em&gt; blog.google &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ https://www.apmdigest.com/mobile-apps-launch-3-seconds?utm_source = chatgpt.com target =“ _ blank”&gt; &lt;em&gt; apmdigest.com &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;）。表现缓慢，不仅是一个麻烦，而且是用户保留和收入的沉默杀手。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Data Pipelines in Cloud-Based Systems: Tools and Techniques】优化基于云的系统中的数据管道：工具和技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-data-pipelines-cloud-tools-techniques</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Data pipelines play a critical role in today&#39;s cloud ecosystems, enabling the processing and transfer of vast amounts of data between sources and targets. As more companies move to the cloud, it is imperative that these pipelines are optimized to deliver scalability, performance, and cost savings. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s take a look at the tools and methods that can be used to optimize data pipelines in the cloud, along with real-world code examples and best practices to maximize performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据管道在当今的云生态系统中起着至关重要的作用，从而实现了来源和目标之间大量数据的处理和传输。随着越来越多的公司转移到云中，必须优化这些管道以提供可扩展性，性能和成本节省。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们看一下可用于优化云中数据管道的工具和方法，以及现实世界中的代码示例和最佳实践，以最大程度地提高性能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advanced Java Garbage Collection Concepts: Weak References, Finalization, and Memory Leaks】高级Java垃圾收集概念：弱参考，最终确定和内存泄漏</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-java-garbage-collection-concepts</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;WeakReference()&lt;/code&gt; class in Java is often touted as being the answer to memory leaks. However, weak references on their own are not necessarily the answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Memory leaks are one of the hardest issues to diagnose. This article looks at a scenario where using weak references in conjunction with an object’s &lt;code&gt;finalize()&lt;/code&gt; method can result in a memory leak.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Java中的&lt;code&gt; feefReference（）&lt;/code&gt;类通常被吹捧为记忆泄漏的答案。但是，本身不一定是答案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;内存泄漏是最难诊断的问题之一。本文查看一个方案，其中使用弱参考与对象的&lt;code&gt; finalize（）&lt;/code&gt;方法结合使用可能导致内存泄漏。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Storage-Computing Integration vs. Separation: Architectural Trade-offs, Use Cases, and Insights from Apache Doris】存储计算集成与分离：建筑折衷，用例和Apache Doris的见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/storage-computing-integration-vs-separation-doris</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In the field of databases and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-trustworthy-is-big-data&#34;&gt;big data&lt;/a&gt;, the architectural debate between “storage-computing integration” and “storage-computing separation” has never ceased. Some people question, “Is storage-computing separation really necessary? Isn’t the performance of local disks sufficient?” The answer is not black and white — the key to technology selection lies in the precise matching of business scenarios and resource requirements. This article takes &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/apache-doris-deepseek-integration&#34;&gt;Apache Doris&lt;/a&gt; as an example to analyze the essential differences, advantages and disadvantages, and implementation scenarios of the two architectures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Storage-Computing Integration vs. Storage-Computing Separation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Storage-Computing Integration: The Tightly-Coupled “All-Rounder”&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Definition: Data storage and computing resources are bound to the same node (such as a local disk + server), and local reading and writing are used to reduce network overhead. Typical examples include the early architecture of Hadoop and traditional OLTP databases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;P Data-Selectable-paragraph =“”&gt;在数据库领域和&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-trustworthy-is-big-data”&gt;大数据&gt;大数据&gt;有人问：“储存分离真的需要吗？当地磁盘的性能是否足够吗？”答案不是黑色和白色，而是技术选择的关键在于业务场景和资源需求的精确匹配。本文以&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/apache-doris-deepseek-integration”&gt; apache doris &lt;/a&gt;作为分析两个架构的本质差异，优势和劣势，并实现的情况。&#xA;&lt;H2数据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;存储计算集成与存储计算分离&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3数据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;存储计算集成：紧密耦合的“全能器” &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据可选 -  paragraph =“”&gt;定义：数据存储和计算资源绑定到同一节点（例如本地磁盘 +服务器），并且本地读取和写入用于减少网络开销。典型的示例包括Hadoop和传统OLTP数据库的早期体系结构。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes Admission Controllers: Your First Line of Defense】Kubernetes录取控制者：您的第一道防线</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-admission-controllers-security-compliance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/open-policy-agent-with-kubernetes-part-one&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Admission Controllers&lt;/a&gt; are a powerful but often overlooked security mechanism. Acting as gatekeepers, they intercept API server requests before objects are persisted in etcd, allowing you to enforce custom policies or inject configurations automatically. Whether it&#39;s blocking privileged containers or ensuring labels are in place, Admission Controllers play a crucial role in securing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-the-power-of-robust-kubernetes-clusters&#34;&gt;Kubernetes clusters&lt;/a&gt; from the inside out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Are Admission Controllers?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Admission Controllers are plugins that govern and modify requests to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/advanced-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes API server&lt;/a&gt;. There are two types:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/open-policy-agent-with-kubernetes-part-one”&gt; kubernetes录取控制器&lt;/a&gt;是一种强大但经常被忽略的安全机制。他们充当网守，他们在持续在etcd中的对象之前拦截了API服务器请求，从而使您可以自动执行自定义策略或注射配置。无论是阻止特权容器还是确保标签到位，入场控制器在确保&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-power-the-power-the-power-the-power-the-power-the-pow------------------kubernetes-clusters”中起着至关重要的作用。&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是入场控制器？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;录取控制器是插件，它管理和修改请求到&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/advanced-kubernetes”&gt; kubernetes api server &lt;/a&gt;。有两种类型：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Salesforce API Integration Guide】Salesforce API集成指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/salesforce-api-integration-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Businesses need seamless communication between Salesforce CRM and external systems. Salesforce API integration enables real-time data flow, eliminating silos that cause operational inefficiencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the API &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.researchandmarkets.com/reports/4758232/api-management-market-by-platform-api-gateways&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;management market reaching&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;$7.67B in 2024, these integrations have become essential for scaling operations and delivering personalized experiences while reducing manual work.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;企业需要Salesforce CRM和外部系统之间的无缝通信。 Salesforce API集成实现了实时数据流，消除了导致运营效率低下的筒仓。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;带有api &lt;a href =“ https://www.researchandmarkets.com/reports/4758232/4758232/ap-management-market-market-by-platform-api-gateways”在减少手动工作的同时，运营和提供个性化的经验​​。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Test Multi-Threaded and Concurrent Java】如何测试多线程和并发Java</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/test-multi-threaded-concurrent-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Testing multi-threaded, concurrent Java code is difficult because each test run only captures one possible thread interleaving, and those interleavings are non-deterministic.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address this, I created the open-source tool &lt;a href=&#34;https://vmlens.com&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;VMLens&lt;/a&gt;. VMLens allows you to test concurrent Java code in a deterministic and reproducible way by executing all possible thread interleavings.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;测试多线程，并发Java代码很困难，因为每个测试仅捕获一个可能的线程相互交织，而这些交织是非确定性的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了解决这个问题，我创建了开源工具&lt;a href =“ https://vmlens.com” rel =“ noopener” target =“ _ blank”&gt; vmlens &lt;/a&gt;。 VMLEN允许您通过执行所有可能的线程交织来以确定性和可重复的方式测试并发Java代码。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Distributed Rate Limiting in Java: A Deep Dive into Bucket4j + PostgreSQL】Java中的分布率限制：深入研究Bucket4J + PostgreSQL</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/distributed-rate-limiting-java-bucket4j-postgresql</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important note:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are implementation details for the integration between PostgreSQL and the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/bucket4j/bucket4j&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;bucket4j library,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;specifically for&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;version 8.14.0. The post&#39;s author is not responsible for future changes, but I&#39;m 90% sure that it will be accurate for a long time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;重要说明：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span style =“ margin：0px; padding：0px;“&gt; &lt;em&gt;有实现详细信息，用于在PostgreSql和&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/github.com/bucket4j/bucket4j/bucket4j/bucket4j”目标=“目标=”&gt; &lt;em&gt; em&gt; em&gt; bucket4 j之间的&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“库，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;专门针对&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;版本8.14.0。帖子的作者对将来的变化不承担任何责任，但是我90％肯定会很长一段时间都准确。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大家好！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>