<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Reclaiming the Architect’s Role in the SDLC】收回建筑师在SDLC中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/reclaiming-the-architects-role-in-the-sdlc</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Over the past decade and a half, following the general shift away from the waterfall model, the industry has increasingly underutilized the expertise of software architects. The pendulum swung almost to the point of making any design work feel redundant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Strong software design and continuous architecture validation are essential for building efficient and reliable systems in real-world applications. Development teams should embed these practices in every iteration of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-complete-guide-to-sdlc&#34;&gt;software development lifecycle&lt;/a&gt; (SDLC) — dynamic enough to guide architectural decisions yet lightweight enough not to slow development down. The same goes for documentation: it’s a valuable part of design work, but many modern engineering teams struggle to create and maintain it effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在过去的十年半中，随着瀑布模型的一般性转移，该行业越来越多地利用了软件架构师的专业知识。钟摆几乎挥舞着使任何设计工作都感到多余。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;强大的软件设计和连续体系结构验证对于在现实世界应用中构建有效和可靠的系统至关重要。开发团队应将这些实践嵌入到&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/the-complete-guide-to-sdlc”&gt;软件开发生命周期&lt;/a&gt;（sdlc）的每一次迭代中 - 足以指导建筑决策，但轻度的功能足够轻巧，无法放慢发展。文档也是如此：这是设计工作的重要组成部分，但是许多现代工程团队都在努力有效地创建和维护它。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Netflix: Why Fintech Recommendations Need a Completely Different Playbook】超越Netflix：为什么金融科技建议需要一本完全不同的剧本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fintech-recommendation-system-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Let’s dive into how to create a recommendation system for fintech—hearing for the first time? But don’t worry, I’ll break it down into bite-sized pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Unique Nature of Financial Recommendations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First off, financial recommendations are a whole different ballgame compared to those you’d get from Netflix or an online store. If Netflix suggests a bad movie, it’s just 90 minutes wasted. But if a fintech app makes a bad investment suggestion, folks could lose their hard-earned savings.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;让我们深入研究如何为金融科技创建推荐系统 - 首次讲话吗？但是请放心，我会将其分解成一口大小的碎片。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;财务建议的独特性质&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，与您从Netflix或在线商店获得的财务建议相比，财务建议是完全不同的球。如果Netflix建议一部糟糕的电影，那就浪费了90分钟。但是，如果金融科技应用程序提出了不好的投资建议，那么人们可能会失去辛苦赚来的积蓄。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Next Frontier in Cybersecurity: Securing AI Agents Is Now Critical and Most Companies Aren’t Ready】网络安全领域的下一个边界：确保AI代理商现在很关键，大多数公司还没有准备好</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agent-security-framework</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;You can’t secure what you don’t understand, and right now, most enterprises don’t understand the thing running half their operations. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agentic-101-understanding-ai-agents&#34;&gt;Autonomous AI agents&lt;/a&gt; are here. They’re booking appointments, executing trades, handling customer complaints, and doing it all without waiting for human permission. But while businesses are busy chasing the productivity boost, they’re sleepwalking into the next generation of cyber threats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In 2024, we passed a quiet milestone: AI agents started negotiating, transacting, and integrating across APIs with minimal human input. These aren’t smart scripts. They’re adaptive, goal-seeking digital operators. And they’re already poking holes in the security assumptions that have held up for the past two decades.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您无法确保自己不了解的内容，而现在，大多数企业都不了解运行一半操作的东西。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agentic-101-undercanding-ai-agents”&gt;自治AI代理&lt;/a&gt;在这里。他们正在预订约会，执行交易，处理客户投诉并做到这一点，而无需等待人类许可。但是，虽然企业正忙着追求生产力提升，但他们正在进入下一代网络威胁。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在2024年，我们通过了一个安静的里程碑：AI代理人开始谈判，交易和整合API，并以最少的人类输入进行谈判。这些不是智能脚本。他们是自适应，寻求目标的数字操作员。他们已经在过去二十年来一直在保证的安全假设中打孔了。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Myth of In-Place Patching: Unpacking Protocol Buffers, FieldMasks, and the &#34;Last Field Wins&#34; Conundrum】现场修补的神话：解开协议缓冲区，fieldmasks和“最后一个场”胜利。</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/in-place-patching-protocol-buffers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Data serialization frameworks like &lt;strong&gt;Google Protocol Buffers (Protobuf)&lt;/strong&gt; have become indispensable. They offer compact binary formats and efficient parsing, making them ideal for everything from inter-service communication to persistent data storage. But when it comes to updating just a small part of an already serialized data blob, a common question arises: can we &#34;patch&#34; it directly, avoiding the overhead of reading, modifying, and rewriting the entire thing?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The short answer, for most practical purposes, is &lt;strong&gt;no&lt;/strong&gt;. While Protobuf provides clever mechanisms that seem to offer direct patching, the reality is more nuanced. Let&#39;s dive into why the full &#34;read-modify-write&#34; cycle remains largely unavoidable and where the true efficiencies lie.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据序列化框架（例如&lt;strong&gt; Google协议缓冲区（ProtoBuf）&lt;/strong&gt;）已变得必不可少。他们提供紧凑的二进制格式和有效的解析，使其非常适合从服务间通信到持续数据存储。但是，仅更新已经序列化的数据斑点的一小部分时，出现了一个常见的问题：我们可以直接“修补”它，避免阅读，修改和重写整个内容的开销？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;出于大多数实际目的，简短的答案是&lt;strong&gt; no &lt;/strong&gt;。尽管Protobuf提供了似乎可以直接修补的巧妙机制，但现实却更加细微。让我们深入了解为什么完整的“读取 - 修改 - 写入”周期在很大程度上不可避免以及真正的效率所在的位置。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How OpenTelemetry Improved Its Code Integrity for Arm64 by Working With Ampere®】OpenTelemetry如何通过与Ampere®合作改善ARM64的代码完整性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-opentelemetry-improved-arm64-code-integrity</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Snapshot&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Challenge:&lt;/strong&gt; Software developers and IT managers need instrumentation and metrics to measure software behavior. When developers and DevOps professionals assume that software will run on a single hardware architecture, they may be overlooking architecture-specific behavior. Arm64-based servers, including the Ampere® Altra® family of processors, offer performance improvements and energy savings over x86, but the underlying architecture is Arm64, which behaves differently to the x86 architecture at a very low level. At the time, mid-2023, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-opentelemetry&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; did not formally support Arm64 deployments. As the popularity of Arm64 instances increased because of their competitive price-performance, monitoring those systems was critical for observability vendors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Solution:&lt;/strong&gt; To help rectify that situation, Ampere Computing donated Ampere Altra-powered servers to the OpenTelemetry team. With these processors, the team could begin retrofitting their telemetry instrumentation for Arm64, and adapting their &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/nodejs&#34;&gt;Node.js&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-python&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; code for the Arm64 architecture.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;快照&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;挑战：&lt;/strong&gt;软件开发人员和IT经理需要仪器和指标来衡量软件行为。当开发人员和DevOps专业人员认为软件将在单个硬件体系结构上运行时，他们可能会忽略特定于架构的行为。基于ARM64的服务器，包括Ampere®Altra®处理器家族，提供了X86的性能改进和节能，但是基础架构是ARM64，其行为与X86架构的行为在非常低的水平上。当时，2023年中，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-with-opentelemetry”&gt; opentelemetry &lt;/a&gt;没有正式支持ARM64部署。随着ARM64实例的普及由于其竞争性价格表现而增加，监视这些系统对于可观察性供应商至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;解决方案：&lt;/strong&gt;为了帮助纠正这种情况，安培计算将捐赠给Ampere Altra驱动的服务器捐赠给OpentElemetry团队。使用这些处理器，团队可以开始重新修改ARM64的遥测仪器，并适应其&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/nodejs”&gt; node.js &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“ href =” href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-python”&gt; python &lt;/a&gt; ARM64架构的代码。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【No More ETL: How Lakebase Combines OLTP, Analytics in One Platform】No More ETL：Lakebase如何在一个平台中结合OLTP，分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/lakebase-serverless-postgres-databricks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/databricks-vs-snowflake-the-definitive-guide?hmsr=joyk.com&amp;amp;utm_source=joyk.com&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&#34;&gt;Databricks&lt;/a&gt;&#39; Lakebase, launched in June 2025, is a serverless Postgres database purpose-built to support modern operational applications and AI workloads—all within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-lake-vs-warehouse-lakehouse-mart&#34;&gt;Lakehouse architecture&lt;/a&gt;. It stands apart from legacy OLTP systems by unifying real-time transactions and lakehouse-native analytics, all without complex provisioning or data pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Under the hood, Lakebase is &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/essential-postgresql&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt;-compatible, which means developers can use existing tools like psql, SQLAlchemy, and pgAdmin, as well as familiar extensions like PostGIS for spatial data and pgvector for embedding-based similarity search—a growing requirement for AI-native applications. It combines the familiarity of Postgres with advanced capabilities powered by Databricks&#39; unified platform.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/databricks-vs-vs-vs-snowflake-the-definistiv--definistiv-------com＆utm_source = joyk.com = joyk.com间专门为支持现代操作应用程序和AI工作负载而建造的 - 所有人都在&lt;a a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/data-lake-vs-ves-warehouse-lakehouse-lakehouse-mart”&gt; Lakehouse Architecture &lt;/a&gt;中。通过统一实时交易和湖泊本地分析，它与传统的OLTP系统不同，所有这些都没有复杂的配置或数据管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在引擎盖下，湖泊是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/refcardz/esential-postgresql”&gt; postgresql &lt;/a&gt; -compatible，这意味着开发人员可以使用诸如psql，sqlalchemy和pgadmin的现有工具以及熟悉的pgial uss uss uss uss usspat and pggadmin，以及基于嵌入的相似性搜索 - 对AI本地应用的需求不断增长。它结合了Postgres的熟悉程度与由Databricks统一平台提供动力的高级功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud Data Engineering for Smarter Healthcare Marketing】更智能医疗保健营销的云数据工程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-data-engineering-healthcare-marketing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Healthcare marketing is going through a major transformation, with data processing happening at a tremendous speed. Organizations are prioritizing well-structured data to understand patient behavior, leveraging cloud data engineering.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Why is this shift happening now? Because the healthcare industry&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.thryve.health/blog/the-power-of-data-in-healthcare&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; style=&#34;border-left-width: 0px; outline: rgb(34, 197, 94) dashed 2px; outline-offset: 1px;&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;generates 2,314 exabytes&lt;/a&gt; of data per year, yet 90% of it goes unused. It includes patient interactions, EHRs, claims, CRM logs, web behavior, and more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;医疗保健营销正在经历重大转型，数据处理以极大的速度进行。组织优先考虑结构良好的数据，以了解患者行为，利用云数据工程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;为什么现在发生这种转变？因为医疗保健行业&lt;a href =“ https://www.thryve.health/blog/the-power-of-data-in-healthcare” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” style =“ border-left-width：border-left-width：0px; outline; outline; outline; outline：rgb（34，197，94） target =“ _ blank”&gt;每年数据生成2,314个exabytes &lt;/a&gt;，但其中90％却没有使用。它包括患者互动，EHR，索赔，CRM日志，网络行为等。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How IoT Devices Communicate With Alexa, Google Assistant, and HomeKit — A Developer’s Deep Dive】IoT设备如何与Alexa，Google Assistant和HomeKit进行通信 - 开发人员深入潜水</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-voice-assistants-control-iot-devices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;727&#34; data-start=&#34;99&#34;&gt;As software developers, we&#39;re immersed in a world of interconnected systems. From microservices orchestrating complex business logic to distributed databases humming along, the art of inter-process communication is our daily bread. Yet, there&#39;s one ubiquitous form of interaction that often feels like magic to the layperson (and sometimes to us): the seamless dance between our smart home gadgets and voice assistants like Alexa, Google Assistant, and Apple HomeKit. When you simply utter, &#34;Alexa, dim the living room lights,&#34; and the room responds, what intricate choreography is truly unfolding in the cloud and on the edge?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1133&#34; data-start=&#34;729&#34;&gt;It&#39;s more than just a convenience; it&#39;s a profound shift in how humans interact with technology. For us, the engineers behind the curtain, understanding this intricate communication isn&#39;t just academic. It&#39;s critical for building robust, secure, and user-friendly smart home experiences. It challenges us to bridge the digital and physical realms, crafting intuitive interfaces for the world around us.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 727” data-start =“ 99”&gt;作为软件开发人员，我们沉浸在一个互连系统的世界中。从精心策划复杂业务逻辑的微服务到分发数据库嗡嗡作响，过程间通信的艺术是我们的日常面包。然而，有一种无处不在的互动形式，对外行人（有时对我们来说）通常感觉像是神奇的：我们智能的家居小工具和诸如Alexa，Google Assistant和Apple HomeKit之类的智能家居小工具和语音助手之间的无缝舞蹈。当您简单地说：“ Alexa，使客厅的灯光变暗”，然后房间回应时，云层和边缘上真正展开了什么复杂的编舞？&lt;/p&gt;？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1133” data-start =“ 729”&gt;不仅仅是便利性；这是人类与技术互动的深刻转变。对我们来说，窗帘背后的工程师不仅了解这种错综复杂的沟通。这对于建立强大，安全和用户友好的智能家庭体验至关重要。它挑战我们桥接数字和物理领域，为我们周围的世界制作直观界面。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Comprehensive Comparison of Serverless Databases and Dedicated Database Servers in the Cloud】云中无服务器数据库和专用数据库服务器的全面比较</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-comprehensive-comparison-of-serverless-databases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-cloud&#34;&gt;cloud computing&lt;/a&gt; landscape has revolutionized how businesses manage their data, offering unprecedented scalability, flexibility, and cost-effectiveness. Within this landscape, the choice between traditional dedicated database servers and the emerging paradigm of serverless databases represents a pivotal decision with significant implications for infrastructure management, performance optimization, and overall operational efficiency.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;The Shifting Sands of Data Management: A Comprehensive Comparison of Serverless Databases and Dedicated Database Servers in the Cloud&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-cloud”&gt;云计算&lt;/a&gt;景观彻底改变了企业如何管理他们的数据，提供前所未有的可伸缩性，灵活性，灵活性和成本效益。在此景观中，传统的专用数据库服务器与无服务器数据库的新兴范式之间的选择代表了一个关键的决策，对基础架构管理，绩效优化和整体操作效率具有重要意义。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;数据管理的转移沙子：云中无服务器数据库和专用数据库服务器的全面比较&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is Codex the End of Boilerplate Code?】Codex是样板代码的结尾吗？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/is-codex-the-end-of-boilerplate-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Boilerplate code has always been the background noise of software development. It’s like lining up bricks of a house. It&#39;s boring, repetitive, and dull, but always necessary.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Whether it’s setting up a web server, writing authentication flows, or configuring logging, most senior developers can do it with their eyes closed. Yet, they still have to do it. But OpenAI’s Codex is here to change that.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;样板代码一直是软件开发的背景噪声。就像在房子的砖头里排队一样。这很无聊，重复和沉闷，但始终是必要的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;是否正在设置Web服务器，编写身份验证流或配置日志记录，大多数高级开发人员都可以闭上眼睛做到这一点。但是，他们仍然必须这样做。但是Openai的法典在这里改变了。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>