<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Introduce a New API Quickly Using Quarkus and ChatGPT】如何使用Quarkus和Chatgpt快速引入新的API</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/introduce-api-quarkus-chatgpt</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;My last two articles (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduce-new-api-spring-boot-gradle&#34;&gt;part 1&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/build-api-with-spring-boot-and-maven&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;part 2&lt;/a&gt;) focused on getting to market quickly using Java. The only difference was the build automation tool that I used for each example. This time, I want to step outside of my comfort zone and try something a little different.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I read about how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-quarkus-serverless-functions&#34;&gt;Quarkus&lt;/a&gt; is a Kubernetes-native Java framework designed for building fast, lightweight microservices. What’s even better is that it is optimized for cloud environments, including features like fast startup times, low memory footprints, and support for both imperative and reactive programming models.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我的最后两篇文章（&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduce-new-api-spring-boot-gradle--&gt;第1部分&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;A href =” target =“ _ blank”&gt;第2部分&lt;/a&gt;）专注于使用Java快速上市。唯一的区别是我用于每个示例的构建自动化工具。这次，我想走出我的舒适区，尝试一些不同的东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我阅读了有关&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-with-with-quarkus-server-functions”&gt; quarkus &lt;/a&gt;是kubernetes-native-native Java框架，设计用于构建快速，轻度的微服务。更好的是，它是针对云环境进行了优化的，包括快速启动时间，低内存足迹以及对命令和反应性编程模型的支持。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enforcing Architecture With ArchUnit in Java】使用Java的Archunit执行建筑</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enforcing-architecture-with-archunit-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;You create a well-defined architecture, but how do you enforce this architecture in your code? Code reviews can be used, but wouldn&#39;t it be better to verify your architecture automatically? With ArchUnit you can define rules for your architecture by means of unit tests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The architecture of an application is described in the documentation. This can be a Word document, a PlantUML diagram, a DrawIO diagram, or whatever you like to use. The developers should follow this architecture when building the application.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您创建一个定义明确的体系结构，但是如何在代码中执行此体系结构？可以使用代码评论，但是最好自动验证您的体系结构吗？使用Archunit，您可以通过单元测试为架构定义规则。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;文档中描述了应用程序的体系结构。这可以是Word文档，Plantuml图，Drawio图或您喜欢使用的任何内容。构建应用程序时，开发人员应遵循此体系结构。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Prioritizing Cloud Security Risks: A Developer&#39;s Guide to Tackling Security Debt】优先考虑云安全风险：解决安全债务的开发指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/prioritizing-cloud-security-risks-developers-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this era of ever-growing digital footprint, decreasing security debt has become so critical for organizations operating in the cloud. The myriads of unresolved security findings expose services vulnerable to emerging threats as well as pose risk to compliance and governance. The solution requires organizations to develop an efficient method for prioritizing security risks based on severity levels across different teams to tackle this problem at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A forward-thinking solution involves creating a centralized security graph that merges various risk and compliance signals into one unified view. Such platforms enable engineering teams and security teams to discover and manage their most critical security risks by assessing their real business impact and risk severity rather than their age or backlog size.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在这个不断增长的数字足迹时代，减少安全债务对于在云中运作的组织变得如此重要。无数未解决的安全发现暴露了容易受到新兴威胁的服务以及对合规和治理的构成风险。该解决方案要求组织开发一种有效的方法来根据不同团队的严重程度的严重程度确定安全风险，以便在大规模解决此问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一种前瞻性的解决方案涉及创建一个集中的安全图，将各种风险和合规性信号合并为一个统一的视图。这样的平台使工程团队和安全团队能够通过评估其实际业务影响和风险严重性而不是年龄或积压大小来发现和管理其最关键的安全风险。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【IoT and Cybersecurity: Addressing Data Privacy and Security Challenges】物联网和网络安全：解决数据隐私和安全挑战</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/iot-cybersecurity-privacy-security-challenges</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;The Internet of Things has shaken up our lives, connecting everything from smart homes to massive industrial systems in a pretty smooth way. Sure, these tech upgrades make our day-to-day so much easier, but they have also brought some real concerns about security and privacy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;With billions of IoT devices out there, are we really ready for the growing cybersecurity threats? &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:240,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ en-us”&gt;物联网震撼了我们的生活，从智能房屋到大型工业系统的所有事物都以一种非常顺利的方式连接起来。当然，这些技术升级使我们的日常工作变得更加容易，但它们也带来了对安全性和隐私的真正担忧。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ en-us”&gt;，那里有数十亿个IoT设备，我们是否真的准备好用于增长的网络安全威胁？   &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {” 134233117“：false，” 134233118“：false，” 201341983“：0，” 335551550 “：6，” 335551620“：6，” 335559738“：240，” 335559739“：0，” 335559740“：276}”：276}&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Future of Java and AI: Coding in 2025】Java和AI的未来：2025年编码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-future-of-java-and-ai-coding-in-2025</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Expanding on the findings of &#34;The State of Coding the Future with Java and AI&#34; survey, this article focuses more on the unique perspective and potential for developers leveraging Quarkus for Java AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34; dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Software development is evolving rapidly, and Java remains a cornerstone for enterprise applications, especially as Artificial Intelligence (AI) reshapes the coding landscape. In 2025, Java developers are at the forefront of this transformation, harnessing AI tools and frameworks like Quarkus to build scalable, cloud-native, and intelligent applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []“ dir =“ ltr”&gt;扩展“使用Java和AI”调查的发现的结果，本文更多地侧重于开发人员利用Quarkus为Java AI。&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []“ dir =“ ltr”&gt;软件开发正在迅速发展，Java仍然是企业应用程序的基石，尤其是当人工智能（AI）重塑编码环境时。在2025年，Java开发人员处于这种转换的最前沿，利用Quarkus（例如Quarkus）的AI工具和框架来构建可扩展，云原状和智能应用程序。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating a Web Project: Caching for Performance Optimization】创建网络项目：用于性能优化的缓存</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/web-project-caching-performance-optimization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In one of the previous articles on identifying issues in your project, “Creating a Web Project: Key Steps to Identify Issues,” we discussed how to analyze application performance and how collecting metrics can assist in this task. However, identifying a problem is only the first step; action must be taken to resolve it. Caching is arguably one of the most effective and widely used methods for accelerating your application.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The principle behind it is that instead of performing complex operations each time, we temporarily save the result of those operations and return it for subsequent similar requests if the inputs have not changed. This way, the application can be sped up, load reduced, and overall stability improved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在以前的有关识别项目中问题的文章之一中，“创建Web项目：识别问题的关键步骤”，我们讨论了如何分析应用程序绩效以及如何收集指标可以帮助完成此任务。但是，确定问题只是第一步。必须采取行动来解决它。可以说，缓存是加速应用程序的最有效和广泛使用的方法之一。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;其背后的原理是，我们并非每次执行复杂操作，而是暂时保存这些操作的结果，并在输入没有更改时将其返回以获取后续的类似请求。这样，可以加速应用程序，减少负载并改善整体稳定性。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agile’s Quarter-Century Crisis】敏捷的四分之一世纪危机</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agiles-quarter-century-crisis</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Agile Failure at Corporate Level&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The data couldn’t be more supportive: Despite 25 years of the Agile Manifesto, countless books, a certification industry, conferences, and armies of consultants, we’re collectively struggling to make Agile work.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My recent survey, although not targeting &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agile-best-practices-values-and-principles-for-effective-teams&#34;&gt;Agile failure&lt;/a&gt;, still reveals systemic dysfunctions that persist across organizations attempting to implement Agile practices:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; TL; DR：公司级别的敏捷失败&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据再也没有支持：尽管有25年的敏捷宣言，无数书籍，认证行业，会议和顾问军队，但我们仍在努力努力从事敏捷的工作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我最近的调查，尽管不是针对&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/agile-best-practices-values-values-and-principles-and-principle-for-effective-teams”&gt;敏捷失败&lt;/a&gt;，仍然揭示了在试图实施agile实践的组织中持续存在的全身功能障碍：</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing the Future: Best Practices for Privacy and Data Governance in LLMOps】确保未来：LLMOPS中隐私和数据治理的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llmops-privacy-data-governance-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Over the last few years, they have rapidly developed in the field of large language models (LLMs) since these models can now underpin anything, from a customer service chatbot to an enterprise-grade solution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Now that such models are more woven into the fabric of daily operations, the definition of importance will extend beyond privacy to strong data governance. The operational infrastructure around LLMs is changing rapidly, focusing on security, compliance, and data protection as their rapid adoption across sectors makes such things poignant.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在过去几年中，它们在大型语言模型（LLMS）领域迅速开发，因为这些模型现在可以支撑任何内容，从客户服务聊天机器人到企业级解决方案。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;现在，此类模型已更加编织到日常操作的结构中，重要性的定义将超出隐私范围，以至于强大的数据治理。 LLMS周围的运营基础设施正在迅速变化，着重于安全性，合规性和数据保护，因为它们在各个部门的迅速采用使这些事情变得凄美。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Merge HTML Documents in Java】如何合并Java的HTML文档</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-merge-html-documents-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Java developers are often handed the challenge of consolidating documents in efficient file processing workflows. &amp;nbsp;With this prompt, HTML might not be the first document format that comes to mind — we might think of “file processing” as pertaining to robust, “business-y” formats like PDF or Excel first and foremost — but HTML’s importance in many modern enterprise environments can’t be understated. Whether it&#39;s a question of processing data pulled together from multiple online sources, piecing scraped web pages together, or consolidating custom web-based reports, programmatically combining and packaging HTML content is often highly relevant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll take a closer look at what it means to merge HTML content programmatically, and we’ll point out some of the specific challenges Java developers can expect to encounter in this endeavor. Towards the end, we’ll touch on some open-source libraries and third-party APIs we can use to build HTML merging capabilities into a file processing workflow, carefully weighing the benefits of each approach.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Java开发人员通常会在有效的文件处理工作流程中合并文档的挑战。  有了这个提示，HTML可能不是想到的第一种文档格式 - 我们可能会认为“文件处理”与强大的，“ business-y”格式有关，例如PDF或Excel，首先也是最重要的 - 但是HTML在许多现代企业环境中的重要性却无法低估。无论是处理从多个在线资源中获取的数据，将刮擦的网页拼凑在一起的问题还是合并基于自定义的基于Web的报告，编程方式结合和包装HTML内容通常非常相关。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将仔细研究以编程方式合并HTML内容的含义，我们将指出Java开发人员可以期望在这项工作中遇到的一些具体挑战。最后，我们将介绍一些可以使用的开源库和第三方API，以将HTML合并功能构建到文件处理工作流程中，仔细权衡每种方法的好处。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring Intercooler.js: Simplify AJAX With HTML Attributes】探索InterCooler.js：用HTML属性简化AJAX</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/intercooler-js-html-ajax</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Intercooler.js is a lightweight JavaScript library that enables developers to add AJAX functionality to their web applications with minimal effort. Inspired by HTML&#39;s simplicity, it allows the use of HTML attributes to handle dynamic updates instead of writing extensive &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/javascript&#34;&gt;JavaScript&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;code. This library is ideal for developers who want the power of AJAX without diving into complex frameworks like React or Angular.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;While Intercooler.js is still supported, its successor,&lt;a href=&#34;https://htmx.org&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;htmx&lt;/a&gt;, offers additional features and enhanced browser capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; InterCooler.js是一个轻巧的JavaScript库，使开发人员能够以最小的努力为其Web应用程序添加AJAX功能。受HTML的简单性的启发，它允许使用HTML属性来处理动态更新，而不是编写广泛的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/javascript”&gt; javascript &lt;/a&gt;代码。该库非常适合想要在不潜入复杂框架（例如React或Angular）的情况下具有Ajax力量的开发人员。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;：虽然Intercooler.js仍然得到支持，但其继任者&lt;a href =“ https://htmx.org” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black” _ blank“ _ blank”&gt; htmx &lt;/a&gt;，提供其他功能，并提供其他功能，并提供了其他功能，并增强了增强的Browser erser sablosions。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>