<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Catalogs Really Break (and How a Copilot Prevents It)】为什么目录真的会崩溃（以及副驾驶如何防止它）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-catalogs-really-break-and-how-a-copilot-preven</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Most catalog incidents aren’t exotic; they’re actually repeatable mistakes. The pattern goes like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Someone copies an old JSON&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;A few fields get changed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;One constraint gets missed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;The downstream service chokes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-docx-has-block-data=&#34;false&#34; data-lark-html-role=&#34;root&#34; data-page-id=&#34;EgoVdN4p9otRrExzdSpcYxdcnzg&#34;&gt;Think of a “Launched” offer with a future start date, or a retail-only promo that accidentally ships to WEB. The blast radius is significant: wrong price on site, agents can’t quote, orders stuck in validation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大多数目录事件并不罕见；它们实际上是可重复的错误。模式是这样的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;有人复制旧的 JSON&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;一些字段发生更改&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;错过了一个约束&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;下游服务阻塞&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-docx-has-block-data=&#34;false&#34; data-lark-html-role=&#34;root&#34; data-page-id=&#34;EgoVdN4p9otRrExzdSpcYxdcnzg&#34;&gt;想象一下未来开始日期的“已启动”优惠，或者意外运送到 WEB 的仅限零售的促销活动。影响范围很大：现场价格错误、代理商无法报价、订单陷入验证困境。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Unified Data Pipelines Transform Modern AI Infrastructure】统一数据管道如何改变现代人工智能基础设施</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unified-data-flows-modern-ai-infrastructure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Over time, the rate of improvement in AI models has outpaced that of pipelines intended to support them. Teams are moving towards more complex signals and higher workloads, but it becomes increasingly difficult for the pipelines to support this. This gap widens with every new data source that adds to this stack, forcing the engineers to hold together workflows that were never designed to work together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Performance slows, iteration decreases, and now the system begins to limit the very models it was built to support. This issue is solved by a unified data flow, which ensures that AI has a scalable structure. The sections below will break down the key details on why this change is so important.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着时间的推移，人工智能模型的改进速度已经超过了旨在支持它们的管道的速度。团队正在转向更复杂的信号和更高的工作负载，但管道支持这一点变得越来越困难。随着每个新数据源添加到该堆栈中，这种差距就会扩大，迫使工程师将从未设计为协同工作的工作流程结合在一起。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;性能变慢，迭代减少，现在系统开始限制它所支持的模型。这个问题可以通过统一的数据流来解决，从而确保人工智能具有可扩展的结构。以下部分将详细介绍为什么此更改如此重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Security and Governance Patterns for Your Conversational AI】对话式 AI 的安全和治理模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/security-governance-patterns-conversational-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;How many times have we heard people talk about the &#34;dream of a SOC copilot?&#34; A copilot woåuld allow an analyst to type something like, &#34;Show me all the SSH login attempts for 10.0.0.5 over the last hour and compare those to the CrowdStrike alerts,&#34; and get the results instantly. This concept suggests the possibility of reducing mean time to resolution (MTTR) and providing Tier 3 knowledge to junior analysts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, in a secure environment, this dream may become a nightmare. In order to connect a probabilistic, hallucinating &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/Conversational-AI-a-Brief-Story&#34;&gt;conversational AI&lt;/a&gt; (LLM) to your SIEM (Splunk, Sentinel) or EDR, you will require a fundamentally different security architecture than what you use for a typical chatbot. If the LLM can write to your systems, it could wipe out logs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们有多少次听到人们谈论“SOC 副驾驶的梦想”？副驾驶将允许分析师输入类似“显示过去一小时内 10.0.0.5 的所有 SSH 登录尝试并将其与 CrowdStrike 警报进行比较”之类的内容，并立即获得结果。这一概念表明可以缩短平均解决时间 (MTTR) 并为初级分析师提供第 3 层知识。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，在安全的环境中，这个梦想可能会变成噩梦。为了将概率性的、幻觉的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/Conversational-AI-a-Brief-Story&#34;&gt;对话式 AI&lt;/a&gt; (LLM) 连接到您的 SIEM（Splunk、Sentinel）或 EDR，您将需要一个与典型聊天机器人所使用的安全架构完全不同的安全架构。如果 LLM 可以写入您的系统，它可能会清除日志。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Avoid BigQuery SQL Injection in Go With saferbq】使用 Saferbq 避免 Go 中的 BigQuery SQL 注入</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/avoid-bigquery-sql-injection-go-saferbq</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;You can build dynamic queries in BigQuery using the Go SDK. When building applications that allow users to select tables or datasets dynamically, you need to include those identifiers in your SQL queries. I was surprised to find that the BigQuery manual and code examples do not warn about SQL injection vulnerabilities when doing this.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even more surprising: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/control-access-to-google-bigquery-data&#34;&gt;BigQuery&lt;/a&gt; does not provide a built-in mechanism to safely handle user input in table or dataset names. The official SDK supports parameterized queries for data values using &lt;code&gt;@&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;?&lt;/code&gt; syntax, but these cannot be used for identifiers that need backtick escaping. You’re forced to use string concatenation, which opens the door to SQL injection. This post explains the problem and introduces a package I wrote to tackle this shortcoming.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您可以使用 Go SDK 在 BigQuery 中构建动态查询。当构建允许用户动态选择表或数据集的应用程序时，您需要在 SQL 查询中包含这些标识符。我惊讶地发现 BigQuery 手册和代码示例在执行此操作时没有警告 SQL 注入漏洞。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更令人惊讶的是：&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/control-access-to-google-bigquery-data&#34;&gt;BigQuery&lt;/a&gt; 没有提供内置机制来安全处理表或数据集名称中的用户输入。官方SDK支持使用&lt;code&gt;@&lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt;?&lt;/code&gt;语法对数据值进行参数化查询，但这些不能用于需要反引号转义的标识符。您被迫使用字符串连接，这为 SQL 注入打开了大门。这篇文章解释了这个问题，并介绍了我为解决这个缺点而编写的一个包。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DevSecOps as a Strategic Imperative for Modern DevOps】DevSecOps 作为现代 DevOps 的战略要务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devsecops-strategic-imperative-modern-devops</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;If you do not take security seriously, you are just begging for trouble. Security should be an integral part of your development process, not something that you add at the end. Patches and updates do not suffice to deter severe attacks, and if you entrust security to another team, then you are simply relying on luck. Only an unwavering, company-wide security commitment can guard the moat that keeps competitors at bay and satisfy the blizzard of new regulatory expectations. Operate this way and your software will stay resilient, compliant, and ultimately, market-winning. DevOps security and DevSecOps both champion security embedded within the modern development workflow, but they place differing emphases throughout the pipeline. DevOps security typically zeroes in on the hardening of pipeline components and the enforcement of security policy across infrastructure and runtime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In contrast, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devsecops-a-complete-guide&#34;&gt;DevSecOps&lt;/a&gt; broadens the mandate, making security everyone’s job from the earliest design phase, marrying threat modeling, secure coding, and security testing with development and release cadence. Collectively, they unite elite defensive posture with the speed and fluidity of continuous integration and continuous delivery, driving home the principle that security velocity must equal delivery velocity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如果你不认真对待安全问题，那你就是自找麻烦。安全性应该是开发过程中不可或缺的一部分，而不是在最后添加的东西。补丁和更新不足以阻止严重的攻击，如果您将安全性委托给另一个团队，那么您只是依靠运气。只有坚定不移的全公司安全承诺才能守住护城河，将竞争对手拒之门外，并满足新的监管期望。以这种方式运营，您的软件将保持弹性、合规性，并最终赢得市场。 DevOps 安全性和 DevSecOps 都支持现代开发工作流程中嵌入的安全性，但它们在整个管道中的侧重点不同。 DevOps 安全性通常侧重于管道组件的强化以及跨基础设施和运行时的安全策略的执行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;相比之下，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/devsecops-a-complete-guide&#34;&gt;DevSecOps&lt;/a&gt; 拓宽了任务范围，从最早的设计阶段就让安全成为每个人的工作，将威胁建模、安全编码和安全测试与开发和发布节奏结合起来。总的来说，它们将精英防御态势与持续集成和持续交付的速度和流动性结合起来，使人们明白安全速度必须等于交付速度的原则。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Rethinking Cloud Compliance With an AI-Driven Approach】使用人工智能驱动的方法重新思考云合规性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-driven-cloud-compliance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The regulatory environment across the world is becoming increasingly stringent day by day. It is expanding across several business sectors, and the technology sector is not far behind. Cloud computing and artificial intelligence (AI) have been at the center stage without a doubt. While both technologies have brought about immense abundance, the industry is grappling with increasing pressure to comply with complex laws and regulatory frameworks such as GDPR, HIPAA, SOC 2, and industry-specific standards. Work on traditional compliance approaches focuses mainly on manual audits, static policies, and periodic reviews. This needs to be rethought, as these approaches need to keep pace with the speed and scale of modern cloud environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this context, AI becomes a powerful tool to manage cloud compliance. AI can assist across a broad scope of use cases — from machine learning and predictive analytics to intelligent automation — the range is endless. Beyond routine automation of day-to-day tasks, AI can enable teams to not only anticipate risks and optimize governance strategies but also maintain proactive compliance across hybrid and multi-cloud infrastructures. In this article, let’s understand the different ways in which AI is redefining cloud compliance, which helps organizations achieve proactive and intelligent governance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;世界各地的监管环境日益严格。它正在向多个业务领域扩张，技术领域也不甘落后。毫无疑问，云计算和人工智能（AI）一直处于中心舞台。虽然这两种技术都带来了巨大的丰富性，但该行业正在努力应对越来越大的压力，要求遵守复杂的法律和监管框架，例如 GDPR、HIPAA、SOC 2 和行业特定标准。传统合规方法的工作主要集中在手动审计、静态策略和定期审查。这需要重新考虑，因为这些方法需要跟上现代云环境的速度和规模。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此背景下，人工智能成为管理云合规性的强大工具。人工智能可以在广泛的用例中提供帮助——从机器学习和预测分析到智能自动化——范围是无穷无尽的。除了日常任务的常规自动化之外，人工智能不仅可以使团队预测风险和优化治理策略，还可以跨混合和多云基础设施保持主动合规性。在本文中，让我们了解人工智能重新定义云合规性的不同方式，这有助于组织实现主动和智能的治理。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bias and Shortcut Tests for Vision Models: A Practical Test Suite From Real-World Experiments】视觉模型的偏差和捷径测试：来自真实世界实验的实用测试套件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vision-model-bias-shortcut-tests</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When I first started working with deep learning image models, I did what most people do:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Train a model&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Check top-1/top-5 accuracy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Look at a few confusion matrices&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On paper, everything looked great. But when I started poking at the models in slightly weird ways, I learned a very uncomfortable truth:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当我第一次开始使用深度学习图像模型时，我做了大多数人所做的事情：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;训练模型&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;检查 top-1/top-5 准确性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;看一些混淆矩阵&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从纸面上看，一切看起来都很棒。但是当我开始以稍微奇怪的方式研究模型时，我了解到了一个非常令人不安的事实：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build a Self-Evolving AI Agent That Learns From Failure】如何构建能够从失败中学习的自我进化人工智能代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/self-evolving-ai-agent-learns-from-failure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;For developers building autonomous systems, today&#39;s generative AI agents present a fundamental challenge: they are amnesiacs. An agent can execute a complex task, fail, and then repeat the same mistake five minutes later. Their capabilities are &#34;test-time static,&#34; meaning they are frozen at the moment their training ends. They cannot learn from their interactions, discard valuable insights, or correct their own errors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;For developers and architects trying to build reliable autonomous systems, this is the primary barrier to adoption. An unreliable agent is not autonomous. It is a brittle system that creates technical debt.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;对于构建自主系统的开发人员来说，当今的生成式人工智能代理提出了一个根本性的挑战：它们是健忘症患者。代理可以执行一项复杂的任务，失败，然后五分钟后重复同样的错误。他们的能力是“测试时静态的”，这意味着他们在训练结束时就被冻结了。他们无法从互动中学习、放弃有价值的见解或纠正自己的错误。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;对于尝试构建可靠的自治系统的开发人员和架构师来说，这是采用的主要障碍。不可靠的代理是不自治的。这是一个脆弱的系统，会产生技术债务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Unified, Access-Aware Search in a Data Mesh】在数据网格中构建统一的、访问感知的搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unified-access-aware-search-data-mesh</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Over the last few years, I have worked on a distributed data platform in which each engineering group owns the data it produces from heterogeneous data processing systems. Our central platform follows a&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-mesh-a-paradigm-shift-in-data-management&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;data mesh model&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, as every domain manages its own pipelines and storage, but discovery in the unified system should be seamless to anyone searching across the mesh. That goal sounded simple, but wasn’t that simple considering we host datasets from ultra and black undisclosed products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The first complaint we heard, repeatedly:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;在过去的几年里，我一直在开发一个分布式数据平台，其中每个工程团队都拥有其从异构数据处理系统生成的数据。我们的中央平台遵循&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-mesh-a-paradigm-shift-in-data-management&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;数据网格模型&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;，因为每个域都管理自己的管道和存储，但统一系统中的发现对于跨网格搜索的任何人来说都应该是无缝的。这个目标听起来很简单，但考虑到我们托管来自超黑未公开产品的数据集，事情就没那么简单了。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;我们反复听到的第一个投诉：&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing for Empathy: Human-Centered AI Patterns for Real Systems】同理心设计：真实系统的以人为中心的人工智能模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/designing-empathy-human-centered-ai-patterns</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;959&#34; data-start=&#34;948&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1298&#34; data-start=&#34;961&#34;&gt;Empathy-aware interaction is becoming a core requirement as AI systems mediate healthcare, education, and public services. For software teams, the challenge is not “make the bot nice,” but: how do we design and ship systems that sense user context, adapt with calibrated empathy, and still remain private, auditable, and predictable?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1548&#34; data-start=&#34;1300&#34;&gt;This article proposes a practice-oriented framework that unifies affect sensing, context modeling, policy-based adaptation, and transparent explanations into a deployable pipeline for human–machine systems. The contributions for developers are:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;959&#34; data-start=&#34;948&#34;&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1298&#34; data-start=&#34;961&#34;&gt;随着人工智能系统在医疗保健、教育和公共服务中发挥作用，同理心感知交互正在成为一项核心要求。对于软件团队来说，挑战不是“让机器人变得更好”，而是：我们如何设计和交付能够感知用户上下文、适应校准同理心并仍然保持私密性、可审计和可预测的系统？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1548&#34; data-start=&#34;1300&#34;&gt;本文提出了一个面向实践的框架，它将情感感知、情境建模、基于策略的适应和透明解释统一到人机系统的可部署管道中。对开发者的贡献是：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>