<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud Migration of Microservices: Strategy, Risks, and Best Practices】微服务云迁移：策略、风险和最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-migration-of-microservices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p align=&#34;justify&#34; lang=&#34;en-US&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The article discusses the principles of microservice architecture and its comparison with monolithic systems. It also covers migration strategies based on the 6R/7R model, as well as analysis of key risks, including budget overruns and security breaches.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p align=&#34;justify&#34; lang=&#34;en-US&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Special attention is given to migration planning, monitoring, and automation methods, such as the use of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;, CI/CD (continuous integration/continuous delivery), DevSecOps (development, security, operations), and the Twelve-Factor App principles. Empirical statistics and comparative analysis of different strategies are also presented in tables. In conclusion, directions for further research are identified, such as using artificial intelligence (AI), multi-cloud approaches, and unifying evaluation methods.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;palign=&#34;justify&#34; lang=&#34;en-US&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;本文讨论了微服务架构的原理及其与单体系统的比较。它还涵盖基于 6R/7R 模型的迁移策略，以及对关键风险的分析，包括预算超支和安全漏洞。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;palign=&#34;justify&#34; lang=&#34;en-US&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;特别关注迁移规划、监控和自动化方法，例如使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt;、CI/CD（持续集成/持续交付）、DevSecOps（开发、安全、运营）和十二要素应用原则。表格中还列出了不同策略的实证统计和比较分析。总之，确定了进一步研究的方向，例如使用人工智能（AI）、多云方法和统一评估方法。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Rethinking QA: From DevOps to Platform Engineering and SRE】重新思考 QA：从 DevOps 到平台工程和 SRE</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rethinking-qa-from-devops-to-platform-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;The Wake-Up Call&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;887&#34; data-start=&#34;242&#34;&gt;The software development landscape is undergoing a significant transformation, challenging traditional roles and requiring new skills. While DevOps has been a key element for over a decade — promoting collaboration and continuous delivery — the specific role of a &#34;DevOps engineer&#34; is changing. Recent market analyses indicate a shift: while some reports suggest a stabilization or slight decrease in dedicated DevOps job postings, platform engineering and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/site-reliability-and-engineering&#34;&gt;site reliability engineering (SRE) roles&lt;/a&gt; are experiencing a rise. This change does not mean the end of DevOps principles, but rather their deeper integration into specialized functions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1297&#34; data-start=&#34;889&#34;&gt;This article argues that the core principles of DevOps are being integrated into new, vital roles, necessitating a significant adjustment for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/Scaling-QA-Processes-for-Enterprise-App-Development&#34;&gt;Quality Assurance (QA)&lt;/a&gt; professionals. Failing to adapt risks QA teams becoming bottlenecks in modern engineering workflows. On the other hand, embracing this change provides QA with a unique chance to expand its influence and become an essential quality facilitator.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;叫醒电话&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;887&#34; data-start=&#34;242&#34;&gt;软件开发环境正在经历重大转变，挑战传统角色并需要新技能。虽然 DevOps 十多年来一直是促进协作和持续交付的关键要素，但“DevOps 工程师”的具体角色正在发生变化。最近的市场分析表明了一种转变：虽然一些报告表明专门的 DevOps 职位发布稳定或略有减少，但平台工程和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/site-reliability-and-engineering&#34;&gt;站点可靠性工程 (SRE) 职位&lt;/a&gt;正在增加。这一变化并不意味着 DevOps 原则的终结，而是意味着它们更深入地集成到专门功能中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1297&#34; data-start=&#34;889&#34;&gt;本文认为，DevOps 的核心原则正在融入新的重要角色，需要对&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/Scaling-QA-Processes-for-Enterprise-App-Development&#34;&gt;质量保证 (QA)&lt;/a&gt; 专业人员进行重大调整。如果无法适应，质量保证团队可能会成为现代工程工作流程中的瓶颈。另一方面，接受这一变化为 QA 提供了一个独特的机会来扩大其影响力并成为重要的质量促进者。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cracking the Innovation Code: Design Thinking Explained】破解创新密码：设计思维解释</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cracking-the-innovation-code-design-thinking-expla</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;156c&#34;&gt;In both personal and professional life, we regularly face problems that are new, ambiguous, or unusually complex. Quick fixes sometimes work, but arriving at a simple, creative, and robust solution usually requires a different approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;559&#34; data-start=&#34;354&#34;&gt;Traditional problem solving often relies on familiar patterns and past experience, which can constrain options and stifle innovation when the context has changed or the problem is not yet fully understood.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;156c&#34;&gt;在个人生活和职业生活中，我们经常面临新的、模糊的或异常复杂的问题。快速修复有时会起作用，但要获得简单、富有创意且强大的解决方案通常需要不同的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;559&#34; data-start=&#34;354&#34;&gt;传统的问题解决通常依赖于熟悉的模式和过去的经验，当环境发生变化或问题尚未完全理解时，这可能会限制选择并扼杀创新。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fortifying Cloud Security Operations with AI-Driven Threat Detection】通过人工智能驱动的威胁检测强化云安全运营</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/fortifying-cloud-security-operations-with-ai-drive</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;1049&#34; data-start=&#34;238&#34;&gt;With the rapid adoption of cloud technologies, organizations are rushing to migrate their workloads and data to the cloud — often at a breakneck pace. Cyber hackers are not far behind in this race. On-premises systems are no longer the primary targets. Cloud environments, including both &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-security-in-hybrid-and-multi-cloud&#34;&gt;hybrid and multi-cloud setups&lt;/a&gt;, have become enticing targets for malicious attackers. Adding to this challenge, attacks are becoming more sophisticated day by day. Relying solely on traditional security methods such as static rules and signature-based detection — often requiring human intervention — is no longer sustainable. Artificial intelligence (AI) is a game changer in this regard. By enabling proactive threat detection and automated workflows, AI has the potential to drive a paradigm shift in cloud security operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-end=&#34;1087&#34; data-start=&#34;1056&#34;&gt;Understanding Cloud Threats&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1325&#34; data-start=&#34;1089&#34;&gt;Cloud environments are becoming increasingly complex. This creates a double-edged sword, as the same complexity that enables scalability also makes these environments vulnerable to novel threats. Let’s explore some common cloud threats:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;1049&#34; data-start=&#34;238&#34;&gt;随着云技术的快速采用，组织正急于将其工作负载和数据迁移到云端，而且速度往往非常快。网络黑客在这场竞赛中也不甘落后。本地系统不再是主要目标。云环境，包括&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-security-in-hybrid-and-multi-cloud&#34;&gt;混合云和多云设置&lt;/a&gt;，已成为恶意攻击者的诱人目标。除了这一挑战之外，攻击也变得日益复杂。仅仅依靠静态规则和基于签名的检测等传统安全方法（通常需要人工干预）已不再可持续。人工智能（AI）在这方面改变了游戏规则。通过实现主动威胁检测和自动化工作流程，人工智能有潜力推动云安全运营的范式转变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-end=&#34;1087&#34; data-start=&#34;1056&#34;&gt;了解云威胁&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1325&#34; data-start=&#34;1089&#34;&gt;云环境变得越来越复杂。这创造了一把双刃剑，因为实现可扩展性的复杂性也使这些环境容易受到新威胁的影响。让我们探讨一些常见的云威胁：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero Trust Model for Nonprofits: Protecting Mission in the Digital Age】非营利组织的零信任模型：保护数字时代的使命</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-model-nonprofits-digital-age</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;981&#34; data-start=&#34;136&#34;&gt;In an increasingly globally connected world, nonprofit organizations are as much at risk and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/common-cybersecurity-threats-and-how-to-protect-yo&#34;&gt;vulnerable to cyber threats&lt;/a&gt; as large multinational corporations, if not more so. To keep cyber threats at bay, traditional security models have often relied on devices such as firewalls, virtual private networks (VPNs), and similar tools, often based on the underlying assumption that anyone inside the network is trusted by default. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-architecture&#34;&gt;Zero Trust Architecture (ZTA)&lt;/a&gt; is based on the concept that nothing is trusted by default, whether it is an internal or external stakeholder. The model offers a fundamentally different approach: never trust, always verify. This approach is particularly critical, as nonprofits often handle sensitive donor information, volunteer and beneficiary data, and other confidential information that must always remain secure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;1048&#34; data-start=&#34;1007&#34;&gt;Why Nonprofits Are Attractive Targets&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1734&#34; data-start=&#34;1031&#34;&gt;Even though nonprofits might have limited budgets, they are still attractive targets for cybercriminals, often because they hold a wealth of sensitive and valuable information. High-value assets that can be exploited include donor databases, payment records, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/8-data-anonymization-techniques-to-safeguard-user&#34;&gt;personally identifiable information (PII)&lt;/a&gt; of beneficiaries. Additionally, nonprofits that rely on volunteers, contractors, or third-party partners can also be at risk if their access controls are weak. These high-value assets can be exploited for financial gain, identity theft, or ransomware attacks. Once a cyberattack occurs, there can be an erosion of donor trust, with regulatory penalties potentially applied if data breaches occur.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;981&#34; data-start=&#34;136&#34;&gt;在一个日益全球化的世界中，非营利组织与大型跨国公司一样面临着同样的风险，并且&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/common-cybersecurity-threats-and-how-to-protect-yo&#34;&gt;容易受到网络威胁&lt;/a&gt;，甚至更严重。为了防范网络威胁，传统的安全模型通常依赖于防火墙、虚拟专用网络 (VPN) 和类似工具等设备，并且通常基于默认情况下网络内的任何人都是可信的基本假设。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-architecture&#34;&gt;零信任架构 (ZTA)&lt;/a&gt; 基于这样的概念：默认情况下，无论是内部利益相关者还是外部利益相关者，都不信任任何内容。该模型提供了一种根本不同的方法：从不信任，始终验证。这种方法尤其重要，因为非营利组织经常处理敏感的捐赠者信息、志愿者和受益人数据以及其他必须始终保持安全的机密信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;1048&#34; data-start=&#34;1007&#34;&gt;为什么非营利组织是有吸引力的目标&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1734&#34; data-start=&#34;1031&#34;&gt;尽管非营利组织的预算可能有限，但它们仍然是网络犯罪分子的有吸引力的目标，通常是因为它们掌握着大量敏感且有价值的信息。可以利用的高价值资产包括捐赠者数据库、付款记录和受益人的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/8-data-anonymization-techniques-to-safeguard-user&#34;&gt;个人身份信息 (PII)&lt;/a&gt;。此外，如果访问控制薄弱，依赖志愿者、承包商或第三方合作伙伴的非营利组织也可能面临风险。这些高价值资产可被用来获取经济利益、身份盗窃或勒索软件攻击。一旦发生网络攻击，捐助者的信任可能会受到侵蚀，如果发生数据泄露，可能会受到监管处罚。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Technology Evolution From Traditional Automation to AI-Driven MCP Servers】从传统自动化到人工智能驱动的 MCP 服务器的技术演变</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/evolution-from-traditional-automation-ai-driven-mcp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;591&#34; data-start=&#34;134&#34;&gt;Technology has always been about solving problems faster, smarter, and more efficiently. Over the past few decades, we’ve witnessed a remarkable transformation in how businesses automate processes — from rigid, rule-based scripts to intelligent, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/learning-on-the-fly-how-adaptive-ai-transforms-ind&#34;&gt;adaptive systems powered by artificial intelligence (AI)&lt;/a&gt;. One of the most fascinating journeys in this evolution is the shift from &lt;strong&gt;traditional automation frameworks&lt;/strong&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;AI-driven Multi-Cloud Platform (MCP) servers&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;790&#34; data-start=&#34;593&#34;&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll explore that journey, why it matters, and what the future holds for organizations embracing this paradigm shift — now with supporting code examples you can adapt to your stack.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;591&#34; data-start=&#34;134&#34;&gt;技术始终致力于更快、更智能、更高效地解决问题。在过去的几十年里，我们见证了企业流程自动化方式的显着转变——从严格的、基于规则的脚本到&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/learning-on-the-fly-how-adaptive-ai-transforms-ind&#34;&gt;由人工智能 (AI) 驱动的自适应系统&lt;/a&gt;。这一演变过程中最引人入胜的旅程之一是从&lt;strong&gt;传统自动化框架&lt;/strong&gt;向&lt;strong&gt;人工智能驱动的多云平台 (MCP) 服务器&lt;/strong&gt;的转变。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;790&#34; data-start=&#34;593&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨这一历程、它为何重要，以及拥抱这种范式转变的组织的未来——现在您可以通过支持代码示例来适应您的堆栈。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Macroscopic Quantum Tunneling: Unlocking the Quantum Secret Inside an Electrical Circuit】宏观量子隧道：解开电路内部的量子秘密</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/macroscopic-quantum-tunneling-electrical-circuit</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This prize recognizes the three researchers &#34;&lt;em&gt;for the discovery of macroscopic quantum tunneling and the quantization of energy in an electrical circuit.&lt;/em&gt;&#34; What are the applications for the development of quantum computing?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Bridging the Divide: The Microscopic and Macroscopic Worlds&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Indeed, this prize is all the more important as quantum mechanics now constitutes the heart of the most advanced digital technologies underpinning research in the field of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-computers-explained&#34;&gt;quantum computing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;该奖项旨在表彰三位研究人员“&lt;em&gt;发现了宏观量子隧道效应和电路中能量的量子化。&lt;/em&gt;”量子计算的发展有哪些应用？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;弥合鸿沟：微观和宏观世界&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;事实上，这个奖项更加重要，因为量子力学现在构成了支持&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/quantum-computers-explained&#34;&gt;量子计算&lt;/a&gt;领域研究的最先进数字技术的核心。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kubernetes 101: Understanding the Foundation and Getting Started】Kubernetes 101：了解基础和入门</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-101-understanding-the-foundation-and-ge</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;About This Series&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;469&#34; data-start=&#34;254&#34;&gt;This is part 1 of a 5-part series on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes implementation&lt;/a&gt;. These posts cut through the hype to focus on practical decisions: what Kubernetes actually does, when you need it, and how to implement it effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-end=&#34;490&#34; data-start=&#34;471&#34;&gt;Series Outline&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;577&#34; data-start=&#34;494&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;512&#34; data-start=&#34;494&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 101&lt;/strong&gt; – What it is, when you need it, and hands-on setup (this post)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;653&#34; data-start=&#34;580&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;594&#34; data-start=&#34;580&#34;&gt;Networking&lt;/strong&gt; – Service discovery, ingress, and how pods actually talk&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;730&#34; data-start=&#34;656&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;681&#34; data-start=&#34;656&#34;&gt;Deployment strategies&lt;/strong&gt; – Rolling updates, blue-green, canary releases&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;798&#34; data-start=&#34;733&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;744&#34; data-start=&#34;733&#34;&gt;Storage&lt;/strong&gt; – Persistent volumes and running stateful workloads&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;880&#34; data-start=&#34;801&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;826&#34; data-start=&#34;801&#34;&gt;Production operations&lt;/strong&gt; – Monitoring, logging, scaling, and troubleshooting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;919&#34; data-start=&#34;887&#34;&gt;What Kubernetes Actually Does&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1216&#34; data-start=&#34;921&#34;&gt;Kubernetes manages containerized workloads across a cluster of machines. You define the desired state in YAML; Kubernetes reconciles the actual state to match. Container crashes? Kubernetes restarts it. A node dies? Kubernetes reschedules pods elsewhere. Need to scale? Update the replica count.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;关于本系列&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;469&#34; data-start=&#34;254&#34;&gt;这是关于&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 实施&lt;/a&gt;的 5 部分系列中的第 1 部分。这些帖子消除了炒作，专注于实际决策：Kubernetes 实际做什么、何时需要它以及如何有效实施它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-end=&#34;490&#34; data-start=&#34;471&#34;&gt;系列大纲&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;577&#34; data-start=&#34;494&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;512&#34; data-start=&#34;494&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 101&lt;/strong&gt; – 它是什么、何时需要以及实际设置（本文）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;653&#34; data-start=&#34;580&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;594&#34; data-start=&#34;580&#34;&gt;网络&lt;/strong&gt; – 服务发现、入口以及 Pod 实际如何通信&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;730&#34; data-start=&#34;656&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;681&#34; data-start=&#34;656&#34;&gt;部署策略&lt;/strong&gt; – 滚动更新、蓝绿、金丝雀发布&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;798&#34; data-start=&#34;733&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;744&#34; data-start=&#34;733&#34;&gt;存储&lt;/strong&gt; – 持久卷和运行有状态工作负载&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;880&#34; data-start=&#34;801&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;826&#34; data-start=&#34;801&#34;&gt;生产操作&lt;/strong&gt; – 监控、日志记录、扩展和故障排除&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;919&#34; data-start=&#34;887&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 实际上做了什么&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1216&#34; data-start=&#34;921&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 跨机器集群管理容器化工作负载。您在 YAML 中定义所需的状态； Kubernetes 会协调实际状态以进行匹配。集装箱崩溃？ Kubernetes 重新启动它。节点死亡？ Kubernetes 将 Pod 重新安排到其他地方。需要扩展吗？更新副本计数。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【End-to-End Test Automation With Playwright, GitHub Page, and Allure Reports】使用 Playwright、GitHub 页面和 Allure 报告进行端到端测试自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/playwright-github-allure-test-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Automated testing is essential for delivering high-quality web applications. Modern &lt;strong&gt;CI/CD&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;pipelines require reliable, scalable, and transparent test automation to ensure confidence in every release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In this article, we explore how Playwright, GitHub Actions, and Allure Reports work together to create a powerful &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-end-to-end-testing-3&#34;&gt;end-to-end testing&lt;/a&gt; automation framework. You will learn how to set up Playwright tests, integrate them into a GitHub Actions CI pipeline, and generate professional Allure reports that provide clear insights into test execution.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;自动化测试对于交付高质量的 Web 应用程序至关重要。现代&lt;strong&gt;CI/CD&lt;/strong&gt;管道需要可靠、可扩展且透明的测试自动化，以确保每个版本的可信度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨 Playwright、GitHub Actions 和 Allure Reports 如何协同工作来创建强大的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-end-to-end-testing-3&#34;&gt;端到端测试&lt;/a&gt;自动化框架。您将学习如何设置 Playwright 测试，将其集成到 GitHub Actions CI 管道中，并生成专业的 Allure 报告，为测试执行提供清晰的见解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Looking at the Evolving Landscape of ITSM Through the Lens of AI】从人工智能的角度审视 ITSM 的演变格局</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/evolving-landscape-of-itsm-through-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As today’s businesses march forward alongside &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-for-ai-systems-automation&#34;&gt;rapid developments in artificial intelligence (AI)&lt;/a&gt;, progress has reached nearly every major functional area of technology. One such area on the cusp of transformational change is Information Technology Service Management (ITSM). For the last decades, traditional ITSM systems have relied heavily on manual workflows and unstructured processes. One can argue that while these systems introduced order and consistency, they also created bottlenecks, long resolution times, and reactive operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1190&#34; data-start=&#34;684&#34;&gt;With the advent of large language models (LLMs) and agentic AI, this technology paradigm is undergoing a rapid shift. As we speak, AI is reshaping how services are delivered, managed, and optimized. With the power of AI, traditional support channels across service desks are gradually evolving into proactive, self-healing ecosystems where issues are anticipated before they disrupt business, and routine manual tasks resolve themselves automatically. In this article, we explore the key ways AI has become the driving force behind the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/harnessing-ai-to-revolutionize-it-service&#34;&gt;ITSM revolution&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着当今的企业随着&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-for-ai-systems-automation&#34;&gt;人工智能 (AI) 的快速发展&lt;/a&gt;不断前进，几乎所有主要的技术功能领域都取得了进步。信息技术服务管理 (ITSM) 就是处于转型变革尖端的此类领域之一。在过去的几十年里，传统的 ITSM 系统严重依赖手动工作流程和非结构化流程。有人可能会说，虽然这些系统引入了秩序和一致性，但它们也造成了瓶颈、较长的解决时间和反应性操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1190&#34; data-start=&#34;684&#34;&gt;随着大型语言模型 (LLM) 和代理 AI 的出现，这种技术范式正在经历快速转变。正如我们所说，人工智能正在重塑服务的交付、管理和优化方式。借助人工智能的力量，跨服务台的传统支持渠道正在逐渐演变为主动、自我修复的生态系统，在问题扰乱业务之前就可以预见到问题，并且日常手动任务会自动解决。在本文中，我们将探讨人工智能成为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/harnessing-ai-to-revolutionize-it-service&#34;&gt;ITSM 革命&lt;/a&gt;背后驱动力的关键方式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>