<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【An Overview of Asynchronous Processing in Salesforce】Salesforce中异步处理的概述</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/asynchronous-processing-salesforce-overview</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When running a process in Salesforce, the first question you should ask is whether to execute it synchronously or asynchronously. If the task can be delayed and doesn&#39;t require an immediate result, it&#39;s always beneficial to leverage Salesforce&#39;s asynchronous processes, as they offer significant advantages to your technical architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is Asynchronous Processing?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/when-to-use-and-not-to-use-asynchronous-programmin&#34;&gt;Asynchronous processes&lt;/a&gt; run in their own thread, allowing the task to complete without keeping the user waiting. Here are the key benefits:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在Salesforce运行过程时，您应该问的第一个问题是是同步还是异步执行它。如果任务可以延迟并且不需要立即结果，那么利用Salesforce的异步流程总是有益的，因为它们为您的技术架构提供了重要的优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是异步处理？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/when-to-use-use-and-not-to-use-sasynchronous-progommin”&gt; asynchronous流程&lt;/a&gt;在他们自己的线程中运行，允许任务完成，而无需保持用户等待。这是关键好处：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Vendor Lock-In Drives Open-Source Adoption in Japan】供应商锁定在日本采用开源的驱动器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vendor-lock-in-drives-open-source-adoption-japan</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I have been looking at open source development in Japan, which is showing increasing signs of playing a bigger part in corporate strategy and becoming more global in reach.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Koichi Shikata, Head of Solutions Architect Division, SUSE Software Solutions, Japan, is a seasoned professional with extensive experience in the software industry, having held significant roles at SUSE, Wind River, and Intel, based both in Japan and the US. Throughout his career, he has been instrumental in promoting &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/japans-next-step-with-open-source-software&#34;&gt;open-source solutions&lt;/a&gt; and fostering innovation within the industry.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我一直在关注日本的开源开发，这表明越来越多地在公司战略中发挥更大作用并变得更加全球化。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; koichi Shikata，Suse Software Solutions，Japan Suse Software Solutions的解决方案部门负责人，是一位经验丰富的专业专业人员，在软件行业拥有丰富的经验，在Suse，Wind River和Intel在日本和美国都担任过重要角色。在他的整个职业生涯中，他一直在促进&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/japans-next-next-step-with-open-source-software”&gt;开放式解决方案&lt;/a&gt;并在行业内促进创新。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Generative AI Agents: Transforming Supply Chain Management】生成AI代理：转换供应链管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-agents-transforming-supply-chain</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Supply chains are the backbone of global commerce, but they&#39;re increasingly complex and vulnerable to disruptions. From pandemic-related shortages to geopolitical conflicts, recent events have exposed fundamental weaknesses in traditional supply chain management approaches.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As organizations seek more resilient and efficient solutions, artificial intelligence — particularly generative AI and large language models (LLMs) — is emerging as a game-changing technology.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;供应连锁店是全球贸易的骨干，但它们越来越复杂且容易受到干扰。从与大流行有关的短缺到地缘政治冲突，最近的事件揭示了传统供应链管理方法中的根本弱点。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着组织寻求更具弹性和高效的解决方案，人工智能（尤其是生成的AI和大型语言模型（LLM））正在成为一种改变游戏规则的技术。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build a ChatGPT Super App】如何构建chatgpt超级应用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-build-a-chatgpt-super-app</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;SingleStore is a powerful multi-model database system and platform designed to support a wide variety of business use cases. Its distinctive features allow businesses to unify multiple database systems into a single platform, reducing the Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) and simplifying developer workflows by eliminating the need for complex integration tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we&#39;ll explore how SingleStore can transform email campaigns for a web analytics company, enabling the creation of personalized and highly targeted email content.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Singlestore是一个强大的多模型数据库系统和平台，旨在支持各种业务用例。它的独特功能使企业可以将多个数据库系统统一到一个平台中，从而减少了总拥有成本（TCO），并通过消除对复杂集成工具的需求来简化开发人员的工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨Singlestore如何为Web Analytics Company转换电子邮件广告系列，从而创建个性化和高度针对性的电子邮件内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Alignment-to-Value Pipeline】对齐管道的对齐管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-alignment-to-value-pipeline</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: The Alignment-to-Value Pipeline&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Effective product development requires both strategic alignment and healthy Product Backlog management. Misalignment leads to backlog bloat, trust erosion, and building the wrong products.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By implementing proper alignment tools, separating discovery from delivery, and maintaining appropriate backlog size (3-6 sprints), teams can build products that truly matter. Success depends on trust, collaboration, risk navigation, and focusing on outcomes over outputs. Learn more about how to embrace the alignment-to-value pipeline and create your product operating model.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; TL; DR：对齐到值管道&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有效的产品开发需要战略一致性和健康产品积压管理。未对准会导致积压膨胀，信任侵蚀和建造错误的产品。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过实施适当的对准工具，将发现与交付分开以及保持适当的积压大小（3-6个冲刺），团队可以构建真正重要的产品。成功取决于信任，协作，风险导航，并专注于产出的结果。了解有关如何拥抱对齐方式到值管道并创建您的产品操作模型的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is AI Responsible for Its Actions, or Should Humans Take the Blame?】AI是对其行为负责的，还是人类应该责备？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/are-you-responsible-or-is-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;3:1-3:438&#34;&gt;The big question is: Can we handle AI responsibly? Or will we let it run wild?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;383&#34; data-start=&#34;201&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-artificial-intelligence&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; (AI) is changing the world. It is used in self-driving cars, healthcare, finance, and education. AI is making life easier, but it also comes with risks. What happens &lt;strong data-end=&#34;425&#34; data-start=&#34;398&#34;&gt;when AI makes a mistake&lt;/strong&gt;? Should AI take the blame, or should &lt;strong data-end=&#34;473&#34; data-start=&#34;463&#34;&gt;humans&lt;/strong&gt; be responsible?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 3：1-3：438”&gt;最大的问题是：我们可以负责任地处理AI吗？还是我们会让它疯狂？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 383” data-start =“ 201”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-mantoduction-to-antercover-intelligence”&gt;人工智能&lt;/a&gt;（AI）正在改变世界。它用于自动驾驶汽车，医疗保健，金融和教育。人工智能使生活更轻松，但也带有风险。 &lt;strong data-end =“ 425” data-start =“ 398”&gt;时会发生什么？ AI应该责备，还是&lt;strong data-end =“ 473” data-start =“ 463”&gt;人类&lt;/strong&gt;负责？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Have You Heard About Cloud Native Buildpacks?】您听说过云本机构建包吗？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/have-you-heard-about-cloud-native-buildpacks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Do you ever get tired of fiddling with a Dockerfile? Dockerfiles and Docker images are a great way to package your app for reusable, containerized deployments. However, writing and maintaining a Dockerfile is not always intuitive, and it takes up time that could otherwise be used for adding features to your app. Enter Cloud Native Buildpacks. Buildpacks exist to pull together everything your app needs to run and put it into an Open Container Initiative (OCI) image — no Dockerfile required.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For all the developers out there who need a container build process that’s easy to use and will save them time and headaches, Cloud Native Buildpacks might be the solution they’re looking for. Interested? I’ll tell you more.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您是否曾经厌倦与Dockerfile一起摆弄？ Dockerfiles和Docker Images是包装应用程序以进行可重复使用的容器部署的好方法。但是，编写和维护Dockerfile并不总是直观的，并且需要时间来添加功能。输入云本机构建包。存在构建包，可以将应用程序运行并将其放入开放容器倡议（OCI）图像中 - 无需Dockerfile所需的所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于所有需要容易使用的容器构建过程的开发人员，可以节省时间和头痛，云本机构建包可能是他们想要的解决方案。感兴趣的？我会告诉你更多。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ETL With Large Language Models: AI-Powered Data Processing】具有大语言模型的ETL：AI驱动的数据处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/etl-large-language-models-ai-powered-data-processing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;The extract, transform, and load (ETL) process is at the heart of modern data pipelines; it helps migrate and process large amounts of data for analytics, AI apps, and BI (business intelligence) for organizations. Conventional ETL used to be explicitly rule-based, which required tons of manual configurations to handle different data formats.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;However, with recent trends of large language models (LLMs), we are starting to see the dawn of transformative AI-driven ETL for data extraction and integration.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;提取物，转换和负载（ETL）过程是现代数据管道的核心；它有助于为组织的分析，AI应用程序和BI（商业智能）迁移和处理大量数据。常规ETL曾经是基于规则的，需要大量的手动配置来处理不同的数据格式。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;但是，随着大语模型（LLM）的最新趋势，我们开始看到用于数据提取和集成的变换AI驱动ETL的曙光。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Time Fraud Detection Using AI and Machine Learning】使用AI和机器学习实时欺诈检测</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-fraud-detection-using-ai-and-ml</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Problem Statement&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the rapid increase of online applications in industries such as finance, e-commerce, and social media, the frequency and sophistication of fraud attempts have surged. E-commerce apps face challenges like unauthorized transactions, fake bank account creation, and bot-driven attacks, leading to financial losses, reputational harm, and decreased user trust.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Current fraud detection methods often rely on post-event analysis, failing to address the need for real-time mitigation. The critical problem is to develop a system capable of detecting and preventing fraud as it occurs while balancing performance, user experience, and data privacy.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;问题语句&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;随着金融，电子商务和社交媒体等行业的在线应用程序的迅速增加，欺诈尝试的频率和复杂性已经激增。电子商务应用程序面临诸如未经授权的交易，伪造银行帐户创建和机器人驱动攻击之类的挑战，导致财务损失，声誉损失和用户信任减少。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;当前的欺诈检测方法通常依赖于事后分析，无法满足实时缓解的需求。关键的问题是开发一个能够在平衡性能，用户体验和数据隐私的同时检测和预防欺诈的系统。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Soaking in the Pressure of Using AI】浸入使用AI的压力</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/soaking-in-the-pressure-of-using-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;When large organizations spend billions of dollars in research and development of a revolutionary technology, a time comes when the technology is ready for prime time. The technology giants put their best foot forward to ensure large-scale global adoption of the technology. These are exciting times for any technology enthusiast, and it is natural to feel the urge to be a part of the bandwagon and not feel left out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;People across the rank and file of an organization are feeling the pressure of using AI-based solutions for every business problem. How do you soak in the pressure and make the right decisions for your business problems? Let&#39;s break down the problem and remove the cobwebs to get a clear picture of when to use AI and when not to.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;当大型组织花费数十亿美元的革命技术的研发时，就到了技术准备好黄金时段的时候。技术巨头迈出了最好的脚步，以确保全球大规模采用该技术。对于任何技术爱好者来说，这都是令人兴奋的时刻，自然会感觉到成为潮流而不感到被排除的冲动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;组织的等级和档案中的人感到为每个业务问题使用基于AI的解决方案的压力。您如何浸泡压力并为您的业务问题做出正确的决定？让我们分解问题并删除蜘蛛网，以清楚地了解何时使用AI以及何时不进行。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 14:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>