<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Write for DZone Publications: Trend Reports and Refcards】如何为 DZone 出版物写作：趋势报告和参考卡</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-write-for-dzone-publications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The DZone team is thrilled that you&#39;re interested in writing for DZone Publications! We are always seeking new authors to build up our author database. However, DZone Publications operate a bit differently from DZone site articles. Keep reading to learn more about writing for DZone Publications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;How to Stand Out on DZone&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;We handpick authors to write for DZone Publications. There are many things we look for when selecting authors, but it all boils down to one thing: &lt;strong&gt;Your DZone profile is your best tool for recognition&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;DZone 团队很高兴您有兴趣为 DZone Publications 撰写文章！我们一直在寻找新的作者来建立我们的作者数据库。然而，DZone 出版物的运作方式与 DZone 网站文章略有不同。继续阅读以了解有关为 DZone Publications 撰写文章的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如何在 DZone 上脱颖而出&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我们精心挑选作者为 DZone Publications 撰稿。在选择作者时，我们会考虑很多因素，但这一切都归结为一件事：&lt;strong&gt;您的 DZone 个人资料是您获得认可的最佳工具&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 12:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Redefining Ethical Web Scraping in the Wake of the Generative AI Boom】在生成式人工智能热潮中重新定义道德网络抓取</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ethical-web-scraping-in-the-wake-of-generative-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Public web data is being used for various purposes, from impactful research to creating and improving products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;One of the most common ways to acquire such data is through web scraping. Because it involves gathering large amounts of data published by businesses or individuals online, it raises questions such as &#34;Is it ethical?&#34; The short answer is yes if you&#39;re following certain practices, but we need to lay the groundwork before diving head-first into it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;公共网络数据被用于各种目的，从有影响力的研究到创建和改进产品。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;获取此类数据的最常见方法之一是通过网络抓取。由于它涉及收集企业或个人在线发布的大量数据，因此引发了诸如“这是否道德？”等问题。如果您遵循某些做法，简短的答案是肯定的，但我们需要在深入研究之前奠定基础。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Idea to Running: One Minute】跑步的想法：一分钟</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/idea-to-running-one-minute</link>
      <description>【&lt;section name=&#34;42c2&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;90a7&#34;&gt;Getting things right requires iteration. And we all know that requires &lt;em&gt;running screens &lt;/em&gt;— they engage users far more than documents or wireframes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;ed94&#34;&gt;Framework complexity leads to this unpleasant situation: months of effort to get running screens, only then to uncover a misunderstanding. Ouch. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/low-code-development-3&#34;&gt;Low code&lt;/a&gt; can help, but it still takes time to design databases and paint screens.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;节名称=“42c2”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;90a7&#34;&gt;要做好事情需要迭代。我们都知道这需要&lt;em&gt;运行屏幕 &lt;/em&gt; - 它们比文档或线框图更能吸引用户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;ed94&#34;&gt;框架的复杂性导致了这种不愉快的情况：花费数月的努力来获得运行屏幕，然后才发现误解。哎哟。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/low-code-development-3&#34;&gt;低代码&lt;/a&gt;可以提供帮助，但设计数据库和绘制屏幕仍然需要时间。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Next Big Thing: How Generative AI Is Reshaping DevOps in the Cloud】下一件大事：生成式 AI 如何重塑云中的 DevOps</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-generative-ai-is-reshaping-devops-in-the-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As businesses grow and cloud systems get more complex, traditional DevOps methods struggle to keep up with fast changes. That’s where Generative AI comes in. This new technology is changing how applications are made and used. It is also evolving DevOps practices by automating repetitive tasks, improving processes, enhancing security, and providing better monitoring insights. AI has become a crucial partner for DevOps teams that aim for agility and strength in a rapidly changing cloud world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will look closely at how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;Generative AI&lt;/a&gt; is transforming DevOps. We will talk about the challenges and opportunities it brings. We will also see how Microtica is leveraging AI to help DevOps teams deliver cloud solutions that are smarter, faster, and more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着业务的增长和云系统变得越来越复杂，传统的 DevOps 方法难以跟上快速的变化。这就是生成式人工智能的用武之地。这项新技术正在改变应用程序的制作和使用方式。它还通过自动化重复任务、改进流程、增强安全性和提供更好的监控见解来发展 DevOps 实践。人工智能已成为 DevOps 团队的重要合作伙伴，这些团队致力于在快速变化的云世界中获得敏捷性和实力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将仔细研究&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;生成式 AI&lt;/a&gt; 如何改变 DevOps。我们将谈论它带来的挑战和机遇。我们还将了解 Microtica 如何利用 AI 帮助 DevOps 团队提供更智能、更快速、更高效的云解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Test PATCH Requests for API Testing With Playwright Java】如何使用 Playwright Java 测试 API 测试的 PATCH 请求</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/testing-patch-requests-for-api-testing-with-playwright-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Automated API testing offers multiple benefits, including speeding up the testing lifecycle and providing faster feedback. It helps in enhancing the efficiency of the APIs and allows teams to deliver the new features speedily to the market.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are multiple tools and frameworks available in the market today that offer automation testing of the APIs, including Postman, Rest Assured, SuperTest, etc. The latest entry on this list is the Playwright framework, which offers API and Web Automation Testing.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;自动化 API 测试具有多种优势，包括加快测试生命周期并提供更快的反馈。它有助于提高 API 的效率，并允许团队将新功能快速推向市场。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当今市场上有多种提供 API 自动化测试的工具和框架，包括 Postman、Rest Assured、SuperTest 等。此列表中的最新条目是 Playwright 框架，它提供 API 和 Web 自动化测试.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring the New Boolean Data Type in Oracle 23c AI】探索 Oracle 23c AI 中的新布尔数据类型</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-the-new-boolean-data-type-in-oracle-23c-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This exciting release of Boolean Data Type Lab for Oracle Database 23c AI introduces native support for the boolean data type, a game-changer for database developers. With this enhancement, you can &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;natively represent &lt;strong&gt;true&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;false&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;null&lt;/strong&gt; values&lt;/span&gt;, simplifying data modeling and making SQL and PL/SQL development more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate, let’s recreate a scenario involving a &lt;strong&gt;Student Information System&lt;/strong&gt;, where we’ll track whether students are currently enrolled in courses using the new boolean data type.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这个激动人心的 Oracle Database 23c AI 布尔数据类型实验室版本引入了对布尔数据类型的本机支持，这为数据库开发人员带来了游戏规则的改变。通过此增强功能，您可以&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;本机表示 &lt;strong&gt;true&lt;/strong&gt;、&lt;strong&gt;false&lt;/strong&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;null&lt;/strong&gt;值&lt;/span&gt;，简化数据建模并使 SQL 和 PL/SQL 开发更加高效。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了说明这一点，让我们重新创建一个涉及&lt;strong&gt;学生信息系统&lt;/strong&gt;的场景，我们将在其中使用新的布尔数据类型跟踪学生当前是否注册了课程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Strategic Roadmap for Modernizing Digital Operations: Transitioning from Legacy Development Models to Agile-Driven Integrated Frameworks】数字化运营现代化战略路线图：从传统开发模型过渡到敏捷驱动的集成框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/modernizing-digital-operations-with-agile-frameworks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the modern world of constant change, change is the only constant for every fast-paced business that must provide a compelling and engaging solution to its target market. There are limitations in the waterfall actualization model, such as the inability to effectively meet the timelines and rush that dynamic customer operations often present. But moving to Agile is more than just a method; it&#39;s a new style of thinking about the interactions between systems, processes and technologies in the organization.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this paper, I present the views of how I participated in migrating a global beauty e-commerce brand from traditional e-commerce architecture to a more integrated approach governed by agile principles. But it wasn&#39;t just about adopting &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agile-development-tutorial-comprehensive-guide-wit&#34;&gt;Agile&lt;/a&gt; — it was about redesigning processes, integrating systems, and building up processes in order to create an environment that looks and feels seamless.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在不断变化的现代世界中，对于每个快节奏的企业来说，变化是唯一不变的，它们必须为其目标市场提供引人注目且有吸引力的解决方案。瀑布实现模型存在局限性，例如无法有效满足动态客户运营经常出现的时间表和仓促情况。但转向敏捷不仅仅是一种方法；它也是一种方法。这是一种关于组织中系统、流程和技术之间交互的新思维方式。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我提出了我如何参与将全球美容电子商务品牌从传统电子商务架构迁移到由敏捷原则管理的更加集成的方法的观点。但这不仅仅是采用敏捷——它还涉及重新设计流程、集成系统，并建立流程以创建一个看起来和感觉无缝的环境。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker Security Best Practices for Enterprise Applications: From Development to Production】企业应用程序的 Docker 安全最佳实践：从开发到生产</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-security-best-practices-for-enterprise-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s enterprise landscape, containerization has become almost synonymous with modern application deployment. However, with containers handling sensitive data and critical business operations, security should be carefully considered and implemented. I&#39;ve spent years securing containerized applications in the financial sector, and today I&#39;m going to share some battle-tested Docker security practices that have helped protect sensitive data for millions of customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Enterprise Container Security Landscape&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we dive into the technical stuff, let&#39;s talk about why &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-explained-an-introductory-guide-to-docker&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; security matters more than ever. With containers handling everything from payment processing to personal data, a single vulnerability can expose your entire infrastructure. Here&#39;s what keeps enterprise security teams up at night:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的企业环境中，容器化几乎已成为现代应用程序部署的代名词。然而，对于处理敏感数据和关键业务操作的容器，应仔细考虑和实施安全性。我花了数年时间保护金融领域的容器化应用程序，今天我将分享一些经过实战检验的 Docker 安全实践，这些实践帮助保护了数百万客户的敏感数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;企业容器安全格局&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在深入讨论技术内容之前，我们先来谈谈为什么&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-explained-an-introductory-guide-to-docker&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt;安全比以往任何时候都更加重要。由于容器处理从支付处理到个人数据的所有事务，一个漏洞就可能暴露您的整个基础设施。以下是让企业安全团队彻夜难眠的原因：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java Application Containerization and Deployment】Java应用程序容器化和部署</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/refcardz/java-application-containerization-and-deployment</link>
      <description>【Application containerization provides a way to combine all required app resources into a single, standardized, easily manageable package. And for Java applications, containerization helps solve the majority of challenges related to portability and consistency. This Refcard walks readers step by step through Dockerfile creation for Java apps, container image builds, deployment strategies, and more.】应用程序容器化提供了一种将所有必需的应用程序资源组合到单个、标准化、易于管理的包中的方法。对于 Java 应用程序来说，容器化有助于解决与可移植性和一致性相关的大多数挑战。此参考卡将逐步引导读者了解 Java 应用程序的 Dockerfile 创建、容器映像构建、部署策略等。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Java Class Extension Library for Data-Oriented Programming - Part 2】使用 Java 类扩展库进行面向数据的编程 - 第 2 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/using-java-class-extension-library-part-2</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This is the second article that presents an object-oriented programming (OOP) approach to effectively separate data from domain-specific logic in data-oriented programming, utilizing the dynamic class extensions using the Java Class Extension Library. You can read the &lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-java-class-extension-library&#34; target=&#34;_self&#34;&gt;first article there&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Let us reconsider the same scenario where we are building a warehouse application designed to handle the shipping of various items. We have established a hierarchy of classes to represent the goods we have:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;这是介绍面向对象编程 (OOP) 方法的第二篇文章，该方法利用动态类扩展，在面向数据的编程中有效地将数据与特定于域的逻辑分离Java 类扩展库。您可以在那里阅读&lt;a data-test-app-aware-link=&#34;&#34; href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-java-class-extension-library&#34; target=&#34;_self&#34;&gt;第一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;让我们重新考虑同样的场景，我们正在构建一个旨在处理各种物品运输的仓库应用程序。我们建立了一个类层次结构来表示我们拥有的商品：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>