<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring the Evolution of Transformers: From Basic To Advanced Architectures】探索 Transformer 的演变：从基础架构到高级架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-the-evolution-of-transformers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In their seminal 2017 paper, &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1706.03762&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Attention Is All You Need&lt;/a&gt;,&#34; Vaswani et al. introduced the Transformer architecture, revolutionizing not only speech recognition technology but many other fields as well. This blog post explores the evolution of Transformers, tracing their development from the original design to the most advanced models, and highlighting significant advancements made along the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Original Transformer&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The original Transformer model introduced several groundbreaking concepts:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在他们 2017 年的开创性论文中，“&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1706.03762&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;注意力就是你所需要的&lt; /a&gt;”，Vaswani 等人。推出了 Transformer 架构，不仅彻底改变了语音识别技术，还彻底改变了许多其他领域。这篇博文探讨了变形金刚的演变，追溯了它们从最初的设计到最先进模型的发展，并强调了这一过程中取得的重大进步。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;原始变压器&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最初的 Transformer 模型引入了几个突破性的概念：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Search Precision With Self-Querying Retrieval (SQR) and Langchain】通过自查询检索 (SQR) 和 Langchain 优化搜索精度</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-search-precision-with-sqr-and-langchain</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is Self-Querying Retrieval?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Self-querying retrieval (SQR) is a method ensuring that &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLMs&lt;/a&gt; are at the core of understanding the user&#39;s intent against a document collection. Key ideas include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Document representation:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Word embedding provides a numerical vector for every document. This helps in fast comparison between the documents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User query:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The user submits a natural language query expressing their need for information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LLM-driven retrieval:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The query and the document representations are fed into the LLM, which then retrieves documents that maximize the user&#39;s intent.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refine and repeat:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;The user is now able to refine his query or ask follow-up questions to narrow the search based on the retrieved documents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Self-Querying Retrieval?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional retrieval systems usually require complex query languages or predefined search facets. However, self-querying retrieval would provide a much more natural and user-friendly approach. Here is why:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是自查询检索？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自查询检索 (SQR) 是一种确保 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLM&lt;/a&gt; 处于理解用户对文档集合的意图的核心。主要想法包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;文档表示：&lt;/strong&gt;词嵌入为每个文档提供一个数值向量。这有助于快速比较文档。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;用户查询：&lt;/strong&gt;用户提交自然语言查询，表达他们对信息的需求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LLM 驱动的检索：&lt;/strong&gt;将查询和文档表示形式输入 LLM，然后 LLM 检索能够最大限度地表达用户意图的文档。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;优化和重复：&lt;/strong&gt;用户现在可以根据检索到的文档优化查询或提出后续问题以缩小搜索范围。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么要进行自查询检索？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统检索系统通常需要复杂的查询语言或预定义的搜索方面。然而，自查询检索将提供一种更加自然和用户友好的方法。原因如下：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Behavioral Biometrics Enhances Fraud Prevention】行为生物识别技术如何增强欺诈预防</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-behavioral-biometrics-enhances-fraud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-fraud-detection-systems-using-machine&#34;&gt;fraud prevention&lt;/a&gt; processes are far smoother than they used to be. Automated alert systems and authentication measures are now standard, but these relatively simple, rules-based solutions are still imperfect. The growing field of behavioral biometrics offers a more reliable alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Higher Detection Accuracy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Behavior biometrics’ accuracy is its primary advantage over conventional fraud detection. Researchers have developed systems capable of identifying fraud &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ksl.com/article/50826530/byu-professors-develop-keystroke-tracking-tech-to-detect-identity-fraud&#34;&gt;95.5% of the time&lt;/a&gt; by tracking keystrokes alone. Such precision is difficult with a rules-based system, especially when it comes to unknown attack patterns.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如今的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-fraud-detection-systems-using-machine&#34;&gt;欺诈预防&lt;/a&gt;流程比以前顺利得多成为。自动警报系统和身份验证措施现已成为标准，但这些相对简单、基于规则的解决方案仍然不完善。不断发展的行为生物识别领域提供了更可靠的替代方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;更高的检测精度&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;行为生物识别技术的准确性是其相对于传统欺诈检测的主要优势。研究人员开发了能够识别欺诈的系统 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ksl.com/article/50826530/byu-professors-develop-keyrinkle-tracking-tech-to-detect-identity-fraud&#34;&gt;95.5%通过单独跟踪击键来节省时间&lt;/a&gt;。对于基于规则的系统来说，如此精确是很困难的，特别是当涉及到未知的攻击模式时。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Use Guardrails for Safeguarding Generative AI Applications Built Using Custom or Third-Party Models】使用 Guardrails 保护使用自定义或第三方模型构建的生成式 AI 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/use-guardrails-for-safeguarding-generative-ai-app</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/guardrails.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock&lt;/a&gt; enables you to implement safeguards for your generative AI applications based on your use cases and responsible AI policies. You can create multiple guardrails tailored to different use cases and apply them across multiple foundation models (FM), providing a consistent user experience and standardizing safety and privacy controls across generative AI applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Until now, you could use Guardrails when directly using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/APIReference/API_runtime_InvokeModel.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;InvokeModel&lt;/a&gt; API, with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/knowledge-base.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Knowledge Base&lt;/a&gt; or an &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/agents.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Agent&lt;/a&gt;. In all these scenarios, Guardrails evaluates both user input entering into the model and foundation model responses coming out of the model. But this approach coupled the guardrail evaluation process with model inference/invocation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/guardrails.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Amazon Bedrock 的 Guardrail&lt;/a&gt;使您能够根据您的用例和负责任的 AI 政策为您的生成式 AI 应用程序实施保护措施。您可以根据不同的用例创建多个护栏，并将它们应用于多个基础模型 (FM)，从而提供一致的用户体验并标准化生成型 AI 应用程序的安全和隐私控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;到目前为止，您可以在直接使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/APIReference/API_runtime_InvokeModel.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34; 时使用 Guardrails _blank&#34;&gt;InvokeModel&lt;/a&gt; API，带有 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/knowledge-base.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34; _blank&#34;&gt;知识库&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/agents.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;代理&lt;/a&gt;。在所有这些场景中，Guardrails 都会评估进入模型的用户输入和从模型中出来的基础模型响应。但这种方法将护栏评估过程与模型推理/调用结合起来。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Key Strategies on How to Advance Your Digital Tech Career】如何推进数字技术职业的关键策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/key-strategies-to-advance-your-digital-tech-career</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The digital technology market is highly saturated and competitive, and to survive there, you need to succeed. Tech employers constantly seek IT professionals with the latest industry knowledge and expertise due to interconnected reasons: digital technology companies compete in international markets with each other, thus they need to be adaptive and constantly introduce new products and features to remain competitive. For every person working in the IT sector, it’s crucial to be up-to-date with the latest and most influential innovations and trends in their industry,&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/20-essential-software-development-books-to-read&#34;&gt; read professional literature&lt;/a&gt;, and constantly develop new skills. What main skills have the most value in the digital tech market? What is the perfect ratio between &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-soft-skills-are-the-hard-skills-of-today&#34;&gt;hard and soft skills&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Hard Skills vs Soft Skills&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each employee&#39;s role is specific to different areas of digital technology, and it is difficult to determine the exact ideal balance between hard and soft skills. However, on average, I would say that for technical roles, the percentage of hard skills is approximately 60-70 percent and 30-40 percent for soft skills. But for managerial roles, on the contrary, hard skills should be slightly less than 50 percent. Among the most important soft skills are clear communication, adaptability, critical and strategic thinking, and time management. Therefore, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/staff-plus-engineer-evolution-of-technical-career&#34;&gt;if your goal is to advance your career in leadership positions&lt;/a&gt;, it’s better to concentrate on polishing your soft skills, or, alternatively, try to achieve an equal balance of hard and soft skills through continuous development in both areas which can lead to a greater career success. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数字技术市场高度饱和且竞争激烈，要在其中生存，您需要取得成功。由于相互关联的原因，科技雇主不断寻求拥有最新行业知识和专业知识的 IT 专业人员：数字技术公司在国际市场上相互竞争，因此他们需要适应并不断推出新产品和功能以保持竞争力。对于每个在 IT 行业工作的人来说，了解行业中最新、最有影响力的创新和趋势至关重要，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/20-essential- software-development-books-to-read&#34;&gt;阅读专业文献&lt;/a&gt;，不断培养新技能。哪些主要技能在数字技术市场中最有价值？ &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-soft-skills-are-the-hard-skills-of-today&#34;&gt;硬技能和软技能&lt;/a&gt;之间的完美比例是多少？&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;硬技能与软技能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个员工的角色都特定于数字技术的不同领域，很难确定硬技能和软技能之间的确切理想平衡。然而，平均而言，对于技术职位，硬技能的比例约为 60-70%，软技能的比例约为 30-40%。但对于管理职位来说，硬技能则相反，应该略低于 50%。最重要的软技能包括清晰的沟通、适应能力、批判性和战略性思维以及时间管理。因此，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/staff-plus-engineer-evolution-of-technical-career&#34;&gt;如果您的目标是在领导职位上提升自己的职业生涯&lt;/a&gt;，那就更好专注于提高你的软技能，或者，通过在这两个领域的不断发展，尝试实现硬技能和软技能的平等平衡，这可以带来更大的职业成功。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Impact of Generative AI in the Cellular and IoT Telecommunication】生成式人工智能对蜂窝和物联网电信的影响</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-impact-of-generative-ai-in-telecom-software</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;The telecommunications industry, known for its constant evolution and technological advancements, is on the brink of a transformative shift with the integration of Generative AI (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-journey-through-generative-ai&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Gen AI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;). This emerging technology promises and is poised to revolutionize telecom operators&#39; operational methodologies, customer interactions, and service delivery. Let&#39;s explore the potential of Gen AI and its exciting future for telecommunication.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Let&#39;s dive deep.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;电信行业以其不断发展和技术进步而闻名，随着生成式人工智能 (Generative AI) 的集成，电信行业正处于变革的边缘 (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href =&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-journey-through-generative-ai&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Gen AI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver -空格=“true”&gt;）。这项新兴技术有望并有望彻底改变电信运营商的运营方法、客户交互和服务交付。让我们探索 Gen AI 的潜力及其在电信领域令人兴奋的未来。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;让我们深入探讨。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Pilot VPC and Advanced NAT: Securely Connect Overlapping Networks to AWS VPC】试点 VPC 和高级 NAT：将重叠网络安全连接到 AWS VPC</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/establish-encrypted-connectivity-between-an-overla</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s dynamic business environment, cloud computing has become a crucial enabler, offering enterprises unmatched scalability, flexibility, and cost-efficiency. Amazon Web Services (AWS), a leading cloud service provider, has transformed how organizations manage their IT infrastructures and applications. With &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/design-and-create-vpc-in-aws-1&#34;&gt;AWS Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)&lt;/a&gt;, businesses can establish secure, isolated environments within the cloud, replicating the capabilities of traditional on-premises networks. However, despite the clear benefits of cloud adoption, bridging the gap between on-premises networks and AWS VPCs can be challenging, particularly when dealing with overlapping IP addresses. Situations often arise where on-premises networks and AWS cloud environments unintentionally use the same private IP addresses, obstructing communication and data exchange across the VPN tunnel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article addresses this specific issue and explores an innovative solution for establishing secure connectivity between overlapping on-premises networks and AWS VPCs. Leveraging AWS site-to-site VPN, the traditional method for connecting on-premises environments and VPCs, enterprises frequently face obstacles when managing conflicting IP addresses. Mergers, acquisitions, and other networking complexities further complicate the situation, making straightforward resolution difficult.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今动态的商业环境中，云计算已成为关键的推动者，为企业提供无与伦比的可扩展性、灵活性和成本效率。 Amazon Web Services (AWS) 是一家领先的云服务提供商，它改变了组织管理其 IT 基础设施和应用程序的方式。借助 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/design-and-create-vpc-in-aws-1&#34;&gt;AWS 虚拟私有云 (VPC)&lt;/a&gt;，企业可以建立安全、隔离的环境在云中复制传统本地网络的功能。然而，尽管采用云有明显的好处，但弥合本地网络和 AWS VPC 之间的差距可能具有挑战性，特别是在处理重叠的 IP 地址时。经常会出现这样的情况：本地网络和 AWS 云环境无意中使用相同的私有 IP 地址，从而阻碍 VPN 隧道上的通信和数据交换。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文解决了这个特定问题，并探讨了一种创新解决方案，用于在重叠的本地网络和 AWS VPC 之间建立安全连接。利用 AWS 站点到站点 VPN（连接本地环境和 VPC 的传统方法），企业在管理冲突的 IP 地址时经常遇到障碍。合并、收购和其他网络复杂性使情况进一步复杂化，使得直接解决变得困难。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Implement a Gateway With Spring Cloud】如何使用 Spring Cloud 实现网关</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-implement-a-gateway-with-spring-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A microservice system could have a high number of components with complex interactions. It is important to reduce this complexity, at least from the standpoint of the clients interacting with the system. A gateway hides the microservices from the external world. It represents a unique entrance and implements common cross requirements. In this article, you will learn how to configure a gateway component for a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-framework-tutorials&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt; application, using the Spring Cloud Gateway package.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Spring Cloud Gateway&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-brief-overview-of-the-spring-cloud-framework&#34;&gt;Spring Cloud&lt;/a&gt; provides a gateway implementation by the Spring Cloud Gateway project. It is based on Spring Boot, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/embracing-reactive-programming-with-spring-webflux&#34;&gt;Spring WebFlux&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reactive-programming-with-project-reactor&#34;&gt;Reactor&lt;/a&gt;. Since it is based on Spring WebFlux, it must run on a Netty environment, not a usual servlet container.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;微服务系统可能具有大量具有复杂交互的组件。至少从客户端与系统交互的角度来看，降低这种复杂性非常重要。网关向外部世界隐藏微服务。它代表了一个独特的入口并实现了共同的交叉要求。在本文中，您将了解如何使用 Spring 为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-framework-tutorials&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt; 应用程序配置网关组件云网关包。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Spring 云网关&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-brief-overview-of-the-spring-cloud-framework&#34;&gt;Spring Cloud&lt;/a&gt;通过Spring Cloud Gateway提供了网关实现项目。它基于 Spring Boot、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/embracing-reactive-programming-with-spring-webflux&#34;&gt;Spring WebFlux&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https: //dzone.com/articles/reactive-programming-with-project-reactor&#34;&gt;反应堆&lt;/a&gt;。由于它是基于Spring WebFlux，所以它必须运行在Netty环境上，而不是通常的servlet容器上。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Developing Event-Driven, Auto-Compensating Saga Transactions For Microservices】为微服务开发事件驱动、自动补偿的 Saga 事务</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/developing-saga-transactions-for-microservices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;8828&#34;&gt;Over the past decade, I have presented many times and written numerous blogs and source code on sagas and event-driven microservices. In those blogs, I’ve discussed the need for sagas in microservices architectures, the preferred and increased use of event-driven patterns and communication for microservices, and the difficulties in implementing sagas, particularly around developing saga participant code for compensating transactions. These are addressed in the product solution I will describe, including an example source code &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/paulparkinson/saga-examples&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and soon, an update of the beta version of the saga workshop showing the same. The features are in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oracle.com/database/free-0/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Oracle Database Free Docker container&lt;/a&gt; and soon in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oracle.com/autonomous-database/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Oracle Autonomous Database&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;9aa7&#34;&gt;Part of what makes the new Oracle Saga Framework so powerful is its combined usage of other features in the Oracle Database including the TxEventQ transactional messaging system and reservation-less locking; therefore, I will describe them and how they contribute to the overall comprehensive solution as well.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name=&#34;8828&#34;&gt;在过去的十年中，我多次发表演讲并撰写了大量有关传奇和事件驱动微服务的博客和源代码。在这些博客中，我讨论了微服务架构中对 sagas 的需求、微服务事件驱动模式和通信的首选和增加使用，以及实现 sagas 的困难，特别是在开发用于补偿事务的 saga 参与者代码方面。这些问题将在我将描述的产品解决方案中得到解决，包括&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/paulparkinson/saga-examples&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/ a&gt;，很快，saga 研讨会的测试版更新也显示了相同的内容。这些功能将在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oracle.com/database/free-0/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Oracle Database Free Docker 容器&lt;/a&gt;中提供，并且很快就会推出在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.oracle.com/autonomous-database/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Oracle 自治数据库&lt;/a&gt;中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;9aa7&#34;&gt;新的 Oracle Saga 框架如此强大的部分原因在于它结合使用了 Oracle 数据库中的其他功能，包括 TxEventQ 事务消息系统和无预留锁定；因此，我将描述它们以及它们如何为整体综合解决方案做出贡献。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OpenTelemetry: Unifying Application and Infrastructure Observability】OpenTelemetry：统一应用程序和基础设施的可观测性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/opentelemetry-unifying-application-observability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;In this insightful Q&amp;amp;A, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/goutham-veeramachaneni/?original_referer=&amp;amp;originalSubdomain=de&#34;&gt;Goutham Veeramachaneni&lt;/a&gt;, a long-time &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; maintainer and Product Manager at &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.com/&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs&lt;/a&gt;, shares his unique perspective on the transformative impact of &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/opentelemetry-moves-past-the-three-pillars&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;(OTel) in the observability landscape. Veeramachaneni discusses how OTel is standardizing telemetry data and inspiring new open-source data collectors and workflows that bridge the gap between application and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/developers-handbook-for-infrastructure-monitoring&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;infrastructure monitoring&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. He offers valuable insights into the evolving ecosystem, the challenges ahead, and the exciting possibilities for developers in composing more effective telemetry data pipelines.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Q: As a Long-Time Prometheus Maintainer, What’s Your Take on the Overall Impact That OpenTelemetry Has Had on the Market?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;It’s given developers and platform teams much greater ownership of their data. It’s given them flexibility and freedom that they didn’t have before. Previously, with no universal open standard for telemetry data, the proprietary vendor mousetraps were designed to make it super difficult to migrate to other solutions, which was insane. These vendors didn’t have a lot of incentive to innovate or compete, because they had instrumented such effective mousetraps to lock users in. They spoke their protocols and collected their metrics, and there was no standardization. OpenTelemetry already has forced the entire market to standardize on the OTLP protocol and its ecosystem of SDKs and APIs. That has taken the power away from vendors and created a standard that is dynamic and open and where everyone collaborates — which is driving a ton of innovation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;在这篇富有洞察力的问答中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/goutham-veeramachaneni/?original_referer=&amp;originalSubdomain=de&#34;&gt;Goutham Veeramachaneni&lt;/a &gt;，长期 &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; 维护者和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.com/&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs&lt;/a&gt; 的产品经理a&gt;，分享了他对 OpenTelemetry 变革性影响的独特视角&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/opentelemetry-moves-past-the- Three-pillars&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/ em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; (OTel) 在可观测性领域。 Veeramachaneni 讨论了 OTel 如何标准化遥测数据并启发新的开源数据收集器和工作流程，以弥合应用程序和应用程序之间的差距&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/developers-handbook-for-基础设施监控&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;基础设施监控&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;。他对不断发展的生态系统、未来的挑战以及开发人员构建更有效的遥测数据管道的令人兴奋的可能性提供了宝贵的见解。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;问：作为 Prometheus 的长期维护者，您对 OpenTelemetry 对市场的整体影响有何看法？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;答：&lt;/strong&gt;它赋予了开发者和平台团队对其数据更大的所有权。它给了他们以前没有的灵活性和自由。以前，由于遥测数据没有通用的开放标准，专有供应商的捕鼠器被设计为使得迁移到其他解决方案变得非常困难，这是疯狂的。这些供应商没有太多创新或竞争的动力，因为他们设置了如此有效的捕鼠器来锁定用户。他们说出自己的协议并收集他们的指标，并且没有标准化。 OpenTelemetry 已经迫使整个市场对 OTLP 协议及其 SDK 和 API 生态系统进行标准化。这剥夺了供应商的权力，并创建了一个动态、开放且每个人都可以协作的标准，这正在推动大量创新。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>