<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Network Sniffing: A Critical Concept in Network Security】网络嗅探：网络安全中的一个关键概念</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/network-sniffing-critical-in-network-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;What Is Network Sniffing?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sniffing includes the passive interception of data packets crossing a network with further analysis. Initially, sniffing was developed to help network administrators troubleshoot connectivity problems, and since then, it has evolved into an important technique of network management and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-need-for-application-security-testing&#34;&gt;security testing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;How Does Network Sniffing Work?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Basically, network sniffing is based on the fact that a network interface card is set in &#34;promiscuous mode:&#34; all network traffic crossing its path is captured, not just packets addressed to the device. Then sniffing software analyzes the packets captured, allowing a user to read and interpret the data crossing the network.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;什么是网络嗅探？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;嗅探包括被动拦截通过网络的数据包并进行进一步分析。最初，嗅探是为了帮助网络管理员解决连接问题而开发的，从那时起，它已发展成为网络管理和应用的一项重要技术。 -security-testing&#34;&gt;安全测试&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;网络嗅探如何工作？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基本上，网络嗅探基于以下事实：网络接口卡设置为“混杂模式”：捕获经过其路径的所有网络流量，而不仅仅是发送到设备的数据包。然后嗅探软件分析捕获的数据包，允许用户读取和解释通过网络的数据。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Spring AI With LLMs To Generate Java Tests】使用 Spring AI 与 LLM 生成 Java 测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/using-spring-ai-with-llms-to-generate-java-tests</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Angular2Guy/AIDocumentLibraryChat&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AIDocumentLibraryChat&lt;/a&gt; project has been extended to generate test code (Java code has been tested). The project can generate test code for publicly available GitHub projects. The URL of the class to test can be provided then the class is loaded, the imports are analyzed and the dependent classes in the project are also loaded. That gives the LLM the opportunity to consider the imported source classes while generating mocks for tests. The &lt;code&gt;testUrl&lt;/code&gt; can be provided to give an example to the LLM to base the generated test. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/library/granite-code&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;granite-code&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/library/deepseek-coder-v2&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;deepseek-coder-v2&lt;/a&gt; models have been tested with Ollama.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The goal is to test how well the LLMs can help developers create tests.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Angular2Guy/AIDocumentLibraryChat&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AIDocumentLibraryChat&lt;/a&gt; 项目已扩展为生成测试代码（Java 代码已已测试）。该项目可以为公开可用的 GitHub 项目生成测试代码。可以提供要测试的类的 URL，然后加载该类，分析导入并加载项目中的依赖类。这使法学硕士有机会在生成测试模拟时考虑导入的源类。可以提供 &lt;code&gt;testUrl&lt;/code&gt; 来为 LLM 提供示例以作为生成测试的基础。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama.com/library/granite-code&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;granite-code&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ollama .com/library/deepseek-coder-v2&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;deepseek-coder-v2&lt;/a&gt; 模型已使用 Ollama 进行了测试。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目标是测试法学硕士如何帮助开发人员创建测试。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a CI/CD Pipeline With Kubernetes: A Development Guide With Deployment Considerations for Practitioners】使用 Kubernetes 构建 CI/CD 管道：针对从业者的开发指南和部署注意事项</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-cicd-pipeline-with-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-kubernetes-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes in the Enterprise: Once Decade-Defining, Now Forging a Future in the SDLC&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the past, before CI/CD and Kubernetes came along, deploying software to &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/home/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; was a real headache. Developers would build stuff on their own machines, then package it and pass it to the operations team to deploy it on production. This approach would frequently lead to delays, miscommunications, and inconsistencies between environments. Operations teams had to set up the deployments themselves, which increased the risk of human errors and configuration issues. When things went wrong, rollbacks were time consuming and disruptive. Also, without automated feedback and central monitoring, it was tough to keep an eye on how builds and deployments were progressing or to identify production issues.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-kubernetes-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;企业中的 Kubernetes：曾经定义十年，现在在 SDLC 中打造未来&lt;/em&gt;&lt; /a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;过去，在 CI/CD 和 Kubernetes 出现之前，将软件部署到 &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/home/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target= &#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; 确实令人头疼。开发人员将在自己的机器上构建内容，然后将其打包并传递给运营团队以将其部署到生产中。这种方法经常会导致延迟、沟通不畅和环境之间的不一致。运营团队必须自己设置部署，这增加了人为错误和配置问题的风险。当出现问题时，回滚既耗时又具有破坏性。此外，如果没有自动反馈和中央监控，就很难关注构建和部署的进展情况或识别生产问题。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 21:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Food Inventory Management App With Next.js, Material-UI, Firebase, Flask, and Hugging Face】使用 Next.js、Material-UI、Firebase、Flask 和 Hugging Face 构建食品库存管理应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-food-inventory-management-app</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;These days, restaurants, food banks, home kitchens, and any other business that deals with products and foods that go bad quickly need to have good food inventory management. Kitchens stay organized and waste is kept to a minimum by keeping track of stock, checking expiration dates, and managing usage well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I will show you how to make a Food Inventory Management App in this guide. With this app, users can:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;如今，餐馆、食品银行、家庭厨房以及任何其他处理容易变质的产品和食品的企业都需要良好的食品库存管理。通过跟踪库存、检查有效期和管理好使用情况，厨房保持井井有条，并将浪费降至最低。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;我将在本指南中向您展示如何制作食品库存管理应用程序。通过此应用程序，用户可以：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Decade of Excellence: The Journey, Impact, and Future of Kubernetes】卓越的十年：Kubernetes 的历程、影响和未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-journey-impact-and-future-of-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-kubernetes-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes in the Enterprise: Once Decade-Defining, Now Forging a Future in the SDLC&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A decade ago, Google introduced Kubernetes to simplify the management of containerized applications. Since then, it has fundamentally transformed the software development and operations landscape. Today, Kubernetes has seen numerous enhancements and integrations, becoming the de facto standard for container orchestration.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-kubernetes-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;企业中的 Kubernetes：曾经定义十年，现在在 SDLC 中打造未来&lt;/em&gt;&lt; /a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;十年前，Google 推出了 Kubernetes 来简化容器化应用程序的管理。从那时起，它从根本上改变了软件开发和运营格局。如今，Kubernetes 已经有了许多增强和集成，成为容器编排事实上的标准。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Haven’t You Upgraded to HTTP/2?】为什么还没有升级到 HTTP/2？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-havent-you-upgraded-to-http2</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;From a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; perspective, I’ve been the beneficiary of some pretty amazing features over the years:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.baeldung.com/java-generics&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Generics&lt;/a&gt; (Java 5)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.baeldung.com/java-streams&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Streams and Lambda Expressions&lt;/a&gt; (Java 8)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.baeldung.com/java-9-collections-factory-methods&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Enhanced Collection Functionality&lt;/a&gt; (Java 9)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.baeldung.com/java-sealed-classes-interfaces&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Sealed Classes&lt;/a&gt; (Java 17)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As key features become available, I’ve been able to reduce development time as I implement features, while also seeing benefits in performance and supportability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;从 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 的角度来看，我一直是一些非常惊人的功能的受益者年：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.baeldung.com/java-generics&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;泛型&lt;/a&gt; (Java 5)&lt;/李&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.baeldung.com/java-streams&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;流和 Lambda 表达式&lt;/a&gt; (Java 8 ）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.baeldung.com/java-9-collections-factory-methods&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;增强的集合功能&lt;/ a&gt;（Java 9）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.baeldung.com/java-sealed-classes-interfaces&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;密封类&lt;/a&gt; ( Java 17）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着关键功能的推出，我在实现功能时能够缩短开发时间，同时还看到了性能和可支持性方面的优势。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transformers: Age of Attention】变形金刚：关注时代</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/transformers-age-of-attention</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;In 2017, a group of researchers (from Google and the University of Toronto) introduced a new way to handle natural language processing (NLP) tasks. Their revolutionary paper “&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1706.03762&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Attention is All You Need&lt;/a&gt;” &amp;nbsp;presented the Transformer model, an architecture that has since become the basis of many advanced AI systems today. The model&#39;s performance, scalability, and versatility have led to its widespread adoption, forming the backbone of state-of-the-art models like BERT (Bidirectional Encoder Representations) and GPT (Generative Pre-trained Transformers).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before the Transformer model, most AI models that processed language relied heavily on a type of neural network called a Recurrent Neural Network (RNN) or its improved version, the Long Short-Term Memory Network (LSTM). In particular, problems like language modeling and machine translation (also called sequence transduction). These models processed words in a sequence, one by one, from left to right (or vice versa). While this approach made sense because words in a sentence often depend on the previous words, it had some significant drawbacks:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;2017 年，一组研究人员（来自 Google 和多伦多大学）推出了一种处理自然语言处理 (NLP) 任务的新方法。他们的革命性论文“&lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/pdf/1706.03762&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Attention is All You Need&lt;/a&gt;”介绍了 Transformer 模型，这是一种架构此后，它已成为当今许多先进人工智能系统的基础。该模型的性能、可扩展性和多功能性使其得到了广泛采用，形成了 BERT（双向编码器表示）和 GPT（生成式预训练变压器）等最先进模型的支柱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Transformer 模型出现之前，大多数处理语言的 AI 模型都严重依赖一种称为循环神经网络 (RNN) 的神经网络或其改进版本，即长短期记忆网络 (LSTM)。特别是语言建模和机器翻译（也称为序列转导）等问题。这些模型按顺序从左到右（或反之亦然）一个接一个地处理单词。虽然这种方法很有意义，因为句子中的单词通常依赖于前面的单词，但它有一些明显的缺点：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agile Primitives】敏捷原语</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agile-primitives</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR: Agile Primitives&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are we losing sight of what truly matters in Agile? The future isn’t about rigidly adhering to or outright dismissing frameworks like Scrum or SAFe. Instead, it’s about returning to the fundamental principles — the Agile Primitives — that genuinely empower teams to adapt, innovate, and deliver real value. By refocusing on these core elements, organizations can move beyond mere methodological compliance and embrace authentic agility.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dive in to explore how the Agile community is coming full circle, rediscovering the essence that made Agile transformative in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR：敏捷原语&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们是否忽视了敏捷中真正重要的东西？未来并不是严格遵守或彻底抛弃 Scrum 或 SAFe 等框架。相反，它是关于回归基本原则——敏捷原语——真正赋予团队适应、创新和交付真正价值的能力。通过重新关注这些核心要素，组织可以超越单纯的方法合规性，并拥抱真正的敏捷性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;深入探索敏捷社区如何回到原点，重新发现敏捷变革的本质。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Improve RAG Quality by Storing Knowledge Graph in Vector Database】如何通过在向量数据库中存储知识图来提高 RAG 质量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/improve-rag-storing-knowledge-graph-in-vector-db</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-docx-has-block-data=&#34;true&#34; data-lark-html-role=&#34;root&#34; data-page-id=&#34;LTpIdvOBjolayyxEO7ucXSR9nzb&#34;&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) techniques, by integrating external knowledge bases, provide additional contextual information for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLMs&lt;/a&gt;, effectively alleviating issues such as hallucination and insufficient domain knowledge of LLM. However, relying solely on general knowledge bases has its limitations, especially when dealing with complex entity relationships and multi-hop questions, where the model often struggles to provide accurate answers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-docx-has-block-data=&#34;true&#34; data-lark-html-role=&#34;root&#34; data-page-id=&#34;LTpIdvOBjolayyxEO7ucXSR9nzb&#34;&gt;Introducing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/organizing-knowledge-with-knowledge-graphs&#34;&gt;Knowledge Graphs&lt;/a&gt; (KGs) into the RAG system provides a new solution to this problem. KGs present entities and their relationships in a structured manner, offering more refined contextual information during retrieval. By leveraging the abundant relational data of KGs, RAG can not only pinpoint relevant knowledge more accurately but also better handle complex question-answering scenarios, such as comparing entity relationships or answering multi-hop questions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-docx-has-block-data=&#34;true&#34; data-lark-html-role=&#34;root&#34; data-page-id=&#34;LTpIdvOBjolayyxEO7ucXSR9nzb&#34;&gt;通过集成外部知识库的检索增强生成 (RAG) 技术，为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;LLM&lt;/a&gt;提供额外的上下文信息，有效缓解幻觉和领域知识不足等问题法学硕士。然而，仅仅依赖通用知识库有其局限性，特别是在处理复杂的实体关系和多跳问题时，模型往往难以提供准确的答案。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-docx-has-block-data=&#34;true&#34; data-lark-html-role=&#34;root&#34; data-page-id=&#34;LTpIdvOBjolayyxEO7ucXSR9nzb&#34;&gt;介绍&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ Articles/organizing-knowledge-with-knowledge-graphs&#34;&gt;将知识图谱（KG）引入到 RAG 系统中为这个问题提供了新的解决方案。知识图谱以结构化方式呈现实体及其关系，在检索过程中提供更精细的上下文信息。通过利用知识图谱丰富的关系数据，RAG不仅可以更准确地定位相关知识，还可以更好地处理复杂的问答场景，例如比较实体关系或回答多跳问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Geo-Location Redirects With AWS CloudFront】使用 AWS CloudFront 进行地理位置重定向</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/geo-location-redirects-with-aws-cloudfront</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the age of global digital services, geo-location-based content is critical for improving user experience and engagement, especially if you implement any shops or subscription services that should be adopted by the local market.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS CloudFront is one of the most widely used content delivery network (CDN) systems. It includes certain necessary features to implement geo-location-based redirection out of the box, but not in a single click.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在全球数字服务时代，基于地理位置的内容对于改善用户体验和参与度至关重要，尤其是当您实施本地市场应采用的任何商店或订阅服务时。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AWS CloudFront 是使用最广泛的内容交付网络 (CDN) 系统之一。它包含某些必要的功能，可以开箱即用地实现基于地理位置的重定向，但不是通过单击即可实现。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>