<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【The New Testing Pattern: Standardizing Regression for Cloud Migrations】新的测试模式：云迁移的标准化回归</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/new-testing-pattern-standardizing-regression-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;619&#34; data-start=&#34;250&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;266&#34; data-start=&#34;250&#34;&gt;“Cloud Lift”&lt;/strong&gt; (migrating on-premises systems to the cloud) is often sold as a simple infrastructure change. In reality, for large-scale administrative systems, it is a high-risk operation. When you move a system handling millions of transactions — such as unemployment insurance or tax processing — you cannot afford a single calculation error or &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/systematic-approach-to-java-performance-debugging&#34;&gt;performance regression&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;849&#34; data-start=&#34;621&#34;&gt;The challenge lies in validating that the new system behaves &lt;em data-end=&#34;691&#34; data-start=&#34;682&#34;&gt;exactly&lt;/em&gt; like the old one across thousands of business scenarios. Manual testing is too slow, and unit tests often miss the holistic impact of infrastructure changes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;619&#34; data-start=&#34;250&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;266&#34; data-start=&#34;250&#34;&gt;“Cloud Lift”&lt;/strong&gt;（将本地系统迁移到云端）通常作为简单的基础架构更改出售。事实上，对于大型行政系统来说，这是一个高风险的操作。当您迁移处理数百万笔交易的系统（例如失业保险或税务处理）时，您无法承受单个计算错误或&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/systematic-approach-to-java-performance-debugging&#34;&gt;性能下降&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;849&#34; data-start=&#34;621&#34;&gt;挑战在于在数千个业务场景中验证新系统的行为&lt;em data-end=&#34;691&#34; data-start=&#34;682&#34;&gt;与旧系统完全一样&lt;/em&gt;。手动测试太慢，单元测试常常错过基础设施变化的整体影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Context Engineering Is a Must-Learn Skill: Here&#39;s How Everyone Can Master It】情境工程是一项必须学习的技能：每个人都可以通过以下方式掌握它</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/context-engineering-is-a-must-learn-skill-how-to</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;The Rise of Context Engineering&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;739&#34; data-start=&#34;306&#34;&gt;In the rapidly &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/next-evolution-ai-autonomous-automation&#34;&gt;evolving landscape of artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt;, a new discipline has emerged that separates those who simply use AI tools from those who truly harness their power: &lt;strong data-end=&#34;507&#34; data-start=&#34;484&#34;&gt;context engineering&lt;/strong&gt;. While prompt engineering has been the buzzword of the past few years, context engineering represents the next evolutionary step — a more sophisticated, systematic approach to working with large language models (LLMs) and AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1227&#34; data-start=&#34;741&#34;&gt;Context engineering is the art and science of designing, constructing, and optimizing the information environment in which an AI model operates. It goes far beyond crafting clever prompts; it encompasses the entire ecosystem of data, instructions, examples, and constraints that shape an AI’s understanding and outputs. As AI systems become more powerful and are integrated into critical business processes, mastering context engineering has become not just advantageous—it’s essential.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;上下文工程的兴起&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;739&#34; data-start=&#34;306&#34;&gt;在快速&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/next-evolution-ai-autonomous-automation&#34;&gt;不断发展的人工智能领域&lt;/a&gt;中，一门新学科的出现将那些仅仅使用人工智能工具的人和真正利用其力量的人区分开来：&lt;strong data-end=&#34;507&#34; data-start=&#34;484&#34;&gt;情境工程&lt;/strong&gt;。虽然即时工程已成为过去几年的流行词，但上下文工程代表了下一个进化步骤——一种更复杂、更系统的方法来处理大型语言模型 (LLM) 和人工智能系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1227&#34; data-start=&#34;741&#34;&gt;情境工程是设计、构建和优化 AI 模型运行的信息环境的艺术和科学。它远远超出了精心设计巧妙的提示；它涵盖了塑造人工智能理解和输出的数据、指令、示例和约束的整个生态系统。随着人工智能系统变得更加强大并集成到关键业务流程中，掌握上下文工程不仅变得有利，而且变得至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Distributed Systems and Cloud Efficiency: A Deep Dive】分布式系统和云效率：深入探讨</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/distributed-systems-and-cloud-efficiency-deep-dive</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-test-render-count=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div data-is-streaming=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;h2 data-end=&#34;257&#34; data-start=&#34;221&#34;&gt;Cost Is a Distributed Systems Bug&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p data-end=&#34;578&#34; data-start=&#34;259&#34;&gt;The first time you watch $18,000 evaporate overnight because someone left autoscaling unbounded on a Kubernetes cluster that decided to provision 400 nodes for a traffic spike that never materialized, you stop thinking about cloud bills as accounting theater. Cost becomes what it always was: a failure mode with teeth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p data-end=&#34;1091&#34; data-start=&#34;580&#34;&gt;Zoom’s FinOps team saw their AWS spend double from $20K to $40K daily — not gradually, not with warning klaxons, just a jump that would burn through $600K in thirty days if left unaddressed. The mechanics were mundane: a feature rollout triggered cascading retries in a microservice mesh, with each retry spawning EC2 Spot instances that didn’t terminate cleanly. The cost spike manifested before the performance degradation did. Traditional monitoring missed it entirely because nobody had instrumented the bill.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-test-render-count=&#34;1&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div data-is-streaming=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;h2 data-end=&#34;257&#34; data-start=&#34;221&#34;&gt;成本是分布式系统的错误&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p data-end=&#34;578&#34; data-start=&#34;259&#34;&gt;当你第一次看到 18,000 美元一夜之间蒸发时，因为有人在 Kubernetes 集群上无限制地自动扩展，并决定为从未实现的流量峰值配置 400 个节点，你就不再将云账单视为会计剧场。成本变得一如既往：一种带有牙齿的故障模式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p data-end=&#34;1091&#34; data-start=&#34;580&#34;&gt;Zoom 的 FinOps 团队发现他们的 AWS 每天支出翻倍，从 2 万美元增加到 4 万美元 — 不是逐渐增加的，也没有鸣笛警告，只是一个跳跃，如果不加以解决，三十天内就会消耗 60 万美元。其机制很平常：功能推出会触发微服务网格中的级联重试，每次重试都会生成未完全终止的 EC2 Spot 实例。成本飙升在性能下降之前就显现出来了。传统监控完全错过了这一点，因为没有人对账单进行检测。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Self-Healing Observability System with AWS Bedrock AgentCore】使用 AWS Bedrock AgentCore 构建自我修复的可观察性系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/self-healing-observability-system-with-aws-bedrock</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;719&#34; data-start=&#34;224&#34;&gt;In today’s fast-paced cloud environments, keeping systems running smoothly isn’t just about monitoring them — it’s about making them smart enough to fix themselves. Enter the world of &lt;strong data-end=&#34;444&#34; data-start=&#34;406&#34;&gt;self-healing observability systems&lt;/strong&gt;, where AI agents detect issues, analyze root causes, and take corrective actions without human intervention. With &lt;strong data-end=&#34;584&#34; data-start=&#34;559&#34;&gt;AWS Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/strong&gt;, a powerful platform for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-build-and-deploy-an-ai-agent-on-kubernetes&#34;&gt;building and deploying AI agents&lt;/a&gt; at scale, you can create a system that is reliable, secure, and efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;951&#34; data-start=&#34;721&#34;&gt;In this article, we’ll dive deep into how to build such a system from scratch, complete with code examples, practical diagrams, and real-world insights. By the end, you’ll have a blueprint to implement your own self-healing setup.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;719&#34; data-start=&#34;224&#34;&gt;在当今快节奏的云环境中，保持系统平稳运行不仅仅在于监控它们，还在于让它们足够智能以进行自我修复。进入&lt;strong data-end=&#34;444&#34; data-start=&#34;406&#34;&gt;自我修复可观测系统&lt;/strong&gt;的世界，其中人工智能代理可以检测问题、分析根本原因并采取纠正措施，无需人工干预。借助 &lt;strong data-end=&#34;584&#34; data-start=&#34;559&#34;&gt;AWS Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/strong&gt; 这一强大的平台，您可以创建一个可靠、安全且高效的系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;951&#34; data-start=&#34;721&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将深入探讨如何从头开始构建这样一个系统，并提供代码示例、实用图表和现实世界的见解。最后，您将拥有一个实现您自己的自我修复设置的蓝图。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agentic DataOps With Guardrails: MCP and MWAA for Pipeline Incident Response】具有 Guardrails 的代理数据操作：用于管道事件响应的 MCP 和 MWAA</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-dataops-with-guardrails-mcp-mwaa</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Failure of data pipelines increasingly feels a lot like a security incident. They occur at inconvenient times; dashboards become stale; delays in data availability impact business decisions; and the on-call engineer loses time navigating across various tools, including CloudWatch logs, tickets, chats, code, and the Airflow UI (MWAA), to identify root causes. Some of the questions you ask yourself during this process are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;What broke, and why did it break?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;What are the logs actually saying?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;What is the safest option to recover?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Is it repeating?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In most teams, the real cost isn&#39;t clicking on retry. It is about finding context: the right DAG, the right task, the right logs, the right log lines, the downstream impact, and the safest next step to the recovery path. Most GenAI pilots in data teams don&#39;t help much since they are still passive. They can explain what to do, but can&#39;t reliably pull CloudWatch logs, correlate failure across runs, or propose a safe action that you can audit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据管道故障越来越让人感觉像是安全事件。它们发生在不方便的时间；仪表板变得陈旧；数据可用性的延迟影响业务决策；值班工程师会浪费时间浏览各种工具，包括 CloudWatch 日志、票证、聊天、代码和 Airflow UI (MWAA)，以找出根本原因。在此过程中您会问自己的一些问题是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;什么东西坏了，为什么坏了？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;日志实际上说了什么？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;最安全的恢复选项是什么？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;是否重复？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在大多数团队中，真正的成本并不是点击重试。它是关于寻找上下文：正确的 DAG、正确的任务、正确的日志、正确的日志行、下游影响以及恢复路径最安全的下一步。数据团队中的大多数 GenAI 飞行员并没有多大帮助，因为他们仍然是被动的。他们可以解释要做什么，但无法可靠地提取 CloudWatch 日志、关联运行中的故障或提出可供您审核的安全操作。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【An AI-Driven Architecture for Autonomous Network Operations (NetOps)】用于自主网络运营 (NetOps) 的人工智能驱动架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-driven-architecture-for-autonomous-network-operations</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;451&#34; data-start=&#34;211&#34;&gt;In the modern enterprise, the divide between Systems Engineering (SE) and Operations (Ops) is growing. SE teams architect complex, zero-trust networks, while Ops teams are left to maintain them with limited visibility and outdated runbooks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;738&#34; data-start=&#34;453&#34;&gt;When a critical incident occurs, the escalation path is predictable: Ops attempts to troubleshoot, fails due to a lack of deep technical context, and escalates to SE. This creates a bottleneck in which senior architects spend their time fighting fires instead of designing new systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;451&#34; data-start=&#34;211&#34;&gt;在现代企业中，系统工程 (SE) 和运营 (Ops) 之间的鸿沟正在扩大。 SE 团队构建复杂的零信任网络，而运维团队则只能以有限的可见性和过时的操作手册来维护它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;738&#34; data-start=&#34;453&#34;&gt;当发生严重事件时，升级路径是可以预测的：运维人员尝试排除故障，但由于缺乏深入的技术背景而失败，然后升级为 SE。这造成了一个瓶颈，高级架构师将时间花在救火上，而不是设计新系统。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Next-Level Persistence in Jakarta EE: How We Got Here and Why It Matters】Jakarta EE 的新水平持久性：我们如何走到这一步以及为什么它很重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/next-level-persistence-jakarta-ee</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Enterprise Java persistence has never really been about APIs. It has always been about assumptions. Long before frameworks, annotations, or repositories entered the picture, the enterprise Java ecosystem was shaped by a single, dominant belief: persistence meant relational databases. That assumption influenced how applications were designed, how teams reasoned about data, and how the Java platform itself evolved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article is inspired by a presentation given by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/arjantijms/?originalSubdomain=nl&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Arjan Tijms&lt;/a&gt;, director of &lt;a href=&#34;https://omnifish.ee/&#34;&gt;OmniFish&lt;/a&gt;, titled &lt;em&gt;“Next-level persistence in Jakarta EE: Jakarta Data and Jakarta NoSQL.”&lt;/em&gt; Delivered in 2024, the talk offers a clear and pragmatic view of why Jakarta EE persistence needed to evolve, how Jakarta Data fits into the platform, and how it relates to Jakarta Persistence and Jakarta NoSQL. While the presentation provides the technical backbone, this article expands on the historical context and architectural motivations behind that evolution.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;企业 Java 持久性从来都不是真正与 API 相关的。它一直与假设有关。早在框架、注释或存储库出现之前，企业 Java 生态系统就被一个单一的主导信念所塑造：持久性意味着关系数据库。这一假设影响了应用程序的设计方式、团队如何推理数据以及 Java 平台本身的发展方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文的灵感来自 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/arjantijms/?originalSubdomain=nl&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Arjan Tijms&lt;/a&gt;（&lt;a href=&#34;https://omnifish.ee/&#34;&gt;OmniFish&lt;/a&gt; 的总监）的演讲，题为“Jakarta EE 的下一级持久性：Jakarta 数据和Jakarta NoSQL。&lt;/em&gt; 该演讲于 2024 年发表，针对 Jakarta EE 持久性为何需要发展、Jakarta Data 如何适应该平台以及它与 Jakarta Persistence 和 Jakarta NoSQL 的关系，提供了清晰而务实的观点。虽然演示文稿提供了技术支柱，但本文扩展了该演变背后的历史背景和架构动机。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agile’s AI-Driven Paradigm Shift】敏捷的人工智能驱动范式转变</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agiles-ai-driven-paradigm-shift</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Agile’s AI-Driven Paradigm Shift&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The paradigm shift is here. Andrej Karpathy, former Tesla AI director and OpenAI co-founder, recently admitted he has never felt this far behind as a programmer. If Karpathy feels overwhelmed, how should the rest of us feel?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article maps the shift across three levels: strategic, product, and individual. Each level demands different responses, while “good enough &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agile-data-management-a-comprehensive-guide&#34;&gt;Agile&lt;/a&gt;” no longer provides an income or perspective. The question is where you are on the journey.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL； DR：敏捷的人工智能驱动范式转变&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;范式转变就在这里。特斯拉前人工智能总监兼 OpenAI 联合创始人安德烈·卡帕蒂 (Andrej Karpathy) 最近承认，作为一名程序员，他从未感到如此落后。如果卡帕斯感到不知所措，我们其他人应该有何感受？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文描绘了三个层面的转变：战略、产品和个人。每个级别都需要不同的响应，而“足够好&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agile-data-management-a-compressive-guide&#34;&gt;敏捷&lt;/a&gt;”不再提供收入或观点。问题是您处于旅程的哪个阶段。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Model Context Protocol Vs Agent2Agent: Practical Integration with Enterprise Data】模型上下文协议与 Agent2Agent：与企业数据的实际集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/model-context-protocol-agent2agent-practical</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;486&#34; data-start=&#34;234&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/creating-ai-agents-using-the-model-context-protocol&#34;&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP)&lt;/a&gt;, introduced by Anthropic in November 2024, and Agent2Agent (A2A), launched by Google in April 2025, are two different ways of designing AI systems that allow language models and agents to work with tools or with each other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;885&#34; data-start=&#34;488&#34;&gt;While both aim to make AI development faster and more efficient, they solve different problems. MCP focuses on deterministic tool integration for language models, meaning it provides predictable ways for models to interact with external tools. A2A, on the other hand, focuses on asynchronous agent-to-agent communication, allowing multiple agents to coordinate and share information independently.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;486&#34; data-start=&#34;234&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/creating-ai-agents-using-the-model-context-protocol&#34;&gt;模型上下文协议 (MCP)&lt;/a&gt;（由 Anthropic 于 2024 年 11 月推出）和 Agent2Agent (A2A)（由 Google 于 2025 年 4 月推出）是设计 AI 系统的两种不同方式，允许语言模型和代理协同工作工具或相互配合。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;885&#34; data-start=&#34;488&#34;&gt;虽然两者的目标都是让人工智能开发更快、更高效，但它们解决的问题不同。 MCP 专注于语言模型的确定性工具集成，这意味着它为模型与外部工具交互提供了可预测的方式。另一方面，A2A 专注于异步代理到代理通信，允许多个代理独立协调和共享信息。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding AI Agent Types:Guide to 8 Modern AI Architectures】了解 AI 代理类型：8 种现代 AI 架构指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-ai-agent-types-ai-architectures</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will discuss eight major AI agent types: LCM, HRM, LAM, SLM, VLM, LRM, MOE, and GPT, optimized for specific problem domains, technological implementations, and practical applications. By understanding the strengths and limitations of each architecture, practitioners can make informed decisions when designing AI systems for production environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The landscape of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-ai-in-dotnet&#34;&gt;AI agents&lt;/a&gt; has transformed dramatically over the past five years. Rather than developing single models to address all problems, the industry has converged on specialized architectures, each tailored to specific computational and reasoning requirements. This article provides practitioners, researchers, and decision-makers with a detailed roadmap of eight foundational agent types, complete with technological stacks and implementation guidance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将讨论八种主要的人工智能代理类型：LCM、HRM、LAM、SLM、VLM、LRM、MOE 和 GPT，针对特定问题领域、技术实现和实际应用进行了优化。通过了解每种架构的优势和局限性，从业者可以在为生产环境设计人工智能系统时做出明智的决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去五年中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-ai-in-dotnet&#34;&gt;人工智能代理&lt;/a&gt;的格局发生了巨大变化。该行业并没有开发单一模型来解决所有问题，而是集中在专门的架构上，每个架构都根据特定的计算和推理要求进行定制。本文为从业者、研究人员和决策者提供了八种基本代理类型的详细路线图，并附有技术堆栈和实施指南。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>