<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【The Invisible Risk in Your Middleware: A Next.js Flaw You Shouldn’t Ignore】中间件中的无形风险：ables.js缺陷，你不应该忽略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/nextjs-middleware-vulnerability</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Web development in 2025 has evolved at an incredible pace. We’ve gone from clunky monoliths to sleek, scalable apps powered by frameworks like Next.js, which millions of developers now rely on for building modern, server-rendered React applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But as our tools get more advanced, so do the threats.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; 2025年的Web开发以令人难以置信的速度发展。我们已经从笨拙的整体变成了由Next.js之类的框架供电的时尚，可扩展的应用程序，现在数百万开发人员现在依靠它来构建现代的，服务器渲染的React应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，随着我们的工具变得越来越高，威胁也是如此。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ZapBot: Building a Chatbot With OpenAI and Gradio】Zapbot：与OpenAI和Gradio建立聊天机器人</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zapbot-building-a-chatbot-with-openai-and-gradio</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-chatbots-and-ai-assistants-a-comprehensiv&#34;&gt;Chatbots&lt;/a&gt; have become a foundational element of modern digital systems, revolutionizing the way businesses and individuals interact with users and automate workflows. Their importance lies in their ability to deliver instant, scalable, and personalized communication while reducing the need for human intervention. As artificial intelligence and natural language processing evolve, chatbots are increasingly capable of handling complex tasks with high efficiency and consistency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of their key advantages is the enhancement of user experience. By offering 24/7 availability and consistent responses, chatbots improve customer satisfaction and reduce service delays. For instance, retail websites use chatbots to assist users with product searches or order tracking, providing real-time support around the clock.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/building-chatbots-and-ai-assistants-a-comprehensiv”&gt; Chatbots &lt;/a&gt;已成为现代数字系统的基本要素，彻底改变了业务和个人与用户和自动化工作量的互动方式。它们的重要性在于他们能够提供即时，可扩展和个性化的交流的能力，同时减少对人类干预的需求。随着人工智能和自然语言处理的发展，聊天机器人越来越能够以高效率和一致性处理复杂的任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他们的关键优势之一是增强用户体验。通过提供24/7的可用性和一致的响应，聊天机器人可以提高客户满意度并减少服务延迟。例如，零售网站使用聊天机器人来协助用户进行产品搜索或订单跟踪，并全面提供实时支持。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 13:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Your IDP Using Centralized Configuration Management With IBM Cloud App Configuration: A Complete Guide】使用IBM Cloud App配置使用集中配置管理优化IDP：完整指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ibm-cloud-app-configuration-idp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://internaldeveloperplatform.org/what-is-an-internal-developer-platform/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Internal Developer Platforms&lt;/a&gt; (IDPs) are becoming essential for boosting efficiency, scalability, and security. These platforms are designed by platform engineering teams with developers in mind, ensuring they have the right tools to streamline their workflows. At the heart of every IDP are five key components (next section) that keeps everything running smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cloud.ibm.com/docs/app-configuration?topic=app-configuration-getting-started&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IBM Cloud App Configuration&lt;/a&gt; (IBM Cloud AC) plays a crucial role in this ecosystem to do centralized configuration management. It offers a scalable, fault tolerant, and secure way to manage dynamic configurations, feature flags, and access (allow listing) management which is all access controlled. It seamlessly aligns with the core components of an IDP, helping teams maintain flexibility and control.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://internaldeveloperplatform.org/what-is-an-internal-developer-platform/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Internal Developer Platforms&lt;/a&gt; (IDPs) are becoming essential for boosting efficiency, scalability, and security.这些平台是由平台工程团队设计的，考虑到开发人员，确保他们具有精简工作流的正确工具。每个IDP的核心是五个关键组件（下一节），可以使所有内容保持平稳运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https：//cloud.ibm.com/docs/app-configuration?topic = app = app-configuration-getting-started started started” rel =“ rel =” noopener noreferrer noreferrer noreferrer noreferrer“ targ进行集中配置管理。它提供了一种可扩展，容错且安全的方法来管理动态配置，功能标志和访问（允许列表）管理，该管理均为访问权限。它与IDP的核心组件无缝保持一致，帮助团队保持灵活性和控制。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maximizing Return on Investment When Securing Our Supply Chains: Where to Focus Our Limited Time to Maximize Reward】确保我们的供应链时，最大化投资回报率：在哪里集中精力以最大程度地提高奖励</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-software-supply-chain-for-maximum-roi</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-security-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Software Supply Chain Security: Enhancing Trust and Resilience Across the Software Development Lifecycle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The goal of DevOps and DevSecOps — and whatever future contractions come next — has been to break down walls, but in practice, it usually means that developers take on a greater burden. Now, developers are not just responsible for delivering a satisfactory product on time, but also managing the operations and security of the product. This begs the question: Is it possible for developers to accomplish all of this? The answer is yes, but only if we spend our time wisely.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ font-size：17px;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;编辑注：以下是为Dzone的2025年2025年趋势报告编写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/link/link/link/link/2025-security-contribity-contributor-contributor-artilecutor-article- sepusence”增强软件开发生命周期的信任和韧性&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; DevOps和Devsecops的目标 - 以及接下来的未来收缩 - 都将破坏墙壁，但实际上，这通常意味着开发人员承担着更大的负担。现在，开发人员不仅负责按时交付令人满意的产品，还负责管理产品的运营和安全性。这就提出了一个问题：开发人员是否有可能完成所有这些？答案是肯定的，但是只有我们明智地花时间。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Engineering High-Scale Real Estate Listings Systems Using Golang, Part 1】使用Golang的工程高规模房地产清单系统，第1部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/high-scale-real-estate-mls-integration-golang</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In high-scale real estate platforms, the real challenge isn’t just about fetching listings, it’s about processing and serving millions of records across diverse MLS (Multiple Listing Service) providers with speed, resilience, and cost-efficiency. Whether you’re integrating with the United States’ BrightMLS or Canada’s TRREB, each MLS comes with its own quirks: &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;varying data models&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;inconsistent metadata,&lt;/em&gt; irregular update cycles, and evolving schemas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At scale, those differences are edge cases no longer; they’re daily roadblocks. Your backend must not only ingest and normalize terabytes’ worth of listing data but also cope with real-time sync, deduplication, tagging, scoring, and advanced filtering, bottleneck-free. For our team at a high-flying Vancouver-based real estate startup, the answer was to design a system in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/golang-first-look-at-generics&#34;&gt;Go (Golang)&lt;/a&gt; that would tolerate high concurrency, have hard memory limits, and operate under realistic production pressure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在高规模的房地产平台中，真正的挑战不仅仅在于获取清单，还涉及以速度，弹性和成本效率的方式处理和为各种MLS（多个上市服务）提供商提供数百万张记录。无论您是与美国的BrightMLS还是加拿大的TRREB集成，每个MLS都有其自己的怪癖：&lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt;不一致的数据模型&lt;/em&gt;，&lt;em&gt;不一致的元数据，&lt;/em&gt;不规则的更新周期和不规则的模式，以及进化的模式。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在大规模上，这些差异不再是边缘案例。他们每天都是障碍。您的后端不仅必须摄入并标准化Terabytes的列表数据价值，还必须应对实时同步，重复数据删除，标记，评分和高级过滤，以及无瓶颈。对于我们在一家位于温哥华高空的房地产创业公司的团队来说，答案是在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/golang-first-look-at-generics”中设计一个系统，</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Real-Time Webcam-Based Sign Language and Speech Bidirectional Translation System】基于实时网络摄像头的手语和语音双向翻译系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-sign-language-speech-bidirectional-translation-system</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Communication between deaf individuals who rely on sign language and those who do not understand sign language remains a significant challenge. Globally, an estimated 466 million people have disabling hearing loss and rely on visual languages like American Sign Language (ASL) as their primary means of communication. Without an interpreter, deaf persons often face barriers in everyday interactions such as education, healthcare, and customer service. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-are-smart-technologies-changing-the-translatio&#34;&gt;AI-powered sign language translation&lt;/a&gt; offers a promising solution by automatically translating sign language into spoken/written language and vice versa, thereby closing the divide in communication. Recent advances in computer vision and deep learning enable robust recognition of hand gestures and facial expressions, while &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-is-nlp-essential-in-speech-recognition-systems&#34;&gt;NLP and speech technologies&lt;/a&gt; can generate fluent sign language or speech output. The objective of this research is to design a two-way translation system that: (1) recognizes sign language from webcam video and converts it to text and audible speech in real time, and (2) converts spoken language (voice) into accurate sign language, presented via an animated avatar. By facilitating bidirectional communication, such a system can greatly enhance the independence and social integration of deaf and hard-of-hearing individuals. In the following sections, we discuss background and related work in sign language recognition and synthesis, detail our methodology including the AI models and system architecture, present experimental results, and examine the impact on the deaf community along with future research directions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Related Work&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Early approaches to automated sign language translation involved instrumented gloves or heuristic computer-vision techniques. For example, instrumented glove devices with sensors have been used to capture hand motions, but these solutions can be intrusive and limited to specific vocabularies. With the rise of computer vision, focus shifted to camera-based sign language recognition. Traditional vision methods employed techniques like skin-color segmentation and handcrafted features (e.g., Haar-like features or optical flow) to detect hand gestures, but often struggled with variability in lighting and sign execution.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;依靠手语的聋人与不了解手语的人之间的沟通仍然是一个重大挑战。在全球范围内，估计有4.66亿人致力于听力损失，并依靠像美国手语（ASL）这样的视觉语言作为其主要交流手段。没有口译员，聋人经常在日常互动中面临障碍，例如教育，医疗保健和客户服务。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-are-are-smart-technologies-changing-the-translatio”&gt; ai-power的手语翻译&lt;/a&gt;通过自动将手语/书面语言和vice vice vise vissa转换为交流中的副语言，从而提供了有希望的解决方案。计算机视觉和深度学习的最新进展使人对手势和面部表情的强烈认识，而&lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/why-is-nlp-esential-nlp-esential-in-spech-rcognition-systems&gt; nlp和语音技术&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;可以产生流畅的手语或语言输出。这项研究的目的是设计一个双向翻译系统，该系统：（1）从网络摄像头视频中识别手语，并将其实时转换为文本和可听见的语音，（2）通过动画化的头像提出，将口语（语音）转换为准确的手语。通过促进双向交流，这种系统可以大大增强聋人和听力障碍个人的独立性和社会融合。在以下各节中，我们讨论了手语识别和综合方面的背景和相关工作，详细介绍了我们的方法论，包括AI模型和系统体系结构，呈现实验结果，并研究对聋人社区的影响以及未来的研究方向。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;相关工作&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自动化手语翻译的早期方法涉及仪器手套或启发式计算机视觉技术。例如，带有传感器的仪器手套设备已用于捕获手动运动，但是这些解决方案可能是侵入性的，并且仅限于特定的词汇。随着计算机视觉的兴起，焦点转移到基于摄像机的手语识别。传统的视觉方法采用了诸如皮肤彩色细分和手工制作的功能（例如，类似于HAAR的功能或光流）来检测手势，但通常在照明和签名执行方面差异。&lt;/p&gt;&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Ingestion: The Front Door to Modern Data Infrastructure】数据摄入：现代数据基础设施的前门</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-data-ingestion-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;927&#34; data-start=&#34;527&#34;&gt;Businesses thrive on data—but only if that data is ingested effectively. Whether it’s retail transactions, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/why-dive-into-iot-sensor-calibration-insights&#34;&gt;IoT sensor&lt;/a&gt; readings, financial records, or user interactions, the ability to collect and move data into operational and analytical systems is mission-critical. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-ingestion-the-definitive-guide&#34;&gt;Data ingestion&lt;/a&gt; is no longer just an ETL job; it’s the front door to modern data infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1221&#34; data-start=&#34;929&#34;&gt;With growing data volumes, real-time use cases, and stricter compliance requirements, organizations must architect ingestion pipelines that are scalable, secure, and purpose-built. AWS offers a rich set of ingestion services, but how do you choose the right one for your business needs?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 927” data-start =“ 527”&gt;业务在数据上蓬勃发展，但只有当该数据有效摄入时，只有当该数据有效地摄入。无论是零售交易，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/why-dive-into-into-iot-sensor-calibration-indights-indights”&gt; IOT传感器&lt;/a&gt;读取，财务记录或用户互动，将数据收集和移动到操作和分析系统中的能力是任务至关重要的。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/data-ingestion-the-definistive-guide”&gt;数据摄入&lt;/a&gt;不再只是ETL工作；这是现代数据基础设施的前门。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1221” data-start =“ 929”&gt;随着数据量的增长，实时用例和更严格的合规性要求，组织必须构建可扩展，安全和专用构建的架构摄入管道。 AWS提供了丰富的摄入服务，但是您如何为您的业务需求选择合适的服务？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Making AI Faster: A Deep Dive Across Users, Developers, and Businesses】更快地使AI：在用户，开发人员和企业之间进行深入研究</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/making-ai-faster-strategies-for-speed</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI isn’t just about building smarter models—it&#39;s about making them practical, performant, and scalable. This means solving for three interdependent axes: speed, quality, and cost. Let’s break down why these matter across three critical stakeholder perspectives:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;End Users expect seamless, trustworthy, and responsive &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-explained-for-curious-minds&#34;&gt;AI&lt;/a&gt; experiences.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/managing-software-engineering-teams-of-ai-devs&#34;&gt;AI Developers&lt;/a&gt; need faster iteration loops, debuggable pipelines, and scalable training.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Business Stakeholders demand ROI, cost efficiency, and regulatory compliance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Think of AI powering a voice assistant or a self-driving car or any other AI use-case. Speed determines usability, accuracy builds trust, and cost dictates feasibility. I am writing these articles as a three part series to help discover practical strategies to accelerate AI development, boost performance, and optimize costs without compromising innovation. Drawing from real-world experiences, we will discuss Making AI Faster, Better, Cheaper.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; AI不仅仅是建立更智能的模型，还涉及使它们实用，性能和可扩展。这意味着解决三个相互依存的轴：速度，质量和成本。让我们分解为什么这些重要的是从三个关键的利益相关者角度来看：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir =“ ltr”&gt;最终用户期望无缝，值得信赖且响应式&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-explaining-fored-for-curious-minds”&gt; ai&gt; ai &lt;/a&gt;体验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/managing-software-gendware-teams-teams-of-ai-devs”&gt; ai开发人员&lt;/a&gt;需要更快的迭代环节，可辩论的管道和可伸缩的培训和可缩放的培训。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/&#xA; &lt;li dir =“ ltr”&gt;业务利益相关者要求投资回报率，成本效率和法规合规性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;想想AI为语音助手或自动驾驶汽车或任何其他AI用例提供动力。速度决定可用性，准确性建立信任，成本决定了可行性。我将这些文章写为三部分系列，以帮助发现实用策略，以加速AI开发，提高绩效并优化成本，而不会损害创新。从现实世界的经验中，我们将讨论使AI更快，更好，更便宜。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamline Your ELT Workflow in Snowflake With Dynamic Tables and Medallion Design】用动态表和奖章设计简化雪花中的ELT工作流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-dynamic-tables-elt-medallion-design</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;433&#34; data-start=&#34;182&#34;&gt;Snowflake offers Dynamic Tables, a declarative way to build automated, incremental, and dependency-aware data transformations. They modernize your data pipelines by delivering real-time insights at scale, with minimal operational overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-end=&#34;463&#34; data-start=&#34;435&#34;&gt;What Are Dynamic Tables?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;608&#34; data-start=&#34;465&#34;&gt;Dynamic Tables are auto-updating, materialized tables in Snowflake that handle your transformation logic for you. All you need to do is define:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 433” data-start =“ 182”&gt; Snowflake提供动态表，这是构建自动化，增量和依赖性吸引数据转换的声明性方法。它们通过大规模提供实时见解，使您的数据管道现代化，并以最少的操作开销。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-end =“ 463” data-start =“ 435”&gt;什么是动态表？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 608” data-start =“ 465”&gt;动态表正在自动更新，在雪花中实现的表，可以为您处理转换逻辑。您需要做的就是定义：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Compliance Automated Standard Solution (COMPASS), Part 8: Agentic AI Policy as Code for Compliance Automation With Prompt Declaration Language】合规性自动化标准解决方案（Compass），第8部分：代理AI政策作为及时声明语言合规性自动化的代码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-for-compliance-w-pdl</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Note: A list of links for all articles in this series can be found at the conclusion of this article.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the last two blog posts of this multi-part series on continuous compliance, we presented Compliance Policy Administration Centers (CPAC) that facilitate the management of various compliance artifacts connecting the Regulatory Policies expressed as Compliance-as-Code with technical policies implemented as Policy-as-Code. This bridging is the key enabler of end-to-end continuous compliance: from authoring controls and profiles to mapping to technical policies and rules, to collecting assessment results from the policy engines, and finally to aggregating them against regulatory compliance into an encompassing posture for the whole environment. A critical limitation that surfaces for the compliance teams is their shortage on technical resources and skills, making the task of bridging into technology level programatic rules, check, and evidence collection extremely challenging.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;（注意：本系列中所有文章的链接列表可以在本文的结论中找到。）&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这个关于连续遵从性的多部分系列的最后两个博客文章中，我们提出了合规性政策管理中心（CPAC），这些中心（CPAC）促进了将各种合规性工件的管理连接起来，将法规政策连接为以合规性为代码的法规政策与实施的政策政策，该政策实现为策略 -  AS CODE。这种桥接是端到端连续遵守的关键推动者：从创建控件和配置文件到映射到技术政策和规则，再到从政策引擎中收集评估结果，最后到将它们反对调节性合规性汇总到整个环境中的姿势。合规团队浮出水面的一个关键限制是他们对技术资源和技能的短缺，使其陷入技术级别的程序规则，检查和证据收集的任务极为挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>