<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Static Pipelines: Enhancing AI Agents With LlamaIndex】超越静态管道：利用 LlamaIndex 增强 AI 代理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-ai-agents-with-llamaindex</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Basic Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;(opens new window)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;data pipelines often rely on hard-coded steps, following a predefined path every time they run. There is no real-time decision-making in these systems, and they do not dynamically adjust actions based on input data. This limitation can reduce flexibility and responsiveness in complex or changing environments, highlighting a major weakness in traditional RAG systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LlamaIndex resolves this limitation by introducing &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.llamaindex.ai/en/stable/use_cases/agents/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;agents&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;(opens new window)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Agents are a step beyond our query engines in that they can not only &#34;read&#34; from a static source of data, but can dynamically ingest and modify data from various tools. Powered by an LLM, these agents are designed to perform a series of actions to accomplish a specified task by choosing the most suitable tools from a provided set. These tools can be as simple as basic functions or as complex as comprehensive LlamaIndex query engines. They process user inputs or queries, make internal decisions on how to handle these inputs, and decide whether additional steps are necessary or if a final result can be delivered. This ability to perform automated reasoning and decision-making makes agents highly adaptable and efficient for complex data processing tasks.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;基本检索增强生成 (RAG)&lt;span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;（打开新窗口）&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;数据管道通常依赖于硬编码步骤，遵循预定义的步骤每次跑步时的路径。这些系统没有实时决策，也不会根据输入数据动态调整操作。这种限制会降低复杂或不断变化的环境中的灵活性和响应能力，凸显传统 RAG 系统的主要弱点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LlamaIndex 通过引入 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.llamaindex.ai/en/stable/use_cases/agents/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;代理&lt;span&gt;&lt; 解决了此限制span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;（打开新窗口）&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。代理比我们的查询引擎更进一步，因为它们不仅可以从静态数据源“读取”，还可以动态地从各种工具中获取和修改数据。这些代理由法学硕士提供支持，旨在通过从提供的工具集中选择最合适的工具来执行一系列操作来完成指定的任务。这些工具可以简单到基本功能，也可以复杂到综合性 LlamaIndex 查询引擎。他们处理用户输入或查询，就如何处理这些输入做出内部决策，并决定是否需要额外的步骤或者是否可以交付最终结果。这种执行自动推理和决策的能力使代理对复杂的数据处理任务具有高度适应性和高效性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Black Hat 2024, Day 2: Charting the Future of Cybersecurity】Black Hat 2024，第 2 天：描绘网络安全的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/charting-the-future-of-cybersecurity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blackhat.com/us-24/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2024 Black Hat&lt;/a&gt; conference in Las Vegas brought together some of the most influential voices in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/5-innovative-cybersecurity-measures&#34;&gt;cybersecurity&lt;/a&gt;, offering critical insights for security professionals navigating an increasingly complex digital landscape. From the philosophical underpinnings of software development to practical strategies for securing critical infrastructure, the keynote speakers provided a comprehensive view of the challenges and opportunities facing the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Magic of Software Development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://moxie.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Moxie Marlinspike&lt;/a&gt;, founder of &lt;a href=&#34;https://signalfoundation.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Signal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://signalfoundation.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, opened his Day Two Keynote with a thought-provoking analogy comparing software development to magic in the Harry Potter universe. He argued that software is one of the few domains where individuals can create powerful, transformative tools with minimal resources:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blackhat.com/us-24/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2024 年黑帽会议&lt;/a&gt;拉斯维加斯汇聚了&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/5-innovative-cybersecurity-measures&#34;&gt;网络安全&lt;/a&gt;领域一些最具影响力的声音，为安全专业人士提供了重要的见解，以应对日益增长的网络安全问题。复杂的数字景观。从软件开发的哲学基础到保护关键基础设施的实用策略，主旨演讲者全面介绍了行业面临的挑战和机遇。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;软件开发的魔力&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://moxie.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Moxie Marlinspike&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https: 的创始人//signalfoundation.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;信号&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://signalfoundation.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，以一个发人深省的类比开始了第二天的主题演讲，将软件开发比作哈利·波特宇宙中的魔法。他认为，软件是个人可以用最少的资源创建强大的、变革性工具的少数领域之一：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Steps for Success With Scrum】使用 Scrum 构建成功步骤</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-steps-for-success-with-scrum</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Discussions about &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/scrum&#34;&gt;Scrum&lt;/a&gt; keep deviating into things that aren&#39;t part of Scrum: user stories, story points, burndown charts, velocity, status meetings, tasks, sprint zero, etc. That doesn&#39;t mean those following Scrum can&#39;t use them; however, one should not perpetrate the myth that they&#39;re part of Scrum.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The goal of Scrum was never to do Scrum, and it&#39;s certainly not a tool to &#34;implement Agile.&#34; It&#39;s an enabler — &amp;nbsp;and when the environment is right and the right things are in focus it will work to deliver results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;关于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/scrum&#34;&gt;Scrum&lt;/a&gt; 的讨论不断偏离 Scrum 之外的内容：用户故事、故事点、燃尽图、速度、状态会议、任务、冲刺零等。这并不意味着那些遵循 Scrum 的人不能使用它们；它们只是一个例子。然而，人们不应该错误地认为它们是 Scrum 的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scrum 的目标从来都不是做 Scrum，它当然也不是“实施敏捷”的工具。它是一个推动者——当环境合适并且关注正确的事情时，它将努力交付成果。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Snowflake and dbt Integration To Enable Advanced Analytics】Snowflake 和 dbt 集成支持高级分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-and-db-enable-advanced-analytics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Data strategies have to be designed today for the modern business person to help in being flexible, growing, and running efficiently. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-snowflake-for-junior-software-engi&#34;&gt;Snowflake&lt;/a&gt;, powered by the Data Cloud, enables you to create data-intensive applications without thinking about the infrastructure that is going to manage it so the focus may rest on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-data-analytics-understanding-data-analytic&#34;&gt;data and analytics&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;dbt is a workflow tool to help teams quickly and collaboratively write analytics code using some of the best practices from software engineering, such as modularity, portability, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-ci-cd&#34;&gt;continuous integration, continuous deployment&lt;/a&gt;, and documentation. Anyone who knows &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-distributed-sql&#34;&gt;SQL&lt;/a&gt; can use dbt to build high-quality data pipelines without needing to manage infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当今必须为现代商务人员设计数据策略，以帮助其灵活、成长和高效运行。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-snowflake-for-junior-software-engi&#34;&gt;Snowflake&lt;/a&gt; 由数据云提供支持，使您能够创建数据密集型应用程序不考虑将要管理它的基础设施，因此重点可能集中在数据和分析上&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;dbt 是一个工作流程工具，可帮助团队使用软件工程的一些最佳实践（例如模块化、可移植性、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what- is-ci-cd&#34;&gt;持续集成、持续部署&lt;/a&gt;和文档。任何了解 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-distributed-sql&#34;&gt;SQL&lt;/a&gt; 的人都可以使用 dbt 构建高质量的数据管道，而无需管理基础设施。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Semantic Web Search App Using Resource Description Framework and Flask for Cyber Resilience】使用资源描述框架和 Flask 构建语义 Web 搜索应用程序以实现网络弹性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-a-semantic-web-search-app-with-rdf-and-flask</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In cyber resilience, handling and querying data effectively is crucial for detecting threats, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/surviving-the-incident&#34;&gt;responding to incidents&lt;/a&gt;, and maintaining strong security. Traditional data management methods often fall short in providing deep insights or handling complex data relationships. By integrating &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introducing-semantic-web-programming-part-i&#34;&gt;semantic web&lt;/a&gt; technologies and RDF (Resource Description Framework), we can significantly enhance our data management capabilities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This tutorial demonstrates how to build a web application using Flask, a popular &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/flask-vs-django-which-python-framework-to-choose&#34;&gt;Python framework&lt;/a&gt;, that leverages these technologies for advanced semantic search and RDF data management.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在网络弹性方面，有效处理和查询数据对于检测威胁、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/surviving-the-incident&#34;&gt;响应事件&lt;/a&gt;以及维护数据至关重要安全性强。传统的数据管理方法通常无法提供深入的见解或处理复杂的数据关系。通过集成&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introducing-semantic-web-programming-part-i&#34;&gt;语义网&lt;/a&gt;技术和RDF（资源描述框架），我们可以显着增强我们的数据管理能力。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本教程演示如何使用 Flask（一种流行的 Python）构建 Web 应用程序框架&lt;/a&gt;，利用这些技术进行高级语义搜索和 RDF 数据管理。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering PUE for Unmatched Data Center Performance】掌握 PUE 以获得无与伦比的数据中心性能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-pue-for-unmatched-data-center-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Data centers use a lot of electricity. Consequently, as they grow, it becomes all the more important to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-emerging-technologies-make-data-centers-more&#34;&gt;understand their energy use&lt;/a&gt; and take steps to reduce it. Learning to measure data center power usage effectiveness (PUE) is a crucial part of that goal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Is Data Center Power Usage Effectiveness?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As its name implies, PUE measures how efficiently a data center uses the energy it consumes. It represents this figure as a ratio between the facility’s total electrical usage and how much of it goes toward IT equipment. The more even the ratio, the better.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;数据中心消耗大量电力。因此，随着它们的成长，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-emerging-technologies-make-data-centers-more&#34;&gt;了解它们的能源使用情况变得更加重要&lt;/a &gt; 并采取措施减少它。学习测量数据中心电力使用效率 (PUE) 是实现这一目标的关键部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;什么是数据中心电力使用效率？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;顾名思义，PUE 衡量数据中心使用其消耗的能源的效率。它将这个数字表示为设施总用电量与 IT 设备用电量之间的比率。比例越均匀越好。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OpenShift Data Foundation on IBM Cloud Using Terraform, Part 1: Deployment】使用 Terraform 在 IBM Cloud 上使用 OpenShift Data Foundation，第 1 部分：部署</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/odf-on-ibm-cloud-using-terraform-pt-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;OpenShift Data Foundation (ODF) is a Software Defined Storage solution that manages and stores large amounts of data across multiple environments in a scalable, efficient, and secure manner. It provides a unified view of data from different sources, including databases, file systems, and cloud storage. With ODF, organizations can manage structured and unstructured data from multiple sources, and gain insights from it through analytics and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; enabling them to build a modern data infrastructure that is flexible, agile, and cost-effective.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Under the hood, ODF utilizes &lt;a href=&#34;https://ceph.io/en/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ceph&lt;/a&gt; as the underlying &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-distributed-systems-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;distributed storage system&lt;/a&gt;. Ceph stores the data and manages data replication and distribution across multiple nodes in the storage cluster, ensuring high availability and data redundancy. &lt;a href=&#34;https://rook.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rook&lt;/a&gt;, integrated with ODF as a storage orchestrator, automates the deployment and management of Ceph within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; cluster. Rook handles tasks like data replication, scaling, and fault tolerance, relieving administrators from dealing with these complexities.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;OpenShift Data Foundation (ODF) 是一种软件定义存储解决方案，能够以可扩展、高效且安全的方式跨多个环境管理和存储大量数据。它提供了来自不同来源（包括数据库、文件系统和云存储）的数据的统一视图。借助 ODF，组织可以管理来自多个来源的结构化和非结构化数据，并通过分析和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习&lt;/a&gt;从中获取见解使他们能够构建灵活、敏捷且经济高效的现代数据基础设施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在底层，ODF 使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ceph.io/en/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ceph&lt;/a&gt; 作为底层 &lt;a href=&#34; https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-distributed-systems-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;分布式存储系统&lt;/a&gt;。 Ceph存储数据并管理存储集群中多个节点之间的数据复制和分发，确保高可用性和数据冗余。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://rook.io/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Rook&lt;/a&gt; 作为存储编排器与 ODF 集成，可在 &lt; href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; 集群。 Rook 可以处理数据复制、扩展和容错等任务，使管理员无需处理这些复杂的问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【In-Depth Understanding of Vector Search for RAG and Generative AI Applications】深入了解 RAG 和生成 AI 应用的矢量搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vector-search-for-rag-and-genai-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;0 0 []&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@talibilat?source=post_page-----7770e52e52c9--------------------------------&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer ugc&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;You might have used large language models like GPT-3.5, GPT-4o, or any of the other models, Mistral or Perplexity, and these large language models are awe-inspiring with what they can do and how much of a grasp they have of language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, today I was chatting with an LLM, and I wanted to know about my company’s policy if I work from India instead of the UK. You can see I got a really generic answer, and then it asked me to consult my company directly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;0 0 []&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@talibilat?source=post_page-----7770e52e52c9---------- ----------------------&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer ugc&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;您可能使用过大型语言模型，例如 GPT-3.5、GPT-4o ，或任何其他模型，Mistral 或 Perplexity，这些大型语言模型的能力和对语言的掌握程度令人惊叹。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所以，今天我正在与一位法学硕士聊天，我想了解如果我在印度而不是英国工作，我的公司的政策。你可以看到我得到了一个非常通用的答案，然后它要求我直接咨询我的公司。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Data Encryption Can Simplify Infrastructure Architecture】数据加密如何简化基础设施架构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-data-encryption-can-simplify-infrastructure-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Product and infrastructure engineering teams are not always aligned with the interests of security engineering teams. While product and infrastructure focus on driving business value and delivering practical solutions, security focuses on detection, prevention, and remediation, which can seem less immediately valuable. Like an insurance policy, it&#39;s not entirely obvious why it&#39;s worth the money or effort when there hasn&#39;t been an incident yet.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead of the traditional cycle of identifying vulnerabilities, applying remediation, and following up through case management, I&#39;ve found it much more effective to advocate for security solutions that also deliver business value. For example, using OAuth and IAM-based access instead of static keys and encryption instead of more granular access control can significantly simplify infrastructure, reduce complexity, and lessen the operational burden, making them very appealing to both product and platform engineering teams.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;产品和基础设施工程团队并不总是与安全工程团队的利益保持一致。产品和基础设施专注于推动业务价值和提供实用的解决方案，而安全则专注于检测、预防和补救，而这些似乎没有那么直接的价值。就像保险单一样，在尚未发生事故的情况下，我们并不完全清楚为什么它值得花钱或付出努力。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我发现倡导同时提供业务价值的安全解决方案比传统的识别漏洞、应用修复和跟进案例管理的周期要有效得多。例如，使用 OAuth 和基于 IAM 的访问而不是静态密钥和加密而不是更精细的访问控制可以显着简化基础设施、降低复杂性并减轻运营负担，从而对产品和平台工程团队都非常有吸引力。&lt;/ p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Construct Azure Shared Access Signature URL To Download File From Azure Blob Storage】构造 Azure 共享访问签名 URL 以从 Azure Blob 存储下载文件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/azure-shared-access-signature-url-to-download-file</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In any web portal, to access a file stored in an Azure Blob Storage account container, we need to connect to the Azure Blob Storage Account and construct the download link for the specified file using its name and Azure storage account details. Constructed Azure Blob URLs can also be used to upload a file and delete a file from the web portal using Java code.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A shared access signature (SAS) enables you to grant limited access to containers and blobs in your storage account. When you create a SAS, you specify its constraints, including which Azure Storage resources a client is allowed to access, what permissions they have on those resources, and how long the SAS is valid.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在任何 Web 门户中，要访问存储在 Azure Blob 存储帐户容器中的文件，我们需要连接到 Azure Blob 存储帐户并使用指定文件的名称和 Azure 存储帐户详细信息构建指定文件的下载链接。构建的 Azure Blob URL 还可用于使用 Java 代码从 Web 门户上传文件和删除文件。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;共享访问签名 (SAS) 使您能够授予对存储帐户中的容器和 blob 的有限访问权限。创建 SAS 时，您可以指定其约束，包括允许客户端访问哪些 Azure 存储资源、它们对这些资源拥有哪些权限以及 SAS 的有效期。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>