<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Faster Startup With Spring Boot 3.2 and CRaC, Part 2】使用 Spring Boot 3.2 和 CRaC 加快启动速度，第 2 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/faster-startup-with-spring-boot-32-and-crac-part-2</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This is the second part of the blog series “Faster Startup With Spring Boot 3.2 and CRaC,&#34; where we will learn how to warm up a Spring Boot application before the checkpoint is taken and how to provide configuration at runtime when the application is restarted from the checkpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/faster-startup-with-spring-boot-32-and-crac-part-1&#34;&gt;the previous blog post&lt;/a&gt;, we learned how to use CRaC to start Spring Boot applications ten times faster using &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.spring.io/spring-framework/reference/integration/checkpoint-restore.html#_automatic_checkpointrestore_at_startup&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;automatic checkpoints&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; provided by Spring Boot 3.2. It, however, came with two significant drawbacks:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这是博客系列“使用 Spring Boot 3.2 和 CRaC 实现更快的启动”的第二部分，我们将在其中学习如何在采取检查点之前预热 Spring Boot 应用程序，以及如何在应用程序运行时提供配置从检查点重新启动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/faster-startup-with-spring-boot-32-and-crac-part-1&#34;&gt;上一篇博文&lt;/a&gt;中，我们学习了如何使用 CRaC 使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.spring.io/spring-framework/reference/integration/checkpoint-restore.html#_automatic_checkpointrestore_at_startup&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer 以十倍的速度启动 Spring Boot 应用程序&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Spring Boot 3.2 提供的&lt;strong&gt;自动检查点&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。然而，它有两个明显的缺点：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Identify Bottlenecks and Increase Copy Activity Throughput in Azure Data Factory】如何识别 Azure 数据工厂中的瓶颈并提高复制活动吞吐量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/identify-bottlenecks-and-increase-copy-activity-adf</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-optimized-etl-pipelines-in-the-cloud&#34;&gt;Azure Data Factory&lt;/a&gt; (ADF) is a cloud-native ETL tool to process data seamlessly across different sources and sinks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Copy activity is mostly used to copy data from one source to another source. While copying data between two different sources, we need to make sure that the activity is completed in a timely manner to meet business needs and process data within the service level agreement.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-optimized-etl-pipelines-in-the-cloud&#34;&gt;Azure 数据工厂&lt;/a&gt; (ADF) 是一种云原生 ETL 工具跨不同源和接收器无缝处理数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;复制活动主要用于将数据从一个源复制到另一个源。在两个不同来源之间复制数据时，我们需要确保活动及时完成，以满足业务需求并在服务级别协议内处理数据。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 20:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring AI-Powered Web Development: OpenAI, Node.js, and Dynamic UI Creation】探索 AI 支持的 Web 开发：OpenAI、Node.js 和动态 UI 创建</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-ai-powered-web-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the rapidly advancing world of web development, artificial intelligence (AI) is paving the way for new levels of creativity and efficiency. This article takes a deep dive into the exciting synergy between OpenAI&#39;s robust API, the flexibility of Node.js, and the possibilities for creating dynamic user interfaces. By examining how these technologies work together, we&#39;ll uncover how they can transform our approach to both web development and UI development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Dynamic UI Creation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dynamic UI Creation involves generating user interfaces that can adapt dynamically based on factors like user input, data, or context. In AI-driven UI generation, this concept is elevated by using artificial intelligence to automatically create or modify UI elements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在快速发展的网络开发领域，人工智能 (AI) 正在为新的创造力和效率水平铺平道路。本文深入探讨了 OpenAI 强大的 API、Node.js 的灵活性以及创建动态用户界面的可能性之间令人兴奋的协同作用。通过研究这些技术如何协同工作，我们将揭示它们如何改变我们的 Web 开发和 UI 开发方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;动态用户界面创建&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;动态 UI 创建涉及生成可以根据用户输入、数据或上下文等因素动态调整的用户界面。在人工智能驱动的 UI 生成中，通过使用人工智能自动创建或修改 UI 元素来提升这一概念。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Smart Routing Using AI for Efficient Logistics and Green Solutions】利用人工智能的智能路线实现高效物流和绿色解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/smart-routing-using-ai-for-efficient-logistics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The growing demand for efficient logistics and the pressing need for environmental sustainability requires innovative solutions to optimize transportation routes and minimize greenhouse gas emissions. This study explores the role of artificial intelligence (AI) in enhancing logistics efficiency and reducing environmental impact by applying various regression models to predict travel times and emissions using real-world industrial logistics datasets. Key factors considered include vehicle types, traffic conditions, weather, distance, fuel consumption, and package attributes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The study employs a range of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; models, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-roadmap-of-linear-regression&#34;&gt;Linear Regression&lt;/a&gt;, Ridge and Lasso Regression, Support Vector Machines (SVM), &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-create-a-perfect-decision-tree&#34;&gt;Decision Trees&lt;/a&gt;, Random Forests, Gradient Boosting, XGBoost, Gaussian Processes, and Multi-layer Perceptron (MLP) Regressors. It also integrates advanced deep learning techniques like LSTM, RNN, CNN, and time series forecasting using ARIMA. The models are evaluated using metrics such as Mean Squared Error (MSE), Mean Absolute Error (MAE), R-squared (R²), and Mean Absolute Percentage Error (MAPE), with hyperparameter tuning to optimize performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;对高效物流日益增长的需求以及对环境可持续性的迫切需求需要创新的解决方案来优化运输路线并最大限度地减少温室气体排放。本研究通过应用各种回归模型，利用现实世界的工业物流数据集来预测行程时间和排放，探讨了人工智能 (AI) 在提高物流效率和减少环境影响方面的作用。考虑的关键因素包括车辆类型、交通状况、天气、距离、油耗和包装属性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该研究采用了一系列&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习&lt;/a&gt;模型，包括&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone .com/articles/the-roadmap-of-linear-regression&#34;&gt;线性回归&lt;/a&gt;、岭回归和套索回归、支持向量机 (SVM)、&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/如何创建完美决策树&#34;&gt;决策树&lt;/a&gt;、随机森林、梯度提升、XGBoost、高斯过程和多层感知器 (MLP) 回归器。它还集成了先进的深度学习技术，如 LSTM、RNN、CNN 和使用 ARIMA 进行时间序列预测。使用均方误差 (MSE)、平均绝对误差 (MAE)、R 平方 (R²) 和平均绝对百分比误差 (MAPE) 等指标来评估模型，并通过超参数调整来优化性能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 17:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Monitoring Kubernetes Service Topology Changes in Real-Time】实时监控Kubernetes服务拓扑变化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/monitoring-kubernetes-service-changes-in-real-time</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Horizontally scalable data stores like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-elasticsearch-1&#34;&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/apache-cassandra&#34;&gt;Cassandra&lt;/a&gt;, and CockroachDB distribute their data across multiple nodes using techniques like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/consistent-hashing-vs-rendezvous-hashing-a-compara&#34;&gt;consistent hashing&lt;/a&gt;. As nodes are added or removed, the data is reshuffled to ensure that the load is spread evenly across the new set of nodes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When deployed on bare-metal clusters or cloud VMs, database administrators are responsible for adding and removing nodes in a clustered system, planning the changes at times of low load to minimize disruption to production workloads.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;水平可扩展的数据存储，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-elasticsearch-1&#34;&gt;Elasticsearch&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https: //dzone.com/refcardz/apache-cassandra&#34;&gt;Cassandra&lt;/a&gt; 和 CockroachDB 使用诸如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/consistency-hashing-vs&#34; 之类的技术将数据分布在多个节点上-rendezvous-hashing-a-compara&#34;&gt;一致的哈希&lt;/a&gt;。添加或删除节点时，数据会重新排列，以确保负载均匀分布在新的节点集上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;当部署在裸机集群或云虚拟机上时，数据库管理员负责在集群系统中添加和删除节点，规划低负载时的更改，以最大程度地减少对生产工作负载的干扰。&lt;/ p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 12:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What the CrowdStrike Crash Exposed About the Future of Software Testing】CrowdStrike 崩溃揭示了软件测试的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/what-the-crowdstrike-crash-exposed-about-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;When users worldwide woke up to their Windows devices inoperable, they feared they had fallen victim to the largest cyber-attack ever seen. But it wasn&#39;t an attack — their devices were down from a faulty CrowdStrike update. This&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://fortune.com/2024/08/03/crowdstrike-outage-fortune-500-companies-5-4-billion-damages-uninsured-losses/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle=&#34;Hyperlink&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle=&#34;Hyperlink&#34;&gt;$5 billion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;mistake could have been avoided with proper testing and quality assurance. With companies striving to update and publish software rapidly, the learnings from this global panic stemming from one endpoint security software update are telling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:240}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-you-can-avoid-a-crowdstrike-fiasco&#34;&gt;ramifications of the CrowdStrike outage&lt;/a&gt; showcase the difficulties in software development today. As our digital world becomes increasingly complex and software evolves rapidly, ensuring high-quality and reliable systems becomes progressively more difficult. Even practiced industry titans can fail to meet quality standards. Therefore, it is crucial to have efficient testing strategies in place.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:240}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;当世界各地的用户醒来发现他们的 Windows 设备无法操作时，他们担心自己已​​成为有史以来最大规模网络攻击的受害者。但这并不是一次攻击——他们的设备因 CrowdStrike 更新错误而瘫痪。这&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://fortune.com/2024/08/03/crowdstrike-outage-fortune-500-companies-5-4-billion-damages-uninsured-losses/&#34; rel=&#34; noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle=&#34;Hyperlink&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle= “Hyperlink&#34;&gt;50 亿美元&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt; 通过适当的测试和质量保证，本可以避免这个错误。随着公司努力快速更新和发布软件，从一次端点安全软件更新引发的全球恐慌中得到的教训很能说明问题。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;335559738&#34;:240}&#34;&gt; &lt;/跨度&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-you-can-avoid-a-crowdstrike-fiasco&#34; &gt;CrowdStrike 中断的后果&lt;/a&gt;展示了当今软件开发的困难。随着我们的数字世界变得越来越复杂，软件迅速发展，确保高质量和可靠的系统变得越来越困难。即使是经验丰富的行业巨头也可能无法达到质量标准。因此，制定有效的测试策略至关重要。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;335559738&#34;:240}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 20:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Boosting Efficiency: Implementing Natural Language Processing With AWS RDS Using CloudFormation】提高效率：使用 CloudFormation 通过 AWS RDS 实施自然语言处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-nlp-with-aws-rds-using-cloudformation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-translation-the-power-of-context-in-n-1&#34;&gt;Natural Language Processing (NLP)&lt;/a&gt; is revolutionizing how organizations manage data, enabling the automation of text-intensive tasks such as analyzing customer feedback, monitoring sentiment, and recognizing entities. NLP can yield significant insights from extensive datasets when integrated with AWS Relational Database Service (RDS) for efficient data storage and retrieval. This article outlines the comprehensive configuration of an NLP-enabled AWS RDS environment utilizing AWS CloudFormation templates (CFT), accompanied by an in-depth cost and performance analysis to illustrate the benefits of NLP.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Advantages of Implementing NLP&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NLP empowers organizations to do the following:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-translation-the-power-of-context-in-n-1&#34;&gt;自然语言处理 (NLP)&lt;/a&gt; 正在彻底改变组织管理数据，实现文本密集型任务的自动化，例如分析客户反馈、监控情绪和识别实体。当与 AWS 关系数据库服务 (RDS) 集成时，NLP 可以从广泛的数据集中产生重要的见解，以实现高效的数据存储和检索。本文概述了利用 AWS CloudFormation 模板 (CFT) 的支持 NLP 的 AWS RDS 环境的全面配置，并进行了深入的成本和性能分析，以说明 NLP 的优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;实施 NLP 的优点&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NLP 使组织能够执行以下操作：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【4 Essential Strategies for Enhancing Your Application Security Posture】增强应用程序安全状况的 4 个基本策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/4-strategies-for-enhancing-appsec-posture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The rapidly evolving cybersecurity landscape presents an array of challenges for businesses of all sizes across all industries. The constant emergence of new cyber threats, including those now powered by AI, is overwhelming current security models. A &lt;a href=&#34;https://ponemonsullivanreport.com/2024/04/the-2024-study-on-the-state-of-ai-in-cybersecurity/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2023 study by the Ponemon Institute&lt;/a&gt; found that organizations receive an average of 22,111 security alerts per week. This deluge of alerts, many of which are false positives, is preventing teams from effectively prioritizing and dealing with potential threats.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A holistic approach to addressing this problem is what Gartner calls Application Security Posture Management (ASPM). The strategies of ASPM address the limitations of traditional AppSec approaches using automation, integration, and the strategic use of open-source tools. Adopting the recommended strategies of ASPM can enable companies to fortify software applications throughout their lifecycle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;快速发展的网络安全格局给各行业各种规模的企业带来了一系列挑战。新的网络威胁的不断出现，包括现在由人工智能驱动的威胁，正在压倒当前的安全模型。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://ponemonsullivanreport.com/2024/04/the-2024-study-on-the-state-of-ai-in-cybersecurity/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; &gt;Ponemon Institute 的 2023 年研究&lt;/a&gt;发现，组织平均每周收到 22,111 条安全警报。大量的警报（其中许多是误报）正在阻止团队有效地确定优先级并处理潜在威胁。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;解决此问题的整体方法被 Gartner 称为应用程序安全状态管理 (ASPM)。 ASPM 的策略使用自动化、集成和开源工具的战略使用来解决传统 AppSec 方法的局限性。采用 ASPM 推荐的策略可以使公司在软件应用程序的整个生命周期中得到强化。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Governance Essentials: Glossaries, Catalogs, and Lineage (Part 5)】数据治理要点：术语表、目录和沿袭（第 5 部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-governance-data-integration-part-5</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Is Data Governance, and How Do Glossaries, Catalogs, and Lineage Strengthen It?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-data-governance-in-data-strategy-part&#34;&gt;Data governance&lt;/a&gt; is a framework that is developed through the collaboration of individuals with various roles and responsibilities. This framework aims to establish processes, policies, procedures, standards, and metrics that help organizations achieve their goals. These goals include providing reliable data for business operations, setting accountability and authoritativeness, developing accurate analytics to assess performance, complying with regulatory requirements, safeguarding data, ensuring data privacy, and supporting the data management lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In the field of data governance, business glossaries, data catalogs, and data lineage are essential for effectively managing data across an organization. With an increase in data, finding the right information has become more challenging. Simultaneously, there are also more rules and regulations than ever before. Here&#39;s a brief overview of each:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;什么是数据治理，术语表、目录和谱系如何加强数据治理？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-role-of-data-governance-in-data-strategy-part &#34;&gt;数据治理&lt;/a&gt;是一个通过具有不同角色和职责的个人协作开发的框架。该框架旨在建立帮助组织实现其目标的流程、政策、程序、标准和指标。这些目标包括为业务运营提供可靠的数据、设定责任和权威、开发准确的分析来评估绩效、遵守监管要求、保护数据、确保数据隐私以及支持数据管理生命周期。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在数据治理领域，业务词汇表、数据目录和数据沿袭对于有效管理整个组织的数据至关重要。随着数据的增加，找到正确的信息变得更加具有挑战性。同时，规章制度也比以往更多。以下是每项的简要概述：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 15:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Platform Engineering Essentials】平台工程要点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/refcardz/platform-engineering-essentials</link>
      <description>【Platform engineering aims to enhance the developer experience through the establishment of secure environments, automated and self-service tools, and streamlined workflows. However, as technology and cyber threats continue to evolve, the integration of automation, security, and AI will be vital to the success of these platforms. &#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;br&gt;In this Refcard, you will learn more about the value of platform engineering, including best practices, tools, core capabilities, how to align business goals, and more. &lt;/br&gt;】平台工程旨在通过建立安全环境、自动化和自助服务工具以及简化的工作流程来增强开发人员体验。然而，随着技术和网络威胁的不断发展，自动化、安全和人工智能的集成对于这些平台的成功至关重要。 &#xA;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;br&gt;在此参考卡中，您将详细了解平台工程的价值，包括最佳实践、工具、核心功能、如何协调业务目标等。 &lt;/br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 15:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>