<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Detecting Supply Chain Attacks in NPM, PyPI, and Docker: Real-World Techniques That Work】检测 NPM、PyPI 和 Docker 中的供应链攻击：有效的实际技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/detecting-supply-chain-attacks-npm-pypi-docker</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The digital ecosystem breathes through trust. Every npm install, every pip install, every docker pull represents a leap of faith — a developer placing confidence in code written by strangers, maintained by volunteers, distributed through systems they&#39;ve never seen. This trust, however, has become the Achilles&#39; heel of modern software development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Supply chain attacks don&#39;t knock on your front door. They slip through the dependencies you invited in yourself.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;数字生态系统以信任为基础。每一次 npm 安装、每一次 pip 安装、每一次 docker pull 都代表着一次信仰的飞跃——开发人员对由陌生人编写、由志愿者维护、通过他们从未见过的系统分发的代码充满信心。然而，这种信任已成为现代软件开发的致命弱点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;供应链攻击不会敲你的前门。他们会忽略您自己邀请的依赖关系。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Resilient Observability Stack in 2025: Practical Steps to Reduce Tool Sprawl With OpenTelemetry, Unified Platforms, and AI-Ready Monitoring】2025 年构建弹性可观测性堆栈：通过 OpenTelemetry、统一平台和 AI 就绪监控减少工具蔓延的实际步骤</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-a-resilient-observability-stack</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor’s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone’s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-observability-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Intelligent Observability: Building a Foundation for Reliability at Scale&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Platform consolidation is an important topic in 2025 as tool sprawl and platform fragmentation are costing engineering teams time, money, and focus. Some &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.elastic.co/blog/guide-observability-consolidation&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;surveys of observability practitioners&lt;/a&gt; show that 80% of teams are working on reducing vendor count and consolidating their observability and monitoring tools.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2025 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-observability-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;智能可观测性：为大规模可靠性奠定基础&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;平台整合是 2025 年的一个重要主题，因为工具蔓延和平台碎片化正在耗费工程团队的时间、金钱和精力。一些&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.elastic.co/blog/guide-observability-consolidation&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;对可观察性从业者的调查&lt;/a&gt;表明，80% 的团队正在致力于减少供应商数量并整合其可观察性和监控工具。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【5 Critical Databricks Performance Hacks That Most Engineers Miss (100x Faster Queries)】大多数工程师忽视的 5 个关键 Databricks 性能技巧（查询速度提高 100 倍）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/databricks-performance-hacks-faster-queries</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Databricks performance tuning is not guesswork; it needs a deep understanding of internals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;In this guide, I will explore six practical optimization techniques every data engineer should apply to achieve faster, cost-efficient production.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Databricks 性能调整不是猜测；而是一种猜测。它需要对内部结构有深入的了解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 在本指南中，我将探讨每个数据工程师都应该应用的六种实用优化技术，以实现更快、更具成本效益的生产。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What Is Agent Observability? Key Lessons Learned】什么是代理可观察性？主要经验教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-agent-observability-key-lessons-learned</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Agents are proliferating like wildfire, yet there is a ton of confusion surrounding foundational concepts such as agent observability. Is it the same as AI observability? What problem does it solve, and how does it work?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fear not, we&#39;ll dive into these questions and more. Along the way, we will cite specific user examples as well as our own experience in pushing a customer-facing AI agent into production.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;代理像野火一样激增，但围绕代理可观察性等基本概念存在大量混乱。和AI可观察性一样吗？它解决了什么问题，它是如何工作的？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不用担心，我们将深入探讨这些问题以及更多问题。在此过程中，我们将引用具体的用户示例以及我们自己将面向客户的人工智能代理投入生产的经验。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Bigfile Tablespace Defaults in Oracle Database 23ai: Impact and Benefits】了解 Oracle Database 23ai 中的大文件表空间默认值：影响和好处</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/oracle-bigfile-tablespace-changes-and-benefits</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Oracle Database 23ai introduces a significant but subtle shift in its default storage architecture, the adoption of &lt;strong&gt;bigfile tablespaces as the default&lt;/strong&gt; for most tablespaces, including core ones like SYSTEM and SYSAUX. This change reflects Oracle’s continued evolution towards simplifying storage management and scaling capabilities. As database professionals with years of experience managing complex environments, understanding this new default and its impact on performance and administration is critical.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Background: What Are Bigfile Tablespaces?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bigfile tablespaces were originally introduced in Oracle 10g as a means to address scalability challenges in very large databases. Unlike traditional &lt;strong&gt;small-file tablespaces&lt;/strong&gt;, which consist of multiple datafiles each limited in size (typically up to 32 GB or 128 GB, depending on block size and OS), a bigfile tablespace consists of a &lt;strong&gt;single large datafile&lt;/strong&gt; that can grow up to 128 terabytes (TB) or more, depending on the platform and block size.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Oracle Database 23ai 在其默认存储架构中引入了重大但微妙的转变，大多数表空间（包括 SYSTEM 和 SYSAUX 等核心表空间）采用&lt;strong&gt;大文件表空间作为默认&lt;/strong&gt;。这一变化反映了 Oracle 在简化存储管理和扩展功能方面的持续发展。作为拥有多年管理复杂环境经验的数据库专业人员，了解这种新的默认设置及其对性能和管理的影响至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;背景：什么是大文件表空间？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大文件表空间最初是在 Oracle 10g 中引入的，作为解决超大型数据库中可扩展性挑战的一种方法。传统的&lt;strong&gt;小文件表空间&lt;/strong&gt;由多个大小有限的数据文件组成（通常最大为 32 GB 或 128 GB，具体取决于块大小和操作系统），而大文件表空间则由&lt;strong&gt;单个大型数据文件&lt;/strong&gt;组成，该数据文件可以增长到 128 TB 或更大，具体取决于平台和块大小。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Navigating the Cyber Frontier: AI and ML&#39;s Role in Shaping Tomorrow&#39;s Threat Defense】畅游网络前沿：人工智能和机器学习在塑造未来威胁防御中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-ml-cybersecurity-future-threat-defense</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores the transformative role of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) in cybersecurity. It delves into innovative strategies such as adaptive cyber deception and predictive behavioral analysis, which are reshaping defense mechanisms against cyber threats. The integration of AI in zero-trust architectures, quantum cryptography, and automation within cybersecurity frameworks highlights a shift towards more dynamic and proactive security measures. Furthermore, the challenges of the &#34;black box&#34; problem in AI decision-making and the potential for AI to automate routine cybersecurity tasks are discussed. The narrative underscores the importance of complementing technology with human insight for effective digital defenses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction: A Personal Encounter With Cyber Evolution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let me rewind a few years back — a time when I was knee-deep in implementing a creditworthiness model at my previous role at Sar Tech LLC/Capital One. It was around the same time I encountered the formidable intersection of artificial intelligence (AI) and cybersecurity. While tuning machine learning (ML) algorithms to reduce loan approval risks, I witnessed firsthand how AI could pivot an organization&#39;s security posture in ways I hadn’t quite imagined before. This realization didn&#39;t stem from an academic paper or industry panel — it came from the challenge of protecting sensitive data while simultaneously fine-tuning predictive models. It was an &#34;aha&#34; moment, one which highlighted the potential of AI and ML in a broader, more dynamic context of cybersecurity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了人工智能 (AI) 和机器学习 (ML) 在网络安全中的变革性作用。它深入研究了自适应网络欺骗和预测行为分析等创新策略，这些策略正在重塑针对网络威胁的防御机制。人工智能在零信任架构、量子密码学和网络安全框架内自动化的集成，凸显了向更加动态和主动的安全措施的转变。此外，还讨论了人工智能决策中“黑匣子”问题的挑战以及人工智能自动化日常网络安全任务的潜力。该叙述强调了将技术与人类洞察力相结合以实现有效数字防御的重要性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;简介：网络进化的亲身经历&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我回顾几年前，当时我在 Sar Tech LLC/Capital One 的上一份工作中全力实施信用模型。大约在同一时间，我遇到了人工智能 (AI) 和网络安全的巨大交叉点。在调整机器学习 (ML) 算法以降低贷款审批风险时，我亲眼目睹了人工智能如何以我以前从未想象过的方式改变组织的安全态势。这种认识并非源于学术论文或行业小组，而是来自保护敏感数据同时微调预测模型的挑战。这是一个“顿悟”时刻，凸显了人工智能和机器学习在更广泛、更动态的网络安全背景下的潜力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【8 Business Continuity Lessons Learned from the CrowdStrike Outage】从 CrowdStrike 中断中汲取的 8 个业务连续性经验教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/business-continuity-lessons-from-crowdstrike-outage</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The July 2024 CrowdStrike outage sent shockwaves across global enterprises, paralyzing operations and forcing services offline. A faulty update to a widely used endpoint detection and response (EDR) solution caused the event to cascade into a full-blown operational crisis. The outage was so disruptive that it has since become a defining case study on preventing the impact of an EDR outage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Many organizations saw it as a wake-up call, making it a critical reminder that business continuity planning (BCP) must evolve alongside the growing adoption of third-party cybersecurity services. Companies now ensure uptime with the following lessons learned from Crowdstrike.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;2024 年 7 月的 CrowdStrike 中断给全球企业带来了冲击，导致运营瘫痪并迫使服务离线。广泛使用的端点检测和响应 (EDR) 解决方案的错误更新导致该事件升级为全面的运营危机。这次中断的破坏性如此之大，以至于它已成为防止 EDR 中断影响的典型案例研究。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;许多组织将其视为一记警钟，提醒人们业务连续性计划 (BCP) 必须随着第三方网络安全服务的日益普及而发展。公司现在通过从 Crowdstrike 吸取的以下经验教训来确保正常运行时间。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Delta Lake 4.0 and Delta Kernel: What&#39;s New in the Future of Data Lakehouses】Delta Lake 4.0 和 Delta Kernel：Data Lakehouse 未来的新增功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/delta-lake-delta-kernel-future-of-data-lakehouses</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In data storage, the idea of a data lakehouse has transformed data storage and analysis in organizations. Data lakehouses combine the low-cost and scalability storage ability of data lakes and data warehouse’s reliability and performance. In this space, some players have emerged, such as Delta Lake, as strong open-source frameworks for implementing robust ACID-compliant data Lakes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Now, with the introduction of Delta Lake 4.0 and the development of Delta Kernel, the future of the lakehouse architecture is in a revolutionary transition. Brimming with features driving performance, scaling, and interoperability, these updates are to keep up with the increasing dynamics of data workloads in 2025 and beyond.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;在数据存储中，数据湖屋的理念已经改变了组织中的数据存储和分析。数据湖房结合了数据湖的低成本和可扩展性存储能力以及数据仓库的可靠性和性能。在这个领域，一些参与者已经出现，例如 Delta Lake，作为强大的开源框架，用于实现强大的符合 ACID 的数据湖。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;现在，随着 Delta Lake 4.0 的推出和 Delta Kernel 的开发，Lakehouse 架构的未来正在发生革命性的转变。这些更新充满了推动性能、扩展和互操作性的功能，旨在跟上 2025 年及以后数据工作负载不断增长的动态。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Human-AI Readiness】人类-人工智能准备就绪</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/human-ai-readiness</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The expectations are cosmic. The investments are colossal. Amazon, Google, Meta, and Microsoft collectively spent over $251 billion on infrastructure investment to support AI in 2024, up 62% from 2023&#39;s $155 billion, and they plan to spend more than $300 billion in 2025. The prize for those who can provide &#34;superior intelligence on tap,&#34; as some are now touting, is infinite. The AI ecosystem is exploding, with new startups and innovative offerings pouring out of global tech hubs. The technology isn’t just evolving; it’s erupting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The theory of AI adoption is also evolving. While everyone acknowledges that risk remains high and vigilance is necessary, concerns are shifting from Terminator-style apocalyptic fantasies to the practical realities of global social disruption anticipated, as AI’s impact cascades through, well, everything. As is becoming clear, we’ll be living next to and collaborating with AI interfaces in every form, from phones and smart glasses to robots and drones.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;期望是巨大的。投资是巨大的。亚马逊、谷歌、Meta 和微软在 2024 年总共花费了超过 2510 亿美元用于支持人工智能的基础设施投资，比 2023 年的 1550 亿美元增长了 62%，并且他们计划在 2025 年花费超过 3000 亿美元。对于那些能够提供“即时高级智能”的人来说，奖励是无限的。人工智能生态系统正在爆炸式增长，新的初创公司和创新产品从全球技术中心涌出。技术不仅在不断发展，而且还在不断发展。它正在爆发。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;人工智能采用的理论也在不断发展。尽管每个人都承认风险仍然很高，必须保持警惕，但随着人工智能的影响波及一切，人们的担忧正在从终结者式的世界末日幻想转向预期的全球社会破坏的实际现实。越来越清楚的是，我们将生活在各种形式的人工智能界面旁边并与之协作，从手机和智能眼镜到机器人和无人机。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Framework for Securing Open-Source Observability at the Edge】确保边缘开源可观测性的框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-open-source-observability-edge</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Edge Observability Security Challenge&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134245417&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:240}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Deploying an open-source observability solution to distributed retail edge locations creates a fundamental security challenge. With thousands of locations processing sensitive data like payments and customers&#39; p&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;ersonally identifiable information (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;PII), every telemetry component running on the edge becomes a potential&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;entry point for&amp;nbsp;attackers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;. Edge environments operate in spaces where there is limited physical security, bandwidth constraints shared with business-critical application traffic, and no technical staff on-site for incident response.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Therefore, traditional centralized monitoring security models do not fit in these conditions because they require abundant resources, dedicated security teams, and controlled physical environments. None of them exists on the edge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559685&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:240}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;边缘可观测性安全挑战&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;134233117&#34;：假，&#34;134233118&#34;：假，&#34;134245417&#34;：假，&#34;2 01341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559738&#34;:0,&#34;335559739&#34;:160,&#34;335559740&#34;:240}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;将开源可观测性解决方案部署到分布式零售边缘站点会带来根本性的安全挑战。由于数千个地点处理付款和客户个人信息等敏感数据&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;个人身份信息 (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;PII)，每个在边缘运行的遥测组件都成为潜在的入口点&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;对于攻击者&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;。边缘环境在物理安全有限、与关键业务应用程序流量共享的带宽限制以及没有现场技术人员进行事件响应的空间中运行。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;因此，传统的集中监控安全模型不适合这些条件，因为它们需要丰富的资源、专门的安全团队和受控的物理环境。它们都不存在于边缘。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;134233117&#34;:false,&#34;134233118&#34;:false,&#34;201341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559685&#34;:0,&#34;335559738&#34;:0,&#34;335559739&#34;:0,&#34;335559740&#34;:240}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>