<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【GPT-4.5 vs o3: The Applicability of AI Models Across Industries】GPT-4.5 vs O3：跨行业AI模型的适用性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-models-applicability-industries</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;OpenAI’s new GPT-4.5 model builds on its predecessors&#39; strengths while addressing key challenges in reliability and creativity. In this article, we explore how GPT-4.5 stands apart, when it should be favored over more specialized models like o3, and what this means for businesses seeking strong solutions in AI/ML development, embedded IoT, cloud solutions, and web/mobile development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;: This article does not offer direct technical comparisons between GPT-4.5 and o3. It provides a preliminary evaluation of their potential applications across industries, noting that GPT-4.5 is in its early release stage and will continue to evolve. For rigorous technical assessments, please refer to detailed benchmark studies as they become available.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; OpenAI的新GPT-4.5模型以其前辈的优势建立，同时解决了可靠性和创造力的关键挑战。在本文中，我们探讨了GPT-4.5如何与众不同，何时应该比O3这样的更专业的模型，这对于在AI/ML开发，嵌入式物联网，Web/Mobile开发中寻求强大解决方案的企业意味着什么。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;免责声明&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;：本文不提供GPT-4.5和O3之间的直接技术比较。它提供了对其在各行业的潜在应用的初步评估，并指出GPT-4.5处于早期发行阶段，并将继续发展。有关严格的技术评估，请参阅详细的基准研究。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The One Interview Question That Lost You the Job】一个失去工作的面试问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-one-interview-question-that-lost-you-the-job</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;People worry — sometimes with justification, but often without — about small things that might have tipped an interview or job hunting interaction against them. Were they dressed “right”? Too dressed up? Not enough? They joined the zoom call 1 minute late, did that ruin the whole thing? Did they answer every single question? Did they ask too many questions themselves? And on and on and on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My perspective — built from 35 years in tech as well as trying to help friends find their own new roles from time to time — is that most interviews are a series of moments that all add up. No individual moment is a deal-breaker. Instead, how a candidate “did” often comes down to the overall sense the interviewer feels after the entire conversation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人们担心 - 有时是有道理的，但往往没有 - 可能会给他们带来面试或寻找工作互动的小事情。他们穿着“正确”吗？太打扮了吗？不够？他们加入了Zoom Call 1分钟，这毁了整个事情吗？他们回答了每个问题吗？他们自己问太多问题吗？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我的观点 - 建立在35年的技术领域，并试图帮助朋友不时找到自己的新角色 - 大多数访谈都是一系列的时刻。没有个人时刻是打破交易的人。相反，候选人的“做”通常取决于面试官在整个谈话之后的总体意义。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java UDFs and Stored Procedures for Data Engineers: A Hands-On Guide】Java UDFS和数据工程师的存储程序：动手指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-udfs-stored-procedures-data-engineers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;522&#34; data-start=&#34;224&#34;&gt;Java has long been the backbone of enterprise applications, but its role in data engineering is growing rapidly. Today, modern data platforms like Snowflake are giving Java developers first-class support to write powerful, flexible, and scalable data logic directly inside the database environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;958&#34; data-start=&#34;524&#34;&gt;This guide demonstrates how Java developers can leverage familiar tools — like classes, streams, and DataFrames — to build &lt;strong data-end=&#34;676&#34; data-start=&#34;643&#34;&gt;user-defined functions (UDFs)&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong data-end=&#34;702&#34; data-start=&#34;681&#34;&gt;stored procedures&lt;/strong&gt; for real-time and batch data processing. By writing this logic in Java, you can encapsulate business rules, perform asynchronous operations, interact with structured or unstructured data, and maintain robust, reusable codebases within your data workflows.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 522” data-start =“ 224”&gt; Java长期以来一直是企业应用程序的骨干，但其在数据工程中的作用迅速增长。如今，诸如Snowflake之类的现代数据平台为Java开发人员提供了一流的支持，可以直接在数据库环境中编写强大，灵活和可扩展的数据逻辑。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 958”数据启动=“ 524”&gt;本指南展示了Java开发人员如何利用熟悉的工具（例如类，流和数据框）来构建&lt;strong data-end =“ 676” data-data-start =“ 643”&gt;用户定义的功能（udfs）&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;强&gt; &lt;/strong data-end forter &lt;/strong &lt;strong data-end forts &lt;/strong data-engort =“ 702” 70 =“ 702” start =“ 702”，“”实时和批处理数据处理。通过在Java中编写此逻辑，您可以封装业务规则，执行异步操作，与结构化或非结构化数据进行交互，并在数据工作流程中维护可重复使用的代码库。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why State Management Is the #1 Challenge for Agentic AI】为什么国家管理是代理AI的第一挑战</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-ai-state-management-challenges</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When you have a conversation with a chatbot, you want it to remember previous interactions within that conversation. That’s what it means to have a conversation, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you use generative AI (genAI) to perform some analysis task beyond a single response to a prompt, you want it to retain the context of earlier prompts within that task.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当您与聊天机器人进行对话时，您希望它记住该对话中的先前互动。毕竟，这就是进行对话的意思。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您使用生成AI（Genai）执行一些分析任务以外的提示以外的单个响应时，您希望它保留在该任务中的早期提示的上下文。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Monitoring journald Logs With Event-Driven Ansible】用事件驱动的Ansible监视日记帐登录</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/monitoring-journald-logs-with-ansible-eda</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Monitoring journald is essential for keeping systems running smoothly and securely. By regularly checking logs generated by systemd, administrators can catch potential issues like failing services or resource constraints — before they turn into major problems. Beyond performance and troubleshooting, journald is a powerful tool for security and compliance. It helps track login attempts, privilege escalations, and unusual service behavior, making it crucial for detecting unauthorized access or potential cyber threats. For organizations that need to meet regulatory requirements, monitoring system logs ensures proper tracking of system changes and security policies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;About the Module&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;ansible.eda.journald&lt;/code&gt; is an Event-Driven Ansible (EDA) plugin that listens to journald logs in real time and triggers automated responses based on log events. This makes it useful for tasks like automatically restarting failed services, detecting security threats, or alerting administrators when critical system issues occur.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;监视日记帐对保持系统的运行平稳，安全运行至关重要。通过定期检查SystemD生成的日志，管理员可以在变成主要问题之前发现服务失败或资源限制的潜在问题。除了性能和故障排除之外，JournalD是安全性和合规性的强大工具。它有助于跟踪登录尝试，特权升级和异常服务行为，这对于检测未经授权的访问或潜在的网络威胁至关重要。对于需要满足监管要求的组织，监视系统日志可确保正确跟踪系统变更和安全策略。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;关于模块&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;code&gt; ansible.eda.journald &lt;/code&gt;是一个事件驱动的Ansible（EDA）插件，可实时倾听日记帐日志，并根据日志事件触发自动响应。这使得它对于自动重新启动失败服务，检测安全威胁或在发生关键系统问题时警告管理员的任务很有用。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transforming Data Analytics by Combining SQL and ML】通过组合SQL和ML来转换数据分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-data-analytics-sql-ml</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;SQL has been the backbone of data and analytics for decades, providing a standardized approach to storing, retrieving, and manipulating data. However, as data volumes grow exponentially and analytical requirements become more complex, traditional SQL approaches face limitations. Here is where AI and ML enter the picture, extending SQL&#39;s capabilities beyond simple querying to include predictive analytics, pattern recognition, and automated optimization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;ML algorithms and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sql-database-schema-beginners-guide-with-examples&#34;&gt;SQL&lt;/a&gt; go hand in hand in creating a synergistic relationship: SQL provides a structured framework for data retrieval and management, while ML algorithms bring advanced analytical capabilities that can uncover hidden patterns and make predictions based on historical data. This integration is transforming how organizations interact with their data, enabling more sophisticated analysis without requiring users to leave their familiar SQL environment.&lt;/p&gt;】数十年来，&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; SQL一直是数据和分析的骨干，为存储，检索和操纵数据提供了标准化的方法。但是，随着数据量呈指数增长，分析要求变得更加复杂，传统的SQL方法会面临限制。这是AI和ML输入图片的地方，扩展了SQL的功能，而不是简单查询，以包括预测分析，模式识别和自动化优化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;ML algorithms and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sql-database-schema-beginners-guide-with-examples&#34;&gt;SQL&lt;/a&gt; go hand in hand in creating a synergistic relationship: SQL provides a structured framework for data retrieval and management, while ML algorithms bring advanced analytical capabilities that can发现隐藏的模式并根据历史数据做出预测。这种集成正在改变组织如何与数据进行交互，从而实现了更复杂的分析，而无需用户离开熟悉的SQL环境。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Context Search With AWS Bedrock, Cohere Model, and Spring AI】与AWS基石，Cohere模型和Spring AI一起搜索上下文搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/context-search-aws-bedrock-cohere-spring-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today, we will create simple applications using the Cohere Embed Multilingual v3 model via Amazon Bedrock and Spring AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;366&#34; data-start=&#34;197&#34;&gt;We’ll skip over basic Spring concepts like bean management and starters, as the main goal of this article is to explore the capabilities of Spring AI and Amazon Bedrock.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;今天，我们将使用Amazon Bedrock和Spring AI使用Cohere嵌入的多语言V3模型来创建简单的应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 366” data-start =“ 197”&gt;我们将跳过基本的春季概念，例如豆类管理和起动器，因为本文的主要目标是探索Spring AI和Amazon Bedrock的功能。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python Packages for Validating Database Migration Projects】用于验证数据库迁移项目的Python软件包</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/python-packages-for-validating-database-migration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Database migrations are critical projects in software systems, ensuring that data is seamlessly transferred from legacy databases to modern systems without corruption, loss, or performance degradation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As software testing professionals, validating database migrations is essential to ensuring data integrity and consistency. Python provides several packages to facilitate database validation. This article analyzes the most useful Python packages for validating database migration projects, complete with code snippets and performance comparisons.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据库迁移是软件系统中的关键项目，可确保数据从传统数据库无缝传输到现代系统，而没有损坏，损失或性能降级。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为软件测试专业人​​员，验证数据库迁移对于确保数据完整性和一致性至关重要。 Python提供了几个软件包，以促进数据库验证。本文分析了用于验证数据库迁移项目的最有用的Python软件包，并配有代码段和性能比较。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How AI Automation Increases Research Productivity】AI自动化如何提高研究生产率</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-ai-automation-increases-research-productivity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Scientific research is about finding quick, dependable, and efficient ways to accomplish goals. As the demand for high-quality data is essential for making accurate analysis, automation has become a necessity for streamlining the workflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div data-cy=&#34;blog-post-article&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;Automation is transforming research in many fields, helping with everything from collecting data to managing workflows, making research faster and more productive. We explore real-life examples of automated systems that are helping businesses and researchers innovate and accelerate discoveries.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;科学研究是关于找到实现目标的快速，可靠和有效的方法。由于对高质量数据的需求对于进行准确的分析至关重要，因此自动化已成为简化工作流程的必要性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div data-cy =“ blog-post-article”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;自动化正在改变许多领域的研究，从收集数据到管理工作流程，使研究更快，更有生产力。我们探讨了自动化系统的现实示例，这些系统正在帮助企业和研究人员进行创新和加速发现。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking the Power of Serverless AI/ML on AWS: Expert Strategies for Scalable and Secure Applications】在AWS上解锁无服务器AI/ML的功能：可扩展和安全应用程序的专家策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/serverless-ai-aws-strategies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Amazon Web Services (AWS) provides an expansive suite of tools to help developers build and manage serverless applications with ease. By abstracting the complexities of infrastructure, AWS enables teams to focus on innovation. When combined with the transformative capabilities of artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML), serverless architectures become a powerhouse for creating intelligent, scalable, and cost-efficient solutions. In this article, we delve into serverless AI/ML on AWS, exploring best practices, implementation strategies, and an example to illustrate these concepts in action.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why Combine AI, ML, and Serverless Computing?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The fusion of serverless computing with AI and ML represents a significant leap forward for modern application development. Serverless systems scale automatically, simplify operational overhead, and use a pay-per-use model that keeps costs in check. On the other hand, AI brings capabilities like natural language processing (NLP), image recognition, and data analytics, while ML enables predictive modeling, dynamic decision making, and personalization. Together, AI and ML unlock opportunities to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/building-ai-driven-intelligent-applications-a-guide&#34;&gt;build intelligent applications&lt;/a&gt; that are not only efficient but also responsive to real-world challenges.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Amazon Web Services（AWS）提供了一套宽敞的工具，可轻松地帮助开发人员构建和管理无服务器应用程序。通过抽象基础架构的复杂性，AWS使团队能够专注于创新。当与人工智能（AI）和机器学习（ML）的变革能力结合使用时，无服务器体系结构成为创建智能，可扩展和成本效益的解决方案的强大力量。在本文中，我们深入研究了AWS的无服务器AI/ML，探索最佳实践，实施策略以及一个在行动中说明这些概念的示例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么组合AI，ML和无服务器计算？ &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无服务器计算与AI和ML的融合代表了现代应用程序开发的重大飞跃。无服务器系统会自动扩展，简化操作开销，并使用每次使用付费模型，以保持费用。另一方面，AI带来了自然语言处理（NLP），图像识别和数据分析等功能，而ML可以实现预测性建模，动态决策和个性化。 AI和ML解释了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/building-ai-driven-indelligent-intelligent-applications-a-guide”&gt;构建智能应用程序&lt;/a&gt;不仅有效，而且对现实世界中的挑战有效。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>