<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Discover Hidden Patterns with Intelligent K-Means Clustering】通过智能 K 均值聚类发现隐藏模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/discover-hidden-patterns-intelligent-kmeans-cluster</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;What is Clustering&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clustering is a type of &lt;strong&gt;unsupervised machine learning technique&lt;/strong&gt; that groups similar data points together. Clustering helps you automatically identify patterns or natural groups hidden in your data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Imagine this scenario&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;什么是聚类&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;聚类是一种&lt;strong&gt;无监督机器学习技术&lt;/strong&gt;，它将相似的数据点分组在一起。聚类可帮助您自动识别数据中隐藏的模式或自然组。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;想象一下这个场景&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing a CPU-Efficient Redis Cluster Topology】设计 CPU 高效的 Redis 集群拓扑</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/design-redis-cluster-topology-saves-cpus</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Redis is a popular in-memory data store that has become an essential component of many modern applications. With its high performance, scalability, and reliability features, Redis has emerged as a top choice for caching, session management, and other use cases. In this article, we&#39;ll explore the deployment &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/manage-redis-cluster-topology-with-command-line&#34;&gt;topology of Redis Cluster&lt;/a&gt;, specifically focusing on the master-replica approach utilizing all the cores on the vms, leveraging the single threaded behaviour of redis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is a Redis Cluster&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Redis Cluster is a distributed deployment that shards your dataset across multiple Redis nodes. It automatically handles data partitioning and replication, ensuring both high availability and horizontal scalability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Redis 是一种流行的内存数据存储，已成为许多现代应用程序的重要组成部分。凭借其高性能、可扩展性和可靠性特性，Redis 已成为缓存、会话管理和其他用例的首选。在本文中，我们将探讨 Redis 集群的部署&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/manage-redis-cluster-topology-with-command-line&#34;&gt;拓扑&lt;/a&gt;，特别关注利用虚拟机上所有核心的主副本方法，利用 Redis 的单线程行为。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是Redis集群&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Redis 集群是一种分布式部署，可将数据集分片到多个 Redis 节点。它自动处理数据分区和复制，确保高可用性和水平可扩展性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS Agentic AI for App Portfolio Modernization】用于应用程序组合现代化的 AWS Agentic AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-agentic-ai-app-portfolio-modernization</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Rethinking Application Modernization in the GenAI Era&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enterprises are accelerating their modernization journeys, driven by cloud mandates and growing demand for digital agility. Yet when faced with large application portfolios, transformation leaders often struggle to make decisions that are objective, scalable, and consistent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the era of Generative AI, a new paradigm is emerging: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/function-calling-and-agents-in-the-agentic-ai&#34;&gt;Agentic AI&lt;/a&gt; systems that not only reason over user input but also collaborate as autonomous agents to deliver reliable, explainable, and business-aligned outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;重新思考 GenAI 时代的应用现代化&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在云要求和对数字敏捷性不断增长的需求的推动下，企业正在加速其现代化进程。然而，当面对大型应用程序组合时，转型领导者通常很难做出客观、可扩展且一致的决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在生成式 AI 时代，一种新的范式正在出现：&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/function-calling-and-agents-in-the-agentic-ai&#34;&gt;代理 AI&lt;/a&gt; 系统不仅可以根据用户输入进行推理，还可以作为自主代理进行协作，以提供可靠、可解释且符合业务的结果。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Containers to WebAssembly: The Next Evolution in Cloud-Native Architecture】从容器到 WebAssembly：云原生架构的下一次演变</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/from-containers-to-webassembly-the-next-evolution</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-docker-concepts&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; first arrived, it felt like magic. I was working at a fintech startup then, and containers instantly killed the dreaded &#34;works on my machine&#34; problem. For the first time, we could package our applications with all their dependencies, ship them anywhere, and trust they&#39;d run exactly the same way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But here&#39;s the thing about revolutions — they expose new problems while solving old ones.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-docker-concepts&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt;第一次出现时，感觉就像魔法一样。当时我在一家金融科技初创公司工作，容器立即解决了可怕的“在我的机器上运行”问题。我们第一次可以将应用程序及其所有依赖项打包，将它们运送到任何地方，并相信它们会以完全相同的方式运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但这就是革命的特点——革命在解决旧问题的同时暴露了新问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Hidden Backbone of AI: Why Data Engineering is Key for Model Success】人工智能的隐藏支柱：为什么数据工程是模型成功的关键</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-data-engineering-is-key-for-model-success</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Everyone is talking about AI models, but only a few are discussing the data pipelines that feed them. We talk about LLM benchmarks, the number of parameters, and GPU clusters. But under the hood, every AI and ML model has an invisible, complex, and messy data pipeline that can either supercharge it or break it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the last 20 years, I have built data pipelines for large companies like Apple. I have seen firsthand how crucial these data pipelines are for any model to succeed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个人都在谈论人工智能模型，但只有少数人在讨论为其提供数据的数据管道。我们讨论 LLM 基准、参数数量和 GPU 集群。但在幕后，每个人工智能和机器学习模型都有一个看不见的、复杂的、混乱的数据管道，这些数据管道要么会增强它，要么会破坏它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在过去 20 年里，我为 Apple 等大公司构建了数据管道。我亲眼目睹了这些数据管道对于任何模型的成功都有多么重要。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The RAG Illusion: Why “Grafting” Memory Is No Longer Enough】RAG 错觉：为什么“嫁接”记忆已经不够了</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rag-illusion-grafting-memory-limitations</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The solution to RAG&#39;s architectural disconnect is not more context, but deep integration. The CLaRa framework achieves a true fusion of retrieval and generation via differentiable retrieval and compressed vectors, leading to 16x efficiency, data autonomy, and superior reasoning performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag&#34;&gt;Retrieval-augmented generation&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) has become a standard tool of modern generative AI. We could say, in a way, that to prevent our models from hallucinating, we grafted search engines onto them. On paper, the promise is kept: AI accesses your enterprise data. But taking a closer look, a structural flaw remains within this hybrid architecture. Concretely, we are facing a functional coexistence rather than a structural integration, where the search module and the generative model ignore each other.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;解决 RAG 架构脱节的方法不是更多上下文，而是深度集成。 CLaRa 框架通过可微分检索和压缩向量实现了检索和生成的真正融合，从而实现 16 倍的效率、数据自治和卓越的推理性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented- Generation-rag&#34;&gt;检索增强生成&lt;/a&gt; (RAG) 已成为现代生成人工智能的标准工具。在某种程度上，我们可以说，为了防止我们的模型产生幻觉，我们将搜索引擎移植到它们上面。从表面上看，我们兑现了承诺：人工智能可以访问您的企业数据。但仔细观察，这种混合架构中仍然存在结构缺陷。具体来说，我们面临的是功能共存，而不是结构集成，搜索模块和生成模型相互忽略。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Going Beyond Authentication: Essential Features for Profile-First Systems】超越身份验证：配置文件优先系统的基本功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/essential-features-for-profile-first-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&#34;Just log in&#34; is not enough&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the evolution of modern web applications, products, and user experience, relying only on authentication and authorization is not enough for user management. It demands personalization, saved preferences, notifications, compliance, and smooth lifecycle controls. How often are users looking for these nowadays?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“Save this search and reuse it later.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“Notify me when this record changes.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“Switch my notifications to email only.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“Download my data before I close my account.”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These are no longer a wishlist, and at the same time, these are not &lt;em&gt;identity&lt;/em&gt; features. They belong in a profile system — the layer that makes your users feel in control and stick with the product/application.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;“仅登录”是不够的&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着现代 Web 应用、产品和用户体验的发展，仅依靠身份验证和授权不足以进行用户管理。它需要个性化、保存的首选项、通知、合规性和平稳的生命周期控制。如今用户寻找这些内容的频率如何？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“保存此搜索并稍后重复使用。” &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“当此记录发生变化时通知我。” &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“将我的通知切换为仅发送电子邮件。” &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;“在关闭帐户之前下载我的数据。”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些不再是愿望清单，同时，这些也不是&lt;em&gt;身份&lt;/em&gt;功能。它们属于配置文件系统 - 该层让您的用户感到掌控并坚持使用产品/应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling RAG for Enterprise Applications Best Practices and Case Study Experiences】为企业应用程序扩展 RAG 最佳实践和案例研究经验</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-rag-for-enterprise-applications-best-practices-and-case-studies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation, or RAG, combines retrieval systems with generative models to improve the accuracy and relevance of AI-generated responses. Unlike traditional language models that rely solely on memorized training data, RAG systems augment generation by retrieving relevant contextual information from curated knowledge bases before generating answers. This two-step approach reduces the risk of fabrications or hallucinations by grounding AI outputs in trustworthy external data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The core idea is to index your knowledge collection, often in the form of documents or databases, using vector-based embeddings that allow semantic search. When a user poses a query, the system retrieves the most relevant information and feeds it to a large language model (LLM) as context. The model then generates responses informed by up-to-date and domain-specific knowledge. This approach is especially effective for applications requiring specialized or frequently changing information.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;检索增强生成（RAG）将检索系统与生成模型相结合，以提高人工智能生成的响应的准确性和相关性。与仅依赖于记忆的训练数据的传统语言模型不同，RAG 系统通过在生成答案之前从策划的知识库中检索相关上下文信息来增强生成能力。这种两步方法通过将人工智能输出置于可信的外部数据中来降低捏造或幻觉的风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;核心思想是使用允许语义搜索的基于向量的嵌入来索引您的知识集合，通常以文档或数据库的形式。当用户提出查询时，系统会检索最相关的信息并将其作为上下文提供给大型语言模型 (LLM)。然后，该模型根据最新的特定领域知识生成响应。这种方法对于需要专门或经常更改信息的应用程序特别有效。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Can Generative AI Enhance Data Exploration While Preserving Privacy?】生成式人工智能能否在保护隐私的同时增强数据探索？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-data-exploration-privacy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;2101&#34; data-start=&#34;1129&#34;&gt;Generative AI is rapidly changing how organizations interrogate their data. Rather than forcing domain experts to learn query languages or spend days writing scripts, modern language-and-reasoning models let people explore data through conversational prompts, auto-generated analyses, and on-demand visualizations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;2101&#34; data-start=&#34;1129&#34;&gt;This democratization is compelling: analysts get higher-velocity insight, business users ask complex “what-if” questions in plain language, and teams can iterate quickly over hypotheses. Yet the same forces that power this productivity — large models trained on vast information and interactive, stateful services — introduce real privacy, compliance, and trust risks. The central challenge is to design &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;GenAI systems&lt;/a&gt; for data exploration so they reveal structure and signal without exposing personal or sensitive details. This editorial argues for a pragmatic, technical, and governance-first approach: enable discovery, but build privacy into the plumbing.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;2101&#34; data-start=&#34;1129&#34;&gt;生成式 AI 正在迅速改变组织查询数据的方式。现代语言和推理模型不是强迫领域专家学习查询语言或花几天时间编写脚本，而是让人们通过对话提示、自动生成的分析和按需可视化来探索数据。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;2101&#34; data-start=&#34;1129&#34;&gt;这种民主化引人注目：分析师获得更快的洞察力，业务用户用简单的语言提出复杂的“假设”问题，团队可以快速迭代假设。然而，推动这种生产力的同样力量——在海量信息和交互式、有状态服务上训练的大型模型——带来了真正的隐私、合规性和信任风险。核心挑战是设计用于数据探索的 GenAI 系统，以便在不暴露个人或敏感细节的情况下揭示结构和信号。这篇社论主张采取务实、技术和治理优先的方法：实现发现，但将隐私纳入管道。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Traditional QA Fails for Generative AI in Tech Support】为什么传统的 QA 无法用于技术支持中的生成式 AI</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/genai-tech-support-qa-failures</link>
      <description>【&lt;div data-en-clipboard=&#34;true&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34; draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; The rapid advancement of generative AI (GenAI) has created unprecedented opportunities to transform technical support operations. However, it has also introduced unique challenges in quality assurance that traditional monitoring approaches simply cannot address. As enterprise AI systems become increasingly complex, particularly in technical support environments, we need more sophisticated evaluation frameworks to ensure their reliability and effectiveness.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;Why Traditional Monitoring Fails for GenAI Support Agents&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Most enterprises rely on what&#39;s commonly called &#34;canary testing&#34; — predefined test cases with known inputs and expected outputs that run at regular intervals to validate system behavior. While these approaches work well for deterministic systems, they break down when applied to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;GenAI&lt;/a&gt; support agents for several fundamental reasons:&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Infinite input variety&lt;/strong&gt;: Support agents must handle unpredictable natural language queries that cannot be pre-scripted. A customer might describe the same technical issue in countless different ways, each requiring proper interpretation.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Resource configuration diversity&lt;/strong&gt;: Each customer environment contains a unique constellation of resources and settings. An EC2 instance in one account might be configured entirely differently from one in another account, yet agents must reason correctly about both.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Complex reasoning paths&lt;/strong&gt;: Unlike API-based systems that follow predictable execution flows, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-agents-transforming-supply-chain&#34;&gt;GenAI agents&lt;/a&gt; make dynamic decisions based on customer context, resource state, and troubleshooting logic.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Dynamic agent behavior&lt;/strong&gt;: These models continuously learn and adapt, making static test suites quickly obsolete as agent behavior evolves.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Feedback lag problem&lt;/strong&gt;: Traditional monitoring relies heavily on customer-reported issues, creating unacceptable delays in identifying and addressing quality problems.&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;A Concrete Example&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Consider an agent troubleshooting a cloud database access issue. The complexity becomes immediately apparent:&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   The agent must correctly interpret the customer&#39;s description, which might be technically imprecise&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   It needs to identify and validate relevant resources in the customer&#39;s specific environment&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   It must select appropriate &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-should-know-about-apis&#34;&gt;APIs&lt;/a&gt; to investigate permissions and network configurations&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   It needs to apply technical knowledge to reason through potential causes based on those unique conditions&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Finally, it must generate a solution tailored to that specific environment&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; This complex chain of reasoning simply cannot be validated through predetermined test cases with expected outputs. We need a more flexible, comprehensive approach.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;The Dual-Layer Solution&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Our solution is a dual-layer framework combining real-time evaluation with offline comparison:&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Real-time component&lt;/strong&gt;: Uses LLM-based &#34;jury evaluation&#34; to continuously assess the quality of agent reasoning as it happens&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Offline component&lt;/strong&gt;: Compares agent-suggested solutions against human expert resolutions after cases are completed&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Together, they provide both immediate quality signals and deeper insights from human expertise. This approach gives comprehensive visibility into agent performance without requiring direct customer feedback, enabling continuous quality assurance across diverse support scenarios.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;How Real-Time Evaluation Works&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; The real-time component collects complete agent execution traces, including:&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Customer utterances&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Classification decisions&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Resource inspection results&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Reasoning steps&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; These traces are then evaluated by an ensemble of specialized &#34;judge&#34; large language models (LLMs) that analyze the agent&#39;s reasoning. For example, when an agent classifies a customer issue as an EC2 networking problem, three different LLM judges independently assess whether this classification is correct given the customer&#39;s description.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Using majority voting creates a more robust evaluation than relying on any single model. We apply strategic downsampling to control costs while maintaining representative coverage across different agent types and scenarios. The results are published to monitoring dashboards in real-time, triggering alerts when performance drops below configurable thresholds.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;Offline Comparison: The Human Expert Benchmark&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; While real-time evaluation provides immediate feedback, our offline component delivers deeper insights through comparative analysis. It:&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Links agent-suggested solutions to final case resolutions in support management systems&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Performs semantic comparison between AI solutions and human expert resolutions&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Reveals nuanced differences in solution quality that binary metrics would miss&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; For example, we discovered our EC2 troubleshooting agent was technically correct but provided less detailed security group explanations than human experts. The multi-dimensional scoring assesses correctness, completeness, and relevance, providing actionable insights for improvement.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Most importantly, this creates a continuous learning loop where agent performance improves based on human expertise without requiring explicit feedback collection.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;Technical Implementation Details&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Our implementation balances evaluation quality with operational efficiency:&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   A lightweight client library embedded in agent runtimes captures execution traces without impacting performance&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   These traces flow into a FIFO queue that enables controlled processing rates and message grouping by agent type&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   A compute unit processes these traces, applying downsampling logic and orchestrating the LLM jury evaluation&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Results are stored with streaming capabilities that trigger additional processing for metrics publication and trend analysis&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; This architecture separates evaluation logic from reporting concerns, creating a more maintainable system. We&#39;ve implemented graceful degradation so the system continues providing insights even when some LLM judges fail or are throttled, ensuring continuous monitoring without disruption.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;Specialized Evaluators for Different Reasoning Components&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Different agent components require specialized evaluation approaches. Our framework includes a taxonomy of evaluators tailored to specific reasoning tasks:&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Domain classification&lt;/strong&gt;: LLM judges assess whether the agent correctly identified the technical domain of the customer&#39;s issue&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Resource validation&lt;/strong&gt;: We measure the precision and recall of the agent&#39;s identification of relevant resources&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Tool selection&lt;/strong&gt;: Evaluators assess whether the agent chose appropriate diagnostic APIs given the context&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;Final solutions&lt;/strong&gt;: Our GroundTruth Comparator measures semantic similarity to human expert resolutions&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; This specialized approach lets us pinpoint exactly where improvements are needed in the agent&#39;s reasoning chain, rather than simply knowing that something went wrong somewhere.&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;Measurable Results and Business Impact&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; Implementing this framework has driven significant improvements across our AI support operations:&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Increased successful case deflection by 20% while maintaining high customer satisfaction scores&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Detected previously invisible quality issues that traditional metrics missed, such as discovering that some agents were performing unnecessary credential validations that added latency without improving solution quality&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Accelerated improvement cycles thanks to detailed, component-level feedback on reasoning quality&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA;   Built greater confidence in agent deployments, knowing that quality issues will be quickly detected and addressed before they impact customer experience&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;Conclusion and Future Directions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As AI reasoning agents become increasingly central to technical support operations, sophisticated evaluation frameworks become essential. Traditional monitoring approaches simply cannot address the complexity of these systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our dual-layer framework demonstrates that continuous, multi-dimensional assessment is possible at scale, enabling responsible deployment of increasingly powerful AI support systems. Looking ahead, we&#39;re working on:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div data-en-clipboard=&#34;true&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&#xA; 生成式人工智能 (GenAI) 的快速发展为技术支持运营转型创造了前所未有的机会。然而，它也给质量保证带来了传统监测方法根本无法解决的独特挑战。随着企业人工智能系统变得越来越复杂，特别是在技术支持环境中，我们需要更复杂的评估框架来确保其可靠性和有效性。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;为什么 GenAI 支持代理的传统监控失败&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 大多数企业依赖于通常所说的“金丝雀测试”——具有已知输入和预期输出的预定义测试用例，定期运行以验证系统行为。虽然这些方法适用于确定性系统，但在应用于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-generative-ai-empowering-enterprises&#34;&gt;GenAI&lt;/a&gt; 支持代理时会崩溃，原因有几个：&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;无限的输入种类&lt;/strong&gt;：支持代理必须处理无法预先编写脚本的不可预测的自然语言查询。客户可能会以无数不同的方式描述同一技术问题，每种方式都需要正确的解释。&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;资源配置多样性&lt;/strong&gt;：每个客户环境都包含独特的资源和设置群。一个账户中的 EC2 实例的配置可能与另一个账户中的 EC2 实例完全不同，但代理必须正确推断两者。&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;复杂的推理路径&lt;/strong&gt;：与遵循可预测执行流程的基于 API 的系统不同，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-agents-transforming-supply-chain&#34;&gt;GenAI 代理&lt;/a&gt;根据客户上下文、资源状态和故障排除逻辑做出动态决策。&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;动态代理行为&lt;/strong&gt;：这些模型不断学习和适应，使得静态测试套件随着代理行为的发展而迅速过时。&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;反馈滞后问题&lt;/strong&gt;：传统监控严重依赖客户报告的问题，在识别和解决质量问题方面造成了不可接受的延迟。&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;具体示例&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 考虑让代理对云数据库访问问题进行故障排除。复杂性立即显而易见：&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   代理必须正确解释客户的描述，这在技术上可能不精确&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div 拖动山墙=“假”&gt;&#xA;   需要识别并验证客户特定环境中的相关资源&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   它必须选择适当的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/everything-you-should-know-about-apis&#34;&gt;API&lt;/a&gt; 来调查权限和网络配置&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   它需要应用技术知识，根据这些独特条件通过潜在原因进行推理&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   最后，它必须生成适合特定环境的解决方案&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 这种复杂的推理链根本无法通过具有预期输出的预定测试用例进行验证。我们需要一种更灵活、更全面的方法。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;双层解决方案&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 我们的解决方案是实时评估与离线比较相结合的双层框架：&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;实时组件&lt;/strong&gt;：使用基于法学硕士的“陪审团评估”来持续评估代理推理的质量&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;离线组件&lt;/strong&gt;：在案件完成后将代理建议的解决方案与人类专家的解决方案进行比较&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 它们共同提供即时的质量信号和来自人类专业知识的更深入的见解。这种方法可以全面了解代理绩效，无需直接客户反馈，从而能够在不同的支持场景中实现持续的质量保证。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;实时评估的工作原理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 实时组件收集完整的代理执行跟踪，包括：&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   客户感言&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   分类决策&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   资源巡查结果&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   推理步骤&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 然后，这些痕迹由一组专门的“判断”大型语言模型（LLM）进行评估，这些模型会分析智能体的推理。例如，当代理将客户问题分类为 EC2 网络问题时，三名不同的 LLM 法官根据客户的描述独立评估该分类是否正确。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 与依赖任何单一模型相比，使用多数投票可以产生更稳健的评估。我们应用战略下采样来控制成本，同时保持不同代理类型和场景的代表性覆盖范围。结果实时发布到监控仪表板，当性能下降到可配置阈值以下时，操纵会发出警报。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;离线比较：人类专家基准&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 虽然实时评估提供即时反馈，但我们的离线组件通过比较分析提供更深入的见解。它：&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   将代理建议的解决方案链接到支持管理系统中的最终案例解决方案&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   对人工智能解决方案和人类专家解决方案进行语义比较&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   揭示二进制指标可能忽略的解决方案质量的细微差别&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 例如，我们发现我们的 EC2 故障排除代理在技术上是正确的，但提供的安全组解释不如人类专家详细。多维度评分评估正确性、完整性和相关性，为改进提供可操作的见解。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 最重要的是，这创建了一个持续的学习循环，代理的性能可以根据人类的专业知识进行改进，而无需收集明确的反馈。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;技术实现细节&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 我们的实施平衡了评估质量和运营效率：&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   嵌入代理运行时的轻量级客户端库可捕获执行跟踪而不影响性能&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   这些跟踪流入 FIFO 队列，该队列支持按代理类型控制处理速率和消息分组&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   计算单元处理这些痕迹，应用下采样逻辑并协调 LLM 陪审团评估&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   结果通过流功能存储，触发指标发布和趋势分析的额外处理&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 该架构将评估逻辑与报告问题分开，创建一个更易于维护的系统。我们已经实施了优雅的降级，因此即使某些法学硕士法官失败或受到限制，系统也能继续提供见解，从而确保持续监控而不会中断。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;针对不同推理组件的专业评估器&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 不同的代理组件需要专门的评估方法。我们的框架包括针对特定推理任务量身定制的评估器分类法：&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;领域分类&lt;/strong&gt;：LLM评委评估代理人是否正确识别了客户问题的技术领域&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/李&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;资源验证&lt;/strong&gt;：我们衡量代理识别相关资源的精确度和召回率&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;工具选择&lt;/strong&gt;：评估人员评估代理是否在给定上下文的情况下选择了适当的诊断 API&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   &lt;strong&gt;最终解决方案&lt;/strong&gt;：我们的 GroundTruth 比较器测量与人类专家决议的语义相似性&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 这种专门的方法让我们能够准确地查明智能体推理链中需要改进的地方，而不是简单地知道某个地方出了问题。&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;可衡量的结果和业务影响&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA; 实施该框架推动了我们的人工智能支持业务的显着改进：&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   将成功案例偏转率提高 20%，同时保持较高的客户满意度分数&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   检测传统指标遗漏的以前看不见的质量问题，例如发现某些代理正在执行不必要的凭证验证，从而增加了延迟，而没有提高解决方案质量&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   通过对推理质量进行详细的组件级反馈，加快了改进周期&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;lidraggable=“假”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div拖拽=“假”&gt;&#xA;   对代理部署建立更大的信心，因为知道质量问题将在影响客户体验之前被快速检测到并得到解决&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 Draggable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;结论和未来方向&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着人工智能推理代理在技术支持操作中变得越来越重要，复杂的评估框架变得至关重要。传统的监控方法根本无法解决这些系统的复杂性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的双层框架表明，大规模连续、多维评估是可能的，从而能够负责任地部署日益强大的人工智能支持系统。展望未来，我们正在努力：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>