<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AI for Agile Coaches: The Upgrade You Didn&#39;t Know You Needed】敏捷教练的AI：您不知道需要的升级</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/AI-for-agile-coaches</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;703&#34; data-start=&#34;335&#34;&gt;I’ve been coaching Agile teams long enough to know one thing for sure: we love sticky notes. We love whiteboards. We love retrospectives that feel like therapy and standups that, when done right, buzz with energy. What we &lt;em data-end=&#34;562&#34; data-start=&#34;555&#34;&gt;don’t&lt;/em&gt; love? Being buried under spreadsheets, chasing metrics across JIRA boards, or losing hours rewriting sprint summaries that no one will read.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;746&#34; data-start=&#34;705&#34;&gt;And now we’re told AI is here to help us.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 703” data-start =“ 335”&gt;我一直在指导敏捷的团队足够长的时间，可以肯定地知道一件事：我们喜欢粘稠的笔记。我们喜欢白板。我们喜欢感觉像治疗和站立的回顾，当做对时，能量嗡嗡作响。我们&lt;em data-end =“ 562” data-start =“ 555”&gt;不爱吗？被埋葬在电子表格下，在JIRA板上追逐指标，或者损失了没有人会读的小时重写Sprint摘要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 746” data-start =“ 705”&gt;，现在我们被告知AI在这里为我们提供帮助。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Open Source Climate Stack: Essential GitHub Repos Powering the Decarbonization Movement】开源气候堆栈：基本的GitHub存储库为脱碳运动提供动力</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/open-source-climate-stack-github-repos-decarbonization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Climate change is accelerating, so there is a growing need for developers to leverage their skills to support global decarbonization efforts. Open-source software helps you with this mission by enabling more solutions. With key tools that monitor emissions and optimize clean energy systems, you can greatly reduce carbon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Importance of Open-Source for Climate Innovation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Open-source software speeds climate innovation by facilitating transparency, reproducibility, and global collaboration. With no licensing restrictions, developers across disciplines can adapt solutions by reducing duplication and fast-tracking implementation. This contribution is especially vital in a space where scalable, verifiable tools are essential to manage complex systems, including:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;气候变化正在加速，因此开发人员越来越需要利用他们的技能来支持全球脱碳工作。开源软件通过启用更多解决方案来帮助您执行此任务。借助监视排放并优化清洁能源系统的关键工具，您可以大大减少碳。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;开源对气候创新的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;开源软件通过促进透明度，可重复性和全球协作来加快气候创新。由于没有许可限制，跨学科的开发人员可以通过减少重复和快速跟踪实施来调整解决方案。在可扩展，可验证的工具对于管理复杂系统至关重要的空间中，这种贡献尤其重要，包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Avoid Downtime: Smart Strategies to Upgrade Legacy Applications Without Breaking Systems】避免停机时间：智能策略升级遗产应用程序而不破坏系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/avoid-downtime-smart-strategies-to-upgrade-legacy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Legacy applications are often categorized as liability assets of an organization. Hard-to-maintain, complex interfaces, outdated technology, and severe security risks are some of the common issues raised that can be major roadblocks to business growth and long-term goals. However, if modernized correctly, they can be valuable resources, eliminating critical challenges related to maintenance costs, security, and compatibility issues with modern systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;After reading this blog, you will have a keen understanding of legacy applications, the risk associated with downtime, the challenges involved in holding on to legacy applications, and smart strategies to implement while upgrading. By following the strategies given below, you should be able to modernize your legacy application without downtime or any disruptions. ftf&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;旧应用程序通常被归类为组织的责任资产。难以维护，复杂的界面，过时的技术和严重的安全风险是提出的一些常见问题，这些问题可能是业务增长和长期目标的主要障碍。但是，如果正确地进行现代化，它们可能是宝贵的资源，消除与现代系统与维护成本，安全性和兼容性问题有关的关键挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;阅读此博客后，您将对传统应用程序，与停机时间相关的风险，坚持遗产应用程序所涉及的挑战以及在升级时实施的智能策略所涉及的挑战。通过遵循以下策略，您应该能够在没有停机时间或任何干扰的情况下对遗产应用程序进行现代化。 ftf &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agile and Quality Engineering: Building a Culture of Excellence Through a Holistic Approach】敏捷和质量工程：通过整体方法建立卓越文化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agile-quality-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the age of digital disruption, organizations face relentless pressure to deliver value faster, reduce time-to-market, and exceed user expectations. Agile methodologies emerged as a response to these challenges, promoting flexibility, collaboration, and continuous delivery. However, agility without quality is a recipe for technical debt, customer dissatisfaction, and inefficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/bolstering-quality-engineering-with-no-code-and-lo&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;q&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;uality engineering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;(&lt;strong&gt;QE&lt;/strong&gt;) steps in — not as a post-development gatekeeper, but as an integral part of the Agile life cycle.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在数字破坏时代，组织面临着不懈的压力，以更快地交付价值，减少上市时间并超出用户期望。敏捷方法论是对这些挑战的回应，促进了灵活性，协作和连续交付。但是，没有质量的敏捷性是技术债务，客户不满和效率低下的秘诀。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那就是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/bolstering-qualtering-qualtering-quality-eentering-with-no-code-and-lo”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Q &lt;strong&gt; Q &lt;&gt; Q &lt;&gt; Q &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;gront&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;（&lt;strong&gt; QE QE &lt;/qe QE &lt;/qe &lt;/qe Qe &lt;/qe &lt;/qe）循环。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Smart-Doc: Generating gRPC API Documentation in Java Projects】Smart-Doc：在Java项目中生成GRPC API文档</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/smart-doc-generate-grpc-api-docs-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Foreword&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In modern Java microservices, gRPC simplifies inter-service communication with its efficient binary protocol and multi-language support. However, maintaining gRPC API documentation can be challenging as projects grow. Among various AI tools, &lt;strong&gt;smart-doc&lt;/strong&gt; stands out as the optimal solution for generating gRPC API documentation in Java projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Advantages of Smart-Doc in Java Projects&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Fast Speed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-smart-doc-to-generate-jmeter-test-scripts&#34;&gt;Smart-doc&lt;/a&gt; is designed to quickly scan code and generate documentation without additional runtime dependencies. It directly extracts &lt;span spellcheck=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;.proto&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/span&gt; files, compiles them into Java code using &lt;span spellcheck=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;protoc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, and then generates documentation by parsing the Java code and comments. This process is much faster than AI tools.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt;前言&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在现代Java微服务中，GRPC用其有效的二进制协议和多语言支持简化了服务间通信。但是，随着项目的增长，维护GRPC API文档可能会具有挑战性。在各种AI工具中，&lt;strong&gt; smart-doc &lt;/strong&gt;是在Java项目中生成GRPC API文档的最佳解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Java项目中Smart-Doc的优势&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3&gt; 1。 &lt;strong&gt;快速&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-smart-doc-to-to-generate-jmeter-test-scripts”&gt; smart-doc &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;旨在快速扫描代码并生成文档，而无需额外的运行时间依赖。它直接提取&lt;span spellCheck =“ false”&gt; &lt;code&gt; .proto &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/span&gt;文件，使用&lt;span spellCheck =“ false”&gt; &lt;code&gt; protoc &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/span&gt;将它们编译为Java代码，然后通过分析Java代码和注释来生成文档。这个过程比AI工具快得多。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Test Pyramid: Test Setup Best Practices】测试金字塔：测试设置最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/test-pyramid-test-setup-best-practices</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Testing our code is essential for maintaining the high quality of our code. In the long term, tests are crucial to ensure that we have maintainable software at all. &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Today, I will dive into the &lt;strong&gt;Test Pyramid&lt;/strong&gt; and present a way to structure your tests to get the most out of them.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a revisited and revamped version of my original article on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rest-apis-test-pyramid&#34;&gt;Test Pyramid&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;测试我们的代码对于维持高质量的代码至关重要。从长远来看，测试对于确保我们完全具有可维护的软件至关重要。 &lt;span style =“ margin：0px; padding：0px;“&gt;今天，我将潜入&lt;strong&gt;测试金字塔&lt;/strong&gt;，并提出一种构造测试以充分利用它们的方法。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是我在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/rest-apis-test-pyramid”&gt;测试Pyramid &lt;/a&gt;上的原始文章的重新审视和修改版本。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【CI/CD at Scale: Smarter Pipelines for Monorepo Mayhem】CI/CD大规模：Monorepo Mayhem的智能管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ci-cd-at-scale-smarter-pipelines-for-monorepos</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Have you ever looked at a large monorepo and thought to yourself, “How the heck am I going to CI/CD this?”. If so, you are not alone. I’ve been there — navigating an endless sea of services, shared libraries, and deploy targets. And eventually, with the right techniques and tools, CI/CD became less of a monster and more of a machine.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Let me share my journey from foundational concepts to being production-ready, so that you can optimize your pipelines and pick up one or two things you hadn’t thought of before.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您是否曾经看过一个大的Monorepo，想着自己：“我该怎么到CI/CD这个？”。如果是这样，您并不孤单。我去过那里 - 导航无尽的服务海洋，共享图书馆和部署目标。最终，借助正确的技术和工具，CI/CD变得越来越不像是怪物，而是一台机器。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;让我分享我从基础概念到准备生产的旅程，以便您可以优化管道并挑选以前从未想过的一两件事。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Configuring Embedded Global Cache for App Connect Enterprise Running in Containers】为在容器中运行的App Connect Enterprise配置嵌入式全局缓存</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/configuring-embedded-global-cache-for-app-connect</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With the release of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-ibm-app-connect-enterprise-120120&#34;&gt;App Connect Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; 13.0.3.0, the new Embedded Global Cache has been introduced as a replacement for the older WebSphere eXtreme Scale (WXS) embedded cache, now referred to as the &lt;em&gt;Embedded WXS grid&lt;/em&gt;. As outlined in the product’s statement of direction, the Embedded WXS grid is now deprecated, though it will remain functional as long as Java 8 continues to be supported in ACE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Similar to its predecessor, the Embedded Global Cache allows you to store and reuse data across the same integration flow, between different flows, or even across multiple integration servers—removing the need for alternative persistence solutions like databases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;With the release of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-ibm-app-connect-enterprise-120120&#34;&gt;App Connect Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; 13.0.3.0, the new Embedded Global Cache has been introduced as a replacement for the older WebSphere eXtreme Scale (WXS) embedded cache, now referred to as the &lt;em&gt;嵌入式WXS网格&lt;/em&gt;。如产品的指示声明中概述的那样，嵌入的WXS网格现在已弃用，尽管只要Java 8继续在ACE中支持Java 8，它将保持功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;类似于其前身，嵌入式的全局缓存允许您在相同的集成流，不同流之间甚至跨多个集成服务器之间存储和重复使用数据，从而消除了诸如数据库之类的替代持久解决方案的需求。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unity Catalog + AI: How Databricks Is Making Data Governance AI-Native in 2025】Unity目录 + AI：Databricks如何在2025年制作数据治理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unity-catalog-ai-databricks-data-governance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The cross-section of artificial intelligence and data governance has come to a defining moment in 2025, but Databricks is taking the lead here. As AI technologies and enterprise data ecosystems evolve rapidly, and the ecosystems themselves become more complex, traditional governance models seem to be incapable of meeting the new requirements.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Databricks has reacted to this by bringing AI natively into &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/automate-databricks-unity-catalog-permissions&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unity Catalog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; — its unified layer for governance — changing how organizations manage, secure, and gain value from data. This integration is a major paradigm shift in data governance from reactive and human-based to proactive, intelligent, and scalable systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;人工智能和数据治理的横截面在2025年取得了决定性的时刻，但Databricks在这里领导着。随着AI技术和企业数据生态系统的发展迅速，生态系统本身变得更加复杂，传统的治理模型似乎无法满足新要求。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Databricks has reacted to this by bringing AI natively into &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/automate-databricks-unity-catalog-permissions&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unity Catalog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; — its unified layer for governance — changing how organizations manage, secure, and gain value from data.这种集成是数据治理从反应性和基于人类的，主动，智能和可扩展系统的主要范式转变。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Modern Data Projects Need Agile Thinking — Not Just Tech】现代数据项目需要敏捷的思考 - 不仅仅是技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-management-project</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Data is an asset. Like software code, it is a valuable organizational resource that must be stored, protected, governed, and leveraged. It retains value over time, drives insights, and requires strong governance. As organizations pivot toward data-driven decision-making, engineering teams and project managers accustomed to software development are finding themselves at the helm of data projects, facing unfamiliar territory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article outlines common points of failure and challenges that Data Project managers and engineering teams face when transitioning from traditional software engineering to leading Agile data projects. It demonstrates how Agile principles can help navigate and mitigate these challenges.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;数据是资产。像软件代码一样，它是必须存储，保护，控制和利用的宝贵组织资源。它会随着时间的流逝保留价值，推动见解并需要强大的治理。随着组织转向数据驱动的决策，习惯于软件开发的工程团队和项目经理正遇到数据项目的领导，面临着陌生的领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;本文概述了数据经理和工程团队从传统软件工程转换为领先的敏捷数据项目时面临的共同失败点和挑战。它展示了敏捷原则如何帮助导航和缓解这些挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>