<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Practical Use of Weak Symbols】弱符号的实际使用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/practical-use-of-weak-symbols</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In today&#39;s software development, flexibility, maintainability, and performance are paramount, especially in systems software programming, embedded systems development, and library design. A lesser-known technique, yet a powerful tool to achieve these goals, is the weak symbol. For developers building frameworks and platform libraries, weak symbols provide a clean way to define default behaviors and enable optional functionality — all without complex build configurations or runtime hacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Let’s explore what weak symbols are, how they work, and where they can unlock better architecture patterns.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在当今的软件开发中，灵活性，可维护性和性能至关重要，尤其是在系统软件编程，嵌入式系统开发和库设计中。一种鲜为人知的技术，是实现这些目标的强大工具，是薄弱的符号。对于开发人员构建框架和平台库，弱符号为定义默认行为和启用可选功能提供了一种干净的方法 - 所有这些都没有复杂的构建配置或运行时骇客。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;让我们探索什么是弱符号，它们的工作方式以及它们可以解锁更好的体系结构模式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Lessons from Migrating an Oracle Database to AWS RDS】从迁移Oracle数据库到AWS RDS的教训</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/migrating-oracle-db-to-aws-rds</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;After nearly a decade of managing our on-premise database infrastructure, our team finally took the plunge into cloud database services with AWS RDS. The migration journey came with its share of surprises — both pleasant and challenging. Here&#39;s what I discovered during our transition to AWS RDS managed services, along with key insights that might help your organization make informed decisions about your own database strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I still remember the morning my boss walked into our weekly team meeting and dropped the bomb: &#34;We&#39;re finally moving our databases to the cloud.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在管理我们的本地数据库基础架构的近十年之后，我们的团队终于使用AWS RDS登上了云数据库服务。迁移之旅带来了令人惊讶的，既令人愉悦又具有挑战性。这是我在过渡到AWS RDS托管服务的过程中发现的内容，以及可能帮助您的组织做出明智决定的有关数据库策略的明智决定的关键见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我仍然记得我的老板进入我们每周的团队会议并放下炸弹：“我们终于将数据库移至云。” &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS CloudTrail Monitoring Using Event-Driven Ansible】AWS CloudTrail使用事件驱动的Ansible监视</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cloudtrail-event-driven-ansible</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AWS CloudTrail is a service that tracks everything happening in your AWS environment. It makes it easier to track activities like unauthorized access, configuration changes, or unusual behavior. It also supports compliance and auditing by maintaining a clear history of activity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When we integrate CloudTrail with Event-Driven Ansible, we can automatically respond to these events in real time without manual intervention. This integration turns monitoring into action, helping teams keep their cloud systems secure, reliable, and easier to manage as they scale.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; AWS CloudTrail是一项跟踪AWS环境中发生的一切的服务。它使跟踪未经授权访问，配置更改或异常行为等活动变得更加容易。它还通过保持清晰的活动历史来支持合规性和审计。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们将CloudTrail与事件驱动的Ansible集成时，我们可以无需手动干预即可自动对这些事件进行响应。这种集成将监视变为行动，帮助团队确保其云系统的安全，可靠和易于管理。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Generative AI Needs Human Oversight to Build Trust】为什么生成的AI需要人类的监督才能建立信任</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-human-oversight-trust</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In 2023, a generative AI-powered chatbot for a financial firm mistakenly gave investment advice that violated compliance regulations, triggering regulatory scrutiny. Around the same time, an AI-powered medical summary tool misrepresented patient conditions, raising serious ethical concerns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As businesses rapidly adopt generative AI (GenAI), these incidents highlight a critical question: &lt;em&gt;Can AI-generated content be trusted without human oversight?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt; 2023年，一家为金融公司的生成性AI驱动的聊天机器人错误地提供了违反合规法规的投资建议，从而触发了监管审查。大约在同一时间，AI驱动的医疗摘要工具错误陈述了患者状况，引起了严重的道德问题。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;随着企业迅速采用生成AI（Genai），这些事件突出了一个关键的问题：&lt;em&gt;可以在没有人类监督的情况下信任AI生成的内容？&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Create Your Own AI-Powered Virtual Tutor: An Easy Tutorial】创建自己的AI驱动的虚拟导师：简单的教程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/create-ai-powered-virtual-tutor-tutorial</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;It is a very powerful world with AI being a thing. Now you can have a tutor who never gets tired, who doesn’t roll their eyes at your dumb questions (we all have them, I do admit it), and who is available 24/7 — no scheduling problems, no coffee breaks, just straight knowledge on demand. That’s the magic of AI-based tutors. But before we start dreaming about how AI could replace your least favorite professors, let’s first discuss how to build one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As someone who has tinkered with AI models for countless hours (and broken them here and there), I have been somewhat obsessed with the notion of an AI tutor. In this guide, I’m going to take you through the main components needed to build one for yourself — from natural language processing (NLP) to knowledge graphs and adaptive learning models. No, this is not a plug-and-play recipe, though it will provide you with a strong road map for your path.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这是一个非常强大的世界，AI是事物。现在，您可以有一个永远不会累的导师，他们不会对您的愚蠢问题（我们都有，我都承认），并且24/7全天候可以使用 - 没有时间安排问题，没有咖啡休息，只是按需直接的知识。那就是基于AI的导师的魔力。但是，在我们开始梦想AI如何取代您最不喜欢的教授之前，让我们首先讨论如何建立一个。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;作为一个用无数小时修补AI模型的人（在这里和那里打破了它们），我对AI导师的概念有些痴迷。在本指南中，我将带您完成为自己建立一个的主要组件 - 从自然语言处理（NLP）到知识图和自适应学习模型。不，这不是插件食谱，尽管它将为您提供强大的路线图。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Protection: Securing The New Attack Frontier】AI保护：确保新的攻击边界</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-protection-securing-the-new-attack-frontier</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;We’re amidst a paradigm shift in society where many product verticals are being reimagined through an ‘AI-first’ architecture. An AI-first architecture is one where much of the core business logic is driven by AI, and the product is architected to fully exploit the capabilities of the underlying AI models. A striking example is IDEs; intelligent editors such as Cursor have quickly gained popularity in the software community. Countless startups have emerged to challenge well-established experiences (email, online shopping, real estate, to name a few) with AI-first alternatives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This promises not only an exciting future but also a more dangerous one. Traditional attack paths are outmoded under the new regime of AI-centric architectures. In this article, we discuss novel attack paradigms that AI-first architectures are vulnerable to and how companies operating in this space can defend against them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在社会的范式转变中，我们正在通过“ AI-First”架构重新构想许多产品垂直行业。 AI-First Architecture是大部分核心业务逻辑由AI驱动的体系结构，并且该产品的架构是完全利用基础AI模型的功能。一个引人注目的例子是IDE；诸如光标之类的智能编辑很快就在软件社区中广受欢迎。已经出现了无数的初创公司，以挑战拥有良好的经验（电子邮件，在线购物，房地产，仅举几例）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这不仅有望令人兴奋的未来，而且承诺了一个更危险的未来。在以AI为中心的建筑的新制度下，传统的攻击路径已过时。在本文中，我们讨论了AI-First Architectures容易受到攻击以及在该领域的公司如何抵制它们的新颖攻击范式。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maintaining ML Model Accuracy With Automated Drift Detection】通过自动漂移检测保持ML模型精度</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ml-model-accuracy-automated-drift-detection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In production machine learning (ML) systems, data drift is defined as changes in the statistical features of input data over time. Such shifts can weaken model performance, resulting in erroneous predictions. As a result, monitoring and mitigating data drift is critical for maintaining the trustworthiness of machine learning models.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;KitOps is an open-source DevOps solution for packaging and versioning AI/ML models, datasets, code, and configurations into a reproducible artifact known as a ModelKit. By standardizing these components, KitOps enables the seamless integration of drift detection and management into MLOps workflows, improving collaboration among data scientists, developers, and operations teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在生产机器学习（ML）系统中，数据漂移定义为随着时间的推移输入数据的统计特征的变化。这种转移会削弱模型性能，从而导致错误的预测。结果，监视和缓解数据漂移对于维持机器学习模型的可信度至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; Kitops是一种开放式DEVOPS解决方案，用于包装和版本化AI/ML模型，数据集，代码和配置，以可重复的伪像被称为Modelskit。通过标准化这些组件，Kitops可以将漂移检测和管理的无缝集成到MLOPS工作流程中，从而改善了数据科学家，开发人员和运营团队之间的协作。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Engineer to Leader: Scaling Impact Beyond Code】从工程师到领导者：超越代码的扩展影响</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-impact-beyond-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Back in college, I thought that technical excellence was everything. But after a decade in the tech industry, I&#39;ve learned that leadership requires a completely different mindset. One day you&#39;re sitting there writing code and shipping features, and suddenly you&#39;re making project plans, helping your teammates, and thinking about the bigger picture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Moving from being an IC to a tech lead can feel like a big and uncomfortable jump. Let me share what I&#39;ve learned about growing beyond just coding through some real examples from my journey.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;回到大学，我认为技术卓越就是一切。但是在技术行业十年后，我了解到领导力需要完全不同的心态。有一天，您坐在那里写代码和运输功能，突然间，您正在制定项目计划，帮助队友并考虑更大的情况。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;从成为IC转变为技术领导可能会感觉像是一个大而不舒服的跳跃。让我分享我所学到的关于成长的知识，而不仅仅是通过我的旅程中的一些真实示例编码。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Efficiently Migrating From Jest to Vitest in a Next.js Project】在下一个项目中有效地从开玩笑迁移到vitest</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/migrating-jest-to-vitest-nextjs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Vitest is a state-of-the-art testing framework that was created to solve problems encountered with older testing frameworks such as Jest. It&#39;s designed to be faster and leaner, with a tidier API, and more importantly, to be more efficient with projects that use modern JavaScript features and toolchains.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Was Vitest Invented?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vitest was created to offer a new spin on testing JavaScript. Light and lightning-fast, it focuses on performance and modern JavaScript features, such as ES modules. Unlike Jest, Vitest is built with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/next-generation-front-end-tooling-vite&#34;&gt;Vite, a modern front-end build tool&lt;/a&gt;, which means it can exploit ES modules (and other shiny new things) to initialize and run tests much more quickly.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; vitest是一种最新的测试框架，是为了解决诸如jest之类的旧测试框架遇到的问题。它的设计速度更快，更苗条，具有更整洁的API，更重要的是，使用现代JavaScript功能和工具链更有效。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么发明了Vitest？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Vitest的创建是为了在测试JavaScript上提供新的旋转。光线和闪电般的速度侧重于性能和现代JavaScript功能，例如ES模块。与开玩笑不同，Vitest是用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/next-generation-front-end-tooling-vite-vite”&gt; vite的，这是一种现代的前端构建工具&lt;/a&gt;，这意味着它可以快速地利用ES模块（以及其他闪亮的新事物）来快速地进行初始化和运行。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Seamless Security Integration Strategies in Software Development】软件开发中的无缝安全集成策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/security-integration-software-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;During the software development, builders face challenges between building a better product faster versus dealing with various responsibilities that come with software development. Getting security right is one of them. Due to the increased cyber attacks, organizations started focusing on security, which resulted in developers spending more time in security-related activities in recent years.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This brings up the critical need for integrating security practices in the software in the early stage instead of making security an afterthought. Integrating security practices early and more often will not only reduce the cost but also be more effective. In this article, we will talk about how we can achieve that.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在软件开发过程中，建筑商在更快地构建更好的产品与处理软件开发所带来的各种职责之间面临挑战。正确的安全是其中之一。由于网络攻击的增加，组织开始专注于安全性，这导致开发人员近年来在与安全有关的活动中花费更多的时间。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这提出了在早期阶段将安全实践集成到软件中的关键需求，而不是事后才想到安全性。尽早整合安全惯例，不仅会降低成本，而且会更有效。在本文中，我们将讨论如何实现这一目标。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>