<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Fluent Bit: Installing Fluent Bit From Source (Part 1)】掌握流利位：从源安装流利位（第1部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/install-fluent-bit-from-source</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This series is a general-purpose getting-started guide for those who want to learn about the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) project Fluent Bit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each article in this series addresses a single topic by providing insights into &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; the topic is, &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; we are interested in exploring that topic, &lt;em&gt;where&lt;/em&gt; to get started with the topic, and &lt;em&gt;how&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;to get hands on with learning about the topic as it relates to the Fluent Bit project.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本系列是想要了解云本机计算基础（CNCF）项目Fluent Fluent lit的通用指南。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本系列中的每篇文章都通过向&lt;em&gt;提供洞察力来解决一个主题。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Vision AI on Apple Silicon: A Practical Guide to MLX-VLM】Apple Silicon的Vision AI：MLX-VLM的实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vision-ai-apple-silicon-guide-mlx-vlm</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Vision AI models have traditionally required significant computational resources and complex setups to run effectively. However, with Apple&#39;s MLX framework and the emergence of efficient vision-language models, Mac users can now harness the power of advanced AI vision capabilities right on their machines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, we&#39;ll explore how to implement &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/model-drift-in-computer-vision-models-understandin&#34;&gt;vision models&lt;/a&gt; using MLX-VLM, a library that leverages Apple&#39;s native Metal framework for optimal performance on Apple Silicon.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;视觉AI模型传统上需要大量的计算资源和复杂的设置才能有效运行。但是，随着Apple的MLX框架和有效的视觉语言模型的出现，Mac用户现在可以利用其机器上的先进AI视觉功能的功能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本教程中，我们将探讨如何实现&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/model-drift-drift-in-computer-vision-models-understandin一下”&gt; Vision Models &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;使用Mlx-vlm，该图书馆是一个利用Apple Apple Apple Apple Metal Metal Metal Fresporwork On Apple Apple Silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silic silicson。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docs That Write Themselves: Scaling With gRPC and Protobuf】写自己的文档：用grpc和protobuf缩放</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/grpc-and-docs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;413&#34; data-start=&#34;340&#34;&gt;In this article, we’ll explore how gRPC and code generation can help you:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;470&#34; data-start=&#34;416&#34;&gt;Write documentation that people actually read and use,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;521&#34; data-start=&#34;473&#34;&gt;Standardize communication between microservices,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end=&#34;563&#34; data-start=&#34;524&#34;&gt;Avoid code duplication across services.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;754&#34; data-start=&#34;565&#34;&gt;Nowadays, many developers are already familiar with gRPC. It’s no longer surprising that service-related teams prefer it for inter-service communication and even for documentation purposes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 413” data-start =“ 340”&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨GRPC和代码生成如何帮助您：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 470” data-start =“ 416”&gt;写文档，人们实际阅读和使用，&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 521” data-start =“ 473”&gt;标准化微服务之间的通信，&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li data-end =“ 563” data-start =“ 524”&gt;避免跨服务重复代码。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 754” data-start =“ 565”&gt;如今，许多开发人员已经熟悉GRPC。与服务相关的团队更喜欢使用服务间交流，甚至用于文档目的，这也就不足为奇了。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is the Model Context Protocol a Replacement for HTTP?】模型上下文协议是否替代了HTTP？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/model-context-protocol-vs-http</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;645&#34; data-start=&#34;357&#34;&gt;With the rise of AI-native applications and agentic systems, a community of developers is being introduced to new techniques, abstractions, and architectural patterns that didn’t exist a few years ago. One term gaining traction — especially in the LLM and Generative AI ecosystem — is the &lt;strong data-end=&#34;644&#34; data-start=&#34;612&#34;&gt;Model Context Protocol&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;694&#34; data-start=&#34;647&#34;&gt;With its rise and attention, it&#39;s also generating confusion and raising the following question:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 645” data-start =“ 357”&gt;随着AI本地应用程序和代理系统的兴起，开发人员社区被引入了几年前不存在的新技术，抽象和建筑模式。一个术语获得吸引力，尤其是在LLM和生成AI生态系统中 - 是&lt;strong data-end =“ 644” data-start =“ 612”&gt;模型上下文上下文协议&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 694” data-start =“ 647”&gt;随着其上升和关注，它也会引起混乱并提出以下问题：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering React App Configuration With Webpack】使用WebPack掌握React App配置</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-react-app-configuration-with-webpack</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Developers who rely on tools like Create React App may not have had direct experience with Webpack. However, configuring Webpack manually provides valuable insight into the underlying mechanics of how modern web applications are built and bundled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide offers a step-by-step walkthrough for setting up a React application with Webpack from scratch, complete with clear and detailed explanations.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;依靠诸如Create React App之类的工具的开发人员可能没有对WebPack的直接经验。但是，手动配置WebPack可以对现代Web应用程序的构建和捆绑的潜在机制提供宝贵的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南提供了一个分步演练，可通过从头开始使用WebPack设置React应用程序，并提供清晰而详细的说明。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Distributed Systems 101】分布式系统101</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/distributed-systems-101</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;335&#34; data-start=&#34;118&#34;&gt;Distributed systems are all around us: Facebook, Uber, Revolut — even the Google search engine is one of them. One search in Google can trigger tens (or hundreds) of calls to different microservices owned by Google.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;558&#34; data-start=&#34;337&#34;&gt;What is more, they are the core of what we work with: multiple services working together, or maybe a database, or just a service or two with some cache layer, or even some service that connects via an async message queue.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 335” data-start =“ 118”&gt;分布式系统遍布我们：Facebook，Uber，Revolut  - 甚至Google搜索引擎也是其中之一。 Google中的一次搜索可以触发数十个（或数百个）的电话，以触发Google拥有的不同微服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 558” data-start =“ 337”&gt;更重要的是，它们是我们使用的工作的核心：多个服务，或者是数据库，或者只是一个或两个带有缓存层的服务，甚至是通过异步消息队列连接的一些服务，</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Gemma 3: Unlocking GenAI Potential Using Docker Model Runner】Gemma 3：使用Docker Model Runner解锁Genai电位</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unlock-genai-potential-gemma-3-docker</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;612&#34; data-start=&#34;216&#34;&gt;The demand for fully local GenAI development is growing — and for good reason. Running large language models (LLMs) on your own infrastructure ensures privacy, flexibility, and cost-efficiency. With the release of &lt;strong data-end=&#34;439&#34; data-start=&#34;428&#34;&gt;Gemma 3&lt;/strong&gt; and its seamless integration with &lt;strong data-end=&#34;497&#34; data-start=&#34;474&#34;&gt;Docker Model Runner&lt;/strong&gt;, developers now have the power to experiment, fine-tune, and deploy GenAI models entirely on their local machines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;803&#34; data-start=&#34;614&#34;&gt;In this Blog, we’ll explore how you can set up and run Gemma 3 locally using Docker, unlocking a streamlined GenAI development workflow without relying on cloud-based inference services.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 612” data-start =“ 216”&gt;对完全局部Genai开发的需求正在增长，这是有充分理由的。在您自己的基础架构上运行大型语言模型（LLM）可确保隐私，灵活性和成本效益。随着&lt;strong data-end =“ 439” data-start =“ 428”&gt; gemma 3 &lt;/strong&gt;的发布，与&lt;strong data-end =“ 497” data-data-start =“ 474”&gt; docker Model Runner &lt;/strong&gt;的无缝集成&lt;/strong&gt;，开发人员现在有能力进行实验，the the genai Models On locune Models on local Models on local Machines instally Machines instally Machines instally Machines installine Machines inter Machines inter Machines nastery Machines &lt;/P&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 803” data-start =“ 614”&gt;在此博客中，我们将探索如何在本地使用Docker在本地设置和运行Gemma 3，从而在不依赖基于云的推销服务的情况下解锁精简的Genai开发工作流程。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why I Built the Ultimate Text Comparison Tool (And Why You Should Try It)】为什么我构建了最终的文本比较工具（以及为什么要尝试）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-i-built-the-ultimate-text-comparison-tool</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve spent years working with messy data, and one problem kept showing up across every project and industry: comparing text that &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; match but doesn&#39;t. Customer names with typos, product descriptions with inconsistent formatting, and addresses with different abbreviation styles. You know the frustration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After trying every solution on the market and finding them all lacking in some critical way, I built my own &lt;a href=&#34;https://likegeeks.com/compare-two-lists/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;list comparison tool&lt;/a&gt; that combines everything I needed in one place. The results have been nothing short of transformative for my work, and I&#39;m excited to share it with fellow data professionals who face the same challenges.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我已经花了多年的时间处理杂乱的数据，并且一个问题在每个项目和行业中都不断出现：比较&lt;em&gt;应该&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;匹配但没有的文本。带有错别字的客户名称，格式不一致的产品描述以及具有不同缩写样式的地址。你知道挫败感。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尝试了市场上的所有解决方案并发现它们都以某种关键的方式缺乏，我构建了自己的&lt;a href =“ https://likegeeks.com/compare-two-lists/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;列表比较工具&lt;/a&gt;将所有东西都组合在一起，我需要一个地方。结果对我的工作来说是不可变的，我很高兴与面对同样挑战的数据专业人士分享。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero Trust Isn&#39;t Just for Networks: Applying Zero-Trust Principles to CI/CD Pipelines】零信任不仅针对网络：将零信任原则应用于CI/CD管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trust-ci-cd-pipeline-principles</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Zero trust has emerged as a cornerstone of modern enterprise security. It is mainly applied to networks, user identities, and endpoints of most organizations. However, the single layer left undersecured is the CI/CD pipeline. These systems orchestrate code validation for production deployment and do so with persistent credentials and system privileges. This contradiction is fundamentally inconsistent with the rest of the zero-trust model, in which, by default, there should be no trust in any service, identity, or connection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But in our environment, we realized that our pipelines had been quietly left out of security scrutiny. Jobs had long-lived secrets, and build containers were reused. The amount of access reached a level beyond what should be expected for any single job. We recognized these risks, and so we deemed that our pipelines should be treated as untrusted by default. This decision radically altered how we would approach automation and access.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;零信任已成为现代企业安全的基石。它主要应用于大多数组织的网络，用户身份和端点。但是，剩下的单层是CI/CD管道。这些系统协调生产部署的代码验证，并具有持久的凭据和系统特权。这一矛盾在根本上与零值模型的其余部分不一致，默认情况下，任何服务，身份或连接都不应有信任。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;，但是在我们的环境中，我们意识到我们的管道已被静静地排除在安全审查之外。乔布斯拥有长期的秘密，并重新使用了构建容器。访问量达到了一个水平，超出了任何一份工作的期望。我们认识到这些风险，因此我们认为我们的管道应被视为默认情况下不信任。该决定从根本上改变了我们将如何进行自动化和访问。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Hidden Breach: Secrets Leaked Outside the Codebase Pose a Serious Threat】隐藏的违规：在代码库外泄漏的秘密构成了严重的威胁</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secrets-leaked-outside-codebase-security-threat</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When you think of secrets scanning, most people immediately think about source code repositories on platforms like GitHub, GitLab, and Bitbucket. While the codebase is a source you absolutely should monitor, this is just a part of the overall secrets security story.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, secrets leaking in code are a major concern. In the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gitguardian.com/files/the-state-of-secrets-sprawl-report-2025?ref=blog.gitguardian.com&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;GitGuardian’s 2025 &lt;em&gt;State of Secrets Sprawl Report&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the scale of this issue has surged dramatically. In 2024 alone, over &lt;strong&gt;23.7 million new hardcoded secrets&lt;/strong&gt; were added to public GitHub repositories — a &lt;strong&gt;25% increase&lt;/strong&gt; from the year before. And that’s just GitHub.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当您想到秘密扫描时，大多数人会立即考虑Github，Gitlab和Bitbucket等平台上的源代码存储库。虽然代码库是您绝对应该监视的来源，但这只是整体秘密安全故事的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;的确，秘密泄漏的秘密是一个主要问题。在&lt;a a href =“ https://www.gitguardian.com/files/the-state-of-secrets-screts-sprawl-report-2025? ref=blog.gitguardian.com”中急剧激增。仅在2024年，&lt;strong&gt;超过2370万个新的硬编码秘密&lt;/strong&gt;就被添加到公共GitHub存储库中 -  &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 25％的增长&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;。那只是github。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>