<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Custom Elements Manifest: The Key To Seamless Web Component Discovery and Documentation】自定义元素清单：无缝 Web 组件发现和文档记录的关键</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/custom-elements-manifest-web-component-discovery</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Even though &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/introduction-to-web-components-and-polymer&#34;&gt;Web Components &lt;/a&gt;have been the talk of being a necessity for developers to create reusable and encapsulated UI components for web applications, in totality, developers can&#39;t embrace it entirely due to the issues around tooling and integration. This is where the Custom Elements Manifest (CEM) comes in: a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-json&#34;&gt;JSON&lt;/a&gt; format that provides structured metadata for Web Components. CEM wishes to make it all simpler, from development to discovery, documentation, and integration within IDEs, making a much smoother developer experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, let&#39;s dig deep into how Custom Elements Manifest works, why it is a game-changer for the development of web components, and how it can power modern tools. We will also see various cases that elucidate how CEM helps enhance the experience for both developers and users.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;尽管&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/introduction-to-web-components-and-polymer&#34;&gt;Web 组件&lt;/a&gt;一直是人们谈论的话题开发人员必须为 Web 应用程序创建可重用且封装的 UI 组件，但总的来说，由于工具和集成方面的问题，开发人员无法完全接受它。这就是自定义元素清单 (CEM) 的用武之地：一种 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-json&#34;&gt;JSON&lt;/a&gt; 格式，为 Web 组件提供结构化元数据。 CEM 希望让一切变得更简单，从开发到发现、文档以及 IDE 内的集成，从而提供更流畅的开发人员体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将深入探讨 Custom Elements Manifest 的工作原理、为什么它会改变 Web 组件开发的游戏规则，以及它如何为现代工具提供支持。我们还将看到各种案例来阐明 CEM 如何帮助增强开发人员和用户的体验。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud Build Unleashed: Expert Techniques for CI/CD Optimization】释放云构建：CI/CD 优化的专家技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimize-cicd-with-cloud-build</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;CI/CD and Its Importance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;We all know &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-ci-cd&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;what CI/CD is&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; and how it fosters&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;a sense of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;collaboration among teams and enables them to deliver high-quality software efficiently and reliably. By automating the integration,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/testing-in-cicd&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; testing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;, and deployment processes, CI/CD helps maintain code quality, reduce manual effort, and provide continuous feedback, ultimately leading to faster and more reliable software delivery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;CI/CD is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;for the following reasons:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;CI/CD 及其重要性&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;我们都知道&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-ci-cd&#34;&gt;&lt;span data- keepr-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;什么是 CI/CD&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; 以及它如何促进&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34; true&#34;&gt;团队之间的协作感&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;让他们能够高效、可靠地交付高质量的软件。通过自动化集成，&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/testing-in-cicd&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;测试&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/ a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;以及部署流程，CI/CD 有助于维护代码质量、减少手动工作并提供持续反馈，最终实现更快、更可靠的软件交付。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;CI/CD &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;重要&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true &#34;&gt;出于以下原因：&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Security Solution for US Federal Customers】为美国联邦客户提供的数据安全解决方案</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-security-solution-for-us-federal-customers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Federal agencies manage highly classified sensitive data, including personal information, medical records, and tax and income details of all U.S. residents. In some cases, temporary visitor data are also retained. They also handle national security information, including susceptible documents, intergovernmental communication details, and document decisions that could impact the safety of the country. The purpose of this article is to walk you through various regulations as a developer that you should know about while developing security software specifically for federal agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All government agencies in the U.S. are required to comply with strict data regulations specified in the Federal Information Security Management Act (FISMA) and the Federal Risk and Authorization Management Program (FedRAMP). Developers, who design and implement data security solutions for federal customers, should ensure that the solutions help address compliance requirements. Let’s explore these requirements in some detail.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;联邦机构管理高度机密的敏感数据，包括所有美国居民的个人信息、医疗记录以及税收和收入详细信息。在某些情况下，还会保留临时访客数据。他们还处理国家安全信息，包括易受影响的文件、政府间通信细节以及可能影响国家安全的文件决策。本文的目的是引导您了解作为开发人员在专门为联邦机构开发安全软件时应该了解的各种法规。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;美国所有政府机构都必须遵守《联邦信息安全管理法案》(FISMA) 和《联邦风险与授权管理计划》(FedRAMP) 中规定的严格数据法规。为联邦客户设计和实施数据安全解决方案的开发人员应确保该解决方案有助于满足合规性要求。让我们更详细地探讨这些要求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Decide Between Relational and Non-Relational Databases for the Project】如何为项目选择关系数据库和非关系数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-decide-between-relational-and-non-relational-dbs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;How do you approach data processing? What aspects are worth special consideration? Find the difference between relational vs non-relational databases to make informed decisions and learn how to choose a database regarding your project needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is a Relational vs Non-Relational Database?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s obviously the first question to address when choosing a database for your project. Knowing the difference between relational vs non-relational databases helps to be more specific with your requirements and leverage the right solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您如何进行数据处理？哪些方面值得特别考虑？找出关系数据库与非关系数据库之间的差异，以做出明智的决策，并了解如何根据您的项目需求选择数据库。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是关系数据库与非关系数据库？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这显然是为您的项目选择数据库时要解决的第一个问题。了解关系数据库与非关系数据库之间的区别有助于更具体地满足您的需求并利用正确的解决方案。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Secure AI LLM APIs: A DevOps Approach To Preventing Data Breaches】构建安全的 AI LLM API：防止数据泄露的 DevOps 方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-secure-ai-llm-apis-a-devops-approach</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As artificial intelligence (AI) continues to evolve, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; have become increasingly prevalent in various industries, from healthcare to finance. However, with their growing use comes the critical responsibility of securing the APIs that allow these models to interact with external systems. A DevOps approach is crucial in designing and implementing &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/api-security-patterns&#34;&gt;secure APIs&lt;/a&gt; for AI LLMs, ensuring that sensitive data is protected against potential breaches. This article delves into the best practices for creating secure AI LLM APIs and explores the vital role of DevOps in preventing data breaches.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Understanding the Importance of API Security in AI LLMs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;APIs are the backbone of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/software-architecture-quality-attributes&#34;&gt;modern software architecture&lt;/a&gt;, enabling seamless communication between different systems. When it comes to AI LLMs, these APIs facilitate the transfer of vast amounts of data, including potentially sensitive information. According to a report by Gartner, 90% of web applications will be more vulnerable to API attacks by 2024, highlighting the growing risk associated with poorly secured APIs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着人工智能 (AI) 的不断发展，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 ( LLM）&lt;/a&gt;在从医疗保健到金融的各个行业中变得越来越普遍。然而，随着它们的使用不断增加，保护允许这些模型与外部系统交互的 API 的安全也成为了一项重要责任。 DevOps 方法对于为 AI LLM 设计和实施&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/api-security-patterns&#34;&gt;安全 API&lt;/a&gt; 至关重要，确保敏感数据免受潜在泄露。本文深入探讨了创建安全 AI LLM API 的最佳实践，并探讨了 DevOps 在防止数据泄露方面的重要作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;了解 API 安全性在 AI LLM 中的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;API 是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/software-architecture-quality-attributes&#34;&gt;现代软件架构&lt;/a&gt;的支柱，可实现不同软件之间的无缝通信系统。对于 AI LLM，这些 API 有助于传输大量数据，包括潜在的敏感信息。根据 Gartner 的一份报告，到 2024 年，90% 的 Web 应用程序将更容易受到 API 攻击，这凸显了与安全性较差的 API 相关的风险日益增加。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transformed Meets the Scrum Guide】转型符合 Scrum 指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/transformed-meets-the-scrum-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Transformed and Scrum&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite criticism from the product community regarding Scrum as a framework for effective product creation, namely Marty Cagan himself, I believe that it is worthwhile to compare the principles that help form successful product teams with those of Scrum. Let’s delve into an analysis of “Transformed” and how its principles align with Scrum’s.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Matching Transformed’s Product Success Principles with Scrum Principles&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last week, Paweł Huryn summarized the product success principles from Marty Cagan’s book &lt;em&gt;Transformed&lt;/em&gt;. (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/pawel-huryn_i-wish-all-companies-lived-and-breathed-by-activity-7229142751550873600-Afta&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;I wish all companies lived and breathed by those principles from TRANSFORMED by Marty Cagan. Is that too much to ask?&#34;&gt;Please find his post on LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; and consider following him.) I took those principles and compared them step-by-step with the principles derived from the Scrum Guide.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL； DR：转型和 Scrum&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管产品社区（即 Marty Cagan 本人）对 Scrum 作为有效产品创建框架提出了批评，但我认为将有助于组建成功产品团队的原则与 Scrum 进行比较是值得的。让我们深入分析一下“Transformed”以及它的原则如何与 Scrum 的原则保持一致。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;将 Transformed 的产品成功原则与 Scrum 原则相匹配&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上周，Paweł Huryn 总结了 Marty Cagan 的《Transformed》一书中的产品成功原则。 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/pawel-huryn_i-wish-all-companies-lived-and-breathed-by-activity-7229142751550873600-Afta&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34; _blank&#34; title=&#34;我希望所有公司都遵循 Marty Cagan 的《TRANSFORMED》中的这些原则，这样的要求是否太过分了？&#34;&gt;请在 LinkedIn 上找到他的帖子&lt;/a&gt;并考虑关注他。）我采纳了这些原则。并将它们与 Scrum 指南中的原则进行了逐步比较。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【API Security: The Cornerstone of AI and LLM Protection】API 安全：AI 和 LLM 保护的基石</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/api-security-the-cornerstone-of-ai-and-llm-protection</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As artificial intelligence and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;large language models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; continue to reshape the technological landscape, the importance of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/api-security-patterns&#34;&gt;API security&lt;/a&gt; has never been more critical. In a recent interview at Black Hat 2024, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/tylershields/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Tyler Shields&lt;/a&gt;, Vice President of Product Marketing at Traceable, shed light on the evolving relationship between API security and AI/LLM applications. This article explores key insights for developers, engineers, and architects navigating this complex terrain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Evolving Landscape of API Vulnerabilities&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the rapid adoption of AI and LLM-driven applications, the API security landscape is undergoing significant changes. Shields highlights a &#34;massive explosion of APIs&#34; driven by several factors:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;作为人工智能和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM)&lt;/a&gt;随着技术格局的不断重塑，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/api-security-patterns&#34;&gt;API 安全&lt;/a&gt;的重要性从未如此重要。在 Black Hat 2024 最近的一次采访中，副总裁 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/tylershields/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Tyler Shields&lt;/a&gt; Traceable 的产品营销部门阐明了 API 安全性与 AI/LLM 应用程序之间不断发展的关系。本文探讨了开发人员、工程师和架构师在应对这一复杂领域时的关键见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;API 漏洞的演变&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着 AI 和 LLM 驱动的应用程序的快速采用，API 安全格局正在发生重大变化。 Shields 强调了由以下几个因素驱动的“API 的大规模爆炸”：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding PolyBase and External Stages: Making Informed Decisions for Data Querying】了解 PolyBase 和外部阶段：为数据查询做出明智的决策</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-querying-with-polybase-and-external-stages</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In the realm of Big Data and AI, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-data-insights-and-architecture&#34;&gt;data lakes and lake houses&lt;/a&gt; play a vital role in bringing insights and advanced analytics. The ability of the lake house is measured effectively when it can query data from external sources like cloud storage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;We have two popular methodologies for querying data from external sources:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在大数据和人工智能领域，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-data-insights-and-architecture&#34;&gt;数据湖和湖边小屋&lt;/a&gt;在提供见解和高级分析方面发挥着至关重要的作用。当 Lake House 能够从云存储等外部来源查询数据时，可以有效衡量 Lake House 的能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;我们有两种流行的方法来从外部源查询数据：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Make a Picture-in-Picture Feature in iOS App Using AVFoundation】如何使用 AVFoundation 在 iOS 应用程序中制作画中画功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-make-a-picture-in-picture-feature-in-ios-ap</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AVFoundation works on Apple’s entire product line. With this framework, you can add recording, editing, and playback features to your apps. In this article, I will show how to place one video over another and thus enable a picture-in-picture (“duet”) mode – one of the most popular TikTok-like features. We are going to use only the native tools for this job.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Building Blocks&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is what we need for this task:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AVFoundation 适用于 Apple 的整个产品线。使用此框架，您可以向应用程序添加录制、编辑和播放功能。在本文中，我将展示如何将一个视频放在另一个视频上，从而启用画中画（“二重奏”）模式——这是最流行的类似 TikTok 的功能之一。我们将仅使用本机工具来完成这项工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;构建块&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是我们完成此任务所需的：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 21:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Benchmarking OpenAI Models for Automated Error Resolution】对 OpenAI 模型进行自动错误解决基准测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/benchmarking-openai-models-for-error-resolution</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs) are increasingly shaping the future of software development, offering new possibilities in code generation, debugging, and error resolution. Recent advancements in these AI-driven tools have prompted a closer examination of their practical applications and potential impact on developer workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores the effectiveness of LLMs in software development, with a particular focus on error resolution. Drawing from industry-wide observations and insights gained through my work with AI Error Resolution at Raygun, I’ll analyze LLMs’ current capabilities and their implications for the future of development practices. The discussion will weigh both the promising advancements and the challenges that arise as these technologies integrate into our daily work.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大型语言模型 (LLM) 正在日益塑造软件开发的未来，为代码生成、调试和错误解决提供新的可能性。这些人工智能驱动工具的最新进展促使人们对其实际应用及其对开发人员工作流程的潜在影响进行更仔细的检查。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了法学硕士在软件开发中的有效性，特别关注错误解决。根据我在 Raygun 的人工智能错误解决工作中获得的全行业观察和见解，我将分析法学硕士当前的能力及其对未来开发实践的影响。讨论将权衡这些技术融入我们日常工作时所带来的前景和挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>