<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Feature Flags in .NET 8 and Azure】.NET 8 和 Azure 中的功能标志</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/feature-flags-in-net-8-and-azure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In an industry where fast, reliable, and iterative development cycles define success, the ability to deploy software while minimizing risks is invaluable. Feature flags have become an essential part of the modern developer’s toolkit, offering a flexible approach to enabling and disabling features dynamically.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s examine how the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-the-good-and-the-bad-of-net-developm&#34;&gt;Microsoft .NET&lt;/a&gt; team, in combination with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/cloud-computing-windows-azure&#34;&gt;Azure&lt;/a&gt;, manages new feature releases efficiently without reverting (redeploying) in case of regressions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在快速、可靠和迭代开发周期决定成功的行业中，部署软件同时最大限度降低风险的能力是非常宝贵的。功能标志已成为现代开发人员工具包的重要组成部分，提供了动态启用和禁用功能的灵活方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们来看看 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-the-good-and-the-bad-of-net-developm&#34;&gt;Microsoft .NET&lt;/a&gt; 团队如何，与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/cloud-computing-windows-azure&#34;&gt;Azure&lt;/a&gt; 结合使用，可以有效管理新功能发布，而无需在出现回归时恢复（重新部署）。&lt;/ p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ArangoDB: Achieving Success With a Multivalue Database】ArangoDB：利用多值数据库取得成功</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/arangodb-success-through-multivalue-database</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Handling diverse database structures often introduces significant complexity to system architecture, especially when multiple database instances are required. This fragmentation can complicate operations, increase costs, and reduce efficiency. Multimodel databases like ArangoDB provide a unified solution to address these challenges. They simplify architecture and streamline data management by supporting multiple data models — key-value, document, and graph — within a single database instance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unlike relational databases, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-nosql-database-1&#34;&gt;NoSQL databases&lt;/a&gt; do not adhere to a universal standard like SQL. Instead, they are categorized based on their storage structure. Among the popular types are:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;处理不同的数据库结构通常会给系统架构带来极大的复杂性，特别是在需要多个数据库实例时。这种碎片化会使操作变得复杂、增加成本并降低效率。 ArangoDB 等多模型数据库提供了统一的解决方案来应对这些挑战。它们通过在单个数据库实例中支持多种数据模型（键值、文档和图形）来简化架构并简化数据管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与关系数据库不同，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-nosql-database-1&#34;&gt;NoSQL 数据库&lt;/a&gt;不遵守 SQL 等通用标准。相反，它们根据存储结构进行分类。流行的类型包括：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Your First Chrome Extension With Rust and WebAssembly】使用 Rust 和 WebAssembly 构建您的第一个 Chrome 扩展</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-chrome-extension-rust-webassembly</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Chrome extensions have traditionally been built using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS. However, with the rise of WebAssembly (Wasm), we can now leverage Rust&#39;s performance, safety, and modern development features in browser extensions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, we will create a simple Chrome extension that uses &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rust-programming-language-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;Rust&lt;/a&gt; compiled to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-webassembly&#34;&gt;WebAssembly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Chrome 扩展程序传统上是使用 JavaScript、HTML 和 CSS 构建的。然而，随着 WebAssembly (Wasm) 的兴起，我们现在可以在浏览器扩展中利用 Rust 的性能、安全性和现代开发功能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本教程中，我们将创建一个简单的 Chrome 扩展程序，该扩展程序使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/rust-programming-language-a-beginners-guide&#34;&gt;Rust&lt;/a&gt; 编译到 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-web assembly&#34;&gt;WebAssembly&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ISO 27001 vs SOC 2: Understanding the Differences】ISO 27001 与 SOC 2：了解差异</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/iso-27001-vs-soc-2</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When organizations handle sensitive information, ensuring its security and maintaining compliance are paramount. Two key frameworks in this domain are ISO 27001 and SOC 2. While they share common goals, they differ significantly in their approach, scope, and purpose. Here’s a deep dive into both frameworks:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is ISO 27001?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-and-comprehensive-guide-to-iso-27001-co-1&#34;&gt;ISO 27001&lt;/a&gt; is an internationally recognized standard established by the International Organization for Standardization (ISO) for implementing and maintaining an Information Security Management System (ISMS). This framework provides a structured methodology for managing sensitive company information, focusing on risk management, preventive measures, and ongoing improvement.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当组织处理敏感信息时，确保其安全性和保持合规性至关重要。该领域的两个关键框架是 ISO 27001 和 SOC 2。虽然它们具有共同的目标，但它们在方法、范围和目的方面存在显着差异。以下是对这两个框架的深入研究：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是 ISO 27001？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-and-compressive-guide-to-iso-27001-co-1&#34;&gt;ISO 27001&lt;/a&gt;是国际公认的标准由国际标准化组织 (ISO) 建立，用于实施和维护信息安全管理体系 (ISMS)。该框架提供了管理敏感公司信息的结构化方法，重点关注风险管理、预防措施和持续改进。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Forensic Product Backlog Analysis: A New Team Exercise】取证产品待办事项分析：一项新的团队练习</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/forensic-product-backlog-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The Forensic Product Backlog Analysis: A 60-minute team exercise to fix your Backlog. Identify what’s broken, find out why, and agree on practical fixes — all in five quick steps. There is no fluff, just results.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want technical excellence and solve customer problems? Start with a solid &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-product-backlog&#34;&gt;Product Backlog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;取证产品待办事项分析：60 分钟的团队练习来修复您的待办事项。找出问题所在，找出原因，并就实际修复方案达成一致——这一切只需五个快速步骤即可完成。没有多余的内容，只有结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想要卓越的技术并解决客户问题？从可靠的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-product-backlog&#34;&gt;产品待办事项列表&lt;/a&gt;开始。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【You Need to Validate Your Databases】您需要验证您的数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/you-need-to-validate-your-databases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Ensuring database consistency can quickly become chaotic, posing significant challenges. To tackle these hurdles, it&#39;s essential to adopt effective strategies for streamlining schema migrations and adjustments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;These approaches help implement database changes smoothly, with minimal downtime and impact on performance. Without them, the risk of misconfigured databases increases — &lt;a href=&#34;https://status.heroku.com/incidents/2558&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;just as Heroku experienced&lt;/a&gt;. Learn how to steer clear of similar mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;确保数据库一致性很快就会变得混乱，带来重大挑战。为了解决这些障碍，必须采取有效的策略来简化模式迁移和调整。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;这些方法有助于顺利实施数据库更改，最大限度地减少停机时间和对性能的影响。如果没有它们，数据库配置错误的风险就会增加——&lt;a href=&#34;https://status.heroku.com/incidents/2558&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;正如 Heroku 所经历的&lt;/a&gt;。了解如何避免类似的错误。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Best Gantt Chart Libraries for React】React 的最佳甘特图库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/best-gantt-chart-libraries-for-react</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Gantt chart is an advanced visualization solution for project management that considerably facilitates planning, scheduling, and controlling the progress of short-, mid-, and long-term projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-gantt-chart-how-and-when-to-use-a-gantt&#34;&gt;Gantt charts&lt;/a&gt; were invented more than a hundred years ago by Henry Gantt, who made a major contribution to the development of scientific management. Decades ago, the entire procedure of implementing Gantt charts in infrastructure projects was really time-consuming. Today, we are lucky to have modern tools that greatly speed up the process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;甘特图是一种先进的项目管理可视化解决方案，可极大地方便规划、安排和控制短期、中期和长期项目的进度。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-a-gantt-chart-how-and-when-to-use-a-gantt&#34;&gt;甘特图&lt;/a&gt; 是一百多年前由亨利·甘特发明的，他为科学管理的发展做出了重大贡献。几十年前，在基础设施项目中实施甘特图的整个过程非常耗时。今天，我们很幸运拥有可以大大加快这一过程的现代工具。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Observability in 10 Minutes Using OpenSearch】使用 OpenSearch 在 10 分钟内掌握可观察性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/master-observability-with-opensearch</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Observability has become a key component in software development as it enables the best customer experience by ensuring system health and performance and detecting systemic issues proactively. However, getting started can often feel overwhelming. OpenSearch simplifies this by providing an open-source, scalable solution for logging, metrics, and visualization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll walk through setting up &lt;strong&gt;observability in 10 minutes&lt;/strong&gt; using &lt;a href=&#34;https://opensearch.org/platform/observability/index.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenSearch Observability&lt;/a&gt;. No complex jargon, just simple steps to get you started with real-world examples.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;可观察性已成为软件开发的关键组成部分，因为它通过确保系统健康和性能以及主动检测系统问题来实现最佳的客户体验。然而，开始时常常会感到不知所措。 OpenSearch 通过为日志记录、指标和可视化提供开源、可扩展的解决方案来简化这一过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opensearch.org/platform/observability/index.html&#34; rel=&#34; &lt;strong&gt;在 10 分钟内设置可观察性&lt;/strong&gt; noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenSearch 可观测性&lt;/a&gt;。没有复杂的术语，只需简单的步骤即可帮助您开始使用现实世界的示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Sharing Using Google Analytics Hub】使用 Google Analytics Hub 进行数据共享</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-sharing-using-google-analytics-hub</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Google Cloud Analytics Hub is a tool built on BigQuery that enables seamless data sharing across the organization by making it easier to share and access datasets. Analytics Hub makes it easy to discover public, private, and internally shared data sources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Accessing Public Datasets in Analytics Hub&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Navigate to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/google-cloud-for-beginners-how-to-choose-a-compute&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Google Cloud&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt; console using the URL &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://console.cloud.google.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://console.cloud.google.com&lt;/a&gt;,&#34; search for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;BigQuery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;, and select BigQuery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Google Cloud Analytics Hub 是一款基于 BigQuery 构建的工具，可以更轻松地共享和访问数据集，从而在整个组织内实现无缝数据共享。 Analytics Hub 可以轻松发现公共、私有和内部共享的数据源。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;访问 Analytics Hub 中的公共数据集&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;导航至 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/google-cloud-for -beginners-how-to-choose-a-compute&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;Google Cloud&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt; 使用 URL“&lt;a href=&#34;https://console.cloud.google.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://console.cloud.google.com&lt;/a&gt; 的控制台， &#34; 搜索 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;BigQuery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;，然后选择 BigQuery。&lt;/span &gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Leaderless Replication for Distributed Data】了解分布式数据的无领导复制</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/leaderless-replication-for-distributed-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Leaderless replication is another fundamental replication approach for distributed systems. It alleviates problems of multi-leader replication while, at the same time, it introduces its own problems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Write conflicts in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/multi-leader-replication-for-distributed-data&#34;&gt;multi-leader replication&lt;/a&gt; are tackled in leaderless replication with quorum-based writes and systematic conflict resolution (e.g., version vectors). Cascading failures, synchronization overhead, and operational complexity can be handled in leaderless replication via its decentralized architecture. Removing leaders can simplify cluster management, failure handling,g and recovery mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;无领导者复制是分布式系统的另一种基本复制方法。它缓解了多领导者复制的问题，同时也引入了自己的问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/multi-leader-replication-for-distributed-data&#34;&gt;多领导复制&lt;/a&gt;中的写入冲突在无领导复制中通过仲裁解决基于写入和系统冲突解决（例如版本向量）。级联故障、同步开销和操作复杂性可以通过其去中心化架构在无领导者复制中得到处理。删除领导者可以简化集群管理、故障处理和恢复机制。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>