<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Go Flags: Beyond the Basics】去国旗：超越基本知识</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/go-flags-beyond-the-basics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;flag&lt;/code&gt; package is one of Go&#39;s most powerful standard library tools for building command-line applications. Understanding flags is essential whether you&#39;re creating a simple CLI tool or a complex application. Let&#39;s look into what makes this package so versatile.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Basic Flag Concepts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s start with a simple example that demonstrates the core concepts:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;code&gt; flag &lt;/code&gt;软件包是GO最强大的标准库工具之一，用于构建命令行应用程序。无论您是创建简单的CLI工具还是复杂的应用程序，了解标志都是必不可少的。让我们看看是什么使此软件包如此通用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;基本标志概念&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们从一个简单的示例开始，该示例演示了核心概念：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【KIAM vs AWS IAM Roles for Service Accounts (IRSA)】Kiam vs AWS IAM服务帐户角色（IRSA）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/comparative-analysis-kiam-vs-aws-iam-roles-for-ser</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As Kubernetes adoption grows in cloud-native environments, securely managing AWS IAM roles within Kubernetes clusters has become a critical aspect of infrastructure management. KIAM and AWS IAM Roles for Service Accounts (IRSA) are two popular approaches to handling this requirement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we discuss the nuances of both tools, comparing their features, architecture, benefits, and drawbacks to help you make an informed decision for your Kubernetes environment.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着Kubernetes采用在云本地环境中的增长，在Kubernetes集群中安全地管理AWS IAM角色已成为基础架构管理的关键方面。 Kiam和AWS IAM服务帐户角色（IRSA）是处理此要求的两种流行方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们讨论了这两种工具的细微差别，比较它们的功能，架构，利益和缺点，以帮助您为Kubernetes环境做出明智的决定。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 18:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Scalability in Spring Boot】在春季启动中掌握可伸缩性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-scalability-in-spring-boot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Scalability is a fundamental concept in both technology and business that refers to the ability of a system, network, or organization to handle a growing amount of requests or ability to grow. This characteristic is crucial for maintaining performance and efficiency as need increases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will explore the definition of scalability, its importance, types, methods to achieve it, and real-world examples.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;可扩展性是技术和业务中的一个基本概念，它是指系统，网络或组织能够处理越来越多的请求或成长能力的能力。这种特征对于随着需求的增加而保持绩效和效率至关重要。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨可伸缩性的定义，其重要性，类型，实现它的方法以及现实世界的示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advanced Error Handling in JavaScript】JavaScript中的高级错误处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-error-handling-in-javascript-custom-error</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Error handling is a fundamental aspect of programming that ensures applications can gracefully handle unexpected situations. In JavaScript, while &lt;code&gt;try-catch&lt;/code&gt; is commonly used, there are more advanced techniques to enhance error handling.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article explores these advanced methods, providing practical solutions to improve your error management strategies and make your applications more resilient.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;错误处理是编程的一个基本方面，可确保应用程序可以优雅地处理意外情况。在JavaScript中，&lt;Code&gt;通常使用&lt;code&gt; try-catch &lt;/code&gt;，但是有更多高级技术来增强错误处理。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了这些高级方法，提供了改善错误管理策略并使您的应用程序更具弹性的实用解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Deep Learning Fraud Detection With AWS SageMaker and Glue】AWS SageMaker和Glue的深度学习欺诈检测</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deep-learning-fraud-detection-aws-sagemaker-glue</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Fraud detection has become a top priority for businesses across industries. With fraudulent activities growing more sophisticated, traditional rule-based approaches often fall short in addressing the constantly evolving threats. Detecting and preventing fraud — be it financial scams, identity theft, or insurance fraud — is crucial, especially when global fraud losses run into billions of dollars annually.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide discusses how deep learning can improve fraud detection with AWS SageMaker and AWS Glue. Deep learning, a branch of machine learning, excels at uncovering complex patterns in large datasets and adapting to emerging fraud techniques. AWS SageMaker, a comprehensive machine learning platform, equips businesses with the tools to build, train, and deploy advanced deep learning models, while &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-data-processing-with-aws-glue&#34;&gt;AWS Glue&lt;/a&gt; streamlines data preparation and integration with its fully managed ETL capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;欺诈检测已成为各个行业企业的重中之重。随着欺诈性活动的增长，基于规则的传统方法通常在解决不断发展的威胁方面往往不足。检测和预防欺诈（无论是财务骗局，身份盗窃还是保险欺诈）至关重要，尤其是当全球欺诈损失每年损失数十亿美元时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南讨论了如何使用AWS Sagemaker和AWS胶水改善欺诈检测。深度学习是机器学习的一个分支，在大型数据集中发现复杂模式并适应新兴欺诈技术方面擅长。 AWS SageMaker是一个全面的机器学习平台，它使企业拥有构建，训练和部署先进深度学习模型的工具，而&lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/Articles/advanced-data-processing-with-aws-with-aws-with-aws-glue“&gt; aws&gt; aws&gt; aws glue &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;流行&lt;/afteral and &lt;/after &lt;/after &lt;/afteral &lt;/a&gt; cab &lt;/pl &lt;/plabibility &lt;/pl &lt;/pl &lt;/plab capab capab capab capab。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【IoT Communication Protocols for Efficient Device Integration】物联网通信协议，用于有效设备集成</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/iot-communication-protocols-efficient-device-integration</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;What Are IoT Communication Protocols?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;IoT communication protocols are the standards and rules that allow devices to communicate over networks. They define how data is transmitted, how devices establish connections, and how they securely exchange information. These protocols ensure that devices understand each other and function seamlessly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Importance of Efficient Device Integration&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Efficient device integration is crucial in IoT ecosystems, where devices from various manufacturers must interact. The right protocol enables reliable, secure, and scalable communication, ensuring devices operate as intended. Effective integration in smart home systems, industrial automation, or health-monitoring devices allows for real-time data exchange, enhancing functionality, performance, and user experience.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;什么是IoT通信协议？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; IoT通信协议是允许设备通过网络通信的标准和规则。他们定义了数据的传输方式，设备如何建立连接以及如何安全地交换信息。这些协议确保设备相互了解并无缝地运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;有效设备集成的重要性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;有效的设备集成在物联网生态系统中至关重要，其中各种制造商的设备必须相互作用。正确的协议可以实现可靠，安全和可扩展的通信，以确保设备按预期运行。有效集成在智能家庭系统，工业自动化或健康监控设备中可以实时数据交换，增强功能，性能和用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Actuator Enhancements: Spring Framework 6.2 and Spring Boot 3.4】执行器增强功能：弹簧框架6.2和Spring Boot 3.4</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/actuator-enhancements-spring-framework-spring-boot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In Spring Boot, an &lt;strong&gt;Actuator&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;is a framework module that provides features for managing and monitoring applications. It helps developers and operations teams to gain insights into the run-time behavior of their applications and provides capabilities for health checking, metrics collection, and application management via a set of built-in and customizable endpoints.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traditional Implementation of Actuators&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Monitor health of the applications using endpoints like &lt;code&gt;/actuator/health&lt;/code&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Provide application metrics such as memory usage and thread count using &lt;code&gt;/actuator/metrics&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Endpoints like &lt;code&gt;/info&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;/env&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;/beans&lt;/code&gt; expose state of the application.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Developers had to integrate monitoring tools manually.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example of traditional use:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在Spring Boot中，&lt;strong&gt;执行器&lt;/strong&gt;是一个框架模块，可提供用于管理和监视应用程序的功能。它可以帮助开发人员和运营团队通过一组内置和可自定义的端点来了解其应用程序的运行时行为，并为健康检查，指标收集和应用程序管理提供功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;执行器的传统实施&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;使用&lt;code&gt;/cartuator/health &lt;/code&gt;之类的端点监视应用程序的健康。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;提供应用程序指标，例如使用&lt;code&gt;/cotuator/artrics &lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;的内存使用和线程计数&#xA; &lt;li&gt;例如&lt;code&gt;/info &lt;/code&gt;，&lt;code&gt;/env&gt; &lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt;/beans &lt;/code&gt;公开应用程序状态。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;开发人员必须手动集成监视工具。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统用途的示例：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How ARIA Snapshot Testing Solves Common Playwright Issues】ARIA快照测试如何解决常见的剧作家问题</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aria-snapshot-testing-playwright</link>
      <description>【&lt;p name=&#34;ff88&#34;&gt;The challenges of testing various elements on a webpage, such as headings and links, noting that traditional code-based tests can become complex and brittle. I am not a huge fan of using screenshots for testing, as they can break with minor layout changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name=&#34;f6ee&#34;&gt;Playwright’s ARIA Snapshots offer a powerful method to validate the accessibility tree of your web applications, ensuring that content is both accessible and correctly structured. By capturing the hierarchical representation of accessible elements, you can compare snapshots over time to detect unintended changes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p name =“ ff88”&gt;在网页上测试各种元素的挑战，例如标题和链接，并指出传统的基于代码的测试可能会变得复杂且脆弱。我不是使用屏幕截图进行测试的忠实拥护者，因为它们可能会随着较小的布局更改而破坏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p name =“ f6ee”&gt;剧作家的咏叹调快照提供了一种强大的方法来验证您的Web应用程序的可访问性树，以确保内容既可以访问又正确地结构。通过捕获可访问元素的层次结构表示，您可以随着时间的推移比较快照以检测意外的更改。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Harnessing Real-Time Insights With Streaming SQL on Kafka】利用kafka上流式SQL利用实时见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-insights-with-streaming-sql-on-kafka</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In the era of real-time data, the ability to process and analyze streaming information has become critical for businesses. Apache Kafka, a powerful distributed event streaming platform, is often at the heart of these real-time pipelines. But working with raw streams of data can be complex. This is where Streaming SQL comes in: it allows users to query and transform Kafka topics with the simplicity of SQL.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is Streaming SQL?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Streaming SQL refers to the application of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/sql-commands-a-brief-guide&#34;&gt;structured query language&lt;/a&gt; (SQL) to process and analyze data in motion. Unlike traditional SQL, which queries static datasets in databases, streaming SQL continuously processes data as it flows through a system. It supports operations like filtering, aggregating, joining, and windowing in real time.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;在实时数据时代，处理和分析流信息的能力对企业至关重要。强大的分布式事件流平台Apache Kafka通常是这些实时管道的核心。但是，使用原始数据流可以很复杂。这是流式SQL所在的地方：它允许用户以SQL的简单性查询和转换Kafka主题。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是流sql？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;流式SQL是指&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/sql-commands-a-brief-guide”&gt;结构化查询语言&lt;/a&gt;（SQL）在运动中处理和分析数据。与传统的SQL（在数据库中查询静态数据集）不同，流式传输SQL在流过系统时会连续处理数据。它支持实时过滤，聚合，加入和窗口等操作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Text2SQL Alone Isn’t Enough: Embracing TAG】为什么单独使用text2sql是不够的：拥抱标签</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-text2sql-alone-isnt-enough-embracing-tag</link>
      <description>【&lt;section name=&#34;637b&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;9246&#34;&gt;Imagine you’re trying to understand why your company’s sales dropped last quarter. You query your database with a simple natural language question: “Why did sales drop last quarter?” The ideal scenario would be that the AI system instantly provides you with a context-rich, insightful answer  —  something that ties together all relevant data points, trends, and market insights. However, the reality is far from ideal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;5142&#34;&gt;Current AI methods for querying databases, such as Text2SQL and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-generative-ai-with-retrieval-augmented&#34;&gt;retrieval-augmented generation&lt;/a&gt; (RAG), fall significantly short. These models are limited by their design, either only interpreting natural language as SQL queries or relying on simple lookups that fail to capture the complexity of real-world questions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;部分名称=“ 637b”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name =“ 9246”&gt;想象您正在尝试了解为什么公司的销售额上一季度下跌。您用一个简单的自然语言问题查询数据库：“为什么上个季度销售下降？”理想的情况是，AI系统立即为您提供了一个富裕，有见地的答案，这些答案将所有相关的数据点，趋势和市场见解联系在一起。但是，现实远非理想。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name =“ 5142”&gt;当前查询数据库的AI方法，例如text2sql和&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/optimizing-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-generative-iai-with-retreval-augment-&gt; reterieval- retereval- reterieval-enevereval-novieval-noviemed overeneval-aughtement-augned agithing opented Generation &lt;/a&gt;（rag），跌落。这些模型受其设计的限制，要么仅将自然语言解释为SQL查询，要么依靠无法捕获现实世界问题复杂性的简单查找。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>