<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Embed SAP Analytics Cloud (SAC) Stories Into Fiori Launchpad for Real-Time Insights】如何将SAP Analytics Cloud（SAC）故事嵌入到Fiori Launchpad中以进行实时见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sap-fiori-launchpad-embed-sac-stories-live-cds-views</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As enterprise decision-making becomes more data-driven, users increasingly expect real-time insights at their fingertips, without switching systems. SAP Analytics Cloud (SAC) is the go-to platform for reporting and dashboarding in modern &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-and-phases-of-data-migration-from-l&#34;&gt;SAP&lt;/a&gt; landscapes, while SAP Fiori Launchpad (FLP) remains the user interface hub for business operations. Embedding SAC stories directly into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-start-with-low-coding-experts-guide-on-deve&#34;&gt;Fiori Launchpad&lt;/a&gt; offers a seamless, role-based analytics experience that empowers users with actionable insights where they work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you are enabling call center agents to monitor customer KPIs or helping sales representatives review order analytics within their business applications, embedded SAC delivers the best of both worlds: real-time data from &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/Test-Automation-Strategies-for-Mobile-Apps-with-SAP-S4HANA&#34;&gt;S/4HANA&lt;/a&gt; or IS-U via live CDS views, and rich visualizations presented natively in the Fiori experience.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着企业决策变得更加数据驱动，用户越来越期望无需切换系统就可以实时见解。 SAP Analytics Cloud（SAC）是现代报告和仪表板的首选平台。将SAC故事直接嵌入到&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-toart-with-with-with-with-low-coding-coding-experts-guide-on-deve”&gt; fiori aunpenationpad &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您是否正在使呼叫中心代理人监视客户KPI或帮助销售代表在其业务应用中审查订单分析，嵌入SAC都可以在&lt;a href =&#39;https：///dzone.com/articles/test-automation-stratemation-strategies-foregies-for-strategies-for-mobile-sapps-with-sapps-with--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------s4hana &lt;/sap4hana &lt;通过实时CD的视图以及在Fiori体验中本地呈现的丰富可视化。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【10 Predictions Shaping the Future of Web Data Extraction Services】10个预测塑造Web数据提取服务的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/web-data-extraction-future-trends-ai-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;AI is reshaping how businesses collect and process online information, bringing a fundamental change to data extraction. Traditional scraping methods are becoming smarter and more adaptable to complex website structures through AI and machine learning technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Web data extraction tools have grown beyond basic data collectors. Modern solutions now include advanced features like immediate monitoring, automated pattern recognition, and enhanced processing capabilities. These improvements help businesses find the quickest way to learn about the big amount of online data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt; AI正在重塑企业如何收集和处理在线信息，从而为数据提取带来了根本性的更改。传统的刮擦方法通过AI和机器学习技术变得更聪明，更适合复杂的网站结构。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {}”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt; Web数据提取工具已经超出了基本数据收集器。现代解决方案现在包括高级功能，例如立即监视，自动化模式识别和增强的处理功能。这些改进有助于企业找到了解大量在线数据的最快方法。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {}”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Micro Frontends to Microservices: Orchestrating a Truly End-to-End Architecture】微服务微服务：精心策划真正的端到端体系结构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/orchestrating-truly-end-to-end-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/patterns-modular-architecture&#34;&gt;Modular architecture&lt;/a&gt; is everywhere in modern app development, but it is rarely done systematically.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;You may have created micro frontends or microservices, but the process of integrating them might feel alien or disjointed. This article aims to bridge that gap by seamlessly connecting React shells down to service meshes utilizing proven patterns.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/patterns-modular-architecture”&gt;模块化体系结构&lt;/a&gt;在现代应用程序开发中无处不在，但是很少有系统地完成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您可能已经创建了微观前端或微服务，但是集成它们的过程可能会感到外星或脱节。本文旨在通过无缝将React Shell的连接到使用经过验证的模式的服务网格来弥合差距。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero-Trace Paradigm: Emerging Technologies in Personal Data Anonymization】零跟踪范式：个人数据匿名的新兴技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-trace-paradigm-emerging-technologies-in-perso</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Emerging technologies like homomorphic encryption and zero-knowledge proofs can definitely help organizations approach zero-trace personal data anonymization. These and similar techniques can bring datasets to a near-zero-trace status, even achieving it in limited cases. There’s a major force that’s acting against efforts at implementing the zero-trace paradigm, though, and it’s difficult to discuss this paradigm without delving into what undermines it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Put simply, personal data has to come from somewhere before anonymization can even be considered. For very large datasets of personal information covering broad swaths of the population, the data broker industry remains the most practical source for many applications. Unfortunately, data brokers have proven themselves incapable of securing the almost exclusively plaintext datasets they hold.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;诸如同态加密和零知识证明之类的新兴技术绝对可以帮助组织接近零跟踪的个人数据匿名化。这些技术和类似的技术可以使数据集达到接近零跟踪的状态，甚至可以在有限的情况下实现它。不过，有一支主要的力量反对实施零轨道范式的努力，而且很难讨论这种范式而不会深入研究它的破坏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;简而言之，甚至可以考虑匿名化之前，必须从某个地方出现。对于涵盖人口广泛的个人信息数据集的大量数据集，数据经纪行业仍然是许多应用程序的最实际来源。不幸的是，数据经纪人已经证明自己无法确保其持有的几乎完全明文数据集。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Unofficial Rules of Not Screwing Up Your Software】不搞砸软件的非官方规则</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/12-principles-great-developer-software-engineering-tips</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;These are not just technical tips, but principles that shaped how I learned and think about engineering. Take &lt;strong&gt;what’s usefu&lt;/strong&gt;l, &lt;strong&gt;ignore what isn’t&lt;/strong&gt;. But remember, being a great developer isn’t only about code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. “The Most Elegant Solution Is the One You Never Have to Maintain.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most effective code is often the code you never have to write. This might sound counter-intuitive, but one of the most profound lessons I&#39;ve learned is that sometimes, the most effective solution is to avoid writing new code altogether.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;这些不仅是技术技巧，而且是塑造我对工程学学习和思考的方式的原则。 &lt;strong&gt;什么是usefu ​​&lt;/strong&gt; l，&lt;strong&gt;忽略什么不是&lt;/strong&gt;。但是请记住，成为一名出色的开发人员不仅与代码有关。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 1。 “最优雅的解决方案是您永远不必维护的解决方案。” &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最有效的代码通常是您不必编写的代码。这听起来可能是违反直觉的，但是我学到的最深刻的教训之一是，有时候，最有效的解决方案是避免完全编写新的代码。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multiple Stakeholder Management in Software Engineering】软件工程中的多个利益相关者管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/multiple-stakeholder-management-software-engineering-tips</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;One of the key &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-impact-beyond-code&#34;&gt;challenges faced by the engineering leaders&lt;/a&gt; is to manage multiple stakeholders. These stakeholders often have different project priorities. This article suggests strategies to deal with the challenges encountered by engineering leaders in managing multiple stakeholders with often conflicting priorities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Managing a mid size engineering team of size ~20 engineers presents multiple challenges, specifically when it comes to stakeholder management and project execution. Engineering leaders in this position frequently find themselves juggling the needs and expectations of multiple stakeholders across multiple projects. This results in the below challenges:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;键&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/scaling-impact-beyond-code”&gt;工程领导者面临的挑战&lt;/a&gt;是要管理多个利益相关者。这些利益相关者通常具有不同的项目优先事项。本文提出了处理工程领导者在管理多个利益相关者经常相互矛盾的优先事项方面遇到的挑战的策略。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;背景&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;管理一个尺寸的中型工程团队〜20工程师提出了多个挑战，特别是在利益相关者管理和项目执行方面。在这个职位上，工程领导者经常发现自己在多个项目中挑战了多个利益相关者的需求和期望。这导致以下挑战：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding N-Gram Language Models and Perplexity】了解N-Gram语言模型和困惑</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/n-gram-language-models-perplexity</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-language-models-with-powerful-prompts&#34;&gt;Language models&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;are designed to predict what words are likely to come next in a sequence, assigning probabilities to each possible continuation. In this article, we explore how an &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-smaller-language-models&#34;&gt;N-gram language model&lt;/a&gt; works, how it assigns probabilities to sentences and sequences of words, and then examine how well this model performs. By understanding and evaluating this approach, we gain insight into how language models handle the complexity of human language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Applications&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Augmentative communication&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Machine translation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Spelling correction&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Speech recognition&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Language Models&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Definition&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A language model consists of a finite set V and a function &lt;em&gt;f&lt;/em&gt;(&lt;em&gt;x&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sub&gt;1&lt;/sub&gt;, &lt;em&gt;x&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;, ..., &lt;em&gt;x&lt;/em&gt;&lt;sub&gt;n&lt;/sub&gt;) such that:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/unlocking-language-models-models-with-power-prompts”&gt;语言模型&lt;/a&gt;旨在预测接下来的单词可能会以序列为单位，为每个可能的持续延续分配概率。在本文中，我们探讨了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-smaller-language-models”&gt; n-gram语言模型&lt;/a&gt;有效，它如何为句子和单词序列分配概率，然后检查此模型的表现如何。通过理解和评估这种方法，我们可以深入了解语言模型如何处理人类语言的复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;应用程序&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;增强沟通&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;机器翻译&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;拼写校正&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;语音识别&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;语言模型&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;定义&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;语言模型由有限集V和函数&lt;em&gt; f &lt;/em&gt;（&lt;em&gt; x &lt;/em&gt; &lt;sub&gt; &lt;sub&gt; 1 &lt;/sub&gt;，&lt;em&gt; x &lt;/em&gt; &lt;sub&gt; 2 &lt;/sub&gt; 2 &lt;/sub&gt;，...</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Evaluating Accuracy in RAG Applications: A Guide to Automated Evaluation】评估抹布应用中的准确性：自动评估指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rag-accuracy-metrics-automated-evaluation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Generative AI applications are rapidly gaining momentum across industries, providing intelligent responses to a wide range of queries. Whether for customer support, content generation, or knowledge management, the ability of AI to deliver contextually relevant and accurate answers is critical. One powerful approach that has emerged is &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag&#34;&gt;Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG)&lt;/a&gt;, which integrates &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-large-language-models-and-how-they-work&#34;&gt;large language models&lt;/a&gt; (LLMs) with external knowledge sources to enhance the quality of AI-generated responses. The retrieval component draws on external databases to provide real-world information, while the generation component refines the content into human-like responses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;RAG’s usefulness lies in its ability to extend the capabilities of traditional language models, making them more context-aware and accurate. Applications of RAG span across multiple industries: for example, in customer support, RAG models dynamically access knowledge bases to deliver real-time, accurate answers to inquiries, reducing the need for manual intervention. In corporate environments, RAG helps automate information retrieval from large document repositories, improving response accuracy in knowledge-sharing platforms. It also plays a crucial role in fields like healthcare and education, where it enhances decision-making by fetching relevant research papers or educational materials, which LLMs can summarize for easy understanding.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;生成的AI应用程序正在迅速在各行业中获得动力，从而对各种查询提供了智能反应。无论是为了客户支持，内容生成还是知识管理，AI提供上下文相关和准确的答案的能力至关重要。出现的一种强大方法是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-tocult-to-to-to-to-to-retrieval-augment-gener-generated-generation-generation-generation-gener-rag”&gt; reterieval-augmented Generation（rag）&lt;/a&gt;，它整合&lt;a href =“ href =”语言模型&lt;/a&gt;（LLMS）具有外部知识来源，以提高AI生成的响应的质量。检索组件借鉴了外部数据库，以提供现实世界的信息，而生成组件将内容完善为类似人类的响应。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; rag的实用性在于其扩展传统语言模型功能的能力，使其更加了解和准确。跨多个行业的RAG跨度的应用：例如，在客户支持中，抹布模型动态访问知识库，以提供实时，准确的查询答案，从而减少了对手动干预的需求。在公司环境中，抹布可以帮助自动化大量文档存储库中的信息检索，从而提高知识共享平台的响应准确性。它还在医疗保健和教育等领域中起着至关重要的作用，通过获取相关的研究论文或教育材料，它可以增强决策，而LLM可以简单地概括。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Rise of the Intelligent AI Agent: Revolutionizing Database Management With Agentic DBA】智能AI代理的兴起：用代理DBA革新数据库管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/agentic-dba-ai-database-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I have spent more than a decade working closely with data teams and have seen firsthand how the role of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reflections-from-a-dba&#34;&gt;database administrator (DBA)&lt;/a&gt; has evolved, and at times, struggled to keep up with the demands of our increasingly data hungry world. I remember my early days of tuning queries manually at 4 am or 5 am chasing intermittent performance issues that seemed to vanish just when logs got interesting. Back then, being a DBA I used to feel like being a firefighter who&#39;s constantly responding to alarms, outages and bottlenecks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Fast forward to today, the landscape looks very different. Thanks to rapid advances in artificial intelligence and machine learning, we&#39;re stepping into a new era as one where database management is no longer reactive, but proactive and even autonomous. Welcome to the age of the AI-powered DBA.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我花了十多年的时间与数据团队紧密合作，并亲眼目睹了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/reflections/reflections/reflections-from-a-dba”&gt;数据库管理员（dba）&lt;/a&gt;有时会随着数据的发展而变得越来越多的数据，该数据越来越多，并且会随着数据的范围而增加，并且会随着数据的范围而变得越来越多，并且会陷入困境，并随着数据的发展而努力。我记得我在早上4点或凌晨5点手动调查查询的早期，追逐间歇性的性能问题，这些问题似乎在日志变得有趣时就消失了。那时，作为DBA，我曾经觉得自己是一名消防员，他不断地回应警报，中断和瓶颈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;快进到今天，景观看起来截然不同。得益于人工智能和机器学习的快速发展，我们进入了一个新时代，因为数据库管理不再是反应性的，而是主动的，甚至是自主的。欢迎来到AI驱动的DBA的年龄。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Advancing DSLs in the Age of GenAI】在Genai时代推进DSL</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dsl-genai-app-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the dynamic realm of software development, we often find ourselves reaching for the familiar comfort of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/tiobe-index-popular-programming-languages&#34;&gt;general-purpose programming languages&lt;/a&gt; (GPLs) like Java, Python, C#, or JavaScript. However, when dealing with highly specialized tasks within specific domains these languages do not offer the same flexibility. Imagine attempting to assemble a complex piece of machinery using only a hammer and a screwdriver - while possible, the process would be inefficient and error prone. This is precisely where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/evolving-domain-specific-languages&#34;&gt;Domain-Specific Languages&lt;/a&gt; (DSLs) step in, offering a more refined and targeted approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A DSL, at its core, is a programming language or specification meticulously designed and optimized for a particular domain or problem area. Unlike GPLs that aim to be all things to all developers, DSLs are laser-focused on expressing solutions within a specific context, using terminology, concepts, and abstractions that are inherently familiar to experts in that field. Think of a DSL as a suit tailored to solve a specific problem, rather than an off-the-rack garment that requires extensive alterations. By embracing the principles of specialization, DSLs empower developers and domain experts to collaborate more effectively, build more maintainable systems, and ultimately deliver greater value.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在软件开发的动态领域中，我们经常发现自己可以为&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/tiobe-index-popular-progular-languages”&gt; General-Purpose-languages“&gt; General-Purpose编程语言&lt;/a&gt;（GPLS）等熟悉的舒适感。但是，在处理特定域内高度专业化的任务时，这些语言并不具有相同的灵活性。想象一下，尝试仅使用锤子和螺丝刀组装复杂的机械 - 虽然可能会效率低下且容易出错。这正是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/evolving-domain-specific-languages”&gt; domain-specific语言&lt;/a&gt;（dsls）介入，提供更精致和有针对性的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; a DSL的核心是针对特定域或问题领域精心设计和优化的编程语言或规范。与旨在成为所有开发人员的所有事物的GPL不同，DSL是针对激光专注于在特定上下文中表达解决方案的，使用该领域专家固有熟悉的术语，概念和抽象。将DSL视为量身定制的用于解决特定问题的西装，而不是需要进行广泛更改的室外服装。通过接受专业化原则，DSLS授权开发人员和领域专家更有效地协作，建立更可维护的系统并最终提供更大的价值。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>