<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Auto-Instrumentation in Azure Application Insights With AKS】与AKS的Azure应用程序中的自动启示</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/auto-instrumentation-in-azure-application-insights</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Monitoring containerized applications in Kubernetes environments is essential for ensuring reliability and performance. Azure Monitor Application Insights provides powerful application performance monitoring capabilities that can be integrated seamlessly with Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article focuses on auto-instrumentation, which allows you to collect telemetry from your applications running in AKS without modifying your code. We&#39;ll explore a practical implementation using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/aritraghosh/monitoring-demo-azure&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;monitoring-demo-azure&lt;/a&gt; repository as our guide.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在Kubernetes环境中监视容器化应用程序对于确保可靠性和性能至关重要。 Azure Monitor应用程序Insights提供了强大的应用程序性能监视功能，可以与Azure Kubernetes服务（AKS）无缝集成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文重点介绍自动启动，该文章使您可以从AK中运行的应用程序中收集遥测而无需修改代码。我们将使用&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/aritraghosh/monitoring-demo-azure” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; Monitoring-demo-azure &lt;/a&gt;作为指导的指导。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing AI Model: A Guide to Improving Performance (3 of 3)】优化AI模型：提高性能的指南（3，3）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimize-ai-model-improve-performance-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;In the rapidly evolving world of Artificial Intelligence (AI), having a working model is not enough. What really matters lies in optimizing that model to perform efficiently across a multitude of scenarios. Performance optimization plays a vital role in unlocking the full potential of your AI system, whether you are fine-tuning hyperparameters, refining your data pipeline, or leveraging advanced evaluation metrics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;This guide, the last of our three-part series about AI, offers insights to help you optimize methods and step-by-step implementation instructions for enhancing AI performance. The first two articles are linked below:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;在迅速发展的人工智能世界（AI）中，具有工作模型是不够的。真正重要的在于优化该模型以在多种情况下有效地执行。性能优化在解锁AI系统的全部潜力方面起着至关重要的作用，无论您是在微调超参数，完善数据管道还是利用高级评估指标。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/per&gt; &lt;/p &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;本指南是我们关于AI的三部分系列的最后一个，提供了见解，可帮助您优化方法和逐步实现指令，以增强AI性能。前两篇文章链接下面：&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why Testing is a Long-Term Investment for Software Engineers】为什么测试是软件工程师的长期投资</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/invest-in-testing-software-engineers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the world of software engineering, we’re constantly racing against the clock—deadlines, deployments, and decisions. In this rush, &lt;strong&gt;testing often gets sidelined&lt;/strong&gt;. Some developers see it as optional, or something they’ll “get to later.” But that’s a costly mistake. Because just like documentation, testing is a long-term investment—one that pays off in quality, safety, and peace of mind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;article data-scroll-anchor=&#34;true&#34; data-testid=&#34;conversation-turn-26&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex=&#34;-1&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div data-message-author-role=&#34;assistant&#34; data-message-id=&#34;1760bce0-3b01-408d-b4d3-4720e02089e1&#34; data-message-model-slug=&#34;gpt-4o&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA;   &lt;p data-end=&#34;274&#34; data-start=&#34;64&#34;&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;84&#34; data-start=&#34;64&#34;&gt;Testing is crucial.&lt;/strong&gt; It’s about ensuring quality, guaranteeing expected behavior, and enabling safe refactoring. Without tests, every change becomes a risk. With tests, change becomes an opportunity to improve.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在软件工程领域，我们一直在与时钟竞争 - 排行榜，部署和决策。在这次匆忙中，&lt;strong&gt;测试通常会被缺口&lt;/strong&gt;。一些开发人员将其视为可选的，或者他们“以后再进行”。但这是一个昂贵的错误。因为就像文档一样，测试是一项长期投资 - 一种在质量，安全和安心方面有所帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;文章data-scroll-andor =“ true” data-testid =“对话-turn-26” dir =“ auto”&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex =“  -  1”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div div data-message-author-role =“助手” data-message-id =“ 1760BCE0-3B01-408D-B4D3-4720E02089E1” data-message-model-slug =“ gpt-4O&#xA;   &lt;p data-end =“ 274” data-start =“ 64”&gt; &lt;strong data-end =“ 84” data-start =“ 64”&gt;测试至关重要。&lt;/strong&gt;这是关于确保质量，保证预期的行为并启用安全重构。没有测试，每个变化都会成为风险。通过测试，变化成为改进的机会。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【CRDTs Explained: How Conflict-Free Replicated Data Types Work】CRDT解释了：无冲突的复制数据类型如何工作</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/conflict-free-replicated-data-types-crdt</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In today&#39;s post, I would like to dive deeper into one of the newest—relatively speaking— topics in the distributed systems domain. As you may have guessed already, the spotlight is on Conflict-free Replicated Data Types or CRDTs for short. I will explain what they are and what role they play in the larger landscape of distributed systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Let’s start our journey from explaining what Strong Eventual Consistency (SEC) means in this context.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在今天的帖子中，我想深入研究分布式系统域中最新的主题之一。正如您可能已经猜到的那样，焦点是在简短的无冲突复制数据类型或CRDT上。我将解释它们是什么以及它们在分布式系统的较大景观中扮演什么角色。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;让我们从解释最终的一致性（SEC）在这种情况下开始我们的旅程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Role of Functional Programming in Modern Software Development】功能编程在现代软件开发中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/role-of-functional-programming</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Functional programming is one approach used in modern software development due to technological advancements. It enables developers to write code that is clean, efficient, and easy to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In addition, programming methods that are focused on pure functions, immutability, and declarative style make it easy for developers to create applications. This article analyzes the major principles of functional programming and their importance in modern software development.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;功能编程是由于技术进步而在现代软件开发中使用的一种方法。它使开发人员能够编写干净，高效且易于维护的代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;此外，专注于纯函数，不变性和声明风格的编程方法使开发人员可以轻松创建应用程序。本文分析了功能编程的主要原则及其在现代软件开发中的重要性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Key Considerations in Cross-Model Migration】跨模型迁移的主要考虑因素</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/key-considerations-in-cross-model-migration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the rampant development and release of AI models every few days, ML engineers are expected to conduct comprehensive experiments with different models to choose the best-performing one. However, this is often not a straightforward process — it requires both art and structured methodology.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Modifying the underlying prompts while ensuring best practices is a key challenge that is often not discussed much. Moreover, while it may seem straightforward to simply “swap out” the underlying model and its associated prompt, there are several more nuances to consider — tokenizers, context window sizes, instruction-following abilities, sensitivity to prompt formatting, structured response generation, latency-throughput tradeoff, etc.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;随着AI模型的猖ramp的开发和释放，ML工程师有望使用不同模型进行全面的实验，以选择表现最佳的实验。但是，这通常不是一个直接的过程，而是需要艺术和结构化方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;修改基础提示，同时确保最佳实践是一个主要挑战，通常不会太多讨论。此外，虽然简单地“交换”了基本模型及其相关的提示似乎很简单，但还有更多的差异需要考虑 - 标记，上下文窗口大小，指导遵循指导的能力，对及时格式化，结构化响应生成的敏感性，延迟延迟交易等等。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【5 Best Node.js Practices to Develop Scalable and Robust Applications】5个最佳节点。</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/nodejs-practices-scalable-robust-applications</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Since the software industry is evolving at an incredibly fast speed, there have been many developments in terms of frameworks and different component libraries to enhance the performance, functionalities, and features of applications. And the name Node.js has come among the top ones as it has taken the app development world by storm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just to clarify, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/watch-a-writer-learn-nodejs-part-1&#34;&gt;Node.js&lt;/a&gt; is not a framework, but it is an open-source JavaScript runtime environment that can be operated on Linux, Unix, macOS, and Windows as well. After its initial release in 2009, Node.js has dominated the software industry.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;由于软件行业正在以令人难以置信的快速发展，因此在框架和不同组件库中有许多发展，以增强应用程序的性能，功能和功能。 Node.js这个名字已经成为最重要的，因为它席卷了应用程序开发世界。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;只是为了澄清，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/watch-a-writer-nodejs-part-1”&gt; node.js &lt;/a&gt;不是一个框架，但它是可以在Linux上操作的开放式JavaScript Runtime环境。 Node.js于2009年首次发行后，已经主导了软件行业。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reinforcement Learning for AI Agent Development: Implementing Multi-Agent Systems】AI代理开发的强化学习：实施多代理系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rl-agents-in-action</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;The field of AI has advanced at a breathtaking pace, and reinforcement learning (RL) is now fast emerging as the leading paradigm for the development of intelligent AI agents. You make RL much more powerful when correctly combined with multi-agent systems. That enables agents to compete, coordinate, and train in dynamic environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;This article introduces the concept of reinforcement learning in building AI agents, and more specifically, how to develop multi-agent systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt; AI领域以令人叹为观止的速度提高了，而增强学习（RL）现在正快速出现，成为开发智能AI代理的领先范式。与多代理系统正确结合时，您可以使RL更强大。这使代理商能够在动态环境中竞争，协调和训练。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;本文介绍了在构建AI代理中的强化学习概念，更具体地说是如何开发多机构系统。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling in Practice: Caching and Rate-Limiting With Redis and Next.js】在实践中扩展：用redis和next.js缓存和限制速率</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/caching-rate-limiting-redis-nextjs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As someone who loves shipping products and tools for people to experiment with and use, it was only a matter of time before scalability issues caught up with me. I always knew what scaling meant and how to scale in theory. I was familiar with vertical and horizontal scaling, and the intricacies of each, but again, in theory. I had actually never needed to implement any of them, as my user base was usually modest.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is until I built a faucet that exceeded my expectations in terms of usage. But this massive traction came with its own set of issues. The TL;DR of the issue was that even though I restricted the frequency with which a wallet address could claim funds to once a day, a user could simply spin up new addresses and keep claiming. This resulted in my faucet being drained frequently.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为一个喜欢运输产品和工具供人们实验和使用的工具的人，这只是时间问题，直到可伸缩性问题吸引了我。我一直都知道缩放的含义以及如何在理论上扩展。我熟悉垂直和水平缩放以及每个缩放的复杂性，但从理论上讲。我实际上永远不需要实施其中的任何一个，因为我的用户群通常是适度的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是直到我建立了一个超出我的使用期望的水龙头。但是，这种巨大的牵引力带来了自己的一系列问题。问题的TL; DR是，即使我限制了钱包地址每天要求资金一次的频率，但用户可以简单地旋转新的地址并继续索赔。这导致我的水龙头经常被排干。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 1: Introduction and Power BI Authoring Overview】Power BI嵌入式分析 - 第1部分：简介和Power BI创作概述</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-power-bi-authoring-overview</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: This is a multi-part series exploring Power BI Embedded Analytics. The other parts of the series are listed below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-part-11-powerbi-authori&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Part 1.1: Power BI Authoring Data Federation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-2-powerbi-a&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Part 2: Power BI Embedded Overview&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-3-powerbi-e&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Part 3: Power BI Embedded Demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Analytics&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Analytics is all about making sense of data — finding patterns, uncovering insights, and using that information to make smarter decisions. It involves various techniques and tools to interpret data, create visualisations, and simplify complex information. Whether it’s businesses optimizing operations or researchers making discoveries, analytics is crucial in improving efficiency, productivity, and competitiveness.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;：这是一个探索功率BI嵌入分析的多部分系列。该系列的其他部分如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-part-11-powerbi-authori” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt;第1.1部分：第1.1部分&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-part-part-part-2-powerbi-a” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” noopener noreferrer“ target =” _ black&#39;&gt;第2部分&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-part-3-powerbi-e”&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Analytics &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Analytics就是要理解数据 - 查找模式，发现见解以及使用这些信息来做出更明智的决策。它涉及各种技术和工具来解释数据，创建可视化并简化复杂信息。无论是企业优化运营还是研究人员发现，分析对于提高效率，生产力和竞争力至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>