<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【It Costs That Much Because Observability Takes Hours】它花费了很多，因为可观察性需要数小时</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/observability-costs-explained</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Today’s blog title is inspired by this song, &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NGR20B2cEBQ&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;It Costs That Much&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&#34; My daughter started singing it regularly after she opened her bakery. Read on for details on that story, and how it relates to observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I thought of it, and my daughter’s reasons for singing it, after a few responses to my recent blog post, &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/observability-expenses&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Observability Expenses: When ‘Pennies on the Dollar’ Add Up Quickly&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&#34; It touched a nerve, which was nice to see. This is an important, nuanced, and complex conversation. I believe that getting folks involved in this conversation is better for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;今天的博客标题的灵感来自这首歌，“ &lt;a href =” https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ngr20b2cebq“ rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt;我的女儿开设面包店后，她开始定期唱歌。请继续阅读有关该故事的详细信息及其与可观察性有关的详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我想到了这件事，以及女儿唱歌的理由，经过一些回复我最近的博客文章，“ &lt;a href =” https://dzone.com/articles/observiability-expenses-em&gt;可观察性支出：&lt;em&gt;可观察性支出：当&#39;美元上的便利&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;&#39;便宜&#39;它触动了神经，很高兴看到。这是一次重要，细微差别且复杂的对话。我相信让人们参与这次谈话对每个人都更好。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 12:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PostgreSQL Performance Tuning】PostgreSQL性能调整</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/postgresql-performance-tuning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/manual-sharding-postgresql-implementation-guide&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL&lt;/a&gt; is already known for its reliability, extensibility, and open-source pedigree and continues to grow and evolve with each release. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/incremental-backups-pg-basebackup-postgresql&#34;&gt;PostgreSQL 17&lt;/a&gt; introduces several performance improvements and features that make it a powerhouse for Online Transaction Processing (OLTP) and Online Analytical Processing (OLAP) workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This blog will explore advanced performance tuning techniques for PostgreSQL 17 and highlight key improvements compared to versions 15 and 16.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/manual-sharding-postgresql-implementation-guide-g rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; postgresql &lt;/a&gt;已经知道其可靠性，可靠性，可扩展性，可扩展性，持续和持续的速度和持续性，并持续且持续和持续供应。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/incremental-backups-pg-basebackup-postgresql”&gt; PostgreSQL 17 &lt;/a&gt;引入了一些绩效改进和功能，使其成为在线交易处理（OLTP）和在线分析处理（OLAP）工作（OLAP）工作量的功能。&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;此博客将探索PostgreSQL 17的高级性能调整技术，并与版本15和16相比，突出了关键改进。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered Smart Contracts: The Future Of Automated Decision-Making】AI驱动的智能合约：自动决策的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-smart-contracts-will-drive-automated-decision-making</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I&#39;ve seen many people struggle with slow, error-prone contracts. It&#39;s frustrating when deals get held up by paperwork or mistakes. I get it — I&#39;ve been there too. But here&#39;s some good news: AI-powered smart contracts are changing the game.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I&#39;ve done a ton of research on this topic. When AI and blockchain team up, they work together to make contracts smarter and faster because they use tech like natural language processing to understand contracts better. I&#39;ll show you how these smart contracts can speed up your work and cut down on errors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我已经看到许多人在缓慢而容易出错的合同中挣扎。当交易因文书工作或错误而陷入困境时，这令人沮丧。我明白了 - 我也去过那里。但这是一些好消息：AI驱动的智能合约正在改变游戏。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我已经对此主题进行了大量研究。当AI和区块链合作时，他们共同努力，使合同更聪明，更快，因为他们使用自然语言处理等技术来更好地理解合同。我将向您展示这些智能合约如何加快您的工作并减少错误。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What is Microsoft Fabric for Azure Cloud (Beyond the Buzz) and How It Competes with Snowflake and Databricks】什么是用于Azure Cloud的Microsoft Fabric（超越嗡嗡声），以及如何与雪花和数据链球竞争</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-microsoft-fabric-for-azure-cloud-beyond-th</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you ask your favorite large language model, &lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Fabric appears to be the ultimate solution for any data challenge&lt;/strong&gt; you can imagine. That’s also the impression many people get from Microsoft’s sales teams. But is it really the silver bullet it’s made out to be? &lt;strong&gt;This article takes a closer look&lt;/strong&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first part explores the glossy marketing and sales definition of the platform. The second part looks at Fabris&#39;s layers and deconstructs it from a more practical perspective. The third part uncovers what Microsoft Fabric is truly built for, and how it fits into the wider data landscape, especially in &lt;strong&gt;comparison to other major players in the data analytics market like Databricks and Snowflake&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您询问自己喜欢的大型语言模型，&lt;strong&gt; Microsoft Fabric似乎是您可以想象的任何数据挑战&lt;/strong&gt;的最终解决方案。这也是许多人从微软的销售团队中得到的印象。但是它真的是它所做的银弹吗？ &lt;strong&gt;本文仔细研究&lt;/strong&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第一部分探讨了平台的光泽营销和销售定义。第二部分着眼于法布里斯的层，并从更实用的角度来解构它。第三部分揭示了Microsoft Fabric的真正构建目的，以及它如何适合更广泛的数据格局，尤其是在&lt;strong&gt;中与数据分析市场中的其他主要参与者（如Databricks and Snowflake &lt;/strong&gt;）进行比较。&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing DevOps Pipelines: A Practical Guide to Balancing Speed and Security】确保DevOps管道：平衡速度和安全的实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devops-pipelines-balancing-speed-and-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Security has been a major concern in today’s world. Security issues lead to data breaches with consequences such as data loss and financial losses. As a result, there is a need to focus on enhancing security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OWASP top 10 is a good guide for DevOps teams to mitigate key web application security risks. Integrating security strategies from the beginning to the end of the process can enable DevOps teams to enhance the overall security of the applications&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;安全一直是当今世界上的主要问题。安全问题导致数据泄露，并带来诸如数据丢失和财务损失之类的后果。结果，有必要专注于增强安全性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OWASP前十名是DevOps团队减轻关键Web应用程序安全风险的好指南。从过程开始到结束时整合安全策略可以使DevOps团队能够增强应用程序的整体安全性&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond Bytecode: Exploring the Relationship Between JVM, JIT, and Performance】超越字节码：探索JVM，JIT和性能之间的关系</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/beyond-bytecode-jvm-jit-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In computing, the execution of programs written in high-level languages requires that the source code be compiled to a low-level or native language. This compilation is referred to as &lt;em&gt;Ahead-of-Time (AOT)&lt;/em&gt; and is typically done during build time. Effectively reducing the work to be done during runtime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;In case of Java, the AOT produces an intermediate binary, viz. bytecode, which is then translated to native machine code during execution by the&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/jvm-architecture-explained&#34;&gt;Java Virtual Machine (JVM)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;This is in line with Java’s philosophy of&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Write-Once-Run-Anywhere (WORA)&lt;em style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;or simply put, platform independence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p数​​据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;在计算中，用高级语言编写的程序的执行要求将源代码汇编为低级或母语。此汇编被称为&lt;em&gt;提前（AOT）&lt;em&gt;，通常在构建时间进行。有效地减少在运行时要完成的工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据选择 -  paragraph =“”&gt; &lt;span style =“背景色：透明;”&gt;在Java的情况下，AOT会产生一个中间二进制，即。字节码，然后通过&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em style =“ backgroment-color：transparent;”&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/jvm-Architection- style =“背景色：透明;”&gt;这与Java的&lt;/span&gt; write-once-once-run-where（era）&lt;em style =“ backick-color：prockerparent;”&gt;，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span style =“ backative-color：proback-color：prockit-color：parkerparent;”&gt; probparent;“</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Domain-Centric Agile Modeling for Legacy Insurance Systems】以领域为中心的遗产保险系统的敏捷建模</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/domain-centric-agile-modeling-for-legacy-insurance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Legacy insurance systems have accumulated decades of complexity in their codebases and business logic. This complexity is spread across batch jobs and shaped by regulation, rather than architecture. Directly applying modern Agile modeling to such a landscape often throws developers off track and into frustration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;That is where Agile can work, but only when recentered around the realities of the domain. A domain-first perspective is captured by the fact that success in these environments cannot be achieved by providing screens and endpoints but by replicating the essence of how the business operates.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;传统保险系统在其代码库和业务逻辑中积累了数十年的复杂性。这种复杂性分布在批处理工作中，并由监管而不是体系结构塑造。直接将现代敏捷建模应用于这样的景观通常会使开发人员脱离轨道并陷入挫败感。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这是敏捷可以工作的地方，但只有在围绕域的现实围绕现实时才能使用。通过提供屏幕和端点，可以通过复制业务运作方式的本质来实现这些环境中的成功来捕获一个领域优先的观点。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing Software Created by AI Agents: The Next Security Paradigm】确保AI代理创建的软件：下一个安全范式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/securing-software-created-by-ai-agents</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The rise of impact has had a direct effect on the software development industry since ChatGPT and Generative AI became mainstream in late 2022. The ability of GenAI tools to write workable code was touted as one of its significant advantages, and AI has continued to improve since then. The rise of agentic AI, which can autonomously write, debug, and deploy code to environments, is the next major shift in software development. It also needs a fresh relook from a security perspective.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For years, cybersecurity professionals have highlighted the shift-left approach as a key security pillar, where controls are integrated as early as possible within the lifecycle. However, as&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agentic-101-understanding-ai-agents&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;agentic AI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;becomes more intelligent, we now need to secure software in an environment written entirely by AI, with no human involvement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;影响的兴起对软件开发行业产生了直接影响，因为Chatgpt和Generative AI在2022年底成为主流。Genai工具编写可行代码的能力被吹捧为其重要优势之一，此后AI从那时起就一直在不断改善。可以自主编写，调试和部署代码到环境的代理AI的兴起是软件开发的下一个重大转变。从安全角度来看，它还需要新的重新亮相。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;多年来，网络安全专业人员将左翼方法强调为关键的安全支柱，其中控制器在生命周期内尽早集成。但是，如&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agentic-101-undercanding-underanding-ai-agents”&gt; &lt;span&gt; agesic ai &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt;变得更加聪明，我们现在需要在没有人类参与的环境中完全编写的环境中的软件，而没有人类参与。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enterprise Data Loss Prevention (DLP) Security Policies and Tuning】企业数据损失预防（DLP）安全策略和调整</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-loss-prevention-dlp-security-policies-tuning</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I’ve worked with a lot of enterprise customers over the years—big ones, too—and a common struggle I see is with their Data Loss Prevention (DLP) policies. Even though they’ve had the product for years, they often face one of two issues: either the policies are too weak and don’t flag anything, or they’re too strict, overwhelming teams with false alerts. When DLP policies aren’t properly tuned, it creates gaps that can lead to business disruptions and even huge losses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A well-known example is NASA’s ITAR email filtering issue in 2019, where an excessively strict DLP policy blocked legitimate emails, grinding operations to a halt. While there are many such cases, enterprises rarely disclose disruptions caused by poor policy design. The stakes are simply too high—reputation, confidential information, and, most importantly, customer trust are all on the line. Because of this, companies are often reluctant to seek external help in refining their security policy infrastructure, even when expert guidance could prevent costly mistakes. Ultimately, security software vendors play a crucial role in simplifying policy tuning, ensuring enterprises can strike the right balance between protection and usability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;多年来，我也与许多企业客户合作（也是企业客户），我看到的常见斗争是预防数据丢失（DLP）政策。即使他们拥有多年的产品，他们也经常面临两个问题之一：要么政策太弱，而且没有标记任何东西，要么他们太严格，压倒性的团队具有虚假的警报。当DLP政策未正确调整时，它会产生差距，从而导致业务中断甚至巨大损失。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;一个众所周知的例子是NASA在2019年的ITAR电子邮件过滤问题，在该问题中，过度严格的DLP策略阻止了合法的电子邮件，将操作局限于停顿。尽管有许多这样的案例，但企业很少披露政策设计不佳造成的中断。赌注太高了 - 意见，机密信息，最重要的是，客户信任都在线。因此，即使专家指导可以防止昂贵的错误，公司通常不愿寻求外部帮助来完善其安全政策基础设施。最终，安全软件供应商在简化策略调整方面发挥了至关重要的作用，确保企业可以在保护和可用性之间取得正确的平衡。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Improving Cloud Data Warehouse Performance: Overcoming Bottlenecks With AWS and Third-Party Tools】改善云数据仓库性能：用AWS和第三方工具克服瓶颈</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/cloud-data-warehouse-performance-aws-tools-bottlenecks</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Performance optimization has become paramount in cloud data warehousing for organisations that need to make decisions based on fast, accurate insights. As cloud-native data platforms become the norm for modern businesses, performance bottlenecks that can slow data processing and query execution times present new challenges. These obstacles slow down operations and can also cause higher operational costs, less efficient data processing, and lost business opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;To address these hurdles, organizations turn to AWS, a robust cloud infrastructure capable of providing scalable and reliable solutions, alongside third-party tools for specific performance challenges. In this article, we&#39;ll examine typical performance bottlenecks, how AWS tools can help mitigate them, and the role of third-party tools in improving cloud data warehouse performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;性能优化已成为需要基于快速，准确的见解做出决策的组织的云数据仓库中的重要性。随着云本地数据平台成为现代业务的规范，可以放慢数据处理并查询执行时间的性能瓶颈带来了新的挑战。这些障碍放慢了操作，还可能导致更高的运营成本，效率较低的数据处理和失去商机。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;为了解决这些障碍，组织转向AWS，这是一个强大的云基础架构，能够提供可扩展和可靠的解决方案，以及针对特定绩效挑战的第三方工具。在本文中，我们将研究典型的性能瓶颈，AWS工具如何帮助减轻它们以及第三方工具在改善云数据仓库性能中的作用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>