<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Estimating Software Projects: A Practical Approach for Tech Leads】估计软件项目：技术潜在客户的实用方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/estimating-software-projects-a-practical-approach</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Accurately estimating software projects has been a big challenge for technical leads for quite some time. While there are many established techniques in the market that explain how to estimate a task at hand, they don’t often provide a systematic process to break down tasks, account for unknowns, and track and revisit the estimates. In practice, estimation is an ongoing exercise that keeps evolving with requirements, spikes, and development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A successful estimation requires an organized approach including collaborating with product managers and architects to clarify and align initial requirements, conducting spikes to reduce uncertainty, systematically revisiting and refining estimates, and incorporating effort for testing, code reviews, and deployment tasks into the planning. It is also important to account for buffers to handle unforeseen delays.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;精确估算软件项目是技术线索的巨大挑战。尽管市场上有许多既定的技术来解释如何估算手头的任务，但他们通常并没有提供系统的过程来分解任务，说明未知数，并跟踪和重新审视估计值。实际上，估计是一种正在进行的练习，它不断发展，随着要求，尖峰和发展的发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;成功的估计需要一种有组织的方法，包括与产品经理和建筑师合作，以澄清和满足初始需求，进行尖峰以减少不确定性，系统地重新审视和完善估计，并纳入测试，代码审查和部署任务和部署任务的努力。考虑缓冲区处理不可预见的延迟也很重要。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI/ML for Engineering Managers: Enhancing Productivity and Quality in Fintech】工程经理的AI/ML：增强Fintech的生产力和质量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aiml-for-eng-managers-enhancing-productivity-and-q</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The fintech landscape is rapidly evolving every day and that puts engineering managers in immense pressure to maintain delivery speed, product/engineering quality, and compliance simultaneously. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ai-ml&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning (AI/ML)&lt;/a&gt; techniques offer very helpful and transformative solutions to these challenges by automating repetitive tasks, enhancing code quality, and streamlining regulatory compliance. As a senior engineering manager with deep experience building a neobank back office technology solutions, I&#39;ve observed firsthand how strategically applied AI/ML can significantly help solve the current challenges to the degree the organization is willing to invest.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Why AI/ML Matters in Fintech Engineering&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI and ML technologies uniquely address fintech challenges such as compliance and governance requirements, fraud detection and prevention, and complex risk management beyond simple rule based systems. Traditional &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-the-technological-landscape-of-fintech&#34;&gt;fintech engineering workflows&lt;/a&gt; often rely heavily on manual testing, repetitive reviews, multiple checkpoints with approvals, and intensive documentation—areas ripe for optimization through AI-driven automation with necessary guardrails. Additionally, given the high stakes associated with financial systems, maintaining superior quality through robust, proactive monitoring and building circuit breakers are critical.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;金融科技景观每天都在迅速发展，这使工程经理承受着巨大的压力，以维持交付速度，产品/工程质量以及同时合规性。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/ai-ml”&gt;人工智能和机器学习（AI/ML）&lt;/a&gt;技术通过使重复任务自动化，增强代码质量和简化监管合规性，为这些挑战提供了非常有用的变革解决方案。作为具有深厚经验的高级工程经理，建立了Neobank Back Office Technology Solutions，我亲眼目睹了AI/ML的战略性应用如何极大地帮助解决该组织愿意投资的程度的当前挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;为什么AI/ML在金融科技工程中很重要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; AI和ML技术独特地应对金融科技挑战，例如合规性和治理要求，欺诈检测和预防，以及基于简单规则的系统以外的复杂风险管理。传统&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-the-technologice-landscape-of-fintech”&gt; Fintech Engineering Workfrows &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;手动测试，重新定位的评论，经过批准的多个检查点，批准和强度的文档，以及通过Aelease fiffiention-aborease-aborefients afient a nime nii deriviender nii deriviender nii deriviender a自动化。此外，鉴于与金融系统相关的高赌注，通过强大的，主动的监视和建筑断路器来保持卓越的质量至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scalable Distributed Architectures in E-Commerce: Proven Case Studies】电子商务中可扩展的分布式体系结构：经过验证的案例研究</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scalable-distributed-architectures-in-e-commerce-case-studies</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern e-commerce platforms must handle &lt;em&gt;massive scale&lt;/em&gt; – from flash sales driving sudden traffic spikes to global user bases demanding low-latency experiences. Achieving this reliability and performance at scale requires robust distributed architectures. In this article, I’ll share three case studies of &lt;strong&gt;scalable e-commerce architectures&lt;/strong&gt; that I’ve analyzed and worked with, each leveraging a different tech stack:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-beginners-guide-to-building-microservices-with-a&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serverless microservices on AWS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; – how Amazon’s cloud (Lambda, SQS, DynamoDB, etc.) solved real-world scaling problems for an online retailer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-step-by-step-guide-to-deploying-containers-in-the-cloud&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Containerized services on Google Cloud&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; – using GCP’s serverless containers (Cloud Run, Firestore, Pub/Sub, BigQuery) for high traffic and maintainability in a retail scenario.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-cloud-native-architecture&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Open-source cloud-native stack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; – a Kubernetes, Kafka, Redis, PostgreSQL architecture that scaled a large online retail platform with open source tooling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each example will include an architecture diagram, key components (with a table where helpful), the challenges faced, and how the design addressed them – along with deployment and operations insights. As an engineering lead, I’ll also highlight practical takeaways from these architectures. Let’s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代电子商务平台必须处理&lt;em&gt;大规模规模&lt;/em&gt;  - 从闪光销售推动突然的交通尖峰到全球用户群，需要低延迟的体验。在大规模上实现这种可靠性和性能需要强大的分布式体系结构。在本文中，我将分享我分析和合作的三个&lt;strong&gt;可扩展的电子商务体系结构&lt;/strong&gt;，每个案例都利用了不同的技术堆栈：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a-beginners-guide-to-building-microservices-microservices-with-a”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; aws &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;  -   -  &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;  - 亚马逊的云（lambda，sqs，sqs，dynamodb等）solved Real for and for An for An for An for An for An for An for An for An for An for An。&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a-step-by-step-guide-to-deploying-containers-containers-in-in-the-cloud”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在Google Cloud Cloud &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;上使用GOGEE Cloud&gt; &lt;/a&gt;  - 使用GCP的无服务器容器（使用GCP的无服务器容器）（Cloud，firestore，firestore，firestore，firestore，li，big/big/big/big/big）&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-cloud-native-architecture”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; open-Source cloud-native stack &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;  -  kubernetes，kubernetes，kafka，kafka，kafka，kafka，redis，redis，toestgresql，具有大型在线架构，缩放了开放式式的lie support forpect inable oper fool recode recuce squine forne li li&gt; &lt;/li/li。&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个示例都将包括一个架构图，关键组件（带有一个有用的表格），面临的挑战以及设计如何解决这些挑战以及部署和操作见解。作为工程领导，我还将重点介绍这些架构的实际收获。让我们潜入。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS SNS (Amazon Simple Notification Service) and Spring Boot With Email as Subscriber】AWS SNS（Amazon简单通知服务）和带有电子邮件的弹簧启动作为订户</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-sns-spring-boot-email-subscriber</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The concepts of &#34;topic&#34; and &#34;subscribe&#34; are often linked, especially in contexts like messaging systems, event-driven architectures, or content platforms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Publisher&lt;/strong&gt;: This is the source or entity that produces messages or events. The publisher doesn&#39;t need to know who will consume its messages.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Topic&lt;/strong&gt;: This acts as a channel or intermediary that categorizes messages. Publishers post messages to specific topics, and subscribers listen to those topics. It&#39;s used in systems like message brokers (e.g., RabbitMQ, AWS SNS, Apache Kafka) to allow publishers to send messages without worrying about who will receive them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subscriber&lt;/strong&gt;: These are the entities that consume the messages from the topics they&#39;re interested in. Subscribers can dynamically choose topics to receive only the information they need.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Amazon SNS (Simple Notification Service) Topic&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/amazon-sns-simple-notification-service-using-visua&#34;&gt;Amazon SNS&lt;/a&gt; provides message delivery from publishers to subscribers using the pub/sub pattern. Publishers send messages to an SNS topic, and subscribers receive those messages through their chosen endpoints.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;“主题”和“订阅”的概念通常是链接的，尤其是在消息传递系统，事件驱动架构或内容平台等上下文中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;发布者&lt;/strong&gt;：这是产生消息或事件的源或实体。发布者不需要知道谁会消耗其消息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;主题&lt;/strong&gt;：这是对消息进行分类的渠道或中介。发布者向特定主题发布消息，订阅者会聆听这些主题。它用于诸如Message Brokers（例如RabbitMQ，AWS SNS，Apache Kafka）之类的系统中，允许发布者发送消息而不必担心谁会收到它们。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;订阅者&lt;/strong&gt;：这些是消耗来自他们感兴趣的主题的消息的实体。订户可以动态选择主题以仅接收所需的信息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; Amazon SNS（简单通知服务）主题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/amazon-sns-simple-notification-notification-service-using-visua”&gt; Amazon sns &lt;/a&gt;使用pub/sub模式提供从发布者到订户的消息传递。发布者将消息发送到SNS主题，订户通过所选端点接收这些消息。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tail Sampling: The Future of Intelligent Observability in Distributed Systems】尾巴采样：分布式系统中智能可观察性的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/tail-sampling-observability-opentelemetry</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Observability has become a critical component for maintaining system health and performance. While traditional sampling methods have served their purpose, the emergence of tail sampling represents a paradigm shift in how we approach trace collection and analysis. This intelligent sampling strategy is revolutionizing the way organizations handle telemetry data, offering unprecedented precision in capturing the most valuable traces while optimizing storage costs and system performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the Sampling Landscape&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before diving into tail sampling, it&#39;s essential to understand the broader context of sampling strategies. Traditional head-based sampling makes decisions at the beginning of a trace&#39;s lifecycle, determining whether to collect or discard telemetry data based on predetermined criteria such as sampling rates or simple rules. While effective for reducing data volume, this approach often results in the loss of critical information about error conditions, performance anomalies, or rare but important system behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;可观察性已成为维持系统健康和性能的关键组成部分。虽然传统的抽样方法已经达到了目的，但尾巴采样的出现代表了我们如何处理痕量收集和分析的范式转变。这种智能抽样策略正在彻底改变组织处理遥测数据的方式，在捕获最有价值的痕迹的同时，在优化存储成本和系统性能的同时，提供了前所未有的精度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解采样景观&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在进行尾巴采样之前，必须了解采样策略的更广泛背景。传统的基于头部的采样在痕迹的生命周期开始时做出决策，确定是基于预定标准（例如采样率还是简单规则）收集还是丢弃遥测数据。尽管有效地减少数据量，但这种方法通常会导致有关错误条件，性能异常或罕见但重要的系统行为的关键信息的丢失。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why I Abandoned My 30-Year Open-Source Project】为什么我放弃了30年的开源项目</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-i-abandoned-my-30-year-open-source-project</link>
      <description>【&lt;div class=&#34;table-responsive&#34; style=&#34;border: none;&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: A Human wrote this article. Other than proofreading and sentence-level style suggestions, no AI was utilized. This is one of the last surviving members of its kind.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I started an open-source project in 1996, I am abandoning now. It was not my first OSS project and certainly not the last one. It definitely was the one that lasted the longest and that I had the most faith in having an impact on the industry.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div class =“ table响应”样式=“ border：none;”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;：一个人写了这篇文章。除了校对和句子级别的建议外，没有使用AI。这是同类人的最后一个幸存的成员之一。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我于1996年启动了一个开源项目，现在我放弃了。这不是我的第一个OSS项目，当然也不是最后一个项目。绝对是持续时间最长的人，我对影响该行业有最大的信心。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Create Your Own Custom LLM: Essential Steps and Techniques】创建自己的自定义LLM：基本步骤和技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/creating-a-custom-llm-steps-and-techniques</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We will start by defining the most fundamental building block of LLMs: Language modeling, which dates back to early statistical NLP methods in the 1980s and 1990s and was later popularized with the advent of neural networks in the early 2010s.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;05/17/2025 07:18 AM&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18408020-1747466290963.png&#34; data-size=&#34;272836&#34; data-id=&#34;18408020&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;272.8 kB&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1747466291583&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-name=&#34;1747466290963.png&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18408020-1747466290963.png&#34; alt=&#34;Language modeling&#34;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In its simplest form, language modeling is essentially about learning to predict the next word in a sentence. This task, known as next-word prediction, is at the core of how LLMs learn language patterns. The model accomplishes this by estimating the probability distribution over sequences of words, allowing it to predict the likelihood of any given next word based on the context provided by the preceding words.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们将首先定义LLM的最基本构建基块：语言建模，该块可以追溯到1980年代和1990年代的早期统计NLP方法，后来随着2010年代初的神经网络的出现而普及。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;img data-new =“ false” data-mimetype =“ image/png” data-creationdateFormatted =“ 05/17/2025 07:18 am” data-url =“ https:///dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage com.com/storage/storage/storage/storage/tempore/tempore/temp/temp/184020-20-20-1777466.ppn.ppet/184074666.ppn data-size =“ 272836” data-id =“ 18408020” class =“ fr-fic fr-dib lazyload” data-image =“ true” data-sizeFormatted =“ 272.8 kb” data-creationdate =“ 17474666291583” data-name =“ 1747466290963.png” data-src =“ https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/storage/temp/18408020-174747466290963.png&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以最简单的形式，语言建模本质上是关于学习预测句子中的下一个单词。该任务称为下字预测，是LLM如何学习语言模式的核心。该模型通过估计单词序列的概率分布来实现这一目标，从而可以根据前面单词提供的上下文来预测任何给定下一个单词的可能性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Simple AIOps Monitoring Dashboard With Prometheus and Grafana】用Prometheus和Grafana构建一个简单的AIOPS监视仪表板</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aiops-monitoring-dashboard-prometheus-grafana</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Machine learning (ML) is being used by AIOps (Artificial Intelligence for IT Operations) to find problems, predict failures, and automate reactions. This is changing how businesses handle their IT environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This guide will show you how to make a simple monitoring dashboard that uses Prometheus to collect data and Grafana to demonstrate it. We&#39;ll also add some basic AIOps tools to the panel to make it better by adding anomaly detection, which will let you keep an eye on things before they go wrong.&lt;/p&gt;】AIOPS（用于IT操作的人工智能）使用&lt;p&gt;机器学习（ML）来发现问题，预测故障和自动反应。这正在改变企业处理其IT环境的方式。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本指南将向您展示如何制作一个简单的监视仪表板，该仪表板使用Prometheus收集数据和Grafana进行演示。我们还将在面板中添加一些基本的AIOPS工具，以通过添加异常检测来使其更好，这将使您在出现问题之前密切注意。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【LangGraph Orchestrator Agents: Streamlining AI Workflow Automation】Langgraph编排代理：简化AI工作流程自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/langgraph-orchestrator-agents-streamline-ai-work</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;In AI-driven applications, complex tasks often require breaking down into multiple subtasks. However, the exact subtasks cannot be predetermined in many real-world scenarios. For instance, in automated code generation, the number of files to be modified and the specific changes needed depend entirely on the given request. Traditional parallelized workflows struggle unpredictably, requiring tasks to be predefined upfront. This rigidity limits the adaptability&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;of AI systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;However, the Orchestrator-Workers Workflow Agents in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/langchain-langgraph-langflow-langsmith-ai-guide&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;LangGraph&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;introduce a more flexible and intelligent approach to address this challenge. Instead of relying on static task definitions, a&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle=&#34;Hyperlink&#34;&gt;central orchestrator LLM dynamically analyses the input&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;, determines the required subtasks, and delegates them to specialized worker LLMs. The orchestrator then collects and synthesizes the outputs, ensuring a cohesive final result. These&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-charstyle=&#34;Hyperlink&#34;&gt;Gen AI services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;enable real-time decision-making, adaptive task management, and higher accuracy, ensuring that complex workflows are handled with smarter agility and precision.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ in-in”&gt;在AI驱动的应用程序中，复杂的任务通常需要分解为多个子任务。但是，在许多实际情况下，确切的子任务不能预先确定。例如，在自动代码生成中，要修改的文件数和所需的特定更改完全取决于给定的请求。传统的并行工作流程不可预测，要求预先定义任务。这种刚度限制了适应性&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ in”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” auto“ auto” lang =“ inan&gt;” aisystems。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ in-in”&gt;但是，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/langchain-langchain-langgraph-langgraph-langflow-langflow-langsmith-langsmith-ai-guide-guide-guide”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ lang =“ in-in”&gt; langgraph &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ in-in”&gt;引入了一种更灵活，更智能的方法来应对这一挑战。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ in”&gt; &lt;span-ccp-carstyle =“ hyperlink”&gt;中央乐曲LLM动态分析输入&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; LLMS。然后，编排者收集并合成输出，确保最终结果。这些&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ in”&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-charstyle =“超链接”&gt; gen ai ai服务&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data data-contrast =“ auto” auto“ lang =“ in in in in in in”&gt;启用实时决策，适应性的任务管理，以及更高的准确性，以及更高的准确性，以及随之而来的工作，以及随之而来的工作，并努力工作。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-ccp-props =“ {” 335551550“：6，” 335551620“：6}”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker Multi-Stage Builds: Optimizing Development and Production Workflows】Docker多阶段构建：优化开发和生产工作流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-multi-stage-builds-image-optimization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Hey there, fellow &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-use-cases-15-most-common-ways-to-use-docker&#34;&gt;Docker&lt;/a&gt; enthusiasts! If you&#39;ve been containerizing applications for a while, you&#39;ve probably run into this all-too-familiar frustration: your &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-image-building-best-practices&#34;&gt;Docker images&lt;/a&gt; are absolutely massive, they take forever to build and deploy, and you&#39;re left wondering if there&#39;s got to be a better way. Trust me, I&#39;ve been there—staring at a 1.4GB image thinking &#34;surely this can&#39;t be right?&#34;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After years of wrestling with bloated containers (and some very unhappy DevOps teammates), I finally embraced multi-stage builds—and honestly, it&#39;s been a complete game-changer. In this article, I&#39;ll share what I&#39;ve learned about this powerful but often overlooked Docker feature that could revolutionize your containerization workflow.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;嘿，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/docker-use-cases-15-most-common-ways-ways-to-use-docker”&gt; docker &lt;/a&gt;爱好者！如果您已经将应用程序化了一段时间了，那么您可能会遇到这种非常熟悉的挫败感：您的&lt;a a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/docker-image-image-building-best-------------&gt; docker映像&lt;/a&gt;绝对是巨大的，如果在那里，您会想知道，如果有更好的构建和部署，那么您就可以更好地想知道。相信我，我去过那里 - 以1.4GB的图像为标题，以为“这肯定是不对的？” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;经过多年与肿的容器（和一些非常不愉快的Devops队友）进行搏斗之后，我终于接受了多阶段的构建，老实说，这是一个完整的改变游戏规则的人。在本文中，我将分享我对这个功能强大但经常被忽略的Docker功能的了解，该功能可能会彻底改变您的容器化工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>