<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring Playwright’s Feature “Copy Prompt”】探索剧作家的功能“复制提示”</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/exploring-playwrights-feature-copy-prompt</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Web automation testing demands both efficient processes and precise outcomes. Microsoft developed Playwright as an open-source framework, which gained recognition for its powerful browser automation across Chromium, Firefox, and WebKit. Playwright consistently releases new features through ongoing updates that optimize workflows for both developers and testers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;The new “&lt;strong&gt;Copy prompt&lt;/strong&gt;”&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;feature introduced in &lt;a href=&#34;https://playwright.dev/docs/release-notes#version-151&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;version 1.51&lt;/a&gt; enhances debugging processes through the capabilities of large language models (LLMs). This blog will explain this feature’s functionality and workings before demonstrating its practical application through an example.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p数​​据选择 - 段落=“” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; Web自动化测试都需要有效的过程和精确的结果。 Microsoft开发了剧作家作为开源框架，该框架因其在铬，Firefox和Webkit的强大浏览器自动化而获得认可。剧作家始终通过正在进行的更新发布新功能，以优化开发人员和测试人员的工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据选择 - 段=“”&gt;新的“ &lt;strong&gt;复制提示&lt;/strong&gt;” &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://playwright.docs/release-notes#version-151”大语言模型（LLM）的功能。该博客将在通过示例演示其实际应用之前解释此功能的功能和工作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SAP HANA Triggers: Enhancing Database Logic and Automation】SAP HANA触发器：增强数据库逻辑和自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/sap-hana-triggers-enhancing-database-logic-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;SAP HANA is a powerful in-memory database platform that offers advanced features to manage and analyze data efficiently. Among these features, triggers play a crucial role in automating database operations and enforcing business logic at the database level.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we will discuss SAP HANA triggers, their types, and practical use cases to demonstrate how they can be leveraged effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; SAP HANA是一个功能强大的内存数据库平台，可提供高级功能来高效管理和分析数据。在这些功能中，触发器在自动化数据库操作并在数据库级别执行业务逻辑中起着至关重要的作用。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将讨论SAP HANA触发器，它们的类型和实际用例，以说明如何有效利用它们。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Distributed Multi-Language Data Science System】构建分布式多语言数据科学系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/distributed-multi-language-data-science-system</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;How can we, software developers of the 2020s, stay competitive in the world of automation? Would LLM-based code-generating AI (GAI), like OpenAI services, take over our jobs? Would template-based code generators/software robots (TSR), like UiPath, Blue Prism, Strapi, etc., make developers irrelevant? The short answer is no! We should embrace automation whenever reasonable and focus on &#34;business valuable&#34; hard-to-automate skills.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To be specific, consider a common distributed microservice information system (IS) in Fig. 1. There are domain microservices, data science (DS)/operations research (OR) microservices, and a composer service to aggregate data from the microservices (See Appendix A for the terminology).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; 2020年代的软件开发人员如何在自动化世界中保持竞争力？基于LLM的代码生成AI（GAI）（例如OpenAI Services）是否会接管我们的工作？基于模板的代码生成器/软件机器人（TSR），例如UIPATH，BLUE PRISM，Strapi等，是否使开发人员无关紧要？简短的答案是否！我们应该在合理的情况下接受自动化，并专注于“有价值的”难以自动化的技能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要具体，请考虑图1中的共同分布式微服务信息系统（IS）。有域微服务，数据科学（DS）/操作研究（OR）微服务（OR）微服务和作曲家服务来汇总微服务（有关术语的附录A）。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 22:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dynamically Scaling Containers With KEDA and IBM App Connect】使用KEDA和IBM App Connect动态缩放容器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dynamically-scaling-containers-keda-ibm-app-connect</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Planning for highly variable workloads has always been a difficult art, with the attendant risks of over-provisioning (leading to waste) or under-provisioning (leading to poor performance) of computing resources, but container-based solutions can handle the challenge in ways that would have been difficult in a static VM world.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address this in some common cases, KEDA (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-kubernetes-event-driven-auto-scali&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Event-Driven Autoscaling&lt;/a&gt;) provides a way to automatically scale containers based on metrics such as IBM MQ queue depths, allowing scaling up as needed and then down to zero when the load dies away.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;规划高度可变的工作负载一直是一项艰巨的艺术，因为有过度提供（导致浪费）或不足的计算资源（导致性能较差）的风险，但是基于容器的解决方案可以以静态VM世界难以应对的方式应对挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address this in some common cases, KEDA (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-kubernetes-event-driven-auto-scali&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Event-Driven Autoscaling&lt;/a&gt;) provides a way to automatically scale containers based on metrics such as IBM MQ queue depths, allowing scaling up根据需要，然后在负载死亡时将其下降到零。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bridging Cloud and On-Premises Log Processing】桥接云和本地日志处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/bridging-cloud-and-on-premises-log-processing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern cloud-native architectures require robust, scalable, and secure log processing solutions to monitor distributed applications. This study presents a hybrid solution for log collection, aggregation, and analysis using Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) for log generation, Fluent Bit for log collection, Azure EventHub for intermediary aggregation, and Splunk deployed on an on-premises Apache CloudStack cluster for comprehensive log indexing and visualization.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We detail the system’s design, implementation, and evaluation, demonstrating how this architecture supports reliable and scalable log processing for cloud-native workloads while retaining control over data on-premises.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代云本地体系结构需要强大，可扩展和安全的日志处理解决方案来监视分布式应用程序。这项研究提供了用于日志收集，聚集和分析的混合解决方案，使用Azure Kubernetes服务（AKS）进行日志生成，流利的log集合，用于日志收集的位，用于中间聚集的Azure EventHub以及部署在本地的Apache CloudStack群集上，用于全面的日志和可视化。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们详细介绍了系统的设计，实施和评估，展示了该体系结构如何支持可靠且可扩展的日志处理，以用于云本地工作负载，同时保留对数据的控制。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Secure File Transfer as a Critical Component for AI Success】安全文件传输作为AI成功的关键组件</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-file-transfer-critical-component-ai-success</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Secure file transfer (SFT) has become one of the most crucial technologies in the modern Information technology (IT) landscape for ensuring data security and confidentiality. SFT is a hot topic in today’s world, especially when decisions are being made based on data. It is used to transfer data between systems in a secure manner to avoid the tempering of data or loss of data integrity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-to-secure-data-transmission-in-a-gl&#34;&gt;SFT helps&lt;/a&gt; in keeping track of data for audit trial purposes to ensure accountability and support compliance. This is even more so for AI projects, which rely on such data to be timely transferred, stored, and processed safely and accurately.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;安全文件传输（SFT）已成为现代信息技术（IT）领域中最关键的技术之一，以确保数据安全性和机密性。 SFT是当今世界上的热门话题，尤其是在根据数据做出决定时。它用于以安全的方式在系统之间传输数据，以避免数据的回火或数据完整性的丢失。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-to-secure-data-transmission-in-a-gl”&gt; sft&gt; sft帮助&lt;/a&gt;以跟踪数据以进行审核试验目的，以确保问责制和支持合规性。对于AI项目而言，这甚至更是如此，这些项目依靠此类数据可以及时传输，存储和准确地处理。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bringing Security to Digital Product Design】将安全性带入数字产品设计</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/bring-security-to-digital-product-design</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;One of the biggest problems in digital product development today is the failure to collaborate with InfoSec or DevSecOps teams. Unfortunately, threats are ubiquitous and increasingly sophisticated. But did you know that there is a way to reduce the time spent remediating security issues by up to 50%?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In 2016, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dora.dev/publications/pdf/state-of-devops-2016.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;State of DevOps Report&lt;/a&gt; published its research indicating that high-performing teams spent less than half the time fixing security issues compared to low-performing teams. And the solution to this is &lt;strong&gt;to move left&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p数​​据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;当今数字产品开发中最大的问题之一是未与Infosec或DevSecops团队合作。不幸的是，威胁无处不在且越来越复杂。但是您是否知道有一种方法可以将修复安全问题花费的时间最多减少50％？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In 2016, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dora.dev/publications/pdf/state-of-devops-2016.pdf&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;State of DevOps Report&lt;/a&gt; published its research indicating that high-performing teams spent less than half the time fixing security与表现不佳的团队相比。解决方案是&lt;strong&gt;向左移动&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Frugal AI: How Efficiency is Reshaping the Future of Tech】节俭的AI：效率如何重塑技术的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/frugal-ai-efficiency-reshaping-tech</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As the energy and climate footprint of digital technologies keeps accelerating, frugal AI emerges as an alternative that seeks to reconcile innovation with environmental responsibility. What is this approach? Can it truly establish itself against current ultra-powerful yet energy-intensive models? What are the challenges and opportunities associated with its adoption? Let&#39;s break it down.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;At a global scale, digital technology today accounts for nearly 4% of greenhouse gas emissions, a figure that is steadily increasing, with an annual growth rate of 6%. This footprint is now comparable to that of the civil aviation sector. Around the world, digital energy consumption is following an exponential trajectory. But how can we balance technological innovation with environmental responsibility? And could frugal AI be a viable solution?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;随着数字技术的能量和气候足迹不断加速，节俭的AI成为一种替代方案，试图将创新与环境责任调和。这是什么方法？它可以真正地与当前的超功能强度但能源密集型模型建立自己的建立？与采用相关的挑战和机遇是什么？让我们分解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在全球范围内，当今的数字技术占温室气体排放的近4％，这一数字正在稳步增长，年增长率为6％。现在，这种足迹与民航部门相媲美。在世界范围内，数字能源消耗遵循指数轨迹。但是，我们如何平衡技术创新与环境责任？节俭的AI可以成为可行的解决方案吗？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Financial Data and RAG Usage in LLMs】LLMS中的财务数据和RAG使用情况</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/financial-data-amp-rag</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The importance of integrating artificial intelligence in finance stems from its ability to process vast amounts of data at unprecedented speeds, enabling financial institutions to make more informed decisions and improve operational efficiencies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To understand what AI brings to the table, let&#39;s first delve into the basics of AI as per recent trends. Let&#39;s start with the basic use case the language models were designed to solve and predict the next word in a sequence based on probability learned from trained data. This training grew to a scale of processing billions of parameters using massive datasets. There comes the true potential realization of the models, allowing models to capture more complex relations in language.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;将人工智能整合到金融中的重要性源于其以前所未有的速度处理大量数据的能力，使金融机构能够做出更明智的决策并提高运营效率。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解AI带来的东西，让我们首先根据最近的趋势来深入研究AI的基础知识。让我们从基本用例开始，该语言模型旨在根据从训练有素的数据中学到的概率来解决和预测下一个单词。使用大量数据集，该培训增长到了数十亿个参数的规模。实现了模型的真正潜在实现，从而使模型可以捕获语言中更复杂的关系。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 20:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Role of Data Annotation Services in AI-Powered Manufacturing】数据注释服务在AI驱动的制造中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-annotation-in-ai-manufacturing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Before diving deep into how AI/ML is a boon for manufacturers, let’s explore how the industry has evolved. Steam and water-powered mechanics disrupted manual processes, thus filling the demand versus supply gap. The introduction of assembly lines followed, allowing manufacturers to increase output while reducing product prices. Partial automation further empowered the manufacturers with mass production capability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, the next big breakthrough came with AI and ML, adding intelligence to the automation formula. In other words, AI is at the forefront of industrial revolution 4.0. Not only this, but a strategic combination of AI with new-age technologies such as cloud computing, IoT, robotics, etc., spearheads the manufacturing industry to new heights, making the processes more accurate, efficient, and scalable.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在深入研究AI/ML是制造商的福音之前，让我们探讨该行业的发展方式。蒸汽和水力力学破坏了手动过程，从而填补了需求与供应差距。随后引入了组装线，使制造商能够在降低产品价格的同时增加产出。部分自动化进一步授权制造商具有质量生产能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，下一个重大突破是AI和ML，为自动化公式增加了智能。换句话说，AI处于工业革命4.0的最前沿。不仅如此，而且AI与云计算，物联网，机器人技术等新时代技术的战略组合将制造行业带到了新的高度，使过程更加准确，高效且可扩展。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>