<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Processing Cloud Data With DuckDB And AWS S3】使用DuckDB和AWS S3处理云数据</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/processing-cloud-data-duckdb-aws</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;DuckDb is a powerful in-memory database that has a parallel processing feature, which makes it a good choice to read/transform cloud storage data, in this case, AWS S3. I&#39;ve had a lot of success using it and I will walk you through the steps in implementing it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I will also include some learnings and best practices for you. Using the &lt;code&gt;DuckDb&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;httpfs&lt;/code&gt; extension and &lt;code&gt;pyarrow&lt;/code&gt;, we can efficiently process Parquet files stored in S3 buckets. Let&#39;s dive in:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; duckDB是一个功能强大的内存数据库，具有并行处理功能，这是读取/转换云存储数据的理想选择，在这种情况下，AWS S3。使用它，我取得了很大的成功，我将带您完成实施的步骤。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我还将为您提供一些学习和最佳实践。使用&lt;code&gt; DuckDB &lt;/code&gt;，&lt;code&gt; httpfs &lt;/code&gt;扩展名和&lt;code&gt; pyarrow &lt;/code&gt;，我们可以有效地处理存储在S3存储桶中的Parquet文件。让我们潜水：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Productivity and Organization Tips for Software Engineers】软件工程师的生产力和组织技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-engineer-productivity-and-organization-tips</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a software engineer for a little over a decade now, and I like to think I’m a pretty organized person. I have a system for everything, and these systems help my mind and my day run more smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organization isn’t something that comes naturally to everyone, so today, I thought I’d share some of my strategies that help me have a productive and fulfilling work day.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我已经是一名软件工程师已经有十多年了，我想认为我是一个非常有条理的人。我有一个适合所有系统的系统，这些系统有助于我的头脑，我的一天运行更加顺利。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;组织并不是每个人都自然而然的事情，所以今天，我想分享一些我的一些策略，可以帮助我度过一个富有成效且充实的工作日。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SOC 2 Made Simple: Your Guide to Certification】SOC 2简单：您的认证指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/soc-two-certification-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;No matter where your company is located and in which field it operates, one thing is always true: today, SOC 2 is one of the standards tech companies should meet to be recognized for their security practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re tackling an audit for the first time, it can feel like you don’t even know where to start. And let’s be honest, hiring expensive security consultants isn’t always an option, especially if cash is tight. That’s exactly why I’m writing this — a practical guide with just enough theory to get you through it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;无论您的公司的地点如何以及在哪个领域运营，一件事始终是正确的：今天，SOC 2是技术公司应为其安全惯例认可的标准技术公司之一。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您是第一次进行审核，那么您甚至都不知道从哪里开始。老实说，雇用昂贵的安全顾问并不总是一种选择，尤其是在现金紧张的情况下。这就是我写这篇文章的原因 - 实用的指南，具有足够的理论来使您完成。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Modern Data Architectures With Azure Data Services】使用Azure数据服务构建现代数据体系结构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-modern-data-architectures-azure-data-services</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Modern data architecture is necessary for organizations trying to remain competitive. It is not a choice. Organizations are finding it difficult to use the exponentially expanding amounts of data effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Importance of Modern Data Architectures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Modern data architectures remain relevant, considering that they offer businesses and foster a systematic way of dealing with large quantities of data and, in return, make faster and quicker decisions. Modern businesses rely on these architectures because they provide real-time processing, powerful analytics, and numerous data sources.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;现代数据体系结构对于试图保持竞争力的组织是必需的。这不是一个选择。组织发现很难有效地使用指数量扩展数量的数据。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;span&gt;现代数据体系结构的重要性&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;考虑到它们为企业提供并促进了处理大量数据的系统方式，并做出更快，更快的决策。现代企业依靠这些架构，因为它们提供了实时处理，强大的分析和众多数据来源。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data Governance Essentials: Policies and Procedures (Part 6)】数据治理要素：政策和程序（第6部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-governance-policies-procedures-part-six</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;s Data Governance, and How Do Data Quality, Policies, and Procedures Strengthen It?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Data governance&amp;nbsp;refers to the overall management of data availability, usability, integrity, and security in an organization. It encompasses people, processes, policies, standards, and roles that ensure the effective use of information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Data quality is a foundational aspect of data governance, ensuring that data is reliable, accurate, and fit for purpose. High-quality data is accurate, complete, consistent, and timely, which is essential for informed decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;的数据治理，以及数据质量，政策和程序如何增强它？&lt;/strong &gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”样式=“ text-align：left;”&gt;数据治理是指组织中数据可用性，可用性，完整性和安全性的整体管理。它涵盖了确保有效利用信息的人员，过程，政策，标准和角色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;数据质量是数据治理的基础方面，可确保数据可靠，准确且适合目的。高质量的数据是准确，完整，一致和及时的，这对于明智的决策至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Automating AWS Infrastructure Deployment】自动化AWS基础架构部署指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automate-aws-infrastructure-deployment</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When it comes to managing infrastructure in the cloud, AWS provides several powerful tools that help automate the creation and management of resources.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most effective ways to handle deployments is through &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cloudformation-getting-started-for-beginners&#34;&gt;AWS CloudFormation&lt;/a&gt;. It allows you to define your infrastructure in a declarative way, making it easy to automate the provisioning of AWS services, including Elastic Beanstalk, serverless applications, EC2 instances, security groups, load balancers, and more.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在管理云中的基础架构时，AWS提供了几种有助于自动化资源创建和管理的强大工具。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;处理部署的最有效方法之一是通过&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cloudformation-getting-getting-started-for-beginners”&gt; aws cloud cloud Formation &lt;/a&gt;。它允许您以声明性的方式定义基础架构，从而轻松自动化AWS服务的配置，包括弹性beanstalk，无服务器应用程序，EC2实例，安全组，负载平衡器等。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Teradata Performance and Skew Prevention Tips】Teradata性能和偏斜预防技巧</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/teradata-performance-skew-prevention-tips</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Understanding Teradata Data Distribution and Performance Optimization&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Teradata performance optimization and database tuning are crucial for modern enterprise data warehouses. Effective data distribution strategies and data placement mechanisms are key to maintaining fast query responses and system performance, especially when handling petabyte-scale data and real-time analytics.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understanding &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-distribution-via-api-can-a-single-developer-d&#34;&gt;data distribution&lt;/a&gt; mechanisms, workload management, and data warehouse management directly affects query optimization, system throughput, and database performance optimization. These database management techniques enable organizations to enhance their data processing capabilities and maintain competitive advantages in enterprise data analytics.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt;了解Teradata数据分布和性能优化&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Teradata性能优化和数据库调整对于现代企业数据仓库至关重要。有效的数据分配策略和数据放置机制是维持快速查询响应和系统性能的关键，尤其是在处理PBABYTE尺度数据和实时分析时。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;理解&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/data-distribution-via-api-can-a-single-developer-d”&gt;数据分布数据仓库管理直接影响查询优化，系统吞吐量和数据库性能优化。这些数据库管理技术使组织能够增强其数据处理能力并保持企业数据分析中的竞争优势。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging Neo4j for Effective Identity Access Management】利用neo4j进行有效的身份访问管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/leveraging-neo4j-for-identity-access-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;A while ago, I explored&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;Neo4j&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;, a powerful graph database, earlier for the implementation of the &#34;&lt;/span&gt;six degrees of separation&#34;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;concept.&lt;/span&gt; I like the way it simplified the complexity of the relationship visually with the advantage of flexible schema representation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;After some time, while exploring another use case in Identity Access Management (IAM) policies, I revisited &lt;a href=&#34;https://neo4j.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Neo4j&lt;/a&gt;. I was amazed by the analytical capabilities it offered and the potential for building Generative AI applications using Neo4j’s GraphRAG.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;span style =“背景色：透明;” ，一个功能强大的图数据库，早些时在视觉上与灵活模式表示的优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;一段时间后，在探索身份访问管理（IAM）策略中的另一个用例时，我重新审视&lt;a href =“ https://neo4j.com/” rel =” noopener noreferrer“ target =“ _ blank”&gt; neo4j &lt;/a&gt;。我对其提供的分析功能以及使用Neo4J的GraphRag构建生成AI应用的潜力感到惊讶。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【4 Reasons Agentic AI Is Reshaping Enterprise Search】代理AI的4个原因正在重塑企业搜索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/reasons-agentic-ai-reshapes-enterprise-search</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Generative AI has been the cutting-edge technology that greatly reshaped the enterprise search landscape. But now, artificial intelligence (AI) development communities are delving into a new industry-leading innovation — Agentic AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agentic-101-understanding-ai-agents&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Agentic AI&lt;/a&gt; is a system that exhibits a high degree of autonomy. It designs workflow and uses available tools to take action independently on behalf of the users and solve complex problems that require multi-step solutions. It also interacts with external environments and goes beyond the data on which the system&#39;s machine learning models were trained.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;生成的AI是极端的技术，它极大地重塑了企业搜索景观。但是现在，人工智能（AI）发展社区正在研究新的行业领先创新 - 代理AI。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agentic-101-undercanding-ai-ocents” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; aCtestic ai &lt;/a&gt;是一个表现出高度自治的系统。它设计工作流程并使用可用的工具代表用户独立采取行动，并解决需要多步解决方案的复杂问题。它还与外部环境交互，超出了系统的机器学习模型的数据。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 14:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Keycloak and Docker Integration: A Step-by-Step Tutorial】KeyCloak和Docker集成：逐步教程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/keycloak-and-docker-integration-tutorial</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;Keycloak is a powerful authentication and authorization solution that provides plenty of useful features, such as roles and subgroups, an advanced password policy, and single sign-on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt; It’s also very easy to integrate with other solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve already shown you how to &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretius.com/blog/keycloak-angular-integration/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;connect Keycloak to your Angular app&lt;/a&gt;, but there’s more you can do. For example, by integrating this technology with Cypress, you can enable the simulation of real-user login scenarios, including multi-factor authentication and social logins, ensuring that security protocols are correctly implemented and functioning as expected.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span style =“背景色：透明;”&gt; keyCloak是一种强大的身份验证和授权解决方案，可提供大量有用的功能，例如角色和子组，高级密码策略和单个签名&lt;/span &lt;/span &gt; &lt;span style =“背景色：透明;”&gt;。&lt;/span&gt;与其他解决方案集成也很容易。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经向您展示了如何&lt;a href =“ https://pretius.com/blog/keycloak-angular-ingular-integration/” rel =“ noopener” target =“ _ black”&gt;将keycloak连接到您的Angular App &lt;/a&gt;，但是您可以做更多的事情。例如，通过将此技术与柏树集成，您可以启用房地产用户登录方案的模拟，包括多因素身份验证和社交登录，确保按预期正确实现安全协议。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>