<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【From Zero to Production: Best Practices for Scaling LLMs in the Enterprise】从零到生产：在企业中扩展LLM的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-scaling-llms</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI adoption is no longer a future trend—it&#39;s happening now. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/ai-at-work-is-here-now-comes-the-hard-part&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2024 Work Trend Index&lt;/a&gt; reports that 75% of knowledge workers already use AI on the job. At the forefront of this revolution are &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; which are transforming the way businesses handle natural language tasks—from automating customer support and information retrieval to generating content. Foundational models are versatile, pre-trained architectures that form the backbone of the Generative AI movement. Trained on vast and diverse datasets—including text and multimodal content—they enable businesses to fine-tune AI capabilities for specific tasks like conversational agents, document summarization, and code generation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-comprehensive-guide&#34;&gt;Generative AI&lt;/a&gt; landscape features several key players, each contributing unique strengths to foundational model development:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; AI的采用不再是未来的趋势，现在正在发生。 The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/worklab/work-trend-index/ai-at-work-is-here-now-comes-the-hard-part&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;2024 Work Trend Index&lt;/a&gt; reports that 75% of knowledge workers already use AI on the job.这场革命的最前沿是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-langue-models”&gt;大语言模型（LLMS）&lt;/a&gt;，这些模型正在转变业务的方式，而企业的方式可以自动化自然的客户支持和信息回溯到生成内容。基础模型是多功能，预训练的架构，构成了生成AI运动的骨干。经过广泛而多样化的数据集的培训（包括文本和多模式内容），使企业能够为对话代理，文档摘要和代码生成等特定任务进行微调AI的功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-comprehend-guide”&gt; Generative ai &lt;/a&gt;景观具有几个关键参与者，每个参与者都为基础模型开发提供了独特的优势：&lt;/p&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why High-Performance AI/ML Is Essential in Modern Cybersecurity】为什么高性能AI/ML在现代网络安全中至关重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-high-performance-aiml-is-essential-in-modern-c</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Today, organizations thrive in a complex and evolving threat landscape, and cybersecurity has become pivotal for digital resilience. Various sophisticated attacks, such as supply chain breaches, ransomware, phishing via malicious email campaigns, and vulnerabilities in cloud and Internet of Things (IOT) environments, need advanced, performance-sensitive solutions that can detect in real time and also respond to and mitigate these attacks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence and machine learning (ML) play a frontal role in these transformations, providing the necessary capabilities to secure digital systems effectively.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;今天，组织在复杂而不断发展的威胁景观中蓬勃发展，网络安全已成为数字弹性的关键。各种复杂的攻击，例如供应链漏洞，勒索软件，通过恶意电子邮件活动的网络钓鱼以及云和物联网环境中的漏洞（IoT）环境中需要高级，性能敏感的解决方案，这些解决方案可以实时检测并响应并减轻这些攻击。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;人工智能和机器学习（ML）在这些转换中起着额叶的作用，提供了有效保护数字系统的必要功能。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Based Threat Detection in Cloud Security】云安全中基于AI的威胁检测</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-based-threat-detection-in-cloud-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This article explores how artificial intelligence (AI) is enhancing threat detection in cloud certificate environments. It explicates how dissimilar AI modeling, such as supervised, unsupervised, and reinforcement learning, is used to describe and respond to security measures and threats in cloud environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;The article also wraps up the architecture of AI-powered security systems, including data compendium, model training, and feedback loops. It highlights real-world use cases like insider threat spotting and explains how emerging technologies like large language models (LLMs) and self-healing systems determine the future of cloud security. Technical, simple, and concise, the article offers deep insight into the practical deployment and limitations of AI in real-time cloud defense systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;摘要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;本文探讨了人工智能（AI）如何增强云证书环境中的威胁检测。它阐明了不同的AI建模，例如监督，无监督和强化学习，用于描述和响应云环境中的安全措施和威胁。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;文章还结束了AI驱动的安全系统的体系结构，包括数据汇编，模型培训和反馈循环。它突出显示了现实世界中的用例，例如内幕威胁发现，并解释了大语模型（LLM）和自我修复系统等新兴技术如何决定云安全的未来。该文章的技术，简单和简洁，深入了解了实时云防御系统中AI的实际部署和局限性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking Data with Language: Real-World Applications of Text-to-SQL Interfaces】用语言解锁数据：文本到SQL接口的现实应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/text-to-sql-llm-based-database-interface</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has long been a difficult task to generate precise SQL queries from customers&#39; natural language inquiries (text-to-SQL). Understanding user queries, appreciating the structure and semantics of a particular database schema, and accurately producing executable SQL statements are some of the elements that contribute to the complexity. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large language models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; have opened up new avenues for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/unleashing-the-power-of-conversational-ai-for-text&#34;&gt;text-to-SQL&lt;/a&gt; research. Superior natural language understanding skills are demonstrated by LLMs, and their scalability offers special chances to improve SQL creation. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;长期以来，从客户的自然语言查询（文本到SQL）中生成精确的SQL查询一直是一项艰巨的任务。了解用户查询，欣赏特定数据库架构的结构和语义以及准确产生可执行的SQL语句是有助于复杂性的一些元素。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-with-large-lange-language-models”&gt;大语言模型（llms）&lt;/a&gt;已经为&lt;a开放了新的途径href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/unleashing-the-power-conversational-ai-for-text”&gt; text-to-to-to-sql &lt;/a&gt;研究。 LLMS证明了出色的自然理解能力，其可伸缩性为改善SQL创建提供了特殊的机会。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Comprehensive Guide to Property-Based Testing in Go: Principles and Implementation】GO中基于财产测试的综合指南：原理和实施</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/property-based-testing-guide-go</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Traditional unit testing often leaves critical edge cases undiscovered, with developers manually crafting test cases that may miss important scenarios. Property-based testing with Go offers a more robust approach, automatically generating hundreds of test cases to validate your code’s behavior across a wide range of inputs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Rather than writing individual test cases, you define properties that your code should always satisfy. The testing framework then generates diverse test scenarios, helping you uncover edge cases and bugs that might otherwise go unnoticed. This comprehensive guide explores how to implement property-based testing using popular Go libraries like gopter and rapid, along with practical examples and best practices for test automation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;传统的单位测试通常会使关键边缘案例未被发现，开发人员手动制作可能会错过重要情况的测试案例。使用GO的基于属性的测试提供了一种更强大的方法，可以自动生成数百个测试用例，以验证您的代码行为在广泛的输入中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;而不是编写单个测试用例，而是定义代码应始终满足的属性。然后，测试框架会生成各种测试方案，帮助您发现可能不会引起注意的边缘案例和错误。该综合指南探讨了如何使用流行的GO库（例如Gopter和Rapid）实施基于物业的测试，以及实用的示例和测试自动化的最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Data Pipelines: Generating PySpark and SQL Jobs With LLMs in Cloudera】自动数据管道：在Cloudera中生成Pyspark和SQL作业</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/generating-pyspark-sql-jobs-llms-cloudera</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With the rise of generative AI and large language models (LLMs), data engineers and analysts can now translate natural language directly into working PySpark or SQL jobs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By integrating LLMs into Cloudera Machine Learning (CML) and executing workloads on Cloudera Data Engineering (CDE) with Iceberg table formats, enterprises can accelerate data pipeline development, improve collaboration, and simplify access to large-scale analytics.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着生成AI和大型语言模型（LLM）的兴起，数据工程师和分析师现在可以将自然语言直接转化为工作的Pyspark或SQL作业。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过将LLMS集成到Cloudera机器学习（CML）中，并将Cloudera数据工程（CDE）的工作负载与冰山表格式执行，企业可以加速数据管道开发，改善协作并简化对大规模分析的访问。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Blue Skies Ahead: An AI Case Study on LLM Use for a Graph Theory Related Application】前面的蓝天：关于LLM用于图理论相关应用的AI案例研究</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/llm-use-graph-theory-case-study</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Research activities necessitate the exploration of ideas which may involve significant software development, experimentation, and testing effort. The ability of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs)&lt;/a&gt; to generate executable software has been demonstrated in various use cases. This study highlights the positive outcomes of a use case involving a graph theory application. Through a series of successful prompts, functional software was produced within minutes, a task that would otherwise have taken several hours or days to complete. Rather than focusing solely on cost savings from reduced engineering effort, this study aims to highlight the substantial opportunity benefits provided by this technology, especially since research typically involves evaluating multiple ideas before selecting the optimal solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When considering great systems thinking quotes, Donnella H. Meadows stands out: “Remember, always, that everything you know, and everything everyone knows, is only a model. Get your model out there where it can be viewed. Invite others to challenge your assumptions and add their own.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;研究活动需要探索可能涉及大量软件开发，实验和测试工作的思想。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-petting-with-large-language-models”&gt;大语言模型（LLMS）&lt;/a&gt;在各种用例中都证明了可执行软件。这项研究强调了涉及图理论应用的用例的积极结果。通过一系列成功的提示，在几分钟之内生产了功能软件，否则该任务将花费数小时或几天才能完成。本研究并非专注于减少工程工作的成本节省，而是旨在强调该技术提供的实质性机会收益，尤其是因为研究通常涉及在选择最佳解决方案之前对多个想法进行评估。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在考虑出色的系统思维行情时，唐纳拉·H·梅多斯（Donnella H. Meadows）脱颖而出：“请记住，始终，您所知道的一切，以及每个人都知道的一切，只是一个模型。将您的模型带到那里。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Trustworthy Is Big Data?】大数据有多值得信赖？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-trustworthy-is-big-data</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Businesses and individual users now employ big data analysis to support decision-making, engineering innovation, and productivity levels. However, the surge in the reliance on big data leads to growing concerns regarding its accuracy and trustworthiness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Although big data provides unprecedented insights and opportunities across all industries, you should be aware of concerns, such as loss of trust in big data, and address them as well. This article explores the perils of bad big data, reasons for the lack of trust in big data, and strategies that can be adopted to combat it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;业务和个人用户现在采用大数据分析来支持决策，工程创新和生产力水平。但是，对大数据的依赖激增导致人们对其准确性和可信度的关注日益加剧。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;尽管大数据提供了所有行业的前所未有的见解和机会，但您应该意识到担忧，例如对大数据的信任丧失，并解决了这些问题。本文探讨了不良大数据的危险，缺乏对大数据的信任的原因以及可以采用它的策略。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is Agile Right for Every Project? When To Use It and When To Avoid It】敏捷适合每个项目吗？何时使用并何时避免</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/is-agile-right-for-every-project-when-to-use-it-an</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/agile&#34;&gt;Agile&lt;/a&gt; has completely changed how teams think about project and task management by introducing flexibility, collaboration, and continuous evolution toward goals. Furthermore, its applicability stretches to software development, product management, and even non-technical fields.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With such a multifaceted environment, it is crucial to determine the exact point where Agile can be applied or when it becomes more of a burden. Knowing where to balance the pros and cons of Agile helps in coming up with the best decisions aligning with your team and organizational objectives.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/agile”&gt;敏捷&lt;/a&gt;通过引入灵活性，协作和对目标的持续发展，完全改变了团队对项目和任务管理的思考。此外，其适用性扩展到软件开发，产品管理甚至非技术领域。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;具有如此多基础的环境，至关重要的是确定可以施加敏捷的确切点，或者何时变得更负担。知道在哪里平衡敏捷的利弊有助于提出与您的团队和组织目标保持一致的最佳决定。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scalable, Resilient Data Orchestration: The Power of Intelligent Systems】可扩展的，弹性的数据编排：智能系统的力量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/scalable-data-orchestration-intelligent-systems</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Data is the key driver for any intelligent solution, including AI/ML. The accuracy and quality of any AI/ML model are directly proportional to the quality of data, regardless of whether it takes the form of input data, a prompt, or a pre-trained knowledge dataset. Often, the training datasets for AI/ML models originate from multiple sources and undergo various stages of data processing before being transformed into useful information that models can rely on for training. To achieve a reliable and continuous flow of data from diverse sources, transform data based on business rules, and extract insights and recommendations, we need a data orchestration solution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  This article discusses the unsung hero that orchestrates data flow across multiple components, including pipelines, to deliver the intended outcome. This article intentionally focuses on the characteristics and principles of a data orchestrator that are architecturally stable and resilient over time. The topics covered in this article are technology-agnostic and applicable to any industry-recognized data orchestration tools. As an engineer, the solution architecture is influenced by the capabilities or non-functional requirements, not purely by the tools available in the market. This article offers a refreshing take on the topic of data orchestration and shares my experience with the distinguished community of software professionals on designing large-scale data orchestration systems that ultimately bring insights and power intelligent systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Data Orchestration?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data orchestration is a set of related tasks executed in an order driven by specific use case needs. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/data-orchestration-on-cloud-essentials&#34;&gt;Data orchestration&lt;/a&gt; can have many names, such as workflow or state machine. Essentially, they are represented as Directed Acyclic Graphs (DAG), composed of nodes and edges. The nodes are represented as individual tasks, while the edges are depicted as triggers. A DAG can compose multiple subsystems and connect them through events that trigger actions, share data payloads along with execution context, thereby making the orchestration well-informed to chart a course of action.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数据是任何智能解决方案（包括AI/ML）的关键驱动力。任何AI/ML模型的准确性和质量与数据质量直接成正比，无论它是否采用输入数据的形式，提示或预先训练的知识数据集。通常，AI/ML模型的培训数据集源自多个来源，并经过各种数据处理阶段，然后将模型可以依靠用于培训的有用信息。为了获得来自不同来源的可靠且连续的数据流，根据业务规则转换数据并提取见解和建议，我们需要一个数据编排解决方案。&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;&#xA;  本文讨论了无名英雄，该英雄精心策划了包括管道在内的多个组件的数据流，以实现预期的结果。本文有意侧重于随着时间的流逝而在建筑稳定且具有弹性的数据编排的特征和原理上。本文涵盖的主题是技术不足的，适用于任何行业认可的数据编排工具。作为工程师，解决方案体系结构受到功能或非功能要求的影响，而不仅仅是市场上可用的工具。本文对数据编排的话题提供了令人耳目一新的看法，并与杰出的软件专业人员社区分享了我在设计大规模数据编排系统方面的经验，这些系统最终带来了见解和电力智能系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是数据编排？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据编排是由特定用例需求驱动的顺序执行的一组相关任务。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/data-orchestration-on-cloud-estentials”&gt;数据编排&lt;/a&gt;可以有很多名称，例如工作流或状态机。从本质上讲，它们作为定向无环图（DAG）表示，由节点和边缘组成。节点表示为单个任务，而边缘则将其描述为触发器。 DAG可以组成多个子系统，并通过触发操作，共享数据有效载荷以及执行上下文的事件将它们连接起来，从而使编排有很好的信息以绘制行动方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>