<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【My Shortcut of Choice: Reading the Source Code】我选择的捷径：阅读源代码</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/my-shortcut-of-choice-reading-the-source-code</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;There is a great post &lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.c2.com/?UseTheSourceLuke&#34;&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on c2.com. &lt;a href=&#34;https://c2.com/&#34;&gt;c2.com&lt;/a&gt; is one of those golden blogs of the past just like &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.codinghorror.com/&#34;&gt;codinghorror&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.joelonsoftware.com/&#34;&gt;Joel on software&lt;/a&gt;. You might have stumbled upon them before especially if you have been around for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the past, it was the norm to encourage individuals to read the source code and be able to figure out how things work. I see a trend against it from time to time including ranting on open source software and its documentation, which feels weird since having the source code available is essentially the ultimate form of documentation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;c2.com 上有一篇很棒的文章&lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.c2.com/?UseTheSourceLuke&#34;&gt;文章&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://c2.com/&#34;&gt;c2.com&lt;/a&gt; 是过去的黄金博客之一，就像 &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.codinghorror.com/&#34;&gt; codinghorror&lt;/a&gt; 和&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.joelonsoftware.com/&#34;&gt;Joel 谈软件&lt;/a&gt;。您以前可能偶然发现过它们，特别是如果您已经存在很长时间了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去，鼓励个人阅读源代码并能够弄清楚事情是如何工作的是常态。我时不时地看到一种反对它的趋势，包括对开源软件及其文档的咆哮，这感觉很奇怪，因为提供可用的源代码本质上是文档的最终形式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ChaosMeta for AI: Taking AI Stability to the Next Level With Chaos Engineering】ChaosMeta for AI：通过混沌工程将 AI 稳定性提升到新水平</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/chaosmeta-for-ai-taking-ai-stability-to-the-next</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s AI era, the architecture of AI systems is becoming increasingly complex, making its stability, resource utilization, and fault self-healing capabilities increasingly important. Addressing issues only when they occur during actual operation not only incurs high costs but also affects user experience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/chaos-engineering-path-to-build-resilient-and-faul&#34;&gt;Chaos engineering&lt;/a&gt; is about proactively exposing and addressing system vulnerabilities, greatly enhancing system resilience. ChaosMeta, an open-source chaos engineering platform developed by Ant Group, provides comprehensive support for the stability of AI systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当今的AI时代，AI系统的架构变得越来越复杂，其稳定性、资源利用率、故障自愈能力变得越来越重要。在实际操作过程中出现问题才去解决，不仅成本高昂，而且影响用户体验。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/chaos-engineering-path-to-build-resilient-and-faul&#34;&gt;混沌工程&lt;/a&gt;是主动暴露和解决系统漏洞，大大增强了系统的弹性。 ChaosMeta是蚂蚁集团开发的开源混沌工程平台，为AI系统的稳定性提供全面支持。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Test Automation in QA】QA 中的测试自动化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/test-automation-in-qa-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Maintaining quality is essential in the dynamic field of software development. Despite being essential, manual testing can become a bottleneck since it takes a lot of time and is prone to human error. One useful method for quickening the quality assurance process is test automation. They include employing software to manage test execution and compare predicted and actual findings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:279}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Let&#39;s dive into the subtleties of&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;test&amp;nbsp;automation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;,&amp;nbsp;including its advantages, best practices, and future industry developments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:279}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;在软件开发的动态领域中，保持质量至关重要。尽管手动测试很重要，但它可能会成为瓶颈，因为它需要花费大量时间并且容易出现人为错误。加快质量保证过程的一种有用方法是测试自动化。其中包括使用软件来管理测试执行并比较预测结果和实际结果。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;134233117&#34;:false,&#34;134233118&#34;:false,&#34;201341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559738&#34; :0,&#34;335559739&#34;:0,&#34;335559740&#34;:279}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;让我们深入探讨一下&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;测试自动化的微妙之处&lt; /span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;，包括其优势、最佳实践和未来行业发展。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;134233117&#34; :false,&#34;134233118&#34;:false,&#34;201341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559738&#34;:0,&#34;335559739&#34;:0,&#34;335559740&#34;:279}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Behavioral Biometrics Enhances Fraud Prevention】行为生物识别技术如何增强欺诈预防</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-behavioral-biometrics-enhances-fraud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-fraud-detection-systems-using-machine&#34;&gt;fraud prevention&lt;/a&gt; processes are far smoother than they used to be. Automated alert systems and authentication measures are now standard, but these relatively simple, rules-based solutions are still imperfect. The growing field of behavioral biometrics offers a more reliable alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Higher Detection Accuracy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Behavior biometrics’ accuracy is its primary advantage over conventional fraud detection. Researchers have developed systems capable of identifying fraud &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ksl.com/article/50826530/byu-professors-develop-keystroke-tracking-tech-to-detect-identity-fraud&#34;&gt;95.5% of the time&lt;/a&gt; by tracking keystrokes alone. Such precision is difficult with a rules-based system, especially when it comes to unknown attack patterns.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;如今的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-fraud-detection-systems-using-machine&#34;&gt;欺诈预防&lt;/a&gt;流程比以前顺利得多成为。自动警报系统和身份验证措施现已成为标准，但这些相对简单、基于规则的解决方案仍然不完善。不断发展的行为生物识别领域提供了更可靠的替代方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;更高的检测精度&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;行为生物识别技术的准确性是其相对于传统欺诈检测的主要优势。研究人员开发了能够识别欺诈的系统 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ksl.com/article/50826530/byu-professors-develop-keyrinkle-tracking-tech-to-detect-identity-fraud&#34;&gt;95.5%通过单独跟踪击键来节省时间&lt;/a&gt;。对于基于规则的系统来说，如此精确是很困难的，特别是当涉及到未知的攻击模式时。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Effortless API Mocking With Playwright】使用 Playwright 轻松进行 API 模拟</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/effortless-api-mocking-with-playwright</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Automated testing of web applications often requires interaction with external APIs. However, relying on actual API responses can introduce variables beyond your control, such as network issues or server downtime. This is where API mocking comes in. Mocking allows you to simulate API responses, making your tests more reliable and faster. In this article, we’ll explore how to mock APIs using Playwright with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.typescriptlang.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;TypeScript&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Mocking APIs in Playwright&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Playwright provides a way to intercept network requests and mock responses using the &lt;code&gt;route&lt;/code&gt; method. Let’s walk through an example where we mock an API response.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Web 应用程序的自动化测试通常需要与外部 API 交互。但是，依赖实际的 API 响应可能会引入您无法控制的变量，例如网络问题或服务器停机时间。这就是 API 模拟的用武之地。模拟允许您模拟 API 响应，使您的测试更可靠、更快速。在本文中，我们将探讨如何使用 Playwright 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.typescriptlang.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;TypeScript&lt;/a&gt; 来模拟 API。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Playwright 中的模拟 API&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Playwright 提供了一种使用 &lt;code&gt;route&lt;/code&gt; 方法拦截网络请求和模拟响应的方法。让我们来看一个模拟 API 响应的示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Hidden Costs of Lombok in Enterprise Java Solutions】企业 Java 解决方案中 Lombok 的隐性成本</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/hidden-costs-of-lombok-in-enterprise-java-solutions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Imagine inheriting a codebase where classes are clean and concise, and developers don&#39;t have to worry about boilerplate code because they can get automatically generated getters, setters, constructors, and even builder patterns. Meet &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-lombok&#34;&gt;Lombok&lt;/a&gt;, a library used for accelerating development through &#34;cleaning&#34; boilerplate code and injecting it automatically during compile time. But, is Lombok a hero or a villain in disguise?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Let&#39;s explore the widespread perceived benefits and potential drawbacks of its adoption in enterprise &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; solutions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;想象一下，继承一个代码库，其中的类干净简洁，开发人员不必担心样板代码，因为他们可以获得自动生成的 getter、setter、构造函数，甚至构建器模式。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-lombok&#34;&gt;Lombok&lt;/a&gt; 是一个库，用于通过“清理”样板代码并在编译时自动注入来加速开发。但是，龙目岛是英雄还是伪装的恶棍？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;让我们探讨一下在企业 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 解决方案中采用 Java 的广泛感知的好处和潜在缺点。&lt; /p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Key Strategies on How to Advance Your Digital Tech Career】如何推进数字技术职业的关键策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/key-strategies-to-advance-your-digital-tech-career</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The digital technology market is highly saturated and competitive, and to survive there, you need to succeed. Tech employers constantly seek IT professionals with the latest industry knowledge and expertise due to interconnected reasons: digital technology companies compete in international markets with each other, thus they need to be adaptive and constantly introduce new products and features to remain competitive. For every person working in the IT sector, it’s crucial to be up-to-date with the latest and most influential innovations and trends in their industry,&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/20-essential-software-development-books-to-read&#34;&gt; read professional literature&lt;/a&gt;, and constantly develop new skills. What main skills have the most value in the digital tech market? What is the perfect ratio between &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-soft-skills-are-the-hard-skills-of-today&#34;&gt;hard and soft skills&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Hard Skills vs Soft Skills&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each employee&#39;s role is specific to different areas of digital technology, and it is difficult to determine the exact ideal balance between hard and soft skills. However, on average, I would say that for technical roles, the percentage of hard skills is approximately 60-70 percent and 30-40 percent for soft skills. But for managerial roles, on the contrary, hard skills should be slightly less than 50 percent. Among the most important soft skills are clear communication, adaptability, critical and strategic thinking, and time management. Therefore, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/staff-plus-engineer-evolution-of-technical-career&#34;&gt;if your goal is to advance your career in leadership positions&lt;/a&gt;, it’s better to concentrate on polishing your soft skills, or, alternatively, try to achieve an equal balance of hard and soft skills through continuous development in both areas which can lead to a greater career success. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;数字技术市场高度饱和且竞争激烈，要在其中生存，您需要取得成功。由于相互关联的原因，科技雇主不断寻求拥有最新行业知识和专业知识的 IT 专业人员：数字技术公司在国际市场上相互竞争，因此他们需要适应并不断推出新产品和功能以保持竞争力。对于每个在 IT 行业工作的人来说，了解行业中最新、最有影响力的创新和趋势至关重要，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/20-essential- software-development-books-to-read&#34;&gt;阅读专业文献&lt;/a&gt;，不断培养新技能。哪些主要技能在数字技术市场中最有价值？ &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-soft-skills-are-the-hard-skills-of-today&#34;&gt;硬技能和软技能&lt;/a&gt;之间的完美比例是多少？&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;硬技能与软技能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个员工的角色都特定于数字技术的不同领域，很难确定硬技能和软技能之间的确切理想平衡。然而，平均而言，对于技术职位，硬技能的比例约为 60-70%，软技能的比例约为 30-40%。但对于管理职位来说，硬技能则相反，应该略低于 50%。最重要的软技能包括清晰的沟通、适应能力、批判性和战略性思维以及时间管理。因此，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/staff-plus-engineer-evolution-of-technical-career&#34;&gt;如果您的目标是在领导职位上提升自己的职业生涯&lt;/a&gt;，那就更好专注于提高你的软技能，或者，通过在这两个领域的不断发展，尝试实现硬技能和软技能的平等平衡，这可以带来更大的职业成功。  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Democratizing Data With Graph RAG: What It Is, What It Can Do, How To Evaluate It】使用 Graph RAG 实现数据民主化：它是什么、它能做什么、如何评估它</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/democratizing-data-with-graph-rag-what-it-is</link>
      <description>【&lt;div&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Are you interested in making your data more accessible? A rhetorical question indeed. Even if you are well-versed in dark arts such as databases, data modeling, data science, and information retrieval, why would you not want to make data more accessible even to non-experts?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Contrary to popular belief, &lt;a href=&#34;https://linkeddataorchestration.com/2024/07/01/data-rules-from-interoperability-to-commensurability/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;data collection started in the analog age&lt;/a&gt;. Accessing analog data imposes severe limitations compared to what is possible with digital data. However, even with digital data, &lt;a class=&#34;external-link&#34; data-tooltip-position=&#34;top&#34; href=&#34;https://hbr.org/2023/11/5-pillars-for-democratizing-data-at-your-organization&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;data democratization is not an easy feat for any organization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;您有兴趣让您的数据更易于访问吗？确实是一个反问句。即使您精通数据库、数据建模、数据科学和信息检索等黑暗艺术，为什么您不想让非专家也更容易访问数据呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA; &lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;与普遍看法相反，&lt;a href=&#34;https://linkeddataorchestration.com/2024/07/01/data-rules-from-interoperability-to-commensurability/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;数据收集始于模拟时代&lt;/a&gt;。与数字数据相比，访问模拟数据存在严重的限制。然而，即使使用数字数据，&lt;a class=&#34;external-link&#34; data-tooltip-position=&#34;top&#34; href=&#34;https://hbr.org/2023/11/5-pillars-for-democratizing-data- at-your-organization&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;数据民主化对于任何组织来说都不是一件容易的事情&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Snowflake Integration Patterns: Apache Kafka vs. Zero ETL and Reverse ETL】雪花集成模式：Apache Kafka 与零 ETL 和反向 ETL</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-integration-patterns-apache-kafka</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Snowflake is a leading cloud-native data warehouse. Integration patterns include batch data integration, Zero ETL, and near real-time data ingestion with Apache Kafka. This blog post explores the different approaches and discovers their trade-offs. Following industry recommendations, it is suggested to avoid anti-patterns like Reverse ETL and instead use data streaming to enhance the flexibility, scalability, and maintainability of enterprise architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Blog Series: Snowflake and Apache Kafka&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Snowflake is a leading cloud-native data warehouse. Its usability and scalability made it a prevalent data platform in thousands of companies. This blog series explores different data integration and ingestion options, including traditional ETL/iPaaS and data streaming with Apache Kafka. The discussion covers why point-to-point Zero-ETL is only a short-term win, why Reverse ETL is an anti-pattern for real-time use cases, and when a Kappa Architecture and shifting data processing “to the left” into the streaming layer helps to build transactional and analytical real-time and batch use cases in a reliable and cost-efficient way.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Snowflake 是领先的云原生数据仓库。集成模式包括批量数据集成、零 ETL 以及使用 Apache Kafka 进行近实时数据摄取。这篇博文探讨了不同的方法并发现了它们的权衡。根据行业建议，建议避免逆向ETL等反模式，而使用数据流来增强企业架构的灵活性、可扩展性和可维护性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;博客系列：Snowflake 和 Apache Kafka&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Snowflake 是领先的云原生数据仓库。其可用性和可扩展性使其成为数千家公司的流行数据平台。本博客系列探讨了不同的数据集成和摄取选项，包括传统的 ETL/iPaaS 和使用 Apache Kafka 的数据流。讨论涵盖了为什么点对点零 ETL 只是短期胜利、为什么反向 ETL 是实时用例的反模式，以及何时 Kappa 架构和将数据处理“向左”转移到流层有助于以可靠且经济高效的方式构建事务和分析实时和批量用例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Use Guardrails for Safeguarding Generative AI Applications Built Using Custom or Third-Party Models】使用 Guardrails 保护使用自定义或第三方模型构建的生成式 AI 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/use-guardrails-for-safeguarding-generative-ai-app</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/guardrails.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock&lt;/a&gt; enables you to implement safeguards for your generative AI applications based on your use cases and responsible AI policies. You can create multiple guardrails tailored to different use cases and apply them across multiple foundation models (FM), providing a consistent user experience and standardizing safety and privacy controls across generative AI applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Until now, you could use Guardrails when directly using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/APIReference/API_runtime_InvokeModel.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;InvokeModel&lt;/a&gt; API, with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/knowledge-base.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Knowledge Base&lt;/a&gt; or an &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/agents.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Agent&lt;/a&gt;. In all these scenarios, Guardrails evaluates both user input entering into the model and foundation model responses coming out of the model. But this approach coupled the guardrail evaluation process with model inference/invocation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/guardrails.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Amazon Bedrock 的 Guardrail&lt;/a&gt;使您能够根据您的用例和负责任的 AI 政策为您的生成式 AI 应用程序实施保护措施。您可以根据不同的用例创建多个护栏，并将它们应用于多个基础模型 (FM)，从而提供一致的用户体验并标准化生成型 AI 应用程序的安全和隐私控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;到目前为止，您可以在直接使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/APIReference/API_runtime_InvokeModel.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34; 时使用 Guardrails _blank&#34;&gt;InvokeModel&lt;/a&gt; API，带有 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/knowledge-base.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34; _blank&#34;&gt;知识库&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/bedrock/latest/userguide/agents.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;代理&lt;/a&gt;。在所有这些场景中，Guardrails 都会评估进入模型的用户输入和从模型中出来的基础模型响应。但这种方法将护栏评估过程与模型推理/调用结合起来。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>