<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Java Enterprise Matters: Why It All Comes Back to Jakarta EE】爪哇企业事务：为什么一切都回到雅加达EE</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/why-jakarta-ee-matters-enterprise-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/java-enterprise-edition-7&#34;&gt;Enterprise Java&lt;/a&gt; has been a foundation for mission-critical applications for decades. From financial systems to telecom platforms, Java offers the portability, stability, and robustness needed at scale. Yet as software architecture shifts toward microservices, containers, and cloud-native paradigms, the question naturally arises: is Jakarta EE still relevant?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For modern Java developers, the answer is a resounding yes. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-to-deal-with-javax-to-jakarta-migra&#34;&gt;Jakarta EE&lt;/a&gt; provides a standardized, vendor-neutral set of APIs for building enterprise applications, and its evolution under the Eclipse Foundation has been a case study in open innovation. It bridges traditional enterprise reliability with the flexibility needed for today’s distributed systems, making it an essential tool for developers who want to build scalable, secure, and cloud-ready applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []”样式=“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https：//dzone.com/refcardz/refcardz/java-enterprise-edition-eedition-7”&gt; Enterprise Java &lt;/a&gt;已成为数十年的秘密申请基础。从金融系统到电信平台，Java提供了规模所需的可移植性，稳定性和鲁棒性。然而，随着软件体系结构转向微服务，容器和云本地范式，自然出现了问题：雅加达EE是否仍然相关？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于现代Java开发人员来说，答案是肯定的。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-to-deal-with-with-javax-to-jakarta-migra”&gt; jakarta ee &lt;/a&gt;提供了一套标准化的，供应商 - 中立的API集，用于建立企业的企业及其进化下的Eclipse Foundation及其构建企业的进化已有一个开放的研究。它使传统的企业可靠性与当今分布式系统所需的灵活性融为一体，这使其成为想要构建可扩展，安全和云的应用程序的开发人员的重要工具。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Cursor and LLM for BDD Testing With Playwright MCP (Model Context Protocol)】将光标和LLM与剧作家MCP（模型上下文协议）集成用于BDD测试的LLM</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-cursor-llm-bdd-testing-playwright-mcp</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Imagine writing automated tests that feel like describing a story, where your natural language ideas transform into robust, executable code in seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;It’s reality, thanks to the convergence of AI-powered tools like Cursor, Large Language Models (LLMs), and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/executeautomation/mcp-playwright&#34; rel=&#34;noopener ugc nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Playwright Model Context Protocol&lt;/a&gt; (MCP). These tools are enhancing Behavior Driven Development (BDD), making test automation faster, smarter, and more collaborative.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p数​​据可选 - 段落=“”&gt;想象一下写自动测试，就像描述一个故事一样，您的自然语言创意在几秒钟内转变为可执行的可执行代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;&lt;P数据选择性-Paragraph =“”&gt;这是现实，这要归功于AI驱动的工具（例如光标，大型语言模型（LLMS））和&lt;a href =“ https：//github.com/github.com/executeautomation/mcp-playwright/mcp-playwright/mcp-playwright” rel = noopollopner of play play play play plant tarm talts &lt;/fland tarts &lt;/fland talts =“ （MCP）。这些工具正在增强行为驱动的发展（BDD），使测试自动化更快，更智能，更合作。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When Agile Teams Fake Progress: The Hidden Danger of Status Over Substance】当敏捷团队虚假进度时：地位对实质的隐藏危险</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/when-agile-teams-fake-progress-the-hidden-danger-o</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Introduction: The Friday Night Hero&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s Friday, 9:42 p.m. The sprint ended at noon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But a developer is still logged in, finalizing a hotfix that wasn’t in scope, wasn’t planned, and definitely wasn’t their responsibility alone. They’ll push the code, document it on Monday, and maybe get a “great hustle” in the next retro.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2 data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []”&gt;简介：星期五晚上英雄&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;是星期五，晚上9:42冲刺在中午结束。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，开发人员仍在登录，最终确定了一个不在范围的热点，没有计划，而且绝对不是他们的责任。他们将推出代码，在星期一记录下来，并可能在下一个复古中获得“很棒的喧嚣”。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software Specs 2.0: An Elaborate Example】软件规格2.0：精心示例</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-specs-an-elaborate-example</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;3:1-3:249&#34;&gt;This article is a follow-up to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/software-specs-ai-evolving-requirements&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; that lays the theoretical foundation for software requirement qualities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;3:1-3:249&#34;&gt;Here, I provide an example for how to craft requirements for a User Authentication Login Endpoint. A practical illustration of how essential software requirement qualities can be interwoven when designing specifications for AI-generated code. I demonstrate the crucial interplay between&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;explicitness&lt;/strong&gt; (to achieve &lt;strong&gt;completeness&lt;/strong&gt;), &lt;strong&gt;unambiguity&lt;/strong&gt; (for &lt;strong&gt;machine-first understandability&lt;/strong&gt;), &lt;strong&gt;constraint definition&lt;/strong&gt; (to guide implementation and ensure &lt;strong&gt;viability&lt;/strong&gt;), and &lt;strong&gt;testability&lt;/strong&gt; (through explicit acceptance criteria). We&#39;ll explore how these qualities can practically be achieved through structured documentation. Our goal is that our AI assistant has a clear, actionable blueprint for generating a secure and functional login service.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 3：1-3：249”&gt;本文是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/software-specs-ai-evolving-requirents- &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos =“ 3：1-3：249”&gt;在这里，我提供了一个如何制定用户身份验证登录端点要求的示例。在设计AI生成的代码规范时，基本软件需求质量如何交织在一起的实用说明。我证明了&lt;strong&gt;显性&lt;/strong&gt;（要实现&lt;strong&gt;完整性&lt;/strong&gt;），&lt;strong&gt; unambiguity &lt;/strong&gt;（对于&lt;strong&gt; Machine-First可理解性&lt;/strong&gt;），&lt;strong&gt;约束定义&lt;/strong&gt;（以指导实施和确保&lt;strong&gt; viblibility &lt;/strong &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;）（通过&lt;strong&gt;）和&lt;/我们将探讨如何通过结构化文档实际上实现这些素质。我们的目标是我们的AI助手具有清晰，可操作的蓝图，用于生成安全和功能的登录服务。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Converting List to String in Terraform】将列表转换为Terraform中的字符串</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/converting-list-to-string-in-terraform</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In Terraform, you will often need to convert a list to a string when passing values to configurations that require a string format, such as resource names, cloud instance metadata, or labels. Terraform uses HCL (HashiCorp Configuration Language), so handling lists requires functions like &lt;code&gt;join()&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;format()&lt;/code&gt;, depending on the context.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;How to Convert a List to a String in Terraform&lt;a href=&#34;https://spacelift.io/blog/terraform-list-to-string#how-to-convert-a-list-to-a-string-in-terraform&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;join()&lt;/code&gt; function is the most effective way to convert a list into &lt;a href=&#34;https://spacelift.io/blog/terraform-string&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a string in Terraform&lt;/a&gt;. This concatenates list elements using a specified delimiter, making it especially useful when formatting data for use in resource names, cloud tags, or dynamically generated scripts.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在Terraform中，当将值传递给需要字符串格式的配置时，您通常需要将列表转换为字符串，例如资源名称，云实例元数据或标签。 Terraform使用HCl（Hashicorp配置语言），因此处理列表需要&lt;code&gt; join&gt; join（）&lt;/code&gt;&gt;或&lt;/code&gt; format（）格式（）&lt;/code&gt;，取决于上下文。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/code&gt;。&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;如何将列表转换为Terraform &lt;a href =“ https://spacelift.io/blog/terraform-list-list-to-string#how-to-convert-to-convert-a-list-a-list-a-list-to-a-a-string-in-terraform”&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;code&gt; join（）&lt;/code&gt;函数是将列表转换为&lt;a href =“ https://spacelift.io/blog/terraform-string“ rel =“ noopener” target =“ _ _ black”&gt; terraform &lt;/a&gt;中的字符串的最有效方法。此使用指定的定界符加入列表元素，使其在格式化数据以用于资源名称，云标签或动态生成的脚本时特别有用。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enterprise-Grade Distributed JMeter Load Testing on Kubernetes: A Scalable, CI/CD-Driven DevOps Approach】Kubernetes上的企业级分布式JMeter负载测试：可扩展的CI/CD驱动DEVOPS方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/distributed-jmeter-load-testing-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Application performance, scalability, and resilience are critical for ensuring a seamless user experience. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-apache-jmeter&#34;&gt;Apache JMeter&lt;/a&gt; is a powerful open-source tool for load testing, but running it on a single machine limits scalability, automation, and distributed execution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This blog presents a Kubernetes-powered JMeter setup on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/running-containers-in-azure&#34;&gt;Azure Kubernetes Service&lt;/a&gt; (AKS), which can also be deployed on other cloud platforms like AWS EKS and Google &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;GKE&lt;/span&gt;, integrated with CI/CD pipelines in Azure DevOps. This approach enables dynamic scaling, automated test execution, real-time performance monitoring, and automated reporting and alerting.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;应用程序性能，可伸缩性和弹性对于确保无缝用户体验至关重要。 &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-parted-with-apache-jmeter”&gt; apache jmeter &lt;/a&gt;是一个强大的开放式工具，用于负载测试，但在单个计算机上运行它，以限制单个计算机的可伸缩性，自动化和分布式执行。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;该博客在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/running-containers-ingainers-in-azure”&gt; azure kubernetes Service &lt;/a&gt;（aks）上展示了kubernetes驱动的jmeter设置&lt;/a&gt; azure kubernetes Service &lt;/a&gt;（aks），它也可以在其他云平台上部署在其他云平台上。 0px;“&gt; gke &lt;/span&gt;，与Azure DevOps中的CI/CD管道集成。这种方法可以使动态缩放，自动测试执行，实时性能监视以及自动报告和警报。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From ETL to ELT to Real-Time: Modern Data Engineering with Databricks Lakehouse】从ETL到ELT到实时：与Databricks Lakehouse的现代数据工程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/etl-elt-real-time-data-databricks-lakehouse</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;682&#34; data-start=&#34;119&#34;&gt;The data engineering landscape has rapidly changed over the past few years, shifting from the classical &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/etl-vs-elt-1&#34;&gt;ETL&lt;/a&gt; (Extract, Transform, and Load) model to the more modern ELT (Extract, Load, Transform) model. In the ETL approach, data was transformed before being stored, which reduced flexibility. ELT reverses this process by first loading raw data into data lakes or warehouses and then transforming it within these environments, enabling more agile, on-demand analytics. However, as data volumes and business requirements have increased, ELT has become inadequate for many real-time use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1163&#34; data-start=&#34;684&#34;&gt;Today, organizations need rapid access to insights to maintain operational agility, which has led to a growing demand for real-time data processing capabilities. Leading this shift is the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-enable-azure-databricks-lakehouse-monitoring&#34;&gt;Databricks Lakehouse&lt;/a&gt; solution, which provides a unified framework that combines the strengths of data lakes with the power of data warehouses. This fully integrated platform enables organizations to move quickly, make data-driven decisions, and maintain flexibility across diverse workloads.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end=&#34;682&#34; data-start=&#34;119&#34;&gt;The data engineering landscape has rapidly changed over the past few years, shifting from the classical &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/etl-vs-elt-1&#34;&gt;ETL&lt;/a&gt; (Extract, Transform, and Load) model to the more modern ELT (Extract, Load, Transform) model.在ETL方法中，在存储之前将数据转换，从而降低了柔韧性。 ELT首先将原始数据加载到数据湖泊或仓库中，然后在这些环境中转换，从而逆转此过程，从而实现了更敏捷的按需分析。但是，随着数据量和业务需求的增加，ELT在许多实时用例中变得不足。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1163” data-start =“ 684”&gt;今天，组织需要快速访问洞察力以维持运营敏捷性，这导致对实时数据处理能力的需求不断增长。领导这一班次是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-to-enable-azure-databricks-lakehouse-monitoring”&gt; databricks lakehouse &lt;/a&gt;解决方案，该解决方案提供了一个统一的框架，可以将数据湖与数据仓库的力量相结合。这个完全集成的平台使组织能够快速移动，做出数据驱动的决策并保持各种工作量的灵活性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Evaluating Similariy Digests: A Study of TLSH, ssdeep, and sdhash Against Common File Modifications】评估类似的摘要：针对公共文件修改的TLSH，SSDEEP和SDHASH的研究</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/similarity-digests-tlsh-ssdeep-sdhash-benchmark</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The field of digital forensics often uses signatures to identify malicious executables. These signatures can take various forms: cryptographic hashes can be used to uniquely identify executables, whereas tools like &lt;a href=&#34;https://virustotal.github.io/yara/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;YARA&lt;/a&gt; can help malware researchers identify and classify &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/common-cybersecurity-threats-and-how-to-protect-yo&#34;&gt;malware&lt;/a&gt; samples. The behavior of files— functions exported, functions called, IP addresses and domains they connect to, files written or read—also provide useful indicators that a system has been compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Cryptographic hashes, YARA rules and indicators of compromise are usually compared against curated databases of trusted or malicious signatures, such as those maintained by the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nsrl.nist.gov/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;National Software Reference Library&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://bazaar.abuse.ch/export/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;MalwareBazaar&lt;/a&gt;. Hashes like MD5 and SHA256 are designed to change drastically even with minor modifications to the original executable, making it easy for malware authors to evade. Modern cloud environments make it easy to evade behavioral detection as well, allowing threat actors to tailor their malware to specific platforms. In general, matching against feeds of known indicators misses unknown or undiscovered threat vectors.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;数字取证的字段通常使用签名来识别恶意可执行文件。这些签名可以采取各种形式：加密哈希可以用来唯一识别可执行文件，而&lt;a href =” https://virustotal.github.io/yara/等工具，“ rel =“ noopener noreferrer” href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/common-cybersecurity-threats-and-and-how-to-protect-yo”&gt;恶意软件&lt;/a&gt;样本。文件的行为（导出的功能，称为函数，IP地址和它们连接到文件的范围，编写或读取的域）也提供了有用的指标，表明系统已被妥协。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;加密哈希，YARA规则和妥协的指标通常与可信或恶意签名的策划数据库进行比较，例如&lt;a a href =“ http://www.nsrl.nist.gov/ href =“ https://bazaar.abuse.ch/export/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; malwarebazaar &lt;/a&gt;。 MD5和SHA256之类的哈希旨在对原始可执行文件进行微小的修改，即使对原始的可执行文件进行了少量修改，使恶意软件作者可以轻松逃避。现代的云环境也使逃避行为检测变得容易，从而使威胁参与者可以将其恶意软件量身定制到特定平台。通常，与已知指标的提要相匹配，错过了未知或未被发现的威胁向量。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Generative AI Services: An Introductory and Practical Guide】建筑物AI服务：介绍和实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-generative-ai-services</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Amazon Web Services (AWS) offers a vast range of generative artificial intelligence solutions, which allow developers to add advanced AI capabilities to their applications without having to worry about the underlying infrastructure. This report highlights the creation of functional applications using Amazon Bedrock, which is a serverless offering based on an API that provides access to core models from leading suppliers, including Anthropic, Stability AI, and Amazon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;134233117&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;134233118&amp;quot;:false,&amp;quot;335559738&amp;quot;:299,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:299}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;As the demand for AI-powered applications grows, developers seek easy and scalable solutions to integrate generative AI into their applications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;provides this capability through the firm&#39;s proprietary generative AI services, and the standout among these is Amazon Bedrock. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/generative-ai-apps-with-amazon-bedrock-getting-sta&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Amazon Bedrock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;none&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt; enables you to access foundation models via API without worrying about underlying infrastructure, scaling, and model training.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ en-us”&gt; Amazon Web Services（AWS）提供了广泛的生成人工智能解决方案，使开发人员可以在其应用程序中添加高级AI功能，而不必担心基础基础架构。该报告强调了使用Amazon Bedrock创建功能应用程序的功能应用程序，该应用程序是基于API的无服务器产品，可从领先的供应商那里访问核心模型，包括人为，稳定性AI和Amazon。 data-ccp-props =“ {” 134233117“：false，” 134233118“：false，” 335559738“：299，” 335559739“：299}：299}”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p lang =“ en-us”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ en-us”&gt;随着对AI驱动应用程序的需求的增长，开发人员寻求简单且可扩展的解决方案以将生成AI集成到其应用程序中。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ en-us”&gt; aws &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-data-contrast =“ none” lang =“ en-us”&gt;通过公司的专有生成AI服务提供了此功能，并且其中出色的出色之处在其中。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/generative-aips-with-amazon-bedrock-getting-sta”&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ none” none“ lang =” en-us“ en-us” eN-us&#39;&gt;基础架构，扩展和模型培训。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Native Platforms: The Unstoppable Alliance of GenAI and Platform Engineering】AI本地平台：Genai和平台工程的不可阻挡联盟</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-native-platforms-genai-platform-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s be honest. Building developer platforms, especially for &lt;strong&gt;AI-native&lt;/strong&gt; teams, is a complex art, a constant challenge. It&#39;s about finding a delicate balance: granting maximum autonomy to development teams without spiraling into chaos, and providing incredibly powerful, cutting-edge tools without adding superfluous complexity to their already dense workload. Our objective as Platform Engineers has always been to pave the way, remove obstacles, and accelerate innovation. But what if the next, inevitable phase of platform evolution wasn&#39;t just about what &lt;em&gt;we&lt;/em&gt; build and provide, but what &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/trendreports/generative-ai&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Generative AI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; can help us co-build, co-design, and co-manage?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;re not talking about a mere incremental improvement, a minor optimization, or a marginal new feature. We&#39;re facing a genuine &lt;strong&gt;paradigm shift&lt;/strong&gt;, a conceptual earthquake where artificial intelligence is no longer merely the &lt;em&gt;final product&lt;/em&gt; of our efforts, the result of our development toils, but becomes the silent &lt;em&gt;partner&lt;/em&gt;, the tireless ally that is already reimagining, rewriting, and redefining our entire development experience. This is the real gamble, the challenge that awaits us: transforming our platforms from simple toolsets, however sophisticated, into &lt;strong&gt;intelligent, dynamic, and self-optimizing ecosystems&lt;/strong&gt;. A place where productivity isn&#39;t just high, but exceptionally high, and innovation flows frictionlessly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;老实说。建筑开发人员平台，尤其是对于&lt;strong&gt; ai-native &lt;/strong&gt;团队，是一项复杂的艺术，是一个持续的挑战。这是要找到一个微妙的平衡：向开发团队授予最大的自主权而不会陷入混乱，并提供令人难以置信的强大，尖端的工具，而不会增加其本来密集的工作量的多余复杂性。我们作为平台工程师的目标一直是铺平道路，消除障碍和加速创新。但是，如果下一个平台发展的不可避免的阶段不仅仅是我们&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https：//dzone.com/trendreports/generative-ai”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;gront&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们并不是在谈论仅仅是渐进的改进，次要优化或边际新功能。我们面临着一个真正的&lt;strong&gt;范式示范&lt;/strong&gt;，这是一种概念地震，在这种地震中，人工智能不再仅仅是我们努力的&lt;em&gt;最终产品&lt;/em&gt;，这是我们的开发辛苦努力的结果，而是无声&lt;em&gt; parternect &lt;/em&gt;，这已经是累人的，已经是重新构成，重新创新，重新创新，重新定义了我们整个发展的经验。这是真正的赌博，等待我们的挑战：将我们的平台从简单的工具集（无论多么复杂）转变为&lt;strong&gt;智能，动态和自我优化的生态系统&lt;/strong&gt;。一个生产力不仅高的地方，而且异常高，创新无摩擦。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>