<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Scalable IoT Architectures on Azure】在Azure上实施可扩展的物联网体系结构</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implementing-scalable-iot-architectures-azure</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things (IoT) comprises smart devices connected to a network, sending and receiving large amounts of data to and from other devices, which generates a substantial amount of data to be processed and analyzed. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge computing, a strategy for computing on location where data is collected or used, allows IoT data to be gathered and processed at the edge, rather than sending the data back to a data center or cloud. Together, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/trendreports/edge-computing-and-iot&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;IoT and edge computing&lt;/a&gt; are a powerful way to rapidly analyze data in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;物联网（IoT）包括连接到网络的智能设备，向其他设备发送和接收大量数据，这些数据生成了大量的数据进行处理和分析。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;边缘计算是一种在收集或使用数据的位置上计算的策略，允许在边缘收集和处理IoT数据，而不是将数据发送回数据中心或云。一起，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/trendreports/edge-computing-and-and-iot” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ blank”&gt; iot和edge Computing &lt;/a&gt;是一种实时快速分析数据的有力方法。&lt;/p&gt; p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Development of System Configuration Management: Working With Secrets, IaC, and Deserializing Data in Go】系统配置管理的开发：与GO中的秘密，IAC和避免数据合作</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/system-configuration-management-secrets-iac-go</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Series Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article is Part 2.1 of a multi-part series: &#34;Development of system configuration management.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The complete series:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt;系列概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文是一个多部分系列的第2.1部分：“系统配置管理的开发。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完整系列：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Blockchain, AI, and Edge Computing: Redefining Modern App Development】区块链，AI和边缘计算：重新定义现代应用程序开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/blockchain-ai-and-edge-computing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The overall landscape of app development is continuing with a transformative shift that is driven by various latest technologies, including AI or artificial intelligence, edge computing, and blockchain. These innovations are enhancing the efficiency and functionality of the apps, catering to new layers of security, improving scalability, and enhancing the user experience. The use of the latest technologies is high among app development companies, and they are trying to optimize app performance through this technology.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article will examine the interconnection of these technologies with others and their specific contributions and impacts on the development process of modern apps.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;应用程序开发的整体景观继续进行，由各种最新技术（包括人工智能或人工智能，边缘计算和区块链）驱动的变革性转变。这些创新正在提高应用程序的效率和功能，迎合新的安全性，提高可扩展性并增强用户体验。在应用程序开发公司中，最新技术的使用很高，他们正试图通过该技术优化应用程序性能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文将研究这些技术与他人的互连及其对现代应用程序开发过程的具体贡献和影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Digital Twins Reborn: How AI Is Finally Fulfilling the Promise of IoT】数字双胞胎重生：AI最终如何实现物联网的承诺</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/digital-twins-reborn-as-ai-fulfills-iot-promise</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Ten years ago, I wrote an article for DZone on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/executive-perspectives-on-the-future-of-iot&#34;&gt;The Future of IoT&lt;/a&gt;. When General Electric unveiled their digital twin technology for aircraft engines, we were on the cusp of an industrial revolution. The idea was compelling: create virtual replicas of physical assets that could be monitored, analyzed, and optimized in real-time. However, as many early IoT enthusiasts discovered, the gap between concept and widespread implementation proved wider than anticipated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Fast-forward to 2025, and digital twins are experiencing a renaissance, powered by advances in artificial intelligence addressing the challenges that once held the technology back.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;十年前，我在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/execnetun-pecten-pective-on-the-future-of-iot-oiot”上写了一篇文章。当通用电气推出他们用于飞机发动机的数字双技术时，我们正处于工业革命的风口浪尖。这个想法令人信服：创建可以实时监控，分析和优化的物理资产的虚拟复制品。但是，正如许多早期的物联网爱好者发现的那样，概念和广泛实施之间的差距比预期的要大。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;快进到2025年，数字双胞胎正在经历文艺复兴时期，这是由人工智能的进步提供支持的，解决了曾经使技术退缩的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Wait, What Format Is That? A Cross—Domain Guide for Everyone】等等，那是什么格式？十字架 - 每个人的域名指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/file-formats-guide-for-tech-professionals</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you an Engineering or Technology Leader who is looking up “what’s that file format”, while sitting in a meeting where they are throwing jargon about file formats?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you an Architect who has switched domains only to discover that there is an entire jungle of file formats that you are unfamiliar with, and now need to integrate into the solution you are building?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是一个工程或技术领导者，当他们坐在会议上，他们在扔关于文件格式的行话时正在查找“什么是文件格式”？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您是否是一个切换域的建筑师，只是发现您不熟悉的整个文件格式丛林，现在需要集成到您正在构建的解决方案中？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Docker Container Logging: Strategies for Scalability and Performance】优化Docker容器记录：可伸缩性和性能的策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-logging-optimization-scalability-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In modern microservices, logging is vital for observability, performance, and incident response. Traditional logging fails at scale, causing latency and storage issues. This article details efficient logging strategies for Docker containers, including log driver selection and centralized aggregation, to mitigate bottlenecks and build a robust, scalable logging infrastructure for any deployment at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding Log Drivers and Types&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Log drivers capture container console output (stdout/stderr) and route it to local files or remote services. If a log driver fails to deliver logs (e.g., remote destination unreachable), the Docker daemon thread can block, potentially causing thread exhaustion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在现代微服务中，记录对于可观察性，性能和事件响应至关重要。传统的日志记录大规模失败，导致延迟和存储问题。本文详细介绍了Docker容器的有效日志记录策略，包括日志驱动程序选择和集中式聚合，以减轻瓶颈并为任何部署进行大规模部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;了解日志驱动程序和类型&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;日志驱动程序捕获容器控制台输出（stdout/stderr），然后将其路由到本地文件或远程服务。如果日志驱动程序未能提供日志（例如，远程目标无法到达），则Docker守护程序线程可以阻止，从而可能导致线程耗尽。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Seamless Storage: Configuring Kubernetes PVC for Windows Shared Folders With SMB】无缝存储：使用SMB配置Windows共享文件夹的Kubernetes PVC</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kubernetes-pvc-windows-shared-folders-smb</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In the new cloud-native era, it is important to be able to scale and manage applications efficiently. Kubernetes, as a leading container orchestration platform, provides strong features for managing storage through &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/dynamically-provisioning-persistent-volumes-with-k&#34;&gt;Persistent Volume Claims&lt;/a&gt; (PVCs). Mapping Kubernetes to traditional enterprise storage solutions, such as Windows shared folders via the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-microsoft-azure-cloud-storage&#34;&gt;Server Message Block&lt;/a&gt; (SMB) protocol, can be especially tricky, however. In this post, you’ll see how to configure Kubernetes PVCs to simply connect to Windows shared folders so that you can leverage your existing infrastructure without losing the scalability and flexibility benefits that &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/demystifying-kubernetes&#34;&gt;Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; has to offer. From app migration of older applications to building new applications, understanding this integration will bring your operational performance to the next level and allow you to achieve seamless workflows. Join us as we walk through the steps of creating this essential connection and getting the most from your Kubernetes configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;source srcset=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/format:webp/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 640w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/format:webp/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 720w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/format:webp/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 750w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/format:webp/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 786w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/format:webp/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 828w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/format:webp/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 1100w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/format:webp/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 1400w&#34; sizes=&#34;(min-resolution: 4dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (min-resolution: 3dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 67vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 3) and (max-width: 700px) 65vw, (min-resolution: 2.5dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2.5) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (min-resolution: 2dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px&#34; type=&#34;image/webp&#34;&gt; &lt;source data-testid=&#34;og&#34; srcset=&#34;https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:640/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 640w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 720w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 750w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 786w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 828w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 1100w, https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/1*SmhVfXEI6nTKazYsZYFUcg.png 1400w&#34; sizes=&#34;(min-resolution: 4dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 4) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (min-resolution: 3dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 67vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 3) and (max-width: 700px) 65vw, (min-resolution: 2.5dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2.5) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, (min-resolution: 2dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 2) and (max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Scenario&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Imagine a bustling enterprise that has relied on a critical application running on a Windows Virtual Machine (VM) for years. This application, developed in .NET, has been seamlessly authenticating to a shared folder on a separate server using a dedicated service account. However, as the organization embraces modern cloud-native practices, the decision is made to migrate the application to a more agile environment — Linux containers running .NET 8.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2数据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据选择性 - 段落=“”&gt;在新的云本地时代，能够有效地扩展和管理应用程序很重要。 Kubernetes作为领先的集装箱编排平台，为通过&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/dynamalysp-provisioning-provisioning-persistent-volumes-with-k”&gt;持续体积索赔&lt;/a&gt;（PVCS）提供了强大的功能。将kubernetes映射到传统的企业存储解决方案，例如通过&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-microsoft-azure-cloud-cloud-storage”&gt;服务器消息块&lt;/a&gt;（SMB）协议，可能是特别棘手的。在这篇文章中，您将看到如何配置kubernetes PVC简单地连接到Windows共享文件夹，以便您可以利用现有的基础架构而不会失去&lt;href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/demystify-kubernetes”&gt; kubernetes“&gt; kubernetes &lt;/a&gt; yess yess yess yess yess yesss off.a&gt; soff。从旧应用程序的应用迁移到构建新应用程序，了解此集成将使您的运营绩效达到一个新的水平，并允许您实现无缝的工作流程。加入我们，浏览创建这种基本连接并从您的Kubernetes配置中获得最大收益的步骤。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figud&gt;&#xA; &lt;div tabindex =“ 0”&gt;&#xA;  &lt;source srcset =“ https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize：640/format:webp/1* smhvfxei6ntkazyszyfucg.png 640w， https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/format:webp/1* smhvfxei6ntkazyszyfucg.png 720w， https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:750/format:webp/1* smhvfxei6ntkazyszyfucg.png 750w， https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/format:webp/1* smhvfxei6ntkazyszyfucg.png 786w， https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:828/format:webp/1* smhvfxei6ntkazyszyfucg.png 828W， https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/format:webp/1* smhvfxei6ntkazyszyfucg.png 1100W， https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1400/format:webp/1* (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (min-resolution: 3dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 67vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 3) and (max-width: 700px) 65vw, (min-resolution: 2.5dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, （-Webkit-Min-device像素比率：2.5）和（最大宽度：700px）80VW，（最小分辨率：2DPPX）和（最大宽度：700px）100VW，（ -  Webkit-Min-Min-Min-Device-Device-evice-evice-pixel-ratio-Ratio-Ratio：2）和（最大范围）和（Max-witth：Max-witth：700px）和700px）10000VW，&lt;700 vw，&lt;） data-testid =“ og” srcset =“ https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize：640/1* smhvfxei6ntkazyszyfucg.png 640w， https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:720/1* https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:786/1* https://miro.medium.com/v2/resize:fit:1100/1* smhvfxei6ntkazyszyfucg.png 1100W，https：//miro.medium.com/v2/resize：Fit:fit:fit:1400/1* 4) and (max-width: 700px) 50vw, (min-resolution: 3dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 67vw, (-webkit-min-device-pixel-ratio: 3) and (max-width: 700px) 65vw, (min-resolution: 2.5dppx) and (max-width: 700px) 80vw, （-Webkit-Min-Device像素比率：2.5）和（最大宽度：700px）80VW，（最小分辨率：2DPPX）和（最大宽度：700px）100VW，（ -  Webkit-Min-Min-Device-Device-Device-device-pixel-pixel-Ratio-Ratio-Ratio：2）和（Max-Width：Max-Width and（Max-Width：70000px）：70000px）100px）&gt;&#xA; &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2数据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;方案&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;P数据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;想象一个繁华的企业多年来一直依赖于在Windows Virtual Machine（VM）上运行的关键应用程序。该应用程序是在.NET中开发的，它已使用专用服务帐户在单独的服务器上无缝地验证了共享文件夹。但是，随着组织采用现代云本地实践，决定将应用程序迁移到更敏捷的环境 -  Linux容器运行.NET 8。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling Real-Time Data Systems With DataOps: Principles, Practices, and Use Cases】使用DataOps缩放实时数据系统：原理，实践和用例</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-dataops-principles-practices-use-cases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2025 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2025-tr-data-engineering-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Data Engineering: Scaling Intelligence With the Modern Data Stack&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Real-time decision making is no longer a competitive advantage; it&#39;s becoming a baseline expectation. From fraud detection to personalized recommendations, modern systems are expected to process and respond to user activity within milliseconds. But while demand for real-time data has exploded, many engineering teams are still struggling with brittle pipelines, silent failures, and fragile deployments.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ font-size：17px;”&gt; &lt;em&gt;编辑注：以下是为Dzone的2025年趋势报告编写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/link/link/link/link/2025-tr-data-tr-data-wribeering-contributor-contributor-contributor-utor-contributor-utor-contributor-utor-contributor-utor-contributor-article-concon-no noore =” noore&gt;工程：使用现代数据堆栈缩放智能&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;实时决策不再是竞争优势；它正成为基准期望。从欺诈检测到个性化建议，现代系统应处理并响应毫秒内的用户活动。但是，尽管对实时数据的需求爆炸了，但许多工程团队仍在挣扎着脆弱的管道，沉默的故障和脆弱的部署。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Build an AI-Powered Search Bar With Vector Embeddings and OpenAI】如何构建具有矢量嵌入和OpenAI的AI驱动搜索栏</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-ai-search-bar-with-vector-embeddings-openai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When you search for something in a search bar, but the results seem off from what you wanted to find, you join many others who have experienced this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve all been there before — you search for &#34;cost&#34; only to come away with nothing because the doc only says &#34;price.&#34; That&#39;s the pitfall of traditional keyword search — it matches words, not meaning.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当您在搜索栏中搜索某些东西时，但是结果似乎与您想找到的东西相关，您会加入许多经历过的其他人。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们之前都去过那里 - 您在搜索“成本”，只是什么都没消失，因为文档只说“价格”。这就是传统关键字搜索的陷阱 - 它与单词相匹配，而不是含义。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Memory Page Sizes on Arm64】了解ARM64上的内存页面大小</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/understanding-memory-page-sizes-on-arm64</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;One of the ways that the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/code-migration-ampere-porting-advisor&#34;&gt;Arm64 architecture&lt;/a&gt; is different from x86 is the ability to configure the size of memory pages in the Memory Management Unit (MMU) of the CPU to 4K, 16K, or 64K. This article summarizes what memory page size is, how to configure page size on &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/top-10-essential-linux-commands&#34;&gt;Linux&lt;/a&gt; systems, and when it might make sense to use a different page size in your applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction to Memory Page Size&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we previously discussed in &lt;a href=&#34;https://amperecomputing.com/tutorials/fixing-page-fault-performance-issue&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Diagnosing and Fixing a Page Fault Performance Issue with Arm64 Atomics&lt;/a&gt;, operating systems present a virtual memory address space to applications, and map physical memory pages to virtual memory addresses using a page table. The CPU then provides a mechanism called the Translation Lookaside Buffer (TLB) to ensure that recently accessed pages of memory can be identified and read faster using L1 or L2 CPU cache.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/codemigration-migration-ampere-porting-advisor”&gt; arm64架构&lt;/a&gt;与x86不同的是能够在CPU的内存管理单元（MMU）中配置内存页面（MMU）（MMU）的能力。本文总结了什么是内存页面大小，如何在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/top-10-esential-linux-commands”上配置页面大小。&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;记忆页面大小简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正如我们先前在&lt;a href =“ https://amperecomputing.com/tutorials/fixing-page-page-fault-performance-performance-issue-RER =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;诊断和修复amm64Athatemict a formatial forival prom forival proge aff y virt and apom64Athatemics &lt;/a&gt;使用页面表的地址。然后，CPU提供了一种称为Translation LookAside缓冲区（TLB）的机制，以确保可以使用L1或L2 CPU缓存来更快地识别存储器的最近访问页面。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>