<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Meets Vector Databases: Redefining Data Retrieval in the Age of Intelligence】AI符合矢量数据库：在智能时代重新定义数据检索</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-meets-vector-databases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Ever wish we could search the internet not with just keywords, but with actual meaning, like what we really meant to say? That’s the magic happening when AI teams up with vector databases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional databases are great for clean, structured stuff, like spreadsheets. But most of the data we create today? It’s messy and unstructured: think tweets, photos, voice notes, even memes. That’s where AI comes in. It’s amazing at understanding all that chaos, but it needs a smart system to store and search through it.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;曾经希望我们可以不仅仅使用关键字搜索互联网，而是具有实际含义，就像我们真正要说的那样？当AI与矢量数据库合作时，这就是发生的魔力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统数据库非常适合清洁，结构化的内容，例如电子表格。但是我们今天创建的大多数数据？这是凌乱而非结构化的：思考推文，照片，语音笔记，甚至模因。这就是AI的来源。了解所有这些混乱，但它需要一个智能系统来存储和搜索它。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering Fluent Bit: Installing and Configuring Fluent Bit on Kubernetes (Part 3)】掌握流利位：安装和配置kubernetes上的流利位（第3部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/installing-configuring-fluent-bit-kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This series is a general-purpose getting-started guide for those of us who want to learn about the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) project Fluent Bit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each article in this series addresses a single topic by providing insights into &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; the topic is, &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; we are interested in exploring that topic, &lt;em&gt;where&lt;/em&gt; to get started with the topic, and &lt;em&gt;how&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;to get hands-on with learning about the topic as it relates to the Fluent Bit project.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;对于那些想了解Cloud Native Computing Foundation（CNCF）项目Fluent Fluent lit的人来说，本系列是通用启动指南。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本系列中的每篇文章都通过向&lt;em&gt;提供洞察力来解决一个主题。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Developer&#39;s Guide to Mastering Agentic AI: From Theory to Practice】掌握代理AI的开发人员指南：从理论到实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/guide-to-mastering-agentic-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Agentic AI represents a paradigm shift from traditional language models that simply respond to prompts. These systems can autonomously make decisions, plan multi-step processes, use tools, maintain memory, and learn from their experiences. As AI capabilities continue to advance, understanding how to develop and work with these agentic systems has become a critical skill for forward-thinking developers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article presents a comprehensive learning path for mastering &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agentic-101-understanding-ai-agents&#34;&gt;Agentic AI&lt;/a&gt; development, along with practical resources and code repositories to jumpstart your journey.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;代理AI代表了与简单响应提示的传统语言模型的范式转变。这些系统可以自主做出决策，计划多步骤过程，使用工具，维护记忆并从其经验中学习。随着AI能力继续提高，了解如何与这些代理系统开发和合作已成为具有前瞻性开发人员的关键技能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文为掌握&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-agentic-101-cond1-understanding-ai-agents”&gt;“ agesic ai &lt;/ai &lt;/a&gt;开发，以及实用的资源和代码重新存储库来跳跃您的旅程。&lt;/p&gt;&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java Virtual Threads and Scaling】Java虚拟线程和缩放</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-virtual-threads-and-scaling</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Java Virtual Threads were introduced in JDK 19 as a preview feature as part of Project Loom, but they are fully supported starting from JDK 21 and beyond (JDK 24 includes further refinements).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Virtual threads primarily help developers by simplifying concurrent programming — eliminating the need to choose between synchronous and reactive models, and reducing the complexity of working with NIO (non-blocking I/O) APIs. They seamlessly translate traditionally blocking operations such as I/O calls, synchronization, and thread sleeping into efficient, non-blocking operations under the hood, while allowing developers to write code in a straightforward, blocking style.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;在JDK 19中引入了Java虚拟线程作为项目织机的一部分，但它们是从JDK 21及以后开始的（JDK 24包括进一步的细化）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;虚拟线程主要通过简化并发编程来帮助开发人员 - 消除了在同步模型和反应性模型之间进行选择的需求，并降低了使用NIO（非块I/O）API的复杂性。他们无缝地翻译了传统上阻止操作，例如I/O呼叫，同步和线程，并在引擎盖下的高效，非阻滞操作中，同时允许开发人员以直接的，阻止的样式编写代码。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking the Benefits of a Private API in AWS API Gateway】解锁AWS API网关中私人API的好处</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/private-api-aws-gateway</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AWS API Gateway is a managed service to create, publish, and manage APIs. It serves as a bridge between your applications and backend services. When creating APIs for our backend services, we tend to open it up using public IPs. Yes, we do authenticate and authorize access. However, oftentimes it is seen that a particular API is meant for internal applications only. In such cases it would be great to declare these as private.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Public APIs expose your services to a broader audience over the internet and thus come with risks related to data exposure and unauthorized access. On the other hand, private APIs are meant for internal consumption only. This provides an additional layer of security and eliminates the risk of potential data theft and unauthorized access.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; AWS API网关是一项托管服务，可创建，发布和管理API。它是您的应用程序和后端服务之间的桥梁。在为我们的后端服务创建API时，我们倾向于使用公共IPS开放它。是的，我们确实对访问权限进行身份验证并授权。但是，通常情况下，特定的API仅用于内部应用。在这种情况下，将其宣布为私人是很棒的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;公共API通过Internet向更广泛的受众展示您的服务，因此会带来与数据曝光和未经授权访问有关的风险。另一方面，私有API仅用于内部消费。这提供了额外的安全层，并消除了潜在数据盗用和未经授权的访问的风险。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OpenSearch: Introduction and Data Management Patterns】OpenSearch：简介和数据管理模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/opensearch-introduction-and-data-management-patter</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this article we will provide an introduction to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transition-from-elasticsearch-to-opensearch&#34;&gt;OpenSearch&lt;/a&gt; for data engineers and platform engineers. We will introduce basic concepts and briefly demonstrate how OpenSearch can be used correctly for data ingestion of log and analytics data at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction to OpenSearch&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenSearch is an open-source search and analytics database engine, which developers use to build solutions for various applications, including search, data observability, data ingestion, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-protection-utilizing-power-of-siem-and-casb&#34;&gt;Security Information and Event Management (SIEM)&lt;/a&gt;, vector databases, and more.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将提供&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/transition-from-elasticsearch-to-opensearch”&gt; opensearch &lt;/a&gt;用于数据工程师和平台工程师的介绍。我们将介绍基本概念，并简要说明如何正确地将OpenSearch用于数据摄入日志和分析数据的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; OpenSearch介绍&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenSearch is an open-source search and analytics database engine, which developers use to build solutions for various applications, including search, data observability, data ingestion, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-protection-utilizing-power-of-siem-and-casb&#34;&gt;Security Information and Event Management (SIEM)&lt;/a&gt;, vector databases, and更多。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Recurrent Workflows With Cloud Native Dapr Jobs】带有云本机DAPR作业的循环工作流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/recurrent-workflows-dapr-jobs</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;We have been learning quite a lot about Dapr now.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;These are some of my previous articles about&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/curating-efficient-dapr-workflows&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Dapr Workflows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/securing-conversations-with-llms&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Dapr Conversation AI&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;components. Today, we will discuss Jobs, another important building block of the Dapr ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;我们现在已经学习了很多有关DAPR的知识。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-preserver-spaces =“ true”&gt;这些是我以前有关&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/curating-curating-dapr-workflows =” target =“ _ _ black”&gt; &lt;span data-preserver-spaces =“ data-preserver-spaces =“ true”&gt;和&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/securing-conversations-with-llms” target =“ _ black”&gt; &lt;span data-proserver-spaces =“ true”&gt; true“ true”&gt; dapr dapr对话ai &lt;/span ai &lt;/span ai &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span-span-perser-spacess-spacess-compents = comments = comments =“”今天，我们将讨论DAPR生态系统的另一个重要组成部分的工作。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【While Performing Dependency Selection, I Avoid the Loss Of Sleep From Node.js Libraries&#39; Dangers】在执行依赖性选择时，我避免了node.js库的危险而失去睡眠</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/avoid-sleepless-nights-nodejs-dependency-risks</link>
      <description>【&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;Running &#34;&lt;code&gt;npm install&lt;/code&gt;&#34; requires trusting unknown parties online.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  Staring at &lt;code&gt;node_modules&lt;/code&gt; for too long leads someone to become a &lt;code&gt;node_modules&lt;/code&gt; expert.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;We Should Have Solved This Issue By 2025&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The registry expands relentlessly at the rate of one new library addition every six seconds while maintaining a current package total of &lt;code&gt;2.9&amp;nbsp;million&lt;/code&gt;. Most packages function as helpful code, while others contain fatal bugs that professionals must avoid altogether because the total number of registrations swells to mass proportions. The back-end services I manage process more than a billion monthly requests, while one rogue script from postinstall can damage uptime service agreements and customer trust.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p&gt;运行“ &lt;code&gt; npm install &lt;/code&gt;”需要在线信任未知方。&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  盯着&lt;code&gt; node_modules &lt;/code&gt;太长导致某人成为&lt;code&gt; node_modules &lt;/code&gt; Expert。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;我们应该在2025年之前解决此问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注册表每六秒钟以一个新图书馆的添加速度不断扩展，同时保持当前的包装总计为290万&lt;/code&gt;。大多数软件包的作用是有用的代码，而其他包装则包含致命的错误，专业人士必须完全避免，因为注册总数膨胀到大量比例。我管理流程的后端服务每月的请求超过10亿，而PostStall的一个流氓脚本可能会损坏正常运行时间服务协议和客户信任。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build Scalable Mobile Apps With React Native: A Step-by-Step Guide】如何使用React Antial构建可扩展的移动应用程序：逐步指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-mobile-apps-with-react-native</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Siloed development teams, fragmented code, and the relentless pressure to keep pace with two distinct platforms — these realities have long affected mobile app development. However, with platforms like React Native, developers have a robust solution for cross-platform apps with native-like features, offering consistent UI/UX across Android and iOS.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Its &#34;write-once, deploy everywhere&#34; methodology has enabled all businesses, from startups to established enterprises, to maintain and refine a unified codebase for their apps. The impact? Reduced development costs, faster market entry, increased agility, and streamlined future updates and maintenance. This write-up will dig into the process of building cross-platform applications with &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/creating-a-react-native-sdk-step-by-step-guide-wit&#34;&gt;React Native&lt;/a&gt;, exploring the key steps and best practices for successful implementation.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;孤立的开发团队，零散的代码以及与两个不同平台保持步伐的不懈压力 - 这些现实长期以来影响了移动应用程序开发。但是，借助React Native等平台，开发人员为具有类似于本机的功能的跨平台应用程序提供了强大的解决方案，并在Android和iOS上提供一致的UI/UX。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它的“写入，部署到处都可以部署”方法使从初创企业到建立企业的所有业务都可以维护和完善其应用程序的统一代码库。影响？降低了开发成本，更快的市场进入，提高敏捷性以及简化了未来的更新和维护。本文章将深入研究跨平台应用程序与&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/creating-a-react-native-sdk-native-sdk-step-by-step-guide-wit”&gt; React satern &lt;/a&gt;，探索成功实施的关键步骤和最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Issue and Present Verifiable Credentials With Spring Boot and Android】发行并提供带有弹簧靴和Android的可验证凭证</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/verifiable-credentials-spring-boot-android</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;995&#34; data-start=&#34;402&#34;&gt;As digital identity ecosystems evolve, the ability to issue and verify digital credentials in a secure, privacy-preserving, and interoperable manner has become increasingly important. Verifiable Credentials (VCs) offer a W3C-standardized way to present claims about a subject, such as identity attributes or qualifications, in a tamper-evident and cryptographically verifiable format. Among the emerging formats, &lt;strong data-end=&#34;863&#34; data-start=&#34;813&#34;&gt;Selective Disclosure JSON Web Tokens (SD-JWTs)&lt;/strong&gt; stand out for enabling holders to share only selected parts of a credential, while ensuring its authenticity can still be verified.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1253&#34; data-start=&#34;997&#34;&gt;In this article, we demonstrate the issuance and presentation of Verifiable Credentials using the &lt;strong data-end=&#34;1112&#34; data-start=&#34;1095&#34;&gt;SD-JWT format&lt;/strong&gt;, leveraging &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-best-practices-for-microservices&#34;&gt;Spring Boot microservices&lt;/a&gt; on the backend and a &lt;strong data-end=&#34;1212&#34; data-start=&#34;1176&#34;&gt;Kotlin-based Android application&lt;/strong&gt; acting as the wallet on the client side.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 995” data-start =“ 402”&gt;随着数字身份生态系统的发展，以安全，隐私性和可互操作方式发行和验证数字凭据的能力变得越来越重要。可验证的凭据（VCS）提供了一种以W3C标准化的方式来提出有关某个主题的主张，例如身份属性或资格，以篡改和密码可验证的格式提出。在新兴格式中，&lt;strong data-end =“ 863” data-start =“ 813”&gt;选择性披露JSON Web令牌（SD-JWTS）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;脱颖而出，可以使持有人仅共享凭据的部分，同时确保其真实性仍然可以验证。&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1253” data-start =“ 997”&gt;在本文中，我们使用&lt;strong data-end =“ 1112” data-start =“ 1095”&gt; sd-jwt格式&lt;/strong&gt; href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/spring-boot-best-practices-for-microservices”&gt; Spring Boot Microservices &lt;/a&gt;在后端和A &lt;strong data-end =“ 1212” data data-start =“ 1176”&gt; kotlin基于Kotlin的Android Android Apply &lt;/android Aptroct at pallet。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>