<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Few-Shot Text Classification With Noisy Channel Language Model Prompting】通过噪声通道语言模型提示增强少镜头文本分类</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-few-shot-text-classification-with-noisy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Few-shot learning is a fascinating area in natural language processing (NLP), where models are trained to perform tasks with very few labeled examples. Traditional approaches often rely on directly modeling the conditional probability of a label given an input text. However, these methods can be unstable, especially when dealing with imbalanced data or the need for generalization to unseen labels. A recent advancement in this area is the &lt;strong&gt;noisy channel language model prompting&lt;/strong&gt;, which takes inspiration from classic noisy channel models in machine translation to improve few-shot text classification.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Here are two concrete examples of problems in few-shot learning that the noisy channel language model prompting aims to solve:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;少样本学习是自然语言处理 (NLP) 中一个令人着迷的领域，其中模型被训练来执行带有很少标记示例的任务。传统方法通常依赖于直接对给定输入文本的标签的条件概率进行建模。然而，这些方法可能不稳定，特别是在处理不平衡数据或需要泛化到看不见的标签时。该领域的最新进展是&lt;strong&gt;噪声通道语言模型提示&lt;/strong&gt;，它从机器翻译中的经典噪声通道模型中汲取灵感，以改进小样本文本分类。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;以下是噪声通道语言模型提示旨在解决的少样本学习问题的两个具体示例：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Performing Advanced Facebook Event Data Analysis With a Vector Database】使用矢量数据库执行高级 Facebook 事件数据分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-facebook-event-data-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s digital age, professionals across all industries must stay updated with upcoming events, conferences, and workshops. However, efficiently finding events that align with one&#39;s interests amidst the vast ocean of online information presents a significant challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This blog introduces an innovative solution to this challenge: a comprehensive application designed to scrape event data from Facebook&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;(opens new window)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;and analyzes the scraped data using MyScale&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;(opens new window&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. While MyScale is commonly associated with the RAG tech stack or used as a vector database, its capabilities extend beyond these realms. We will utilize it for data analysis, leveraging its vector search functionality to analyze events that are semantically similar, thus providing better results and insights.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的数字时代，各行业的专业人士都必须及时了解即将举行的活动、会议和研讨会。然而，在浩瀚的在线信息海洋中有效地找到符合自己兴趣的事件是一项重大挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本博客介绍了应对这一挑战的创新解决方案：一款旨在从 Facebook 抓取事件数据的综合应用程序&lt;span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;（打开新窗口）&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;以及使用 MyScale&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;（打开新窗口&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;）分析抓取的数据。虽然 MyScale 通常与 RAG 技术堆栈相关联或用作矢量数据库，但它的我们将利用它进行数据分析，利用其矢量搜索功能来分析语义相似的事件，从而提供更好的结果和见解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Cost and Carbon Footprint With Smart Scaling Using SQS Queue Triggers: Part 1】使用 SQS 队列触发器通过智能扩展优化成本和碳足迹：第 1 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimising-cost-and-carbon-footprint-with-smart-sc</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The rising demand for sustainable and eco-friendly computing solutions has given rise to the area of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/green-software-and-carbon-hack&#34;&gt;green computing&lt;/a&gt;. According to Wikipedia, Green computing, green IT (Information Technology), or ICT sustainability, is the study and practice of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Environmentally_sustainable&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;environmentally sustainable&lt;/a&gt; computing or IT. &amp;nbsp;With the rise of cloud computing in the last few decades, green computing has become a big focus in the design and architecture of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reducing-carbon-footprint-in-hybrid-cloud-modernization&#34;&gt;software systems in the cloud&lt;/a&gt;. This focus on optimizing the resources for energy efficiency allows us to focus on cost optimization in addition to reducing the carbon footprint. AWS is one of the cloud providers leading the movement from the front. AWS is investing heavily in renewable energy and designing its data centers with efficiency in mind.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aboutamazon.com/planet/climate-pledge&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Amazon Climate Pledge&lt;/a&gt;, Amazon aims to achieve net-zero carbon emissions by 2040 and has already made significant strides, including powering its operations with 100% renewable energy by 2025. Additionally, AWS provides tools like the AWS Carbon Footprint Calculator, enabling customers to monitor and reduce their carbon emissions, thereby fostering a more sustainable digital ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;对可持续和环保计算解决方案不断增长的需求催生了&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/green-software-and-carbon-hack 领域”绿色计算&lt;/a&gt;。根据维基百科，绿色计算、绿色IT（信息技术）或ICT可持续性是&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Environmentally_sustainable&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;目标的研究和实践=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;环境可持续&lt;/a&gt;计算或 IT。  随着过去几十年云计算的兴起，绿色计算已成为设计和架构中的一大焦点&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reducing-carbon-footprint-in-hybrid-云现代化&#34;&gt;云中的软件系统&lt;/a&gt;。这种对优化资源以提高能源效率的关注使我们除了减少碳足迹之外还可以专注于成本优化。 AWS 是引领这场变革的云提供商之一。 AWS 正在大力投资可再生能源，并在设计数据中心时考虑到效率。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;根据&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aboutamazon.com/planet/climate-pledge&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;亚马逊气候承诺&lt;/a &gt;，亚马逊的目标是到 2040 年实现净零碳排放，并且已经取得了重大进展，包括到 2025 年使用 100% 可再生能源为其运营提供动力。此外，AWS 还提供 AWS 碳足迹计算器等工具，使客户能够监控和减少碳排放碳排放，从而培育更加可持续的数字生态系统。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Machine Learning and AI are Transforming Healthcare Diagnostics in Mobile Apps】机器学习和人工智能如何改变移动应用程序中的医疗诊断</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ml-and-ai-in-healthcare-mobile-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Healthcare has long been a data-intensive domain, and today, the integration of artificial intelligence and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; is opening new frontiers, especially in the field of diagnostics. As developers, we&#39;re at the forefront of this transformation, building mobile applications that help both patients and healthcare professionals make better decisions, faster. From improving diagnostic accuracy to speeding up early disease detection, AI-powered mobile apps are becoming indispensable tools in modern healthcare.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll explore how AI is being integrated into healthcare apps to provide diagnostic tools and assist in early disease detection, along with a few technical insights from a developer&#39;s perspective.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;医疗保健长期以来一直是一个数据密集型领域，如今，人工智能和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习&lt;/a&gt;的集成正在开辟新的领域，特别是在诊断领域。作为开发人员，我们处于这一转型的最前沿，构建移动应用程序来帮助患者和医疗保健专业人员更快地做出更好的决策。从提高诊断准确性到加快早期疾病检测，人工智能驱动的移动应用程序正在成为现代医疗保健中不可或缺的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们将探讨如何将人工智能集成到医疗保健应用中，以提供诊断工具并协助早期疾病检测，并从开发人员的角度提供一些技术见解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Observability With eBPF】eBPF 的可观察性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/observability-with-ebpf</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;5:1-5:36&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/A-Gentle-Intro-to-eBPF&#34;&gt;eBPF&lt;/a&gt; is a groundbreaking technology that allows you to run sandboxed programs within the Linux kernel. This provides a safe and efficient way to extend the kernel&#39;s capabilities without modifying its source code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-sourcepos=&#34;7:1-7:12&#34;&gt;High-Level Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;7:1-7:12&#34;&gt;Below is an overview of the stack:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;5:1-5:36&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/A-Gentle-Intro-to-eBPF&#34;&gt;eBPF&lt;/a&gt; 是一个突破性的允许您在 Linux 内核中运行沙盒程序的技术。这提供了一种安全有效的方法来扩展内核的功能，而无需修改其源代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-sourcepos=&#34;7:1-7:12&#34;&gt;高级概述&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-sourcepos=&#34;7:1-7:12&#34;&gt;下面是堆栈的概述：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 21:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Battle of the RabbitMQ Queues: Performance Insights on Classic and Quorum】RabbitMQ 队列之战：Classic 和 Quorum 的性能见解</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/battle-of-the-rabbitmq-queues-performance-insights</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rabbitmq.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RabbitMQ&lt;/a&gt; is a powerful and widely used message broker that facilitates communication between distributed applications by handling the transmission, storage, and delivery of messages. As a message broker, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/message-queue-rabbit-mq-beginners-introduction&#34;&gt;RabbitMQ serves as an intermediary &lt;/a&gt;between producers (applications that send messages) and consumers (applications that receive messages), ensuring reliable message delivery even in complex, distributed environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;One of the core components of RabbitMQ is the queue, where messages are temporarily stored until they are consumed. Queues play a critical role in RabbitMQ’s architecture, enabling &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/asynchronous-vs-synchronous-programming-when-to-us&#34;&gt;asynchronous&lt;/a&gt; communication and decoupling the producers and consumers. This decoupling allows applications to operate independently, promoting scalability, resilience, and fault tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rabbitmq.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RabbitMQ&lt;/a&gt; 是一个功能强大且广泛使用的消息代理，通过处理消息的传输、存储和传递来促进分布式应用程序之间的通信。作为消息代理，RabbitMQ 充当生产者（发送消息的应用程序）之间的中介&lt;/a&gt;和消费者（接收消息的应用程序），即使在复杂的分布式环境中也能确保可靠的消息传递。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;RabbitMQ 的核心组件之一是队列，消息临时存储在队列中，直到被消费为止。队列在 RabbitMQ 的架构中发挥着关键作用，支持异步通信并解耦生产者和消费者。这种解耦允许应用程序独立运行，从而提高可扩展性、弹性和容错能力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Handle a Crisis in a Software Project and Solve Disaster】如何处理软件项目危机并化解灾难</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-handle-a-crisis-in-a-software-project</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Crises are part of life. When it comes to software development, crises are not a matter of &#34;if,&#34; but &#34;when,&#34; so you always have to be prepared for such situations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Imagine this scenario: Everything seems to be going well with your mobile app development project. Suddenly, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/levelling-up-the-non-technical-skills-every-aspiri&#34;&gt;senior developer&lt;/a&gt; has to leave the project due to force majeure, and only the junior developers are left to lead the project. The delivery deadline is very close and the client is anxious. What to do?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;危机是生活的一部分。对于软件开发来说，危机不是“如果”的问题，而是“何时”的问题，因此您必须始终为此类情况做好准备。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;想象一下这个场景：您的移动应用开发项目似乎一切进展顺利。突然，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/levelling-up-the-non-technical-skills-every-aspiri&#34;&gt;高级开发人员&lt;/a&gt;因不可抗力而不得不离开项目，只剩下初级开发人员来领导该项目。交货期限已经临近，客户焦急万分。该怎么办？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Server-Side Rendering With Spring Boot】使用 Spring Boot 进行服务器端渲染</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/server-side-rendering-with-spring-boot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Understanding the shared steps in the project setup is crucial before delving into the specifics of each client-augmenting technology. My requirements &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-short-history-of-ajax-and-ssr&#34;&gt;from the last post&lt;/a&gt; were quite straightforward:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;I&#39;ll assume the viewpoint of a backend developer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;No front-end build step: no TypeScript, no minification, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;All dependencies are managed from the backend app, i.e., Maven&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s important to note that the technology I&#39;ll be detailing, except Vaadin, follows a similar approach. Vaadin, with its unique paradigm, really stands out among the approaches.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在深入研究每种客户端增强技术的具体细节之前，了解项目设置中的共享步骤至关重要。我的要求&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-short-history-of-ajax-and-ssr&#34;&gt;上一篇文章&lt;/a&gt;非常简单：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA; &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;我将假设后端开发人员的观点。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;无前端构建步骤：无 TypeScript、无缩小等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;所有依赖项均由后端应用程序（即 Maven）管理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;值得注意的是，我将详细介绍的技术（Vaadin 除外）都遵循类似的方法。 Vaadin 以其独特的范式在众多方法中脱颖而出。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 13:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Predicting Traffic Volume With Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning】利用人工智能和机器学习预测交通量</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/predicting-traffic-volume-with-ai-and-ml</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Effective traffic forecasting is important for urban planning, especially in reducing congestion, improving traffic flow, and maintaining public safety. This study examines the performance of machine learning models of linear regression, decision trees, and random forest to predict traffic flow along the westbound I-94 highway, using datasets collected between 2012 and 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Exploratory data analysis revealed traffic volume patterns related to weather, holidays, and time of day. The models were evaluated based on R2 and mean squared error (MSE) metrics, with random forest outperforming others, obtaining an R2 of 0.849 and lower MSE than linear regression and decision tree models.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;有效的交通预测对于城市规划非常重要，特别是在减少拥堵、改善交通流量和维护公共安全方面。本研究使用 2012 年至 2018 年收集的数据集，检查线性回归、决策树和随机森林的机器学习模型的性能，以预测 I-94 高速公路西行的交通流量。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;探索性数据分析揭示了与天气、节假日和一天中的时间相关的交通量模式。基于 R2 和均方误差 (MSE) 指标对模型进行评估，随机森林优于其他模型，获得 0.849 的 R2 和低于线性回归和决策树模型的 MSE。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Refining Your JavaScript Code: 10 Critical Mistakes to Sidestep】优化你的 JavaScript 代码：避免犯的 10 个严重错误</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/javascript-10-critical-mistakes-to-sidestep</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/javascript-frameworks-past-present-and-future&#34;&gt;JavaScript,&lt;/a&gt; the backbone of modern web development, is a powerful and versatile language. JavaScript&#39;s flexibility and dynamic nature make it both a blessing and a curse for new developers. While it allows for rapid development and creativity, it also has quirks that can trip up the uninitiated. By familiarizing yourself with these common mistakes, you&#39;ll be better equipped to write &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/clean-code-tips&#34;&gt;clean&lt;/a&gt;, efficient, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/along-came-a-bug&#34;&gt;bug&lt;/a&gt;-free code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Mistake 1: Not Declaring Variables Properly&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;One of the most common mistakes beginners make is not properly declaring variables. JavaScript allows you to declare variables using &lt;code&gt;var&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;let&lt;/code&gt;, or &lt;code&gt;const&lt;/code&gt;. Failing to declare a variable properly can lead to unexpected behavior and hard-to-track bugs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/javascript-frameworks-past-present-and-future&#34;&gt;JavaScript 是现代 Web 开发的支柱，一种强大且多功能的语言。 JavaScript 的灵活性和动态特性对于新开发人员来说既是福也是祸。虽然它允许快速开发和创造力，但它也有一些怪癖，可能会给外行带来麻烦。通过熟悉这些常见错误，您将能够更好地编写&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/clean-code-tips&#34;&gt;干净&lt;/a&gt;、高效且&lt;a href =&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/along-came-a-bug&#34;&gt;无错误&lt;/a&gt;代码。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;错误 1：没有正确声明变量&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;问题&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;初学者最常犯的错误之一是没有正确声明变量。 JavaScript 允许您使用 &lt;code&gt;var&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;let&lt;/code&gt; 或 &lt;code&gt;const&lt;/code&gt; 声明变量。未能正确声明变量可能会导致意外行为和难以跟踪的错误。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>