<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Commonly Occurring Errors in Microsoft Graph Integrations and How To Troubleshoot Them (Part 6)】Microsoft Graph 集成中常见的错误以及如何排除这些错误（第 6 部分）</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/errors-in-microsoft-graph-integrations-part-six</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This article discusses the following example: changing a column value for a list item of a “user-defined” SharePoint list, which represents a PDF file within a sub-folder of the SharePoint drive, using a DriveItem, which also represents the PDF file. SharePoint lists are central data structures that make it possible to store, organize, and manage information in tabular form. The test aims to demonstrate and explain how the MS-Graph API can be successfully used to change values in a list and correctly transfer this change to SharePoint. This ensures that the integrity of the file is maintained after the change and that no unexpected errors occur during API communication.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Microsoft Graph API&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Microsoft Graph API is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/restful-api-lifecycle-management&#34;&gt;REST-based&lt;/a&gt; programming interface that provides access to a variety of services and data within the Microsoft 365 platform. It offers developers the ability to access a central interface to read, write, and manage data from services such as Azure Active Directory, Outlook, OneDrive, SharePoint, Microsoft Teams, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本文讨论以下示例：使用 DriveItem（也代表 SharePoint 驱动器的子文件夹中的 PDF 文件）更改“用户定义”SharePoint 列表的列表项的列值，该列表代表 SharePoint 驱动器的子文件夹中的 PDF 文件。 PDF 文件。 SharePoint 列表是中心数据结构，可以以表格形式存储、组织和管理信息。该测试旨在演示和解释如何成功使用 MS-Graph API 更改列表中的值并将此更改正确传输到 SharePoint。这可确保更改后保持文件的完整性，并且 API 通信期间不会出现意外错误。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;微软图形API&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Graph API 是一个&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/restful-api-lifecycle-management&#34;&gt;基于 REST&lt;/a&gt; 的编程接口，提供对各种服务的访问以及 Microsoft 365 平台内的数据。它使开发人员能够访问中央界面，以读取、写入和管理来自 Azure Active Directory、Outlook、OneDrive、SharePoint、Microsoft Teams 等服务的数据。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Programming Language With No Syntax?】没有语法的编程语言？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/programming-language-with-no-syntax</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Is it possible to have a programming language that has no syntax? It sounds like a contradiction. Programming languages are all about syntax, plus a bit of code generation, optimization, run-time environment, and so on. But syntax is the most important part as far as programmers are concerned. When encountering a new programming language, it takes time to learn the syntax.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Could we just make the syntax disappear or at least make it as simple as possible? Could we also make the syntax arbitrary so that the programmer writing the code can define it for themselves?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;是否有可能有一种没有语法的编程语言？听起来很矛盾。编程语言都是关于语法的，再加上一些代码生成、优化、运行时环境等等。但对于程序员而言，语法是最重要的部分。当遇到一种新的编程语言时，需要花时间来学习语法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们能否让语法消失或者至少让它尽可能简单？我们是否也可以使语法任意，以便编写代码的程序员可以自己定义它？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Founder Mode?】创始人模式？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/founder-mode</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR: The Perils of Founder Mode&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article delves into the darker aspects of Founder Mode, popularized by Paul Graham and others. It offers a critical perspective for agile practitioners, product leaders, startup founders, and managers who embrace this paradigm and probably fall victim to survivorship bias; the Jobs and the Cheskys are the exception, not the rule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The article explores how resulting tendencies, such as micromanagement, lack of strategic transparency, team devaluation, and reckless risk-taking, can undermine organizational health, stifle innovation, and conflict with agile principles. These can jeopardize long-term success while making work in organizations with a failed founder mode application miserable for everyone below the immediate leadership level and the founder himself.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;TL;DR：创始人模式的危险&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文深入探讨了由 Paul Graham 等人推广的创始人模式的阴暗面。它为敏捷从业者、产品领导者、初创公司创始人和管理者提供了一个批判性的视角，他们接受这种范式，并可能成为幸存者偏差的受害者；乔布斯和切斯基家族是例外，而不是规则。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文探讨了由此产生的趋势，例如微观管理、缺乏战略透明度、团队贬值和鲁莽的冒险，会如何破坏组织健康、抑制创新以及与敏捷原则发生冲突。这些可能会危及长期成功，同时使创始人模式应用失败的组织中的工作对直接领导层以下的每个人和创始人本人来说都是痛苦的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Troubleshooting PostgreSQL Low Free Memory】PostgreSQL 可用内存不足故障排除</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/troubleshooting-postgresql-low-free-memory</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Memory usage is one of the most important aspects of the database system. Having not enough memory directly affects every performance metric and negatively impacts the performance. This in turn affects our users and the business. In this blog post, we are going to understand how databases (and PostgreSQL specifically) manage memory and how to troubleshoot low free-memory scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;How Databases Read Data&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To understand how to deal with memory, we need to understand how things work. Let’s see some basic databases and operating systems mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;内存使用是数据库系统最重要的方面之一。内存不足会直接影响每个性能指标并对性能产生负面影响。这反过来又会影响我们的用户和业务。在这篇博文中，我们将了解数据库（特别是 PostgreSQL）如何管理内存以及如何解决可用内存不足的情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;数据库如何读取数据&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解如何处理内存，我们需要了解事物是如何工作的。让我们看看一些基本的数据库和操作系统机制。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Algorithmic Advances in AI-Driven Search: Optimizing Query Processing for Precision and Speed】人工智能驱动搜索的算法进步：优化查询处理以提高精度和速度</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/algorithmic-advances-in-ai-driven-search</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today’s data-driven world, efficient and accurate information retrieval is crucial. The rapid growth of unstructured data across industries poses a significant challenge for traditional search algorithms. AI has revolutionized query processing and data retrieval by introducing sophisticated techniques that optimize both the precision and speed of search results. This article dives deep into the algorithms behind AI-driven search and how they enhance query processing, enabling intelligent, relevant, and scalable search experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Traditional To AI-Enhanced Query Processing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional query processing methods, such as Boolean search and simple keyword-based matching, relied heavily on manual indexing and rigid rule-based systems. These methods often failed to capture the user’s intent or adapt to complex queries. In contrast, AI-enhanced query processing employs &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;machine learning (ML)&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/practitioners-guide-to-deep-learning-projects&#34;&gt;deep learning (DL)&lt;/a&gt; models to understand the semantics of a query, providing more accurate results by interpreting the context rather than focusing solely on keyword matching.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今数据驱动的世界中，高效、准确的信息检索至关重要。各行业非结构化数据的快速增长对传统搜索算法提出了重大挑战。人工智能通过引入优化搜索结果的精度和速度的复杂技术，彻底改变了查询处理和数据检索。本文深入探讨人工智能驱动搜索背后的算法，以及它们如何增强查询处理，从而实现智能、相关且可扩展的搜索体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;从传统查询处理到人工智能增强型查询处理&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统的查询处理方法，例如布尔搜索和简单的基于关键字的匹配，严重依赖于手动索引和严格的基于规则的系统。这些方法通常无法捕捉用户的意图或适应复杂的查询。相比之下，人工智能增强型查询处理采用&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习 (ML)&lt;/a&gt; 和&lt;a href=&#34;https:// dzone.com/articles/practitioners-guide-to-deep-learning-projects&#34;&gt;深度学习 (DL)&lt;/a&gt; 模型来理解查询的语义，通过解释上下文而不是仅仅关注于提供更准确的结果关键字匹配。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【High-Load Systems: Overcoming Challenges in Social Network Development】高负载系统：克服社交网络开发中的挑战</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/high-load-systems-in-social-network-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I am Alexander Kolobov. I worked as a team lead at one of the biggest social networks, where I led teams of up to 10 members, including SEO specialists, analysts, and product manager. As a developer, I designed, developed, and maintained various features for the desktop and mobile web versions of a social network across backend, frontend, and mobile application APIs. My experience includes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Redesigning the social network interface for multiple user sections&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Completely rewriting network widgets for external sites&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Maintaining privacy settings for closed profiles and the content archiving function&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Overhauling the backend and frontend of the mail notification system, handling millions of emails daily&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Creating a system for conducting NPS/CSI surveys that covered the two largest Russian social networks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, I am going to talk about high-load systems and the challenges they bring. I want to touch upon the following aspects:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我是亚历山大·科洛博夫。我曾在最大的社交网络之一担任团队负责人，领导着多达 10 名成员的团队，其中包括 SEO 专家、分析师和产品经理。作为一名开发人员，我跨后端、前端和移动应用程序 API 设计、开发和维护社交网络的桌面和移动 Web 版本的各种功能。我的经验包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为多个用户部分重新设计社交网络界面&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;完全重写外部站点的网络小部件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;维护已关闭个人资料和内容存档功能的隐私设置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;检修邮件通知系统的后端和前端，每天处理数百万封电子邮件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;创建一个覆盖俄罗斯最大的两个社交网络的 NPS/CSI 调查系统&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我将讨论高负载系统及其带来的挑战。我想谈谈以下几个方面：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI and Technical Debt: Balancing Innovation and Sustainability】人工智能和技术债务：平衡创新和可持续发展</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-and-technical-debt</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As artificial intelligence (AI) continues to revolutionize the tech industry, developers, engineers, and architects face a new challenge: managing the technical debt that comes with rapid AI adoption. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeffhollan/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Jeff Hollan&lt;/a&gt;, Head of Apps and Developer Tools at &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-snowflake-for-junior-software-engi&#34;&gt;Snowflake&lt;/a&gt;, shares invaluable insights on how to balance innovation and sustainability in AI projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The AI Adoption Dilemma&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The rush to implement AI solutions has created a unique landscape where organizations must carefully navigate between seizing opportunities and avoiding potential pitfalls. As Hollan points out,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着人工智能 (AI) 不断革新科技行业，开发人员、工程师和架构师面临着新的挑战：管理人工智能快速采用带来的技术债务。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeffhollan/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Jeff Hollan&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href= 应用程序和开发者工具主管“https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-snowflake-for-junior-software-engi&#34;&gt;Snowflake&lt;/a&gt;，分享了有关如何平衡人工智能项目的创新和可持续性的宝贵见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能采用困境&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;急于实施人工智能解决方案创造了一个独特的局面，组织必须在抓住机遇和避免潜在陷阱之间小心翼翼。正如 Hollan 指出的那样，&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 18:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Database Keys: A Comprehensive Guide】数据库键：综合指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/database-keys-a-comprehensive-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the world of database management, keys play a crucial role in organizing, accessing, and maintaining data integrity. Whether you&#39;re a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reflections-from-a-dba&#34;&gt;seasoned database administrator&lt;/a&gt; or just starting your journey in data management, understanding the various types of database keys is essential. In this post, we&#39;ll explore all the different types of keys, their purposes, and how they contribute to effective &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-good-database-design&#34;&gt;database design&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate these concepts, we&#39;ll use a simple university database with the following tables:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在数据库管理领域，密钥在组织、访问和维护数据完整性方面发挥着至关重要的作用。无论您是&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reflections-from-a-dba&#34;&gt;经验丰富的数据库管理员&lt;/a&gt;还是刚刚开始数据管理之旅，了解各种类型的数据库密钥是必不可少的。在这篇文章中，我们将探讨所有不同类型的密钥、它们的用途以及它们如何有助于有效&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-good-database-design&#34;&gt;数据库设计&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了说明这些概念，我们将使用一个简单的大学数据库，其中包含下表：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Test Automation for Mobile Apps: Strategy for Improved Testing Results】移动应用程序的测试自动化：改进测试结果的策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/test-automation-for-mobile-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;We can hardly imagine our lives without the smartphones that we use every day — from staying connected with others to managing tasks. Some people may even become&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reviews.org/mobile/cell-phone-addiction/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;addicted&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;to them: 56.9% of Americans identify as addicted to their phones, with an average screen time of 4 hours and 25 minutes per day and checking their phones within the first 10 minutes of waking up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:279}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;And considering that the number of mobile app downloads across various categories continues to surge, they must operate flawlessly to provide consistently good user experience and allow people to seamlessly perform daily activities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:279}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;我们很难想象没有我们每天使用的智能手机的生活——从与他人保持联系到管理任务。有些人甚至可能会变得&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reviews.org/mobile/cell-phone-addiction/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast =&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;对它们上瘾&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt; 对它们上瘾：56.9% 的美国人认为对它们上瘾每天平均使用手机的时间为 4 小时 25 分钟，并在起床后的前 10 分钟内查看手机。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;201341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559739 &#34;:160,&#34;335559740&#34;:279}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;考虑到各个类别的移动应用下载量持续激增，它们必须完美运行，以提供始终如一的良好用户体验，并让人们能够无缝地执行日常活动。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;201341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559739&#34;:160,&#34;335559740&#34;:279}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Hands-On Guide to OpenTelemetry: Manual Instrumentation for Developers】OpenTelemetry 实践指南：面向开发人员的手动检测</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/hands-on-guide-to-otel-manual-instrumentation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to start your journey on the road to collecting telemetry data from your applications?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this series, you&#39;ll explore how to adopt &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; and how to instrument an application to collect tracing telemetry. You&#39;ll learn how to leverage out-of-the-box automatic instrumentation tools and understand when it&#39;s necessary to explore more advanced manual instrumentation for your applications. By the end of this series, you&#39;ll have an understanding of how telemetry travels from your applications to the OpenTelemetry Collector, and be ready to bring OpenTelemetry to your future projects. Everything discussed here is supported by &lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a hands-on, self-paced workshop&lt;/a&gt; authored &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;by Paige Cruz&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您准备好开始从应用程序收集遥测数据的旅程了吗？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本系列中，您将探索如何采用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; 以及如何检测一个应用程序来收集跟踪遥测数据。您将学习如何利用开箱即用的自动仪表工具，并了解何时需要为您的应用探索更高级的手动仪表。在本系列结束时，您将了解遥测如何从应用程序传输到 OpenTelemetry Collector，并准备好将 OpenTelemetry 引入您未来的项目。这里讨论的所有内容均由&lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;动手、自定进度的研讨会&lt;/ a&gt; 作者：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;由 Paige Cruz&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>