<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Test Automation for Mobile Apps: Strategy for Improved Testing Results】移动应用程序的测试自动化：改进测试结果的策略</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/test-automation-for-mobile-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;We can hardly imagine our lives without the smartphones that we use every day — from staying connected with others to managing tasks. Some people may even become&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reviews.org/mobile/cell-phone-addiction/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;addicted&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;to them: 56.9% of Americans identify as addicted to their phones, with an average screen time of 4 hours and 25 minutes per day and checking their phones within the first 10 minutes of waking up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:279}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;And considering that the number of mobile app downloads across various categories continues to surge, they must operate flawlessly to provide consistently good user experience and allow people to seamlessly perform daily activities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:160,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:279}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;我们很难想象没有我们每天使用的智能手机的生活——从与他人保持联系到管理任务。有些人甚至可能会变得&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reviews.org/mobile/cell-phone-addiction/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast =&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;对它们上瘾&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt; 对它们上瘾：56.9% 的美国人认为对它们上瘾每天平均使用手机的时间为 4 小时 25 分钟，并在起床后的前 10 分钟内查看手机。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;201341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559739 &#34;:160,&#34;335559740&#34;:279}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;考虑到各个类别的移动应用下载量持续激增，它们必须完美运行，以提供始终如一的良好用户体验，并让人们能够无缝地执行日常活动。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;201341983&#34;:0,&#34;335559739&#34;:160,&#34;335559740&#34;:279}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Performing Advanced Facebook Event Data Analysis With a Vector Database】使用矢量数据库执行高级 Facebook 事件数据分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/advanced-facebook-event-data-analysis</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&#39;s digital age, professionals across all industries must stay updated with upcoming events, conferences, and workshops. However, efficiently finding events that align with one&#39;s interests amidst the vast ocean of online information presents a significant challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This blog introduces an innovative solution to this challenge: a comprehensive application designed to scrape event data from Facebook&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;(opens new window)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;and analyzes the scraped data using MyScale&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;(opens new window&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. While MyScale is commonly associated with the RAG tech stack or used as a vector database, its capabilities extend beyond these realms. We will utilize it for data analysis, leveraging its vector search functionality to analyze events that are semantically similar, thus providing better results and insights.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今的数字时代，各行业的专业人士都必须及时了解即将举行的活动、会议和研讨会。然而，在浩瀚的在线信息海洋中有效地找到符合自己兴趣的事件是一项重大挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本博客介绍了应对这一挑战的创新解决方案：一款旨在从 Facebook 抓取事件数据的综合应用程序&lt;span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;（打开新窗口）&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;以及使用 MyScale&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;sr-only&#34;&gt;（打开新窗口&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;）分析抓取的数据。虽然 MyScale 通常与 RAG 技术堆栈相关联或用作矢量数据库，但它的我们将利用它进行数据分析，利用其矢量搜索功能来分析语义相似的事件，从而提供更好的结果和见解。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Few-Shot Text Classification With Noisy Channel Language Model Prompting】通过噪声通道语言模型提示增强少镜头文本分类</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-few-shot-text-classification-with-noisy</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Few-shot learning is a fascinating area in natural language processing (NLP), where models are trained to perform tasks with very few labeled examples. Traditional approaches often rely on directly modeling the conditional probability of a label given an input text. However, these methods can be unstable, especially when dealing with imbalanced data or the need for generalization to unseen labels. A recent advancement in this area is the &lt;strong&gt;noisy channel language model prompting&lt;/strong&gt;, which takes inspiration from classic noisy channel models in machine translation to improve few-shot text classification.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Here are two concrete examples of problems in few-shot learning that the noisy channel language model prompting aims to solve:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;少样本学习是自然语言处理 (NLP) 中一个令人着迷的领域，其中模型被训练来执行带有很少标记示例的任务。传统方法通常依赖于直接对给定输入文本的标签的条件概率进行建模。然而，这些方法可能不稳定，特别是在处理不平衡数据或需要泛化到看不见的标签时。该领域的最新进展是&lt;strong&gt;噪声通道语言模型提示&lt;/strong&gt;，它从机器翻译中的经典噪声通道模型中汲取灵感，以改进小样本文本分类。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;以下是噪声通道语言模型提示旨在解决的少样本学习问题的两个具体示例：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Zero To AI Hero, Part 4: Harness Local Language Models With Semantic Kernel; Your AI, Your Rules】从零到人工智能英雄，第 4 部分：利用语义内核的本地语言模型；你的人工智能，你的规则</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-four-local-language-models</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We have covered a lot of grounds in this series so far. If you are looking to start with Semantic Kernel, I highly recommend starting with&lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-one-semantic-kernel&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-one-semantic-kernel&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-one-semantic-kernel&#34;&gt;Part 1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. In this AI developer series, I write articles on AI developer tools and frameworks and provide working GitHub samples at the end of each one. We have already experimented with AI &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-three-power-of-agents&#34;&gt;Agents&lt;/a&gt;, Personas, Planners, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-two-semantic-kernel-plugins&#34;&gt;Plugins&lt;/a&gt;. One common theme so far has been we have used an Open AI GPT-4o model deployed in Azure to do all our work. Now it is time for us to pivot and start using local models such as Phi-3 in Semantic Kernel so that you can build AI automation systems without any dependencies. This would also be a favorite solution for cyber security teams, as they don&#39;t need to worry about sensitive data getting outside of an organization&#39;s network. But I believe the happiest would be the indie hackers who want to save on cost and still have an effective Language Model that they can use without worrying about token cost and tokens per minute.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is the Small Language Model?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-smaller-language-models&#34;&gt;Small language models (SLMs)&lt;/a&gt; are increasingly becoming the go-to choice for developers who need robust AI capabilities without the baggage of heavy cloud dependency. These nimble models are designed to run locally, providing control and privacy that large-scale cloud models can’t match. SLMs like Phi-3 offer a sweet spot — they’re compact enough to run on everyday hardware but still pack enough punch to handle a range of AI tasks, from summarizing documents to powering conversational agents. The appeal? It’s all about balancing power, performance, and privacy. By keeping data processing on your local machine, SLMs help mitigate privacy concerns, making them a natural fit for sensitive sectors like healthcare, finance, and legal, where every byte of data matters.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;到目前为止，我们已经在本系列中介绍了很多内容。如果您想从语义内核开始，我强烈建议从&lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-one-semantic-内核&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-one-semantic-kernel&#34;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-one-semantic-kernel&#34;&gt;第 1 部分&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /强&gt;。在这个 AI 开发人员系列中，我撰写了有关 AI 开发人员工具和框架的文章，并在每篇文章的末尾提供了工作 GitHub 示例。我们已经尝试过人工智能&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-third-power-of-agents&#34;&gt;智能体&lt;/a&gt;、角色、规划师、和&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/zero-to-ai-hero-part-two-semantic-kernel-plugins&#34;&gt;插件&lt;/a&gt;。到目前为止，一个共同的主题是我们使用部署在 Azure 中的 Open AI GPT-4o 模型来完成所有工作。现在是时候我们转向并开始在语义内核中使用本地模型（例如 Phi-3），以便您可以在没有任何依赖的情况下构建 AI 自动化系统。这也将是网络安全团队最喜欢的解决方案，因为他们不需要担心敏感数据会流出组织的网络。但我相信最幸福的将是那些想要节省成本并仍然拥有有效的语言模型的独立黑客，他们可以使用该语言模型而无需担心代币成本和每分钟的代币。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是小语言模型？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-smaller-language-models&#34;&gt;小语言模型 (SLM)&lt;/a&gt; 越来越成为需要强大功能的开发人员的首选人工智能功能没有严重依赖云的包袱。这些灵活的模型旨在本地运行，提供大规模云模型无法比拟的控制和隐私。像 Phi-3 这样的 SLM 提供了一个最佳选择——它们足够紧凑，可以在日常硬件上运行，但仍然具有足够的功能来处理一系列人工智能任务，从总结文档到为对话代理提供动力。上诉？这一切都是为了平衡功耗、性能和隐私。通过将数据处理保留在本地计算机上，SLM 有助于减轻隐私问题，使其非常适合医疗保健、金融和法律等敏感行业，这些行业的每个数据字节都很重要。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 15:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Case Study: Scaling Intuit’s Revenue Platform for Global Commerce】案例研究：扩展 Intuit 的全球商业收入平台</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/case-study-scaling-intuits-revenue-platform</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A few years back, in my role as a platform product manager at Intuit, I was charged with the responsibility of building and scaling the revenue platform that fuels all of Intuit’s products such as QuickBooks and TurboTax. The system I managed was integral to Intuit’s trading networks and money-making capabilities which accounted for over $10 billion in annual revenues. This case study discusses the problems, principles of architecture, and best practices that I implemented in order to create a scalable country-agnostic customer-agnostic platform supporting both B2B and B2C transactions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Challenge: Building a Unified Revenue Platform&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Intuit’s product suite covers different areas, ranging from accounting software like QuickBooks designed for small and medium businesses (B2B) to consumer tax preparation services like TurboTax (B2C). This compilation posed a special challenge: How do we build a revenue platform that caters to multiple product lines, different pricing models, and varied customer segments while guaranteeing frictionless scalability and performance?&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;几年前，在 Intuit 担任平台产品经理时，我负责构建和扩展收入平台，为 QuickBooks 和 TurboTax 等所有 Intuit 产品提供动力。我管理的系统是 Intuit 交易网络和赚钱能力不可或缺的一部分，该系统的年收入超过 100 亿美元。本案例研究讨论了我为了创建支持 B2B 和 B2C 交易的可扩展的、与国家/地区无关、与客户无关的平台而实施的问题、架构原则和最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;挑战：构建统一的收入平台&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Intuit 的产品套件涵盖不同领域，从专为中小型企业 (B2B) 设计的 QuickBooks 等会计软件到 TurboTax (B2C) 等消费者报税服务。此编译提出了一个特殊的挑战：我们如何构建一个满足多个产品线、不同定价模型和不同客户群的收入平台，同时保证无摩擦的可扩展性和性能？&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 14:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Nobody Cares About Security】没有人关心安全</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/nobody-cares-about-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Nobody cares about security.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There. I said it. I said the thing everyone feels, some people think, but very few have the temerity to say out loud. But before you call me a blasphemous heathen, I will ask for just a few moments of your time to offer context. I even have some ideas and solutions.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;没有人关心安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在那里。我说过了。我说的是每个人的感受，有些人认为，但很少有人敢大声说出来。但在你称我为亵渎神明的异教徒之前，我想请你花一点时间来提供背景信息。我什至有一些想法和解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 14:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing Your Enterprise With an Identity-First Security Strategy】通过身份优先的安全策略保护您的企业</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/securing-your-enterprise-with-an-identity-first-se</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;According to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fortunebusinessinsights.com/software-as-a-service-saas-market-102222&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Fortune Business Insights,&lt;/a&gt; the global Software as a Service (SaaS) market is projected to grow from USD 317 billion in 2024 to USD 1.2 trillion by 2032, with a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 18.4%. This substantial growth in SaaS and cloud service adoption is primarily driven by modern technological advancements, such as artificial intelligence, and a predominantly hybrid workforce that requires productivity to remain competitive. However, this increased reliance on SaaS software has also led to a rise in cyberattacks. &lt;a href=&#34;https://eng.umd.edu/news/story/study-hackers-attack-every-39-seconds&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;A study from the University of Maryland&lt;/a&gt; reveals that hackers attempt an attack every 39 seconds on average. With the emergence of AI, cyberattacks are becoming more sophisticated. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forbes.com/advisor/education/it-and-tech/cybersecurity-statistics/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;With the average cost of a cyberattack nearing $4.45 million&lt;/a&gt;, it is crucial for enterprises to evolve their security infrastructure to protect against the evolving threat landscape posed by modern cyberattacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking an Identity-First Approach to Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Malicious actors are no longer limited to targeting traditional VPN networks for unauthorized access. With the rise of remote work and organizations allowing employees to work from anywhere, attackers are increasingly targeting identities and employing modern techniques, such as social engineering attacks, to gain access to systems. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.verizon.com/business/resources/reports/dbir/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;According to the 2024 Verizon Data Breach Investigations Report&lt;/a&gt;, 68% of data breach attacks involve a human element, like a person falling victim to a social engineering attack.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;根据 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fortunebusinessinsights.com/software-as-a-service-saas-market-102222&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; &gt;《财富商业洞察》&lt;/a&gt;，全球软件即服务 (SaaS) 市场预计将从 2024 年的 3170 亿美元增长到 2032 年的 1.2 万亿美元，复合年增长率 (CAGR) 为 18.4%。 SaaS 和云服务采用率的大幅增长主要是由人工智能等现代技术进步以及需要生产力保持竞争力的混合型劳动力主导推动的。然而，对 SaaS 软件依赖的增加也导致了网络攻击的增加。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://eng.umd.edu/news/story/study-hackers-attack-every-39-seconds&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;马里兰大学的一项研究&lt;/a&gt; 显示黑客平均每 39 秒就会尝试一次攻击。随着人工智能的出现，网络攻击变得越来越复杂。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forbes.com/advisor/education/it-and-tech/cybersecurity-statistics/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;网络攻击的平均成本接近445 万美元&lt;/a&gt;，对于企业来说，发展其安全基础设施以防范现代网络攻击带来的不断变化的威胁环境至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;采用身份优先的安全方法&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;恶意行为者不再局限于针对传统 VPN 网络进行未经授权的访问。随着远程工作和允许员工在任何地方工作的组织的兴起，攻击者越来越多地针对身份并采用社会工程攻击等现代技术来获取对系统的访问权限。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.verizon.com/business/resources/reports/dbir/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;根据 2024 年 Verizon 数据泄露调查报告&lt;/a&gt;， 68% 的数据泄露攻击涉及人为因素，例如成为社会工程攻击的受害者。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 16:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Common Mistakes While Implementing Self-Recursive Calls in MuleSoft [Video]】在 MuleSoft 中实现自递归调用时的常见错误 [视频]</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/common-mistakes-self-recursive-calls</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Are Self-Recursive Loops?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A self-recursive loop refers to a pattern where a flow or sub-flow calls itself recursively to process data iteratively. This is typically used to handle scenarios where data needs to be processed repetitively, such as iterating over nested data structures, managing pagination, or processing large payloads in chunks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;In short, it’s similar to the while/do-while loop in Java.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是自递归循环？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;自递归循环是指流程或子流程递归调用自身以迭代处理数据的模式。这通常用于处理需要重复处理数据的场景，例如迭代嵌套数据结构、管理分页或处理块中的大型有效负载。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;简而言之，它类似于 Java 中的 while/do-while 循环。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 16:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kafka Message Testing】Kafka消息测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/kafka-message-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;This article offers an approach to writing integration tests for Kafka-based applications that focuses on interaction specification, making tests more readable and easier to maintain. The proposed method not only enhances testing efficiency but also contributes to a better understanding of the integration processes within the application.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 366px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;590.0 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/jpeg&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1725515321544&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/05/2024 05:48 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17901771-kafkamessagetesting.jpeg&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;590041&#34; data-name=&#34;kafkamessagetesting.jpeg&#34; data-id=&#34;17901771&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17901771-kafkamessagetesting.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Duck with net and envelopes&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The article builds on three ideas presented in relevant articles: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/arranging-http-request-testing-in-spring&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;writing tests with a clear separation of Arrange-Act-Assert stages&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/isolation-in-testing-with-kafka&#34;&gt;isolation in Kafka tests&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-the-visibility-of-integration-tests&#34;&gt;using tools to enhance test visibility&lt;/a&gt;. I recommend reviewing these before delving into the material of this article.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;本文提供了一种为基于 Kafka 的应用程序编写集成测试的方法，该方法侧重于交互规范，使测试更具可读性且更易于维护。所提出的方法不仅提高了测试效率，还有助于更好地理解应用程序内的集成过程。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 366px;&#34; class =“fr-fic fr-dib lazyload”data-image =“true”data-new =“false”data-sizeformatted =“590.0 kB”data-mimetype =“image/jpeg”data-creationdate =“1725515321544”数据-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/05/2024 05:48 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17901771-kafkamessagetesting.jpeg&#34; data-modificationdate= “空”数据大小=“590041”数据名称=“kafkamessagetesting.jpeg”数据id=“17901771”数据-src=“https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17901771-kafkamessagetesting.jpeg” &#34; alt=&#34;带网和信封的鸭子&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文基于相关文章中提出的三个想法：&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/arranging-http-request-testing-in-spring&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34; _blank&#34;&gt;编写明确分离 Arrange-Act-Assert 阶段的测试&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/isolation-in-testing-with-kafka&#34;&gt;Kafka 中的隔离测试&lt;/a&gt;，以及&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/enhancing-the-visibility-of-integration-tests&#34;&gt;使用工具增强测试可见性&lt;/a&gt;。我建议在深入研究本文的内容之前先查看这些内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 17:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Cost and Carbon Footprint With Smart Scaling Using SQS Queue Triggers: Part 1】使用 SQS 队列触发器通过智能扩展优化成本和碳足迹：第 1 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimising-cost-and-carbon-footprint-with-smart-sc</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The rising demand for sustainable and eco-friendly computing solutions has given rise to the area of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/green-software-and-carbon-hack&#34;&gt;green computing&lt;/a&gt;. According to Wikipedia, Green computing, green IT (Information Technology), or ICT sustainability, is the study and practice of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Environmentally_sustainable&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;environmentally sustainable&lt;/a&gt; computing or IT. &amp;nbsp;With the rise of cloud computing in the last few decades, green computing has become a big focus in the design and architecture of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reducing-carbon-footprint-in-hybrid-cloud-modernization&#34;&gt;software systems in the cloud&lt;/a&gt;. This focus on optimizing the resources for energy efficiency allows us to focus on cost optimization in addition to reducing the carbon footprint. AWS is one of the cloud providers leading the movement from the front. AWS is investing heavily in renewable energy and designing its data centers with efficiency in mind.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aboutamazon.com/planet/climate-pledge&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Amazon Climate Pledge&lt;/a&gt;, Amazon aims to achieve net-zero carbon emissions by 2040 and has already made significant strides, including powering its operations with 100% renewable energy by 2025. Additionally, AWS provides tools like the AWS Carbon Footprint Calculator, enabling customers to monitor and reduce their carbon emissions, thereby fostering a more sustainable digital ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;对可持续和环保计算解决方案不断增长的需求催生了&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/green-software-and-carbon-hack 领域”绿色计算&lt;/a&gt;。根据维基百科，绿色计算、绿色IT（信息技术）或ICT可持续性是&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Environmentally_sustainable&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;目标的研究和实践=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;环境可持续&lt;/a&gt;计算或 IT。  随着过去几十年云计算的兴起，绿色计算已成为设计和架构中的一大焦点&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/reducing-carbon-footprint-in-hybrid-云现代化&#34;&gt;云中的软件系统&lt;/a&gt;。这种对优化资源以提高能源效率的关注使我们除了减少碳足迹之外还可以专注于成本优化。 AWS 是引领这场变革的云提供商之一。 AWS 正在大力投资可再生能源，并在设计数据中心时考虑到效率。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;根据&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.aboutamazon.com/planet/climate-pledge&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;亚马逊气候承诺&lt;/a &gt;，亚马逊的目标是到 2040 年实现净零碳排放，并且已经取得了重大进展，包括到 2025 年使用 100% 可再生能源为其运营提供动力。此外，AWS 还提供 AWS 碳足迹计算器等工具，使客户能够监控和减少碳排放碳排放，从而培育更加可持续的数字生态系统。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 18:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>