<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker Base Images Demystified: A Practical Guide】Docker Base Images脱颖而出：实用指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-base-images-demystified</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;What Is a Docker Base Image?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;A Docker base image is the foundational layer from which containers are built. Think of it as the “starting point” for your application’s environment. It’s a minimal, preconfigured template containing an operating system, runtime tools, libraries, and dependencies. When you write a Dockerfile, the &lt;code&gt;FROM&lt;/code&gt; command defines this base image, setting the stage for all subsequent layers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;For example, you might start with a lightweight Linux distribution like Alpine, a language-specific image like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-tutorial-for-beginners-a-comprehensive-guid&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/watch-a-writer-learn-nodejs-part-1&#34;&gt;Node.js&lt;/a&gt;, or even an empty &#34;scratch&#34; image for ultimate customization. These base images abstract away the underlying infrastructure, ensuring consistency across development, testing, and production environments. Choosing the right base image is critical, as it directly impacts your container’s security, size, performance, and maintainability. Whether optimizing for speed or ensuring compatibility, your base image shapes everything that follows.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2数据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;什么是Docker Base Image？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据选择 - 段落=“”&gt; docker base图像是构建容器的基础层。将其视为应用程序环境的“起点”。这是一个最小的预配置模板，其中包含操作系统，运行时工具，库和依赖项。当您编写Dockerfile时，&lt;/code&gt;命令的&lt;code&gt;命令定义了此基础图像，为所有后续层设置了阶段。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;For example, you might start with a lightweight Linux distribution like Alpine, a language-specific image like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/python-tutorial-for-beginners-a-comprehensive-guid&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/watch-a-writer-learn-nodejs-part-1”&gt; node.js &lt;/a&gt;，甚至是一个空的“ scratch”映像以用于最终自定义。这些基本图像抽象了基础基础架构，确保在开发，测试和生产环境之间保持一致性。选择正确的基本图像至关重要，因为它直接影响了您的容器的安全性，尺寸，性能和可维护性。无论是优化速度还是确保兼容性，您的基本图像都塑造了随后的所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Azure Synapse Analytics: Scaling Hurdles and Limitations】Microsoft Azure Synapse Analytics：扩展障碍和限制</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/microsoft-azure-synapse-analytics-scaling-hurdles</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Azure Synapse Analytics is a strong tool for processing large amounts of data. It does have some scaling challenges that can slow things down as your data grows. There are also a few built-in restrictions that could limit what you’re able to do and affect both performance and overall functionality. So, while Synapse is powerful, it’s important to be aware of these potential roadblocks as you plan your projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Data Distribution and Skew&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Data skew remains a significant performance bottleneck in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/azure-synapse-analytics-new-insights-into-data-sec&#34;&gt;Synapse Analytics&lt;/a&gt;. Poor distribution key selection can lead to:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; Azure Synapse Analytics是处理大量数据的强大工具。它确实有一些缩放挑战，可以随着数据的增长而减慢事物。还有一些内置限制，可以限制您的能力并影响性能和整体功能。因此，尽管突触很强大，但在计划项目时要了解这些潜在的障碍很重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2数据选择 - 段落=“” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; data Distribution and Skew &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph =“” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;数据倾斜仍然是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/azure-synapse-synapse-analytics-new-inew-inew-inew-intoights-into--into-into-into-into-into-data-sec-sec--sec”&gt; Synapse&gt; Synapse Analytics &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。分布较差的关键选择可能会导致：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking AI Coding Assistants Part 4: Generate Spring Boot Application】解锁AI编码助手第4部分：生成Spring Boot应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-coding-assistants-generate-spring-boot-application</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this final installment of our &lt;em&gt;Unlocking AI Assistants&lt;/em&gt; series, we will create a Spring Boot application from scratch using an AI coding assistant. The goal is not to just merely create a working application, but to create production-grade code. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some tasks are executed with the help of an AI coding assistant. The responses are evaluated and different techniques are applied, which can be used to improve the responses when necessary.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我们的&lt;em&gt;解锁AI Assistants系列的最后一期中，我们将使用AI编码助手从头开始创建一个Spring Boot应用程序。目标不仅是创建一个工作应用程序，还要创建生产级代码。享受！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在AI编码助手的帮助下执行某些任务。评估响应并应用不同的技术，可在必要时用于改善响应。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Fragmentation to Focus: A Data-First, Team-First Framework for Platform-Driven Organizations】从分裂到重点：一个针对平台驱动组织的数据优先，团队优先的框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/data-first-team-framework-platform-optimization</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Success in today&#39;s complex, engineering-led enterprise organizations, where autonomy and scalability are paramount, hinges on more than adopting the latest tools or methodologies. The real challenge lies in aligning decentralized teams with shared goals while embedding governance without stifling innovation, creating a framework where teams can innovate freely, stay aligned, and ensure data is no longer treated as a second-class citizen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While CI/CD revolutionized software development, it overlooked the unique challenges of managing and governing data at scale. Data pipelines, quality, and compliance often remain fragmented, manual, or inconsistent, creating bottlenecks and risks. Enter &lt;strong&gt;Continuous Governance (CG)&lt;/strong&gt;: the evolution that puts data on equal footing with software, embedding compliance, quality, and automation directly into workflows without stifling creativity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今以工程为主导的企业组织中的成功，在该组织中，自主性和可扩展性至关重要，而不是采用最新工具或方法。真正的挑战在于使分散的团队与共同的目标保持一致，同时嵌入治理而不扼杀创新，创建一个框架，使团队可以自由创新，保持一致并确保数据不再被视为二等公民。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管CI/CD彻底改变了软件开发，但它忽略了管理和管理数据的独特挑战。数据管道，质量和合规性通常保持分散，手动或不一致，从而产生瓶颈和风险。输入&lt;strong&gt;连续治理（CG）&lt;/strong&gt;：将数据与软件平等地基础，嵌入合规性，质量和自动化直接嵌入工作流中的发展而不扼杀创造力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Rethinking Recruitment: A Journey Through Hiring Practices】重新思考招聘：招聘实践的旅程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/hiring-process-recruitment-candidate-first</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;It is hard to ignore that &lt;strong&gt;hiring processes are becoming increasingly lengthy and intricate&lt;/strong&gt;. What troubles me is the apparent lack of genuine innovation in this space. While candidates are required to invest more effort and energy into these processes, I find it difficult to see the proportional increase in value or impact for companies. In this article, I aim to share my thoughts, personal experiences, and some strategies that have worked for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Last year, I participated in several hiring processes that felt remarkably familiar. As I navigated through the steps, it became evident that the approach, structure, and overall experience closely mirrored what I encountered four years ago.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;很难忽略&lt;strong&gt;雇用过程变得越来越冗长且复杂&lt;/strong&gt;。困扰我的是这个领域中显然缺乏真正的创新。尽管要求候选人在这些过程中投入更多的精力和精力，但我发现很难看到对公司的价值或影响的比例增加。在本文中，我的目标是分享我的想法，个人经验和一些对我有用的策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt;去年，我参加了几个非常熟悉的招聘过程。当我通过这些步骤导航时，很明显的是，方法，结构和整体经验紧密反映了我四年前遇到的东西。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Rust and WebAssembly: Unlocking High-Performance Web Apps】Rust and WebAssembly：解锁高性能的Web应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rust-and-webassembly-for-web-apps</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Information technology continues to transform at an accelerated pace because modern businesses seek faster, high-performance applications. JavaScript-based development solutions from the past tend to fall behind when performing complex computations, which produce performance issues along with ineffective execution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fast, efficient web applications emerge through a synergistic relationship between Rust and Wasm technology. WebAssembly offers developers a novel technology to achieve native-level execution speed in web applications alongside standard web platform benefits.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;信息技术继续以加速的速度转变，因为现代企业寻求更快，高性能的应用程序。在执行复杂的计算时，基于JavaScript的开发解决方案往往会落后，这会产生性能问题以及无效的执行。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过Rust技术与WASM技术之间的协同关系，快速，高效的Web应用程序出现了。 WebAssembly为开发人员提供了一项新型技术，可与标准Web平台的收益以及标准的Web平台收益以及在Web应用程序中实现本地级别的执行速度。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Large Tech Companies Architect Resilient Systems for Millions of Users】大型科技公司的建筑师的弹性系统适用于数百万用户</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/resilient-systems-for-millions-tech-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When you are serving millions of users, resilience cannot be something you add later. It has to be part of the design from the very beginning. Otherwise, with the way user expectations keep climbing and how global traffic patterns shift, your system simply won’t keep up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What I want to walk you through today is how top companies think about resilience at scale. We will go through the strategies that work in the real world — not just theory — and look at how availability, cost, observability, scaling, and system design all come together.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当您为数百万用户提供服务时，弹性不可能是您稍后添加的东西。从一开始就必须成为设计的一部分。否则，随着用户期望继续攀升的方式以及全球流量模式的变化，您的系统根本不会跟上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我今天想让您经历的是顶级公司如何评价弹性。我们将仔细研究现实世界中起作用的策略，而不仅仅是理论，并研究可用性，成本，可观察性，扩展性和系统设计的方式。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Breaking Bottlenecks: Applying the Theory of Constraints to Software Development】破坏瓶颈：将约束理论应用于软件开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/apply-theory-constraints-software-development-bottlenecks</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tocinstitute.org/theory-of-constraints.html_of_constraints&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;The Theory of Constraints (TOC)&lt;/a&gt; is a problem-solving and continuous improvement methodology first introduced by Dr. Eliyahu M. Goldratt in his book &lt;em&gt;The Goal&lt;/em&gt;. Although TOC originally gained popularity in manufacturing and supply chain management, its application soon became far broader: at its core, TOC asserts that any system has at least one limiting factor—or “bottleneck”—that determines its overall efficiency. By identifying and eliminating this constraint, an organization can significantly boost productivity in virtually any process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my view, despite TOC’s roots in managing physical goods and delivery chains, its fundamental principles easily carry over into software development. Whether the “bottleneck” lies in code review, testing, or deployment, each stage of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-the-role-of-a-delivery-manager&#34;&gt;software development lifecycle&lt;/a&gt; can become a constraint for the entire process. From my experience, finding and removing these constraints often marks the difference between slow releases and a fast, efficient workflow.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.tocinstitute.org/theory-of-constraints.html_of_constraints” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt;约束理论（toc）&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;是一个问题的改进方法。目标&lt;/em&gt;。尽管TOC最初在制造和供应链管理方面广受欢迎，但其应用很快就变得更加广泛：托克（Toc）断言，任何系统至少具有一个限制因素或“瓶颈”）决定了其整体效率。通过识别和消除这一约束，组织几乎可以在任何过程中都显着提高生产率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我认为，尽管TOC源于管理物理商品和交付链的根源，但其基本原理很容易延续到软件开发中。 “瓶颈”是否在于代码审查，测试或部署，&lt;a a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-the-the-poding-the-poding-the-po-------o-------o--a-delivery-manager”&gt;软件开发生命周期生命周期&lt;/a&gt;可以成为整个过程的约束。根据我的经验，找到和删除这些约束通常标志着缓慢发行和快速，高效的工作流程之间的差异。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Assisted Coding for iOS Development: How Tools like CursorAI Are Redefining the Developer Workflow】AI辅助编码iOS开发：Cursorai之类的工具如何重新定义开发人员工作流程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-coding-ios-development-cursorai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The landscape of iOS engineering has seen a remarkable transformation since its inception, evolving from days of Interface Builder to AI enhanced development workflows. Programmers from all backgrounds are reporting an increase in productivity through AI assistance. We are seeing a fundamental shift in how iOS applications are conceptualized and built. However, this rise in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-ai-is-changing-the-way-developers-write-code&#34;&gt;AI assisted development&lt;/a&gt; brings both opportunities and challenges that every iOS developer needs to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Evolution of iOS Development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;iOS engineering has come a long way, just like the arch of software engineering in general. Back in the day, iOS engineers used Interface Builder and XIB files, which were like XML files for creating static views.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; iOS工程的景观自成立以来就发生了一个显着的转变，从界面构建器的天数到AI增强了开发工作流程。来自所有背景的程序员都报告通过AI帮助提高了生产率。我们看到iOS应用程序的概念化和构建方式的基本转变。但是，这在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-ai-is-is-changing-the-way-developers-write-code”&gt; ai辅助开发&lt;/a&gt;带来了每个iOS开发人员都需要理解的机会和挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt; iOS开发的演变&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; iOS工程已经走了很长一段路，就像一般软件工程的拱门一样。回到当天，iOS工程师使用了接口构建器和XIB文件，就像XML文件一样用于创建静态视图。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimize Deployment Pipelines for Speed, Security and Seamless Automation】优化速度，安全性和无缝自动化的部署管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deployment-pipeline-boost-speed-security-automation</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;A developer&#39;s work doesn&#39;t stop once the code is written. The real action begins when it’s deployment day. The process—managing multiple environments, testing new features, or ensuring seamless uptime during releases—must be fast, secure, and efficient.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Can you imagine a world where deployment is smooth, automated, and risk-free—where strategies scale, adapt, and are successful every single time?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;一旦编写代码，开发人员的工作就不会停止。真正的动作是在部署日开始的。该过程 - 管理多个环境，测试新功能或确保发行期间无缝的正常运行时间 - 必须快速，安全和高效。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;您能想象一个部署平稳，自动化和无风险的世界 - 策略规模，适应并每次都成功吗？ &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>