<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Why AI-Assisted Code Generation Is Transforming Software Development】为什么人工智能辅助代码生成正在改变软件开发</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-assisted-code-generation-transforming-software</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Software development and architecture is continuously evolving with artificial intelligence (AI). AI-assisted code generation stands out as a particularly revolutionary advancement, offering developers the ability to create high-quality code more efficiently and accurately than ever before. This innovation not only enhances productivity, but also opens the door to new possibilities in software creation, particularly in the realm of microservices development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;The Evolution of Code Generation: Traditional Coding vs. AI-Assisted Coding&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditional coding requires developers to write and test extensive lines of code manually. This process is time consuming and prone to errors. Conversely, AI-assisted code generation leverages machine learning algorithms to analyze patterns in existing codebases, understands programming logic, and generates code snippets or entire programs based on specific requirements. This technology can drastically reduce the time spent on repetitive coding tasks and minimize human errors. It is not a substitute for developers, but rather a productivity tool that eliminates tedious and monotonous infrastructure and plumbing code.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;软件开发和架构随着人工智能 (AI) 的发展而不断发展。人工智能辅助代码生成是一项特别革命性的进步，使开发人员能够比以往更高效、更准确地创建高质量代码。这项创新不仅提高了生产力，而且为软件创建的新可能性打开了大门，特别是在微服务开发领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;代码生成的演变：传统编码与人工智能辅助编码&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统编码需要开发人员手动编写和测试大量代码。这个过程非常耗时并且容易出错。相反，人工智能辅助代码生成利用机器学习算法来分析现有代码库中的模式，理解编程逻辑，并根据特定要求生成代码片段或整个程序。该技术可以大大减少重复编码任务所花费的时间，并最大限度地减少人为错误。它不是开发人员的替代品，而是一种生产力工具，可以消除繁琐单调的基础设施和管道代码。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Default Map Value】默认地图值</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/default-map-value</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this post, I&#39;ll explain how to provide a default value when querying an absent key in a hash map in different programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Java&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s start with Java, my first professional programming language.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我将解释如何在使用不同编程语言查询哈希映射中不存在的键时提供默认值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Java&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们从 Java 开始，这是我的第一个专业编程语言。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What Is SQL Injection and How Can It Be Avoided?】什么是 SQL 注入以及如何避免？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-sql-injection-and-how-can-it-be-avoided-1</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;SQLi is one of the code injection techniques that may enable an attacker to modify the queries that the application provides to the database.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;By far the most frequent and severe web application security threats always hide in web applications that have some connections with a database.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;From such&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-the-sql-injection-vulnerability-amp-how-to&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;SQL injections&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;, attackers can get around the login procedure, get, change, or even update the database, perform the administrative procedure, or do whichever variants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding SQL Injection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;To be able to explain what&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;SQL Injection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;is, one has to understand some basic principles of SQL.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;Indeed, it has become the common language of dealing with and virtual manipulation of these databases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;It is employed in querying, inserting, updating, and erasing database records and is used by nearly all web applications to access their database; it is authored in&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.php.net/manual/en/intro-whatis.php&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;PHP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.python.org/doc/essays/blurb/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.java.com/en/download/help/whatis_java.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.privateinternetaccess.com/vpn-server/usa-vpn/utah-vpn&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;PIA Utah VPN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt; and .&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dotnet.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/dotnet/what-is-dotnet&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;NET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;closed&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;SQLi 是一种代码注入技术，攻击者可以利用该技术修改应用程序向数据库提供的查询。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;到目前为止，最常见、最严重的 Web 应用程序安全威胁始终隐藏在与数据库有一定连接的 Web 应用程序中。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;来自这样的&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-the-sql-injection- vulnerability-amp-how-to&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;SQL 注入&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;,攻击者可以绕过登录过程，获取、更改甚至更新数据库，执行管理过程，或执行任何变体。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;了解 SQL 注入&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;能够解释什么是&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;SQL 注入&lt;/span&gt;&lt; span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt; 是，必须了解 SQL 的一些基本原理。 事实上，它已经成为处理和虚拟操作这些数据库的通用语言。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;它用于查询、插入、更新和删除数据库记录，几乎所有 Web 应用程序都使用它来访问其数据库；它是在 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.php.net/manual/en/intro-whatis.php&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state 中编写的=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;PHP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;，&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www. python.org/doc/essays/blurb/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span 数据-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.java.com/en/download/help/whatis_java.html&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target= &#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt;，&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.privateinternetaccess.com/vpn-server/usa-vpn/utah-vpn&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button &#34;&gt;PIA 犹他州 VPN&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=&#34;close&#34; type=&#34;button&#34;&gt; 和 . &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dotnet.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/dotnet/what-is-dotnet&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span 数据状态=“关闭”类型=“按钮”&gt;NET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-state=“关闭”类型=“按钮”&gt;。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【React Server Components (RSC): The Future of React】React 服务器组件 (RSC)：React 的未来</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/react-server-components-rsc-the-future-of-react</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;React Server Components (RSC) represent a paradigm shift in how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/reactjs-essentials&#34;&gt;React&lt;/a&gt;&#39;s applications are rendered in its 10th anniversary. RSCs were first introduced in late 2020, and the first stable version of this feature was launched in 2024 as part of React 19. Traditionally, React applications were run on the client. This meant the browser would download the JavaScript bundle containing all the code that&#39;s needed to run the application, and then render the application. Though this had some advantages, this approach caused slow initial loads and the need to fetch and process the data on the client made things even slower. With React Server Components, React can now run on the server without necessarily being sent to the client, fundamentally changing how React works at its core and how we use it to build applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Server Side Rendering (SSR)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order to understand React Server Components (RSC), we need to first understand how &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-server-side-rendering-and-why-do-you-need&#34;&gt;Server Side Rendering&lt;/a&gt; (SSR) works. If you are already familiar with SSR feel free to skip this section. SSR is a web development technique that renders a web page on the server rather than in the browser.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;React 服务器组件 (RSC) 代表了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/reactjs-essentials&#34;&gt;React&lt;/a&gt; 应用程序在其诞生 10 周年之际呈现方式的范式转变。 RSC 于 2020 年底首次引入，该功能的第一个稳定版本于 2024 年作为 React 19 的一部分推出。传统上，React 应用程序在客户端上运行。这意味着浏览器将下载包含运行应用程序所需的所有代码的 JavaScript 包，然后呈现应用程序。尽管这有一些优点，但这种方法会导致初始加载缓慢，并且需要在客户端上获取和处理数据使速度变得更慢。借助 React Server Components，React 现在可以在服务器上运行，而无需发送到客户端，从根本上改变了 React 的核心工作方式以及我们使用它构建应用程序的方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;服务器端渲染 (SSR)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了理解 React Server Components (RSC)，我们需要首先了解 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-server-side-rendering-and-why-do -you-need&#34;&gt;服务器端渲染&lt;/a&gt; (SSR) 有效。如果您已经熟悉 SSR，请随意跳过本节。 SSR 是一种 Web 开发技术，可在服务器而不是浏览器中呈现网页。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Hands-On Guide to OpenTelemetry: Visualizing Instrumentation for Developers Using Jaeger】OpenTelemetry 实践指南：使用 Jaeger 为开发人员提供可视化仪器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/otel-guide-visualizing-instrumentation-in-jaeger</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to start your journey on the road to collecting telemetry data from your applications? Great observability begins with great instrumentation!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this series, you&#39;ll explore how to adopt &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; and how to instrument an application to collect tracing telemetry. You&#39;ll learn how to leverage out-of-the-box automatic instrumentation tools and understand when it&#39;s necessary to explore more advanced manual instrumentation for your applications. By the end of this series, you&#39;ll have an understanding of how telemetry travels from your applications to the OpenTelemetry Collector, and be ready to bring OpenTelemetry to your future projects. Everything discussed here is supported by &lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;a hands-on, self-paced workshop&lt;/a&gt; authored &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;by Paige Cruz&lt;/a&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您准备好开始从应用程序收集遥测数据的旅程了吗？出色的可观测性始于出色的仪器！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本系列中，您将探索如何采用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel)&lt;/a&gt; 以及如何检测一个应用程序来收集跟踪遥测数据。您将学习如何利用开箱即用的自动仪表工具，并了解何时需要为您的应用探索更高级的手动仪表。在本系列结束时，您将了解遥测如何从应用程序传输到 OpenTelemetry Collector，并准备好将 OpenTelemetry 引入您未来的项目。这里讨论的所有内容均由&lt;a href=&#34;https://o11y-workshops.gitlab.io/workshop-opentelemetry/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;动手、自定进度的研讨会&lt;/ a&gt; 作者：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/paigerduty/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;由 Paige Cruz&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Aren’t We Transformed Yet? Why Digital Transformation Needs More Work】我们还没有转变吗？为什么数字化转型需要更多工作</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/arent-we-transformed-yet</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-digital-age-the-era-we-all-are-living-in-and-d&#34;&gt;Digital transformation&lt;/a&gt; remains a clear focus for many organizations, with proactive leaders seeing opportunities worth navigating the complexities of technology and process disruption.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;According to Kristy Ellmer, a managing director for Boston Consulting Group, “&lt;a href=&#34;https://chiefexecutive.net/nailing-the-pivot/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;thirty percent of any given sector is in transformation at any given time&lt;/a&gt;. Companies that go into a transformation mindset when they’re in a place of strength will be more successful than if they do it reactively. And then how you execute it and move the organization behind it is what actually creates competitive advantage.”&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/the-digital-age-the-era-we-all-are-living-in-and-d&#34;&gt;数字化转型&lt;/a&gt; 仍然是许多组织的明确关注重点，积极主动的领导者看到了值得应对技术和流程中断复杂性的机会。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;波士顿咨询集团董事总经理 Kristy Ellmer 表示，“&lt;a href=&#34;https://chiefexecutive.net/nailing-the-pivot/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target= &#34;_blank&#34;&gt;任何特定行业的 30% 在任何特定时间都处于转型之中&lt;/a&gt;。在处于优势地位时进入转型思维的公司会比被动地采取转型思维更成功。然后，如何执行它并推动其背后的组织才能真正创造竞争优势。”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Revolutionizing Billing Processes With AI: Enhancing Efficiency and Accuracy】利用人工智能彻底改变计费流程：提高效率和准确性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/revolutionizing-billing-processes-with-ai</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The market for software as a service (SaaS) has expanded at an extraordinary pace and given businesses access to scalable solutions. However, one major difficulty still stands in its way: generating and collecting revenue efficiently and accurately. Traditional billing systems often prove inadequate leading to inefficiencies and inaccuracies. This blog post examines the integration of AI into SaaS pricing methods, with a focus on improving efficiency and effectiveness by highlighting data analysts, data scientists, data product managers, and data-driven software professionals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Role of AI in Modern Billing Systems&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) is changing the face of Saas business by addressing many challenges related to traditional billing systems. Fundamental technologies like machine learning (ML), predictive analytics, or automation simplify billing processes and make them more accurate.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;软件即服务 (SaaS) 市场以惊人的速度扩张，并为企业提供了可扩展的解决方案。然而，仍然存在一个主要困难：高效、准确地产生和收取收入。传统的计费系统往往存在不足，导致效率低下和不准确。这篇博文探讨了人工智能与 SaaS 定价方法的集成，重点是通过强调数据分析师、数据科学家、数据产品经理和数据驱动软件专业人员来提高效率和有效性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能在现代计费系统中的作用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;人工智能 (AI) 通过解决与传统计费系统相关的许多挑战，正在改变 SaaS 业务的面貌。机器学习 (ML)、预测分析或自动化等基础技术简化了计费流程并使其更加准确。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unboxing the Black Box】拆箱黑匣子</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unboxing-the-black-box</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today, several significant and safety-critical decisions are being made by deep &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/neural-network-essentials&#34;&gt;neural networks&lt;/a&gt;. These include driving decisions in autonomous vehicles, diagnosing diseases, and operating robots in manufacturing and construction. In all such cases, scientists and engineers claim that these models help make better decisions than humans and hence, help save lives. However, how these networks reach their decisions is often a mystery, for not just their users, but also for their developers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;These changing times, thus, necessitate that as engineers we spend more time &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-making-the-black-box-transparent&#34;&gt;unboxing these black boxes&lt;/a&gt; so that we can identify the biases and weaknesses of the models that we build. This may also allow us to identify which part of the input is most critical for the model and hence, ensure its correctness. Finally, explaining how models make their decisions will not only build trust between AI products and their consumers but also help meet the diverse and evolving regulatory requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;今天，深度&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/neural-network-essentials&#34;&gt;神经网络&lt;/a&gt;正在做出一些重大且安全关键的决策。其中包括自动驾驶汽车的驾驶决策、诊断疾病以及在制造和建筑业中操作机器人。在所有这些情况下，科学家和工程师声称这些模型有助于做出比人类更好的决策，从而有助于拯救生命。然而，这些网络如何做出决策往往是一个谜，不仅对于它们的用户来说，而且对于它们的开发人员来说也是如此。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;因此，时代的变化要求我们作为工程师花更多的时间&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-making-the-black-box-transparent ”拆箱这些黑匣子&lt;/a&gt;，以便我们能够识别我们构建的模型的偏见和弱点。这也可以让我们识别输入的哪一部分对模型最关键，从而确保其正确性。最后，解释模型如何做出决策不仅可以在人工智能产品与其消费者之间建立信任，还有助于满足多样化且不断变化的监管要求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tour of Snowflake Ingestion Using CockroachDB and Redpanda Connect】使用 CockroachDB 和 Redpanda Connect 进行雪花摄取之旅</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/snowflake-ingestion-using-cockroachdb-and-redpanda</link>
      <description>【&lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Previous Articles on Snowflake&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-snowflake-with-trino&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;Integrating Snowflake with Trino&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Previous Articles on CockroachDB CDC&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-apache-pulsar&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;Using CockroachDB CDC with Apache Pulsar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-azure-event-hubs&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;Using CockroachDB CDC with Azure Event Hubs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/saas-galore-integrating-cockroachdb-with-confluent&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;SaaS Galore: Integrating CockroachDB with Confluent Kafka, FiveTran, and Snowflake&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-confluent-cloud-kafka-a&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;Using CockroachDB CDC with Confluent Cloud Kafka and Schema Registry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cockroachdb-cdc-using-minio-as-cloud-storage-sink&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;CockroachDB CDC using Minio as cloud storage sink&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cockroachdb-cdc-with-hadoop-ozone-s3-gateway-and-d&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;CockroachDB CDC using Hadoop Ozone S3 Gateway as cloud storage sink&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;div dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;I work with financial services clients, and it&#39;s common to encounter a need for streaming changes in the operational data store into a data warehouse or a data lake. A former colleague recently reached out for advice on the fastest and most efficient way to load trade data into Snowflake. I&#39;ve come up with at least three methods, which I will explore in a follow-up series of articles. However, I&#39;ve decided to first explore &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redpanda.com/connect&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Redpanda Connect&lt;/a&gt;, a solution that has recently caught my attention. This is by no means a conclusive guide on how changefeed data must be loaded into Snowflake; we&#39;re merely exploring the possibilities and discussing the pros and cons in later articles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;CockroachDB changefeeds are an enterprise feature and require a license. In this tutorial, I&#39;m using a free-to-start version of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cockroachlabs.com/lp/serverless/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CockroachDB Serverless&lt;/a&gt;, which has enterprise changefeeds enabled.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;div 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;之前关于雪花的文章&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/integrating-snowflake-with-trino&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;将 Snowflake 与 Trino 集成&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;之前关于 CockroachDB CDC 的文章&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-apache-pulsar&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;将 CockroachDB CDC 与 Apache Pulsar 结合使用&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-azure-event-hubs&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;将 CockroachDB CDC 与 Azure 事件中心结合使用&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /里&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/saas-galore-integrating-cockroachdb-with-confluence&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;SaaS Galore：将 CockroachDB 与 Confluence Kafka、FiveTran 和 Snowflake 集成&lt; /a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/using-cockroachdb-cdc-with-confluence-cloud-kafka-a&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;将 CockroachDB CDC 与 Confluence Cloud Kafka 和架构注册表结合使用&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cockroachdb-cdc-using-minio-as-cloud-storage-sink&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;CockroachDB CDC 使用 Minio 作为云存储接收器&lt;/一个&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cockroachdb-cdc-with-hadoop-ozone-s3-gateway-and-d&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow&#34;&gt;CockroachDB CDC 使用 Hadoop Ozone S3 网关作为云存储接收器&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;div 目录=“自动”&gt;&#xA; &lt;h2 dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;动机&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;我与金融服务客户合作，经常需要将操作数据存储中的更改流式传输到数据仓库或数据湖中。一位前同事最近寻求有关将贸易数据加载到 Snowflake 的最快、最有效方法的建议。我已经提出了至少三种方法，我将在后续系列文章中对其进行探讨。不过，我决定首先探索 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redpanda.com/connect&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Redpanda Connect&lt;/a&gt;，这是一个最近推出的解决方案引起了我的注意。这绝不是关于如何将变更源数据加载到 Snowflake 中的决定性指南；我们只是探索可能性并在后面的文章中讨论其优缺点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;CockroachDB 变更源是一项企业功能，需要许可证。在本教程中，我使用免费启动版本的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cockroachlabs.com/lp/serverless/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CockroachDB Serverless &lt;/a&gt;，它启用了企业变更源。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Relationship Between Performance and Security】性能与安全性之间的关系</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-relationship-between-performance-and-security</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The software landscape has undergone a profound transformation over the past two decades. In the past, a substantial portion of software was designed for local desktop use. However, today, the norm for computer users is to access web-based software services through a web browser.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With the prevalence of web-based software, the paradigm has changed. We, as users, have our data residing on someone else’s server. It mostly doesn’t matter how robust your computing device is, as everything happens on servers.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;过去二十年来，软件格局发生了深刻的转变。过去，很大一部分软件是为本地桌面使用而设计的。然而，如今，计算机用户的常态是通过网络浏览器访问基于网络的软件服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着基于网络的软件的流行，范式已经改变。作为用户，我们的数据驻留在别人的服务器上。您的计算设备有多强大并不重要，因为一切都发生在服务器上。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>