<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Dynamic Forms With Camunda and Spring StateMachine】Camunda和Spring Statemachine的动态形式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/dynamic-forms-camunda-spring-statemachine</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In modern process automation, flexibility and adaptability are key. Processes often require dynamic forms that can change based on user input, business rules, or external factors. Traditional approaches, where forms are hardcoded into the process definition, can be rigid and difficult to maintain.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article presents a flexible and scalable approach to handling dynamic forms in process automation, using Camunda BPM and Spring StateMachine as the underlying engines. We’ll explore how to decouple form definitions from process logic, enabling dynamic form rendering, validation, and submission. This approach is applicable to both Camunda and Spring StateMachine, making it a versatile solution for various process automation needs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在现代过程自动化中，灵活性和适应性是关键。流程通常需要动态表格，这些表格可以根据用户输入，业务规则或外部因素进行更改。将形式进行了硬编码为过程定义的传统方法可能是僵化且难以维护的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文使用Camunda BPM和Spring Statemachine作为基础发动机提出了一种在过程自动化中处理动态形式的灵活和可扩展方法。我们将探讨如何将表单定义与过程逻辑，启用动态形式渲染，验证和提交相结合。这种方法适用于Camunda和Spring Statemachine，使其成为各种过程自动化需求的多功能解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Deploying and Validating Kata Containers】部署和验证KATA容器</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deploying-validating-kata-containers</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In Part 1, we explored how Kata Containers bring together the agility of Kubernetes pods and the robust security of virtual machines, offering a powerful solution for cloud-native workloads.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this part, we’ll provide a hands-on guide to deploying and validating Kata Containers in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/accelerate-development-and-deployment-with-ibm-clo&#34;&gt;IBM Cloud&lt;/a&gt;, a platform well-suited for secure, scalable, and enterprise-grade cloud solutions. From configuring the runtime to testing its performance and security, we’ll walk you through the entire process. By the end of this guide, you’ll have the practical knowledge to integrate Kata Containers into your IBM Cloud environment and enhance the security of your containerized applications.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在第1部分中，我们探索了Kata容器如何将Kubernetes Pods的敏捷性和虚拟机的稳健安全性汇总在一起，从而为云本地工作负载提供了强大的解决方案。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这一部分中，我们将提供一个动手指南，以在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/accelerate-development-and-deployment-with-ibm-clo”中部署和验证Kata容器，以提供安全的，可提供安全的，可扩展的，Enterprese-groade clouds clouds cloud。从配置运行时到测试其性能和安全性，我们将为您完成整个过程。在本指南的最后，您将拥有实践知识将KATA容器集成到IBM云环境中并增强您的容器应用程序的安全性。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go Flags: Beyond the Basics】去国旗：超越基本知识</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/go-flags-beyond-the-basics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;flag&lt;/code&gt; package is one of Go&#39;s most powerful standard library tools for building command-line applications. Understanding flags is essential whether you&#39;re creating a simple CLI tool or a complex application. Let&#39;s look into what makes this package so versatile.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Basic Flag Concepts&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s start with a simple example that demonstrates the core concepts:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;code&gt; flag &lt;/code&gt;软件包是GO最强大的标准库工具之一，用于构建命令行应用程序。无论您是创建简单的CLI工具还是复杂的应用程序，了解标志都是必不可少的。让我们看看是什么使此软件包如此通用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;基本标志概念&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们从一个简单的示例开始，该示例演示了核心概念：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Explainable AI Is Building Trust in Everyday Products】AI如何对日常产品建立信任</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/explainable-ai-building-trust-everyday-products</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI is the potential ally of the common people because it becomes an integral part of our daily lives. From personalized shopping suggestions to curated music playlists, along with other AI systems, they continuously accentuate our adventures.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Nevertheless, as these are developed into increasingly intelligent machines, they create the following riddles: What motivated the product to be offered to me? How is that application capable of reasoning my preferences with such accuracy? These are the kinds of questions that are there to respond to the requirement for the definition of AI (XAI) to be transparent and accountable.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; ai是普通百姓的潜在盟友，因为它成为我们日常生活中不可或缺的一部分。从个性化的购物建议到精心策划的音乐播放列表以及其他AI系统，它们不断强调我们的冒险经历。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;尽管如此，由于这些机器越来越智能机器，它们创造了以下谜语：是什么促使产品提供给我的？该应用如何以如此准确的方式推理我的偏好？这些是响应AI（XAI）透明且负责的定义的要求的问题。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DevOps: The Key to Reliable AI Data and Governance】DevOps：可靠的AI数据和治理的关键</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/devops-key-to-reliable-ai-data-governance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI and machine learning (AI/ML) are changing industries, opening up new revenue streams, and enhancing the capabilities of developers and the solutions they create, regardless of whether they have yet to impact your processes or products directly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;However, enormous responsibility accompanies immense power, innovation, and opportunity. All AI models rely on data, and your teams and technology are in charge of that data&#39;s quality, source, and compliance. No matter how strong and convincing the data provider&#39;s guarantees and protections are, you cannot rely on them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; AI和机器学习（AI/ML）正在改变行业，开放新的收入来源，并增强开发人员的能力以及他们创建的解决方案，无论他们是否尚未直接影响您的流程或产品。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;但是，巨大的权力，创新和机会伴随着巨大的责任。所有AI模型都依靠数据，您的团队和技术负责该数据的质量，来源和合规性。无论数据提供商的保证和保护有多强大和说服力，您都不能依靠它们。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhanced Query Caching Mechanism in Hibernate 6.3.0】Hibernate 6.3.0中增强的查询缓存机制</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/enhanced-query-caching-mechanism-in-hibernate</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Efficient &lt;strong&gt;query caching&lt;/strong&gt; is a critical part of application performance in data-intensive systems. Hibernate has supported query caching through its second-level cache and query cache mechanisms. However, earlier implementations lacked flexibility, and developers had limited control over cache invalidation and customization. Hibernate 6.3.0, released in December 2024, addresses these problems by introducing enhanced query caching mechanisms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article talks about the traditional query caching approach in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-hibernate&#34;&gt;Hibernate&lt;/a&gt; and its limitations, along with how the new enhancements in Hibernate 6.3.0 improve the process.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;有效的&lt;strong&gt;查询缓存&lt;/strong&gt;是数据密集型系统应用程序性能的关键部分。 Hibernate通过其二级缓存和查询缓存机制支持查询缓存。但是，较早的实现缺乏灵活性，开发人员对缓存无效和自定义的控制有限。 Hibernate 6.3.0于2024年12月发布，通过引入增强的查询缓存机制来解决这些问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文讨论了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-hibernate”&gt; Hibernate &lt;/a&gt;的传统查询缓存方法&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;及其限制，以及如何改善Hibernate 6.3.0的新增强。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Non-Project Backlog Management for Software Engineering Teams】软件工程团队的非项目积压管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/non-project-backlog-management-software-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Objective&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;A common challenge for engineering leadership is the management of non-project backlogs, which consist of unresolved issues from previous projects, such as technical debt, outstanding bugs, and incomplete documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34; style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This article examines the inherent difficulties and proposes implementation guidelines for mitigating the negative impact of these backlogs on current development efforts, ultimately aiming to enhance productivity and project success.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; objective &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;工程领导者的一个普遍挑战是管理非项目的积压，其中包括以前项目的未解决的问题，例如技术债务，未完成的错误和不完整的文档。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr” style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;本文研究了固有的困难，并提出了实施指南，以减轻这些积压的负面影响对当前发展工作的负面影响，最终旨在提高生产力和项目成功。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Podcast Promotion With AI and Event-Driven Design】使用AI和事件驱动的设计自动播客促销</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-podcast-promotion-ai-event-driven-design</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;I host two podcasts, &lt;em&gt;Software Engineering Daily&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Software Huddle&lt;/em&gt;, and often appear as a guest on other shows. Promoting episodes — whether I’m hosting or featured — helps highlight the great conversations I have, but finding the time to craft a thoughtful LinkedIn post for each one is tough. Between hosting, work, and life, sitting down to craft a thoughtful LinkedIn post for every episode just doesn’t always happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;To make life easier (and still do justice to the episodes), I built an AI-powered LinkedIn post generator. It downloads podcast episodes, converts the audio into text, and uses that to create posts. It saves me time, keeps my content consistent, and ensures each episode gets the spotlight it deserves.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;我主持了两个播客，&lt;em&gt;软件工程每日&lt;/em&gt;和&lt;em&gt;软件huddle &lt;/em&gt;，经常出现在其他节目中。宣传情节（无论我是主持人还是特色）有助于突出我的出色对话，但要找时间为每个帖子制作一个周到的LinkedIn帖子，这是艰难的。在主持，工作和生活之间，坐下来制作每个情节的周到的LinkedIn帖子并不总是发生。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;为了使生活更轻松（并且仍然对情节伸张正义），我建立了一个AI驱动的LinkedIn Post Generator。它下载播客剧集，将音频转换为文本，并使用它来创建帖子。它节省了我的时间，使我的内容保持一致，并确保每集都有应有的焦点。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Build Slack App for Audit Requests】如何为审核请求构建Slack应用程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-build-slack-app-for-audits</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Auditing for any B2B software is crucial for understanding how teams utilize products, measuring efficiency created due to the product usage, security, and data compliance. Organizations may require different types of audits to ensure proper usage, identify potential risks, and support technical engagements.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;This article will walk you through how to use a technical architecture designed for audits to create a Slack audit application that can facilitate various audit types in a flexible, efficient manner.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;对任何B2B软件的审核对于了解团队如何利用产品，衡量由于产品使用，安全性和数据合规性而创建的效率至关重要。组织可能需要不同类型的审核，以确保适当使用，确定潜在的风险并支持技术参与。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;本文将引导您了解如何使用设计用于审核的技术体系结构来创建一个Slack Audit应用程序，该应用程序可以以灵活，高效的方式促进各种审核类型。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Performance Optimization Techniques for Snowflake on AWS】AWS上雪花的性能优化技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/optimize-snowflake-performance-on-aws</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;As organizations scale their data operations in the cloud, optimizing Snowflake performance on AWS becomes crucial for maintaining efficiency and controlling costs. This comprehensive guide explores advanced techniques and best practices for maximizing Snowflake performance, backed by practical examples and implementation strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;Understanding Snowflake&#39;s Architecture on AWS&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-beginners-guide-to-snowflake-architecture&#34;&gt;Snowflake&#39;s&lt;/a&gt; multi-cluster, shared-data architecture on AWS consists of three distinct layers:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;随着组织在云中扩展其数据操作，优化AWS上的雪花性能对于维持效率和控制成本至关重要。本综合指南探讨了以实践和实施策略的支持，探索了最大化雪花表现的高级技术和最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style =“ text-align：left;”&gt;了解雪花在AWS上的体系结构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/a-beginners-guide-to-snowflake-architection”&gt; snowflake&#39;s &lt;/af &lt;/a&gt;多cluster &lt;/a&gt; AWS上的多cluster，共享的data体系结构包括三个不同的层次：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>