<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Unit Integration Testing With Testcontainers Docker Compose】使用 Testcontainers Docker Compose 进行单元集成测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/unit-integration-testing-with-testcontainers-docker-compose</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Is your test dependent on multiple other applications and do you want to create an integration test using Testcontainers? Then the Testcontainers Docker Compose Module is the solution. In this blog, you will learn how convenient it is to create an integration test using multiple Testcontainers. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Using &lt;a href=&#34;https://testcontainers.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Testcontainers&lt;/a&gt; is a very convenient way to write a unit integration test. Most of the time, you will use it in order to test the integration with a database, a message bus, etc. But what if your application interacts with an application that consists of multiple containers? How can you add these containers to your unit integration test? The answer is quite simple: you should use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://java.testcontainers.org/modules/docker_compose/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker Compose Module&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您的测试是否依赖于多个其他应用程序，并且您想使用测试容器创建集成测试吗？那么 Testcontainers Docker Compose 模块就是解决方案。在本博客中，您将了解使用多个测试容器创建集成测试是多么方便。享受吧！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://testcontainers.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Testcontainers&lt;/a&gt; 是编写单元集成测试的一种非常方便的方法。大多数时候，您将使用它来测试与数据库、消息总线等的集成。但是，如果您的应用程序与由多个容器组成的应用程序交互怎么办？如何将这些容器添加到单元集成测试中？答案非常简单：您应该使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://java.testcontainers.org/modules/docker_compose/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker Compose 模块&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How JavaScript DataTable Libraries Address Challenging Requirements in Web Data Management】JavaScript DataTable 库如何解决 Web 数据管理中的挑战性要求</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-javascript-datatable-libraries-address-challen</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Web data management is becoming increasingly important as applications move towards being more complex and data-intensive. The necessity to manage large and complex datasets causes numerous challenges that demand effective solutions from development teams. Fortunately, web developers can rely on ready-made tools such as a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/object-oriented-javascript&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt; data table library (or simply a grid) that make it easier to deal with such issues effectively.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 698px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;288.7 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/jpeg&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1726495448616&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/16/2024 02:04 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17922635-glasses-4966989-1280.jpg&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;288691&#34; data-name=&#34;glasses-4966989-1280.jpg&#34; data-id=&#34;17922635&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17922635-glasses-4966989-1280.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Photo of spreadsheets, pen, notebook, and glasses&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In this article, we’ll consider the most challenging &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-management-in-complex-systems&#34;&gt;data management&lt;/a&gt; requirements encountered in web apps and highlight how popular JavaScript grid components help address these pain points.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着应用程序变得更加复杂和数据密集，Web 数据管理变得越来越重要。管理大型且复杂的数据集的必要性带来了许多挑战，需要开发团队提供有效的解决方案。幸运的是，Web 开发人员可以依赖现成的工具，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/object-oriented-javascript&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt; 数据表库（或简单的网格）这使得更容易有效地处理此类问题。&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 698px;&#34; class =“fr-fic fr-dib lazyload”data-image =“true”data-new =“false”data-sizeformatted =“288.7 kB”data-mimetype =“image/jpeg”data-creationdate =“1726495448616”数据-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/16/2024 02:04 PM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17922635-glasses-4966989-1280.jpg&#34; data-modificationdate =“null”data-size =“288691”data-name =“glasses-4966989-1280.jpg”data-id =“17922635”data-src =“https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage” /temp/17922635-glasses-4966989-1280.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;电子表格、笔、笔记本和眼镜的照片&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将考虑最具挑战性的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/data-management-in-complex-systems&#34;&gt;数据管理&lt;/a &gt; Web 应用程序中遇到的要求，并强调流行的 JavaScript 网格组件如何帮助解决这些痛点。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java 23: What Developers Need to Know】Java 23：开发人员需要了解什么</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/java-23-what-developers-need-to-know</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;As &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; implements its 23rd major release on September 17, 2024, developers are in for a treat with many new features and improvements. Oracle&#39;s latest release promises to make development more efficient and enjoyable while enhancing the platform&#39;s performance, stability, and security. Let&#39;s dive into the key aspects developers should be excited about in Java 23.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;The Six-Month Release Cadence Continues&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Oracle is sticking to its six-month release cycle for Java, now in its seventh year. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/alikemaltasci-the-evolution-of-java-time-based-release&#34;&gt;This approach&lt;/a&gt; has successfully delivered regular updates and innovations to the Java ecosystem. A Long-Term Support (LTS) version is released every two years, providing stability for enterprises that prefer less frequent updates. Java 23 marks the 14th release in this six-month cadence.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 于 2024 年 9 月 17 日实现第 23 个主要版本，开发人员将迎来一个处理许多新功能和改进。 Oracle 的最新版本承诺使开发更加高效和愉快，同时增强平台的性能、稳定性和安全性。让我们深入探讨 Java 23 中开发人员应该感到兴奋的关键方面。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;六个月的发布节奏仍在继续&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Oracle 坚持 Java 的六个月发布周期，现在已经是第七个年头了。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/alikemaltasci-the-evolution-of-java-time-based-release&#34;&gt;这种方法&lt;/a&gt;成功地为 Java 生态系统提供了定期更新和创新。长期支持 (LTS) 版本每两年发布一次，为不喜欢频繁更新的企业提供稳定性。 Java 23 是这六个月周期中的第 14 个版本。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 14:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transforming Manufacturing: AI-Driven Quality Control and Predictive Maintenance Using Cloud and IoT】制造业转型：利用云和物联网进行人工智能驱动的质量控制和预测性维护</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-manufacturing-ai-driven-quality-control</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;In modern manufacturing, the key to sustaining product reliability, compliance with regulatory standards, and maintaining operational efficiency lies in robust quality control and advanced maintenance management. This study delves into the integration of AI technologies to interpret sensor data from production equipment. By employing predictive modeling techniques such as Stacked LSTM networks, RNNs, Random Forests, Gradient Boosting, SVM, ARIMA, and SARIMA, the goal is to forecast potential equipment failures, implement proactive maintenance solutions, and uphold rigorous quality checks through automated systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;This research showcases how AI-driven insights can be displayed through interactive dashboards and comprehensive reports, aiding in meeting regulatory standards while substantially improving operational dependability in manufacturing. Beyond the immediate benefits of reduced downtime and increased productivity, anomaly detection, especially in rotating machinery, plays a pivotal role in AI-driven predictive maintenance (PdM). The findings highlight how predictive modeling transforms equipment management, fostering innovation and supporting sustainability across various industries by utilizing sensors, cameras, and laser beam sensing technology.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;在现代制造业中，维持产品可靠性、符合监管标准和保持运营效率的关键在于强大的质量控制和先进的维护管理。这项研究深入探讨了人工智能技术的集成，以解释来自生产设备的传感器数据。通过采用堆叠 LSTM 网络、RNN、随机森林、梯度提升、SVM、ARIMA 和 SARIMA 等预测建模技术，目标是预测潜在的设备故障，实施主动维护解决方案，并通过自动化系统进行严格的质量检查。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;这项研究展示了如何通过交互式仪表板和综合报告显示人工智能驱动的见解，帮助满足监管标准，同时大幅提高制造中的运营可靠性。除了减少停机时间和提高生产率等直接好处之外，异常检测（尤其是旋转机械中的异常检测）在人工智能驱动的预测性维护 (PdM) 中发挥着关键作用。研究结果强调了预测建模如何利用传感器、摄像头和激光束传感技术来改变设备管理、促进创新并支持各个行业的可持续发展。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Key Considerations for Effective AI/ML Deployments in Kubernetes】在 Kubernetes 中有效部署 AI/ML 的关键考虑因素</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/effective-AL-ML-deployments-Kubernetes</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-kubernetes-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes in the Enterprise: Once Decade-Defining, Now Forging a Future in the SDLC&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes has become a cornerstone in modern infrastructure, particularly for deploying, scaling, and managing artificial intelligence and machine learning (AI/ML) workloads. As organizations increasingly rely on machine learning models for critical tasks like data processing, model training, and inference, Kubernetes offers the flexibility and scalability needed to manage these complex workloads efficiently. By leveraging Kubernetes&#39; robust ecosystem, AI/ML workloads can be dynamically orchestrated, ensuring optimal resource utilization and high availability across cloud environments. This synergy between Kubernetes and AI/ML empowers organizations to deploy and scale their ML workloads with greater agility and reliability.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-kubernetes-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;企业中的 Kubernetes：曾经定义十年，现在在 SDLC 中打造未来&lt;/em&gt;&lt; /a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes 已成为现代基础设施的基石，特别是在部署、扩展和管理人工智能和机器学习 (AI/ML) 工作负载方面。随着组织越来越依赖机器学习模型来完成数据处理、模型训练和推理等关键任务，Kubernetes 提供了有效管理这些复杂工作负载所需的灵活性和可扩展性。通过利用 Kubernetes 强大的生态系统，可以动态编排 AI/ML 工作负载，确保跨云环境的最佳资源利用率和高可用性。 Kubernetes 和 AI/ML 之间的这种协同作用使组织能够以更高的敏捷性和可靠性部署和扩展其 ML 工作负载。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 19:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS LetsEncrypt Lambda or Why I Wrote a Custom TLS Provider for AWS Using OpenTofu and Go】AWS LetsEncrypt Lambda 或为什么我使用 OpenTofu 和 Go 为 AWS 编写自定义 TLS 提供程序</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-letsencrypt-lambda-why-i-wrote-a-custom-tls-provider-for-aws</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;These days, it&#39;s challenging to imagine systems that have public API endpoints without TLS certificate protection. There are several ways to issue certificates:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Paid wildcard certificates that can be bought from any big TLS provider&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Paid root certificates that sign all downstream certificates that are issued by corporate PKI systems&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Free certificates issued by TLS providers like LetsEncrypt or AWS Certificate Manager&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;Self-signed certificates, issued by &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.openssl.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenSSL&lt;/a&gt; or another tool&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 433px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;151.6 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1727140455051&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/24/2024 01:14 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17937601-1727140453760.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;151639&#34; data-name=&#34;1727140453760.png&#34; data-id=&#34;17937601&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17937601-1727140453760.png&#34; alt=&#34;Let&#39;s Encrypt logo&#34;&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Within the context of this post, I will mainly discuss free certificates that can be used inside of AWS, but not only by AWS services. Clearly, using anything other than &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/certificate-manager/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;AWS Certificate Manager&lt;/a&gt; makes no sense if you exclusively use managed AWS services and don&#39;t have strict security requirements. AWS Certificate Manager offers a very convenient and speedy method of issuing certificates via DNS or HTTP challenges; however, you face basic AWS limitations if you need to use these certificates outside of AWS services (API Gateway, ALB, NLB, etc.), such as an EC2 instance running Nginx that needs a physical certificate file. Additionally, even if you request it, AWS Certificate Manager does not display the certificate content.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如今，很难想象具有公共 API 端点而没有 TLS 证书保护的系统。颁发证书有多种方式：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;可以从任何大型 TLS 提供商处购买付费通配符证书&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;付费根证书，用于签署企业 PKI 系统颁发的所有下游证书&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;由 LetsEncrypt 或 AWS Certificate Manager 等 TLS 提供商颁发的免费证书&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;自签名证书，由 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.openssl.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;OpenSSL&lt;/a&gt; 或其他工具颁发&lt;br&gt;&lt; br&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;宽度: 433px;&#34; class =“fr-fic fr-dib lazyload”data-image =“true”data-new =“false”data-sizeformatted =“151.6 kB”data-mimetype =“image / png”data-creationdate =“1727140455051”数据-creationdateformatted=&#34;09/24/2024 01:14 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17937601-1727140453760.png&#34; data-modificationdate= “null”data-size =“151639”data-name =“1727140453760.png”data-id =“17937601”data-src =“https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/17937601-1727140453760.png” &#34; alt=&#34;让我们加密徽标&#34;&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将主要讨论可在 AWS 内部使用的免费证书，但不仅限于 AWS 服务。显然，如果你专门使用托管AWS服务并且没有严格的安全要求。 AWS Certificate Manager 提供了一种非常方便快捷的方法，通过 DNS 或 HTTP 质询来颁发证书；但是，如果您需要在 AWS 服务（API Gateway、ALB、NLB 等）之外使用这些证书，例如运行 Nginx 的 EC2 实例需要物理证书文件，您将面临基本的 AWS 限制。此外，即使您请求，AWS Certificate Manager 也不会显示证书内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top 6 Cybersecurity Threat Detection Use Cases: How AI/ML Can Help Detect Advanced and Emerging Threats】六大网络安全威胁检测用例：AI/ML 如何帮助检测高级和新兴威胁</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-6-cybersecurity-threat-detection-use-cases</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;AI/ML tools and technologies heavily influence the modern digital landscape by introducing numerous use cases involving &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-genetic-algorithm-in-malware-detection&#34;&gt;AI-based malware detection&lt;/a&gt;, preventing social engineering attacks, and threat identification and remediation. Many organizations have acknowledged AI/ML&#39;s prominence in the cybersecurity threat landscape and have started to leverage AI/ML in their business and security requirements. AI/ML-based solutions assist employees to complete their day-to-day tasks more efficiently and in no time. However, at the same time, we have also witnessed an exponential increase in the cybersecurity threat landscape. Hence, cybersecurity professionals and software developers have also started using AI/ML to build more innovative, adaptive, and robust systems and applications to protect an organization&#39;s IT and network infrastructure. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Statistics: AI/ML in Cybersecurity&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In recent times, we have witnessed the widespread adoption and exponential growth of&amp;nbsp;AI and ML technologies. Below are the statistics taken after thorough research highlighting the impact of&amp;nbsp;AI/ML tools and techniques&amp;nbsp;on&amp;nbsp;cybersecurity threat detection&amp;nbsp;and increasing overall cybersecurity performance.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;人工智能/机器学习工具和技术通过引入大量涉及人工智能的用例，对现代数字格局产生了重大影响基于的恶意软件检测，防止社会工程攻击，以及威胁识别和修复。许多组织已经认识到人工智能/机器学习在网络安全威胁领域的突出地位，并开始在其业务和安全需求中利用人工智能/机器学习。基于人工智能/机器学习的解决方案可帮助员工更高效、更迅速地完成日常任务。但与此同时，我们也目睹了网络安全威胁形势呈指数级增长。因此，网络安全专业人员和软件开发人员也开始使用 AI/ML 来构建更具创新性、适应性和强大的系统和应用程序，以保护组织的 IT 和网络基础设施。    &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;统计数据：网络安全中的人工智能/机器学习&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;近年来，我们见证了 AI 和 ML 技术的广泛采用和指数级增长。以下是经过深入研究后得出的统计数据，强调了人工智能/机器学习工具和技术对网络安全威胁检测和提高整体网络安全性能的影响。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Misconfiguration Madness: Thwarting Common Vulnerabilities in the Financial Sector】错误配置的疯狂：阻止金融部门的常见漏洞</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/thwarting-common-vulnerabilities-financial-sector</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Ever since people started putting their money into banks and financial institutions, other people have sought to steal those deposits or otherwise fraudulently obtain those protected assets. When someone asked infamous 1920s-era bank robber &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fbi.gov/history/famous-cases/willie-sutton#:~:text=When%20asked%20why%20he%20robbed,Trust%20Company%20in%20Philadelphia%2C%20Pennsylvania.&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Willie Sutton&lt;/a&gt; why he robbed banks, he simply replied, “Because that’s where the money is.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Today, much of the money held by banks and other financial institutions is in digital form, and many of the sensitive records held by those firms can be just as valuable as the digital currency itself. But the reasons behind the targeting of financial institutions by threat actors remain much the same as they were in Sutton’s time over 100 years ago: that’s where the money — and at least some valuable personal data — is kept.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;自从人们开始将钱存入银行和金融机构以来，其他人就一直试图窃取这些存款或以其他方式欺诈性地获取这些受保护的资产。当有人问臭名昭著的 20 年代银行抢劫犯 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fbi.gov/history/known-cases/willie-sutton#:~:text=When%20asked%20why%20he%20robbed,Trust %20Company%20in%20Philadelphia%2C%20Pennsylvania。” rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;威利·萨顿&lt;/a&gt;为什么要抢劫银行，他简单地回答道：“因为钱就在那里。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;如今，银行和其他金融机构持有的大部分资金都是数字形式，这些公司持有的许多敏感记录可能与数字货币本身一样有价值。但威胁行为者瞄准金融机构的原因与 100 多年前萨顿时代的情况大致相同：那是资金（以及至少一些有价值的个人数据）的保存场所。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Comprehensive Guide to Database Sharding: Building Scalable Systems】数据库分片综合指南：构建可扩展系统</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-comprehensive-guide-to-database-sharding</link>
      <description>【&lt;section name=&#34;3377&#34;&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;b7f3&#34;&gt;In this article, we’ll dive deep into the concept of database sharding, a critical technique for scaling databases to handle large volumes of data and high levels of traffic. Here’s what you can expect to learn:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;c110&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Sharding?:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;We’ll start by defining what sharding is and why it’s essential for modern, high-performance databases. You’ll understand how sharding can help overcome the limitations of traditional database scaling methods.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;125e&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Types of Sharding:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Next, we’ll explore the different types of sharding, including horizontal and vertical sharding. We’ll discuss the benefits and challenges of each approach, helping you decide which might be best for your use case.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;8cc5&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Selecting a Shard Key:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Choosing the right shard key is crucial for the success of a sharded database. In this section, we’ll walk through the factors to consider when selecting a shard key, common mistakes to avoid, and how to balance performance with even data distribution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;7bb6&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Routing Requests to Shards:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Finally, we’ll cover the methods for routing queries to the correct shard. This section will provide insights into the architecture and strategies to ensure efficient query processing in a sharded environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;7743&#34;&gt;By the end of this guide, you’ll have a comprehensive understanding of database sharding, enabling you to implement it effectively in your systems.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;部分名称=“3377”&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;b7f3&#34;&gt;在本文中，我们将深入探讨数据库分片的概念，这是一种扩展数据库以处理大量数据和高流量的关键技术。以下是您可以学到的内容：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA; &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;c110&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是分片？：&lt;/strong&gt;我们首先定义什么是分片以及为什么它对于现代高性能数据库至关重要。您将了解分片如何帮助克服传统数据库扩展方法的局限性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;125e&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;分片类型：&lt;/strong&gt;接下来，我们将探讨不同类型的分片，包括水平分片和垂直分片。我们将讨论每种方法的优点和挑战，帮助您决定哪种方法最适合您的用例。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;8cc5&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;选择分片键：&lt;/strong&gt;选择正确的分片键对于分片数据库的成功至关重要。在本节中，我们将介绍选择分片键时要考虑的因素、要避免的常见错误，以及如何在性能与均匀数据分布之间取得平衡。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li name=&#34;7bb6&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;将请求路由到分片&lt;/strong&gt;：最后，我们将介绍将查询路由到正确分片的方法。本部分将深入介绍确保分片环境中高效查询处理的架构和策略。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;p name=&#34;7743&#34;&gt;读完本指南后，您将对数据库分片有一个全面的了解，从而能够在您的系统中有效地实施它。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 21:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hyperscale Data Centers Ignite Construction Surge】超大规模数据中心引发建设热潮</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/hyperscale-data-centers-ignite-construction-surge</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Despite the lack of a universal definition for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-lies-ahead-for-data-center-operators&#34;&gt;hyperscale data centers&lt;/a&gt;, many people view them as massive facilities that typically handle mission-critical workloads distributed across numerous servers. These buildings have collectively contributed to a data center construction boom, emphasizing the world’s substantial and growing dependence on technologies and the infrastructure supporting them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Emerging Technologies Spurring Data Center Construction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When a February 2024 study examined the state of the global data center industry, the results revealed some of the primary drivers of the current construction boom. One finding was many of the largest hyperscale providers increasingly accommodate clients’ artificial intelligence applications and other computing-intensive requirements.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;尽管&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-lies-ahead-for-data-center-operators&#34;&gt;超大规模数据中心缺乏通用定义&lt; /a&gt;，许多人将它们视为大型设施，通常处理分布在众多服务器上的关键任务工作负载。这些建筑共同推动了数据中心建设热潮，凸显了世界对技术及其支持基础设施的日益依赖。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;新兴技术推动数据中心建设&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;2024 年 2 月的一项研究调查了全球数据中心行业的状况，结果揭示了当前建设热潮的一些主要驱动因素。一项发现是，许多最大的超大规模提供商越来越多地满足客户的人工智能应用程序和其他计算密集型需求。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>