<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Apache Doris and DeepSeek: Redefining Intelligent Data Analytics】Apache Doris和DeepSeek：重新定义智能数据分析</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/apache-doris-deepseek-integration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to-apache-doris-a-next-generation-rea&#34;&gt;Apache Doris&lt;/a&gt;, a high-performance real-time data warehouse, has been gaining significant attention in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/llm-powered-olap-the-tencent-experience-with-apach&#34;&gt;OLAP&lt;/a&gt; (Online Analytical Processing) space in recent years. With its strong query performance, real-time data processing capabilities, and flexible data models, it is widely used in scenarios such as business intelligence, user behavior analysis, and real-time monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;The rise of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-ai-driven-data-analytics-deepseek&#34;&gt;DeepSeek&lt;/a&gt;, on the other hand, has injected new vitality into data analysis. Through DeepSeek’s natural language processing capabilities, users can directly query data using everyday language, greatly reducing the threshold for data analysis.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;P Data-selectable-paragraph =“”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-to--apache-doris-a-a-next-generation-rea--rea-&gt; apache doris &lt;/a&gt;，高度性能的实时数据仓库在&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/llm-powered-olap-the-tencent-experience-with-apach”&gt; olap &lt;/a&gt;（在线分析处理）近年来。凭借其强大的查询性能，实时数据处理功能和灵活的数据模型，它被广泛用于商业智能，用户行为分析和实时监控等方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph =“”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-ai-driven-data-analytics-deepseek”&gt; deepseek &lt;/a&gt;另一方面，将新的活力注入了数据分析中。通过DeepSeek的自然语言处理功能，用户可以使用日常语言直接查询数据，从而大大降低了数据分析的阈值。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Elevating LLMs With Tool Use: A Simple Agentic Framework Using LangChain】使用工具使用LLM：使用Langchain的简单代理框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/LLM-tool-agentic-framework-using-langchain</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Large Language Models (LLMs) are significantly changing the way we interact with data and generate insights. But their real superpower lies in the ability to connect with external tools. Tool calling turns LLMs into agents capable of browsing the web, querying databases, and generating content — all from a simple natural language prompt.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we go one step beyond single-tool agents and show how to build a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-langchain-and-large-language-models&#34;&gt;multi-tool LangChain agent.&lt;/a&gt; We’ll walk through a use case where the agent:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大语言模型（LLM）正在显着改变我们与数据互动并生成洞察力的方式。但是它们真正的超级大国在于能够与外部工具建立联系。工具调用将LLMS变成能够浏览网络，查询数据库和生成内容的代理 - 全部来自简单的自然语言提示。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我们迈出了单人工具代理商的一步，并展示了如何构建&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/what-is-langchain-and-langchain-and-lange-lange-langue-models”&gt; Multi-Tool langchain Agent。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI&#39;s Cognitive Cost: How Over-Reliance on AI Tools Impacts Critical Thinking】AI的认知成本：对AI工具的过度依赖如何影响批判性思维</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-cognitive-cost-impact-of-over-reliance-on-ai-tools</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;Tools driven by artificial intelligence (AI) are improving our learning, working, and decision-making processes. There is a cost involved in this change, though. With an eye toward cognitive offloading—the process by which we assign mental tasks to outside aids like digital assistants, search engines, or recommendation systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;In this article, I examine a&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mdpi.com/2075-4698/15/1/6&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;2025 study&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-US&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;by &lt;strong&gt;Michael Gerlich&lt;/strong&gt;. It provides a thorough and sophisticated investigation into how artificial intelligence tools influence critical thinking. The study offers a data-rich perspective on a rising issue: depending more on AI to think for us reduces our own cognitive capacity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;由人工智能（AI）驱动的工具正在改善我们的学习，工作和决策过程。但是，这种变化涉及成本。着眼于认知卸载，这是我们将心理任务分配给数字助理，搜索引擎或推荐系统等外部辅助工具的过程。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt;在本文中，我检查&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.mdpi.com/2075-4698/15/15/15/15/1/6” lang =“ en-us”&gt; 2025研究&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span data-contrast =“ auto” lang =“ en-us”&gt; by &lt;strong&gt; Michael Gerlich &lt;/strong&gt;。它对人工智能工具如何影响批判性思维提供了彻底而复杂的研究。该研究提供了关于上升问题的数据丰富的观点：更多地取决于AI的思考，可以降低我们自身的认知能力。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding the 5 Levels of LeetCode to Crack Coding Interview】了解破解编码访谈的5个leetcode级别</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/leetcode-progression-guide-coding-interview</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;There are five levels of &lt;a href=&#34;https://leetcode.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;LeetCode&lt;/a&gt;, and most people are stuck at levels one and two. Many of you can &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/getting-ready-for-interviews-in-software-engineeri&#34;&gt;solve LeetCode problems&lt;/a&gt; but still cannot get a job. Why is that?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Whether you like it or not, coding interviews are a competition. There are other people who are interviewing for the exact same position as you. At the end of the day, it&#39;s all about what your level is compared to them.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://leetcode.com/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; leetcode &lt;/a&gt;，大多数人被困在一级和两个级别上。你们中的许多人可以&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/getting-dready-for-interviews-in-software-engineeri”&gt;解决leetcode问题&lt;/a&gt;，但仍然无法找到工作。为什么是？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;无论您是否喜欢，编码访谈都是一场比赛。还有其他人正在面试与您完全相同的位置。归根结底，这一切都与您的水平与他们相比。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Driving Streaming Intelligence On-Premises: Real-Time ML With Apache Kafka and Flink】驾驶流媒体智能本地：带有Apache Kafka和Flink的实时ML</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/real-time-ml-apache-kafka-flink</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Lately, companies, in their efforts to engage in real-time decision-making by exploiting big data, have been inclined to find a suitable architecture for this data as quickly as possible. With many companies, including SaaS users, choosing to deploy their own infrastructures entirely on their own, the combination of Apache Flink and Kafka offers low-latency data pipelines that are built for complete reliability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Particularly due to the financial and technical constraints it brings, small and medium-sized enterprises often have a number of challenges to overcome when using cloud service providers. One major issue is the complexity of cloud pricing models, which can lead to unexpected costs and budget overruns. This article explores how to design, build, and deploy a predictive machine learning (ML) model using Flink and Kafka in an on-premises environment to power real-time analytics.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;最近，公司在利用大数据通过利用大数据进行实时决策的努力中倾向于尽快找到适合此数据的架构。对于包括SaaS用户在内的许多公司，选择完全由自己部署自己的基础架构，Apache Flink和Kafka的组合提供了用于完全可靠性的低延迟数据管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尤其是由于它带来的财务和技术限制，中小型企业在使用云服务提供商时通常需要克服许多挑战。一个主要问题是云价格模型的复杂性，这可能导致意外的成本和预算超支。本文探讨了如何在本地环境中使用Flink和Kafka设计，构建和部署预测机器学习（ML）模型，从而为实时分析提供动力。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Achieve SOC 2 Compliance in AWS Cloud Environments】如何在AWS云环境中实现SOC 2合规性</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/achieve-soc-compliance-aws-cloud</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Did you know &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.statista.com/statistics/511283/worldwide-survey-cloud-computing-risks/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;cloud security&lt;/a&gt; was one of the most evident challenges of using cloud solutions in 2023? As businesses increasingly depend on Cloud services like Amazon Web Services (AWS) to host their applications, securing sensitive data in the Cloud becomes non-negotiable.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organizations must ensure their technology infrastructure meets the highest security standards. One such standard is &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.techtarget.com/searchsecurity/definition/Soc-2-Service-Organization-Control-2&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;SOC 2 (Systems and Organization Controls 2) compliance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您是否知道&lt;a href =” https://www.statista.com/statistics/511283/worldwide-survey-clod-cloud-computing-computing-risks/“ rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black” _ _ black“ _ _ _ black”&gt; cloud Security &lt;/a&gt;是最多的cloude counderations of deventes counldites of counderes of counderes of counderes counldites in 2023333？随着企业越来越依赖诸如Amazon Web Services（AWS）之类的云服务来托管他们的应用程序，因此在云中确保敏感数据变得不可谈判。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;组织必须确保其技术基础设施符合最高的安全标准。一个这样的标准是&lt;a href =“ https://www.techtarget.com/searchsecurity/definition/soc-2-service-organization-control-control-control-2” re =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; SOC 2（系统和组织控制2（系统和组织控制2）Complians 2）Compliance 2）Compliance &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Your Private Cloud at Home】在家里建立私人云</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/build-your-private-cloud-at-home</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;OpenStack is a popular open-source cloud platform. Through this article, I plan to provide a guide for creating a basic OpenStack cloud at home!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/openstack-core-components&#34;&gt;OpenStack cloud nodes&lt;/a&gt; can be generally divided into two categories:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; OpenStack是一个流行的开源云平台。通过本文，我计划为在家中创建基本的OpenStack Cloud提供指南！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/openstack-core-components”&gt; OpenStack Cloud Nodes &lt;/a&gt;通常可以分为两类：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Effective Exception Handling in Java and Spring Boot Applications】Java和Spring Boot应用程序中有效的例外处理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/effective-exception-handling-java-spring-boot-application</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;406&#34; data-start=&#34;104&#34;&gt;When you&#39;re building Java applications, especially with frameworks like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/spring-h2-tutorial&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt;, it’s easy to overlook &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/beautiful-java-exception-handling&#34;&gt;proper exception handling&lt;/a&gt;. However, poorly managed exceptions can make your application harder to debug, more difficult to maintain, and a nightmare for anyone dealing with production issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;607&#34; data-start=&#34;408&#34;&gt;In this post, we’ll explore how to handle exceptions effectively by avoiding generic &lt;code&gt;catch&lt;/code&gt; blocks, using custom exceptions, and centralizing exception handling with Spring Boot’s &lt;code data-end=&#34;606&#34; data-start=&#34;587&#34;&gt;@ControllerAdvice&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 406” data-start =“ 104”&gt;当您构建Java应用程序时，尤其是在诸如&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/spring-h2-tutorial”之类的框架中例外处理&lt;/a&gt;。但是，管理不善的例外可能会使您的应用程序更难进行调试，更难以维护以及对处理生产问题的任何人的噩梦。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 607” data-start =“ 408”&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将探索如何通过避免通用&lt;code&gt; catch &lt;/code&gt;块有效地处理异常，使用自定义，并使用Spring boot的&lt;code data-end =“ 606” data data-data start =“ 587” 587“ 587” 587“ 587”&gt;@controllerAdvice &lt;/code &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Kung Fu Commands: Shifu Teaches Po the Command Pattern with Java Functional Interfaces】功夫命令：SHIFU使用Java功能接口来教PO命令模式</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/command-pattern-java-functional-interface</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Po was supposed to be practicing the Dragon Scrolls. Instead, he was… well, eating.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shifu&lt;/strong&gt; (arms crossed): &#34;Po! Again? Training time, not dumpling time.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice =“ 1 1 []&gt; PO应该在练习龙卷轴。相反，他在……好吧，吃饭。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; shifu &lt;/strong&gt;（手臂交叉）：“ po！再次？训练时间，不是饺子时间。” &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Decade of Transformation: The Evolution of Web Development】转变十年：网络开发的发展</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/evolution-web-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Over the past decade, web development has undergone a silent revolution, quietly reshaping the digital world landscape. The browser compatibility issues that once kept developers awake at night have become relics of the past, thanks to the wave of standardization led by Chrome. The era of jQuery, characterized by its rudimentary approach, has long been illuminated by component-based frameworks like React, Vue, and Angular, making complex interactions as effortless as building with blocks. We have witnessed the transformation of front-end development into the core engine driving trillion-dollar applications, extending the boundaries of code from the browser to the realms of the Internet of Things and artificial intelligence in a symphony of cloud and microservices. In this article, I will explore this transformation from various dimensions, inviting you to witness its greatness together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Conditions Driving the Transformation of Web Development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The changes in web development are not singular; they are intertwined with historical contexts and the evolution of the internet. To understand the transformation of web development, we must also grasp the reasons and environments that drive these changes, and which factors are closely related to this change.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在过去的十年中，网络开发发生了一场无声的革命，悄悄地重塑了数字世界的景观。由于Chrome领导的标准化浪潮，曾经使开发人员在夜间保持开发人员的浏览器兼容性问题已成为过去的遗物。以基本方法为特征的jQuery时代长期以来一直被基于组件的框架（如React，Vue和Angular）所照亮，使复杂的互动与构建构建一样轻松。我们目睹了前端开发转换为驱动数万亿美元应用程序的核心发动机，将代码的边界从浏览器范围扩展到了云和微服务交响曲中的物联网和人工智能领域。在本文中，我将探索从各个方面的转变，邀请您一起见证它的伟大。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;驱动Web开发转换的条件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Web开发的变化不是单数。它们与历史背景和互联网的演变交织在一起。要了解Web开发的转换，我们还必须掌握推动这些变化的原因和环境，哪些因素与此变化密切相关。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>