<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Use the H2 Database With Spring Boot】如何通过 Spring Boot 使用 H2 数据库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-use-the-h2-database-with-spring-boot</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this tutorial, we’ll review an example application that is written in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://groovy-lang.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Groovy Programming Language&#34;&gt;Groovy programming language&lt;/a&gt; and demonstrate how to use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://h2database.com/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;H2 relational database&#34;&gt;H2 relational database&lt;/a&gt; (H2 DB/H2) with &lt;a href=&#34;https://spring.io/projects/spring-boot&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Spring Boot&#34;&gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The benefit of using the Groovy Programming Language, in this case, is that it allows an example to ship exactly one file which contains everything we need to run the application.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在本教程中，我们将回顾一个使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://groovy-lang.org/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Groovy 编写的示例应用程序编程语言&#34;&gt;Groovy 编程语言&lt;/a&gt;并演示如何使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://h2database.com/&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;H2关系数据库&#34;&gt; H2 关系数据库&lt;/a&gt; (H2 DB/H2) 与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://spring.io/projects/spring-boot&#34; rel=&#34;nofollow noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; title=&#34;Spring Boot&#34; &gt;Spring Boot&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本例中，使用 Groovy 编程语言的好处是，它允许示例发送一个文件，其中包含运行应用程序所需的所有内容。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing Your Machine Identities Means Better Secrets Management】保护您的机器身份意味着更好的秘密管理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/secure-machine-identities-better-secrets-management</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In 2024, GitGuardian released the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gitguardian.com/files/the-state-of-secrets-sprawl-report-2024&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;State of Secrets Sprawl&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;report. The findings speak for themselves; with over 12.7 million secrets detected in GitHub public repos, it is clear that hard-coded plaintext credentials are a serious problem. Worse yet, it is a growing problem, year over year, with 10 million found the previous year and 6 million found the year before that. These are not cumulative findings!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When we dig a little deeper into these numbers, one overwhelming fact springs out: specific secrets detected, the vast majority of which are API keys, outnumber generic secrets detected in our findings by a significant margin. This makes sense when you realize that API keys are used to authenticate specific services, devices, and workloads within our applications and pipelines to enable machine-to-machine communication. This is very much in line with research from CyberArk, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cyberark.com/resources/blog/why-machine-identities-are-essential-strands-in-your-zero-trust-strategy&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;machine identities outnumber human identities by a factor of 45 to one&lt;/a&gt;. This gap is only going to widen continually as we integrate more and more services in our codebases and with ever-increasing velocity.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;2024 年，GitGuardian 发布了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gitguardian.com/files/the-state-of-secrets-sprawl-report-2024&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank &#34;&gt;《秘密蔓延状况报告》&lt;/a&gt;。研究结果不言自明；在 GitHub 公共存储库中检测到超过 1270 万个秘密，很明显，硬编码的明文凭证是一个严重的问题。更糟糕的是，这个问题逐年加剧，前一年发现了 1000 万个，前年发现了 600 万个。这些不是累积的发现！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当我们更深入地研究这些数字时，一个压倒性的事实浮出水面：检测到的特定秘密（其中绝大多数是 API 密钥）的数量远远超过我们的调查结果中检测到的通用秘密。当您意识到 API 密钥用于验证应用程序和管道中的特定服务、设备和工作负载以实现机器对机器通信时，这是有意义的。这与 Cyber​​Ark 的研究非常一致，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cyberark.com/resources/blog/why-machine-identities-are-essential-strands-in-your-zero-trust- Strategy&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;机器身份数量是人类身份数量的 45 比&lt;/a&gt;。随着我们在代码库中集成越来越多的服务并且速度不断加快，这种差距只会不断扩大。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 20:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Pure Storage Empowers Developers and Data Scientists With Agile, High-Performance Storage for AI and Modern Applications】Pure Storage 为开发人员和数据科学家提供适用于人工智能和现代应用的敏捷、高性能存储</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/pure-storage-provides-high-performance-storage</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the rapidly evolving world of artificial intelligence (AI) and modern application development, agility and high-performance storage are crucial for success. &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.purestorage.com&#34;&gt;Pure Storage&lt;/a&gt;, with its innovative solutions like FlashBlade and Evergreen//One for AI, is empowering developers and data scientists to accelerate their workloads and drive business value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Architecting FlashBlade for Predictable AI Performance at Scale&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI and machine learning (ML) workloads demand storage that can deliver consistent, high-bandwidth performance at scale. FlashBlade, Pure Storage&#39;s unified fast file and object storage solution, is uniquely architected to meet these challenges head-on.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在人工智能 (AI) 和现代应用程序开发快速发展的世界中，敏捷性和高性能存储对于成功至关重要。 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.purestorage.com&#34;&gt;Pure Storage&lt;/a&gt; 凭借 FlashBlade 和 Evergreen//One for AI 等创新解决方案，帮助开发人员和数据科学家加速工作负载并推动业务发展值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;构建 FlashBlade 以实现大规模可预测的 AI 性能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;AI 和机器学习 (ML) 工作负载需要能够大规模提供一致、高带宽性能的存储。 FlashBlade 是 Pure Storage 的统一快速文件和对象存储解决方案，其独特的架构可以直面这些挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering the Art of ChatGPT: 15 Prompt Engineering Techniques】掌握 ChatGPT 的艺术：15 项快速工程技术</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mastering-the-art-of-chatgpt-15-prompt-engineering</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Imagine you’re at your favorite burger place. You walk up to the counter and say, “Food, please!”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;The server might give you anything from a salad to a fish sandwich — definitely not what you were craving.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;想象一下您在您最喜欢的汉堡店。你走到柜台前说：“请吃东西！”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;服务器可能会为您提供从沙拉到鱼三明治的任何东西 - 绝对不是您想要的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maven Archetypes: Simplifying Project Template Creation】Maven 原型：简化项目模板创建</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/maven-archetypes-simplifying-project-template-crea</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;With Maven Archetypes, you can create a template for your Maven projects. It is a great way to enable and apply best practices within your project or organization. In this blog, you will learn how to create archetypes from scratch and based on an existing project. Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://maven.apache.org/guides/introduction/introduction-to-archetypes.html&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Maven Archetypes&lt;/a&gt; serve as templates for creating Maven projects. Often, you will have some best practices for your organization or team on how to create Maven projects. You can describe these on an intranet or Confluence, but it is even better to create templates for it. And that is what Maven Archetypes can do for you. You can create templates from scratch or you can create a project first and generate a template from the project. And even more, it is not very complicated. So let’s get started and see how this works!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用 Maven Archetypes，您可以为 Maven 项目创建模板。这是在项目或组织中启用和应用最佳实践的好方法。在本博客中，您将学习如何从头开始并基于现有项目创建原型。享受吧！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://maven.apache.org/guides/introduction/introduction-to-archetypes.html&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer noopener&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Maven 原型&lt;/a&gt;充当用于创建 Maven 项目的模板。通常，您的组织或团队会有一些关于如何创建 Maven 项目的最佳实践。您可以在 Intranet 或 Confluence 上描述这些内容，但最好为其创建模板。这就是 Maven Archetypes 可以为您做的事情。您可以从头开始创建模板，也可以先创建一个项目并从该项目生成模板。更重要的是，它并不是很复杂。那么让我们开始看看它是如何工作的！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Master AWS IAM Role Configuration With Terraform】使用 Terraform 掌握 AWS IAM 角色配置</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/master-aws-iam-role-configuration-with-terraform</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It&#39;s super important today to keep things secure and make sure everything is running as it should. AWS Identity and Access Management (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identity-and-access-management-best-practices-for&#34;&gt;IAM&lt;/a&gt;) helps with this by letting you manage who can get into what parts of your AWS account. One cool thing about IAM is that it lets you give permissions to different parts or people in your account without having to share sensitive info like passwords. Today, I&#39;m going to talk about using Terraform, a tool that lets you set up infrastructure through code, to create and set up these IAM roles easily.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding AWS IAM Roles and Terraform&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we get into how to use Terraform for setting up IAM roles in AWS, it&#39;s key to grasp what AWS IAM roles and Terraform are all about. In your AWS account, you can create IAM roles, which are basically identities with certain permissions attached. These roles let you give specific rights to different parts of your AWS setup without any hassle. On the flip side, Terraform is a tool that lets you manage your infrastructure through code instead of doing everything manually. It’s made specifically for working smoothly with services such as those offered by AWS, thanks to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/terraform-with-aws&#34;&gt;Terraform AWS&lt;/a&gt; provider.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;今天，确保一切安全并确保一切正常运行非常重要。 AWS Identity and Access Management (&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/identity-and-access-management-best-practices-for&#34;&gt;IAM&lt;/a&gt;) 可以帮助您管理谁可以进入您的 AWS 账户的哪些部分。 IAM 的一件很酷的事情是，它允许您向帐户中的不同部分或人员授予权限，而无需共享密码等敏感信息。今天，我将讨论如何使用 Terraform，这是一个可让您通过代码设置基础设施的工具，以轻松创建和设置这些 IAM 角色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;了解 AWS IAM 角色和 Terraform&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们了解如何使用 Terraform 在 AWS 中设置 IAM 角色之前，关键是要了解 AWS IAM 角色和 Terraform 的全部内容。在您的 AWS 账户中，您可以创建 IAM 角色，这些角色基本上是附加了某些权限的身份。这些角色可让您轻松地为 AWS 设置的不同部分授予特定权限。另一方面，Terraform 是一个工具，可让您通过代码管理基础设施，而不是手动执行所有操作。得益于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/terraform-with-aws&#34;&gt;Terraform AWS&lt;/a&gt; 提供商，它专为与 AWS 等服务顺利协作而设计。&lt;/ p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Build an AI Knowledge Base With RAG】如何使用 RAG 构建 AI 知识库</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-build-an-ai-knowledge-base-with-rag</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/custom-training-of-large-language-models-a-compreh&#34;&gt;Large Language Models&lt;/a&gt; are immensely powerful and can quickly generate intelligent and natural-sounding responses. Their major problem, however, is a limitation of training data – GPT-4, for instance, has a knowledge cutoff date in September 2021. This means that the model is unaware of any events or developments after this date. LLMs also have consistent troubles with the accuracy of information and “hallucinations” – coherent and logical, but factually incorrect responses. Finally, LLMs are unaware of specific, niche information, and can only generate responses on a certain level of generality.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;To solve these issues and make the LLM usable for specific and information-heavy tasks, LLMs can be connected to AI knowledge bases – repositories of information that consist of organized data – product documentation, articles, messages, and other materials. In this article, I explain how to create a knowledge base that would later be connected to the LLM model and enable it to generate factually correct and specific responses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/custom-training-of-large-language-models-a-compreh&#34;&gt;大型语言模型&lt;/a&gt;非常强大并可以快速生成智能且听起来自然的响应。然而，他们的主要问题是训练数据的限制——例如，GPT-4 的知识截止日期是 2021 年 9 月。这意味着该模型不知道该日期之后的任何事件或发展。法学硕士还一直存在信息准确性和“幻觉”方面的问题——连贯且合乎逻辑，但实际上不正确的反应。最后，法学硕士不知道具体的利基信息，只能生成一定程度的通用性响应。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;为了解决这些问题并使法学硕士可用于特定的信息密集型任务，法学硕士可以连接到人工智能知识库——由有组织的数据组成的信息存储库——产品文档、文章、消息、和其他材料。在本文中，我将解释如何创建一个知识库，该知识库稍后将连接到 LLM 模型，并使其能够生成事实上正确且具体的响应。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cache Wisely: How You Can Prevent Distributed System Failures】明智地缓存：如何防止分布式系统故障</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/Prevent-distributed-system-failures</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introducing-amp-assimilating-caching-quick-read-fo&#34;&gt;Caching&lt;/a&gt; is often implemented as a generic solution when we think about improving the latency and availability characteristics of dependency service calls. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/managing-tail-latency&#34;&gt;Latency&lt;/a&gt; improves as we avoid the need to make the network round trip to the dependency service, and availability improves as we don’t need to worry about temporary downtimes of the dependency service given that the cache serves the required response that we are looking for. It is important to note that caching does not help if our requests to a dependency service lead to a distinct response every time, or if a client makes vastly different request types with not much overlap between responses. There are also additional constraints to using caching if our service cannot tolerate stale data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;We won’t be delving into caching types, techniques, and applicability as those are covered broadly on the internet. Instead, we will focus on the less talked about risk with caching that gets ignored as systems evolve, and this puts the system at risk of a broad outage.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introducing-amp-assimilated-caching-quick-read-fo&#34;&gt;缓存&lt;/a&gt;通常作为通用解决方案实现当我们考虑改善依赖服务调用的延迟和可用性特征时。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/managing-tail-latency&#34;&gt;延迟&lt;/a&gt;得到改善，因为我们避免了网络往返到依赖服务的需要，并且可用性也得到改善鉴于缓存提供了我们正在寻找的所需响应，因此无需担心依赖项服务的临时停机。值得注意的是，如果我们对依赖服务的请求每次都会导致不同的响应，或者如果客户端发出截然不同的请求类型且响应之间没有太多重叠，则缓存无济于事。如果我们的服务不能容忍陈旧的数据，那么使用缓存还会受到其他限制。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;我们不会深入研究缓存类型、技术和适用性，因为互联网上已经广泛介绍了这些内容。相反，我们将重点关注较少被提及的缓存风险，随着系统的发展，这些风险会被忽略，这会使系统面临大范围停机的风险。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mitigate the Security Challenges of Telecom 5G IoT Microservice Pods Architecture Using Istio】使用 Istio 缓解电信 5G IoT 微服务 Pod 架构的安全挑战</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/overcome-the-security-challenges-of-the-telecom-5g</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Deploying microservices in a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/kubernetes-multi-cluster-management-and-governance&#34;&gt;Kubernetes cluster&lt;/a&gt; is critical in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/operation-management-of-telecom-5g-network-functions&#34;&gt;5G Telecom&lt;/a&gt;. However, it also introduces significant security risks. While firewall rules and proxies provide initial security, the default communication mechanisms within Kubernetes, such as unencrypted network traffic and lack of access control, are inherently insecure. This insecurity could compromise sensitive data. Therefore, implementing additional security measures within each microservice pod is not just a recommendation but a crucial step to ensure secure communication within the cluster. So, additional configuration inside each application is needed.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio provides a robust solution to these challenges by effectively managing communication between individual 5G telecom microservice pods. With its control plane, Istio automatically injects a sidecar proxy into individual microservices pods, ensuring secure and efficient communication.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/kubernetes-multi-cluster-management-and-governance&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 集群&lt;/a&gt;中部署微服务对于 &lt;a href=&#34;https 至关重要://dzone.com/articles/operation-management-of-telecom-5g-network-functions&#34;&gt;5G 电信&lt;/a&gt;。然而，它也带来了重大的安全风险。虽然防火墙规则和代理提供了初始安全性，但 Kubernetes 内的默认通信机制（例如未加密的网络流量和缺乏访问控制）本质上是不安全的。这种不安全性可能会损害敏感数据。因此，在每个微服务 Pod 中实施额外的安全措施不仅仅是建议，而且是确保集群内安全通信的关键步骤。因此，需要在每个应用程序内部进行额外的配置。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Istio 通过有效管理各个 5G 电信微服务 Pod 之间的通信，为这些挑战提供了强大的解决方案。借助其控制平面，Istio 自动将 sidecar 代理注入各个微服务 Pod，确保安全高效的通信。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【This Is How SSL Certificates Work: HTTPS Explained in 15 Minutes】SSL 证书的工作原理：15 分钟解释 HTTPS</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/this-is-how-ssl-certificates-work-https-explained</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The world of online security may seem complex, but understanding the basics of how SSL certificates work and why HTTPS is essential can empower you to make safer choices online. Just like Jane, you can navigate the digital landscape with confidence, knowing that your data is protected from prying eyes. So next time you browse the web, remember the story of Jane and the coffee shop hacker and choose secure, trusted websites for your online activities. Let’s start our day with Jane who was enjoying her coffee peacefully.&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fr-video fr-deletable fr-fvc fr-dvb fr-draggable&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34; draggable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fr-responsive-iframe fr-draggable&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fEmQxxVqYEE?&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen class=&#34;fr-draggable&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Chapter 1: The Coffee Shop Conundrum&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was a sunny afternoon, and Jane decided to take a break from her hectic day. She headed to her favorite coffee shop, ordered a latte, and found a cozy corner to catch up on some online shopping and emails. As she settled in, she connected her laptop to the coffee shop’s free Wi-Fi and began browsing. Little did she know, a hacker named Bob was sitting just a few tables away, eager to intercept her data.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在线安全世界可能看起来很复杂，但了解 SSL 证书工作原理以及 HTTPS 为何至关重要的基础知识可以帮助您做出更安全的在线选择。就像 Jane 一样，您可以自信地浏览数字环境，因为您知道您的数据不会被窥探。因此，下次您浏览网页时，请记住简和咖啡店黑客的故事，并为您的在线活动选择安全、值得信赖的网站。让我们和简一起开始新的一天，她正在安静地享用咖啡。&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fr-video fr-deletable fr-fvc fr-dvb fr-draggable&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;draggable=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fr-responsive-iframe fr-draggable&#34; contenteditable=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/fEmQxxVqYEE?&amp;wmode=opaque “frameborder =“0”allowfullscreen class =“fr-draggable”loading =“lazy”&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;第一章：咖啡店难题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那是一个阳光明媚的下午，简决定从忙碌的一天中休息一下。她前往她最喜欢的咖啡店，点了一杯拿铁，然后找了一个舒适的角落来处理一些网上购物和电子邮件。安顿好后，她将笔记本电脑连接到咖啡店的免费 Wi-Fi 并开始浏览。她几乎不知道，一位名叫鲍勃的黑客就坐在几张桌子之外，急于拦截她的数据。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>