<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Security into the Feature During the Design Phase】在设计阶段将安全性纳入功能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-security-into-design-phase</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It is exciting how different disciplines can be merged to make the processes more efficient. In 2009, DevOps was coined to address the friction between the Development and Operations teams. As a result, the industry moved towards clubbing both teams together so that the development team was responsible for the entire cycle, from writing code to production deployment. Of course, who would better understand intricacies than the people who developed them?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After this shift, we have seen features being shipped rapidly and the time to market for new features coming down rapidly. DevOps also served as the foundation for many other practices like MLOps, DataOps, GitOps, and undoubtedly many more have emerged.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如何合并不同的学科以提高流程的效率，这令人兴奋。 2009年，DevOps创造了解决开发团队和运营团队之间的摩擦。结果，该行业朝着将两个团队融合在一起，以使开发团队负责从编写代码到生产部署的整个周期。当然，谁能比开发它们的人更好地理解复杂性？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;转变后，我们看到了功能迅速运输，并且有时间销售新功能的迅速下降。 DevOps还为MLOP，DATAOPS，GITOPS等许多其他实践的基础都是基础。&lt;/p&gt;毫无疑问。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging LLMs for Software Testing】利用LLM进行软件测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/leveraging-llms-for-software-testing</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As software systems become more complex, traditional testing methods often fall short in keeping up with the fast-paced development cycles and changing user needs. Fortunately, advancements in machine learning and generative AI are bringing intelligent and adaptive testing strategies that improve test coverage and decrease maintenance efforts to speed up the entire testing process.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article details using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-large-language-models-and-how-they-work&#34;&gt;large language models&lt;/a&gt; (LLMs) to test a Python codebase project.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着软件系统变得越来越复杂，传统的测试方法通常在跟上快节奏的开发周期和不断变化的用户需求的过程中差不多。幸运的是，机器学习和生成AI的进步正在带来智能和适应性的测试策略，以改善测试覆盖范围并减少维护工作以加快整个测试过程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文使用&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-large-lange-lange-models-models-models-and-how-they-work”&gt;大语言模型&lt;/a&gt;（llms）测试Python Codebase Project。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【All About GPU Threads, Warps, and Wavefronts】所有关于GPU线程，扭曲和波前的信息</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/all-about-gpu-threads-warps-and-wavefronts</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;On a GPU, the threads are always run as a group of threads called warps. In that sense, the granularity of thread execution is always 32 (or 64, as explained later) on GPU. If a user requests for one thread, that one thread in the warp acts as an active thread while the rest of the threads are inactive. &lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;It is&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;not conventional&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;to request a single thread in GPU programming.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The threads inside the warp run in parallel (and not concurrent) and execute the instructions in a SIMD (Single Instruction Multiple Data) fashion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在GPU上，这些线程始终以一组称为WARPS的线程运行。从这个意义上讲，在GPU上，线程执行的粒度始终为32（或64个，如稍后所述）。如果用户请求一个线程，则经纱中的一个线程充当一个活动线程，而其余的线程则不活动。 &lt;span style =“背景色：透明;”&gt;它是&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em style =“ backick-color：透明;”&gt;不是常规&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;spar style =“ backick-color：pracherparent;”&gt;请求GPU编程中的单个线程&#xA;&lt;p&gt;经纱内的线程并行运行（而不是并发），并以SIMD（单个指令多个数据）方式执行指令。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Attribute-Level Governance Using Apache Iceberg Tables】使用Apache冰山表的属性级治理</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/attribute-level-governance-apache-iceberg-tables</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Large organizations where the number of users accessing crucial data is pretty high have to face a lot of challenges in managing fine-grained access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A variety of AWS services like&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-iam-basics-identity-and-access-management&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;IAM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, Lake Formation, and S3 ACL can help in fine-grained access control. But there are scenarios where a single entity containing the global data needs to be accessed by multiple user groups across the system with restrictive access. Also, organizations with a global presence might be working in different environments and with different toolsets, so data movement and cataloging become very tedious.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大型组织访问关键数据的用户数量很高，必须在管理细粒度访问方面面临许多挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/aws-iam-basics-indice-andity-and-yccess-managements”&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; iam &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt; &lt;span&gt;，湖泊形成，S3 ACL有助于获得良好的访问控制。但是，在某些情况下，包含全局数据的单个实体需要由整个系统中的多个用户组访问，并具有限制性访问。同样，具有全球存在的组织可能在不同的环境和不同的工具集中运行，因此数据移动和编目变得非常乏味。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Navigating Innovations and Challenges of Conversational AI】导航对话人AI的创新和挑战</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/navigating-conversational-ai-innovations-challenges</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Large language models (LLMs) are sophisticated AI models with the ability to understand, generate, and process natural language. They employ deep neural networks, more precisely transformer models, which enable them to perform many language tasks like answering questions and text generation, language translation, and summarization of content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/Conversational-AI-a-Brief-Story&#34;&gt;Conversational AI&lt;/a&gt; is a type of artificial intelligence that is committed to facilitating natural human-to-human-like dialogue through voice or text-based interfaces. It works on the principles of natural language processing and machine learning technologies and has been further enhanced by the development of LLMs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;大语言模型（LLM）是具有理解，生成和处理自然语言的能力的复杂AI模型。他们采用深层神经网络，更精确的变压器模型，使他们能够执行许多语言任务，例如回答问题和文本生成，语言翻译和内容的摘要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/conversational-ai-a-brief-story”&gt;对话ai &lt;/a&gt;是一种人工智能，致力于通过语音或基于文本的接口来促进自然的人类对人类对人类对人类的对话。它根据自然语言处理和机器学习技术的原则开展起作用，并通过LLM的开发进一步增强了。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Rebalancing Agile: Bringing People Back into Focus】重新平衡敏捷：使人们重新焦点</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/rebalancing-agile-bringing-people-back-into-focus</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Agile methodologies were introduced to enhance collaboration, foster continuous improvement, and promote the growth of both software and people. The intent was to create a framework that not only improved delivery but also empowered teams to innovate, learn, and contribute beyond their immediate tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, what started as a noble idea has, in many cases, devolved into a system focused purely on delivery. Teams are increasingly confined to ticking checkboxes in user stories, following rigid processes, and participating in endless meetings, leaving little room for creativity, autonomy, or professional growth.&lt;/p&gt;】引入了&lt;p&gt;敏捷方法，以增强协作，促进持续改进并促进软件和人员的增长。目的是创建一个框架，不仅改善了交付，而且还授权团队来创新，学习和贡献他们的紧急任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，在许多情况下，最初的想法最初是一种纯粹针对交付的系统。团队越来越局限于用户故事中的复选框，遵循严格的过程，参加无尽的会议，几乎没有创造力，自治或专业成长的空间。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Top Terraform and OpenTofu Tools to Use in 2025】2025年使用的Terraform和Opentofu工具</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/top-terraformopentofu-tools-to-use-in-2025</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Infrastructure-as-Code (IaC) has become a trusted approach for managing and provisioning infrastructure. As the field evolves, the number of IaC tools continues to grow, with frequent updates, new features, and improvements being introduced.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;One of the most popular tools in this space is &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-terraforms-core-concepts&#34;&gt;Terraform&lt;/a&gt;, a leader in the IaC ecosystem. There is a wide range of smaller tools that work alongside Terraform, adding extra features and making it even more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;基础架构-as代码（IAC）已成为管理和配置基础架构的一种可信赖的方法。随着场地的发展，IAC工具的数量继续增加，频繁更新，新功能和改进。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;这个空间中最受欢迎的工具之一是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/an-introduction-to-treduction-to-terraforms-core-concepts”&gt; Terraform&gt; Terraform &lt;/a&gt;，IAC生态系统的领导者。有多种较小的工具与Terraform一起使用，添加了额外的功能并使其更强大。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Best Practices for Data Warehouses in Microsoft Fabric】Microsoft Fabric中数据仓库的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/best-practices-data-warehouses-microsoft-fabric</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;To succeed, companies must transform raw data into actionable insights that support their operational growth. Users maintain separate tools for data lakes, ETL pipelines, and analytical tasks under traditional data warehousing, which results in complex conditions. Users can operate every aspect of their data analytics work via one platform when they use Microsoft Fabric for ingestion, storage, transformation, and analysis.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Overview of Microsoft Fabric Data Warehouse&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/empowering-insights-unleashing-the-potential-of-mi&#34;&gt;Microsoft Fabric&lt;/a&gt; combines data lake and warehouse functions into one simplified analytics platform. The platform integrates data engineering with data warehouse, data science, real-time analytics, and Power BI into a single operational space.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;为了成功，公司必须将原始数据转换为支持其运营增长的可行见解。用户在传统数据仓库下维护数据湖，ETL管道和分析任务的单独工具，从而导致复杂的条件。当用户使用Microsoft Fabric进行摄入，存储，转换和分析时，他们可以通过一个平台操作数据分析的各个方面。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir =“ ltr”&gt; Microsoft Fabric Data Warehouse &lt;/h2&gt;的概述&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/empowering-insights-unleashing-the-potential-of-mi--mi”&gt; Microsoft Fabric &lt;/a&gt;将数据湖和仓库功能结合到一个简化的分析平台中。该平台将数据工程与数据仓库，数据科学，实时分析和Power BI集成到一个单一的操作空间中。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Migrating From SQLite to MySQL】从sqlite迁移到mysql</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/migrate-from-sqlite-to-mysql</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introducing SQLite&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SQLite is a kind of open-source RDBMS that is distinguished from most other database management systems built on a client-server model since it is a server-less embedded database. This means that the SQLite database runs within the software that accesses the data, eliminating the need for a separate server. Due to such architecture, SQLite is a highly reliable, efficient system that works perfectly in low-memory environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the major benefits of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-sqlite-database-works&#34;&gt;SQLite&lt;/a&gt; is its cross-platform compatibility, allowing it to run on various modern OS. As an RDBMS contained within a C library, SQLite can be utilized by applications written in any programming language that can connect to external libraries written in C. For example, it is ideal for developing embedded software in digital devices, such as mobile phones, game consoles, cameras, and set-top boxes. Additionally, SQLite can serve as a temporary dataset for applications to process data.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;介绍sqlite &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; sqlite是一种开源RDBMS，它与构建在客户端服务器模型上的大多数其他数据库管理系统区别，因为它是一个无服务器的嵌入式数据库。这意味着SQLite数据库在访问数据的软件中运行，从而消除了对单独服务器的需求。由于这种架构，SQLite是一个高度可靠，高效的系统，在低内存环境中完美工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/how-sqlite-database-works”&gt; sqlite &lt;/a&gt;是其跨平台兼容性，可以在各种现代OS上运行。作为C库中包含的RDBM，可以通过使用任何编程语言编写的应用程序来使用SQLite，该应用程序可以连接到C中编写的外部库。例如，它非常适合在数字设备中开发嵌入式软件，例如手机，游戏机，摄像机，摄像头和设定盒。此外，SQLite可以用作处理数据的应用程序的临时数据集。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Agile Prompt Engineering Framework】敏捷及时工程框架</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/the-agile-prompt-engineering-framework</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;TL; DR: Bridging Agile and AI With Proper Prompt Engineering&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Agile teams have always sought ways to work smarter without compromising their principles. Many have begun experimenting with new technologies, frameworks, or practices to enhance their way of working. Still, they often struggle to get relevant, actionable results that address their specific challenges. Regarding generative AI, there is a better way for agile practitioners than reinventing the wheel team by team — the Agile Prompt Engineering Framework.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn why it solves the challenge: a structured approach to prompting AI models designed specifically for agile practitioners who want to leverage this technology as a powerful ally in their journey.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; TL; DR：桥接敏捷和AI，具有适当的及时工程&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;敏捷团队一直在寻求智能工作的方法，而不会损害他们的原则。许多人已经开始尝试新技术，框架或实践来增强其工作方式。尽管如此，他们经常努力获得相关，可行的结果，以应对他们的具体挑战。关于生成的AI，敏捷从业者有更好的方法比按团队重塑轮子的敏捷工程框架。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解为什么它解决挑战：一种结构化方法，用于促使AI模型专为想要在旅途中作为强大盟友的敏捷从业者而设计的AI模型。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>