<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Accelerating AI Inference With TensorRT】加速AI推断张力</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/accelerate-ai-interference-tensorrt</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deep learning models can be computationally expensive, especially when they&#39;re deployed in latency-sensitive scenarios like autonomous vehicles. Having a powerful GPU does not guarantee quick predictions if your model isn&#39;t optimized for inference. This is where &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/new-tools-and-platforms-to-accelerate-gen-ai&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NVIDIA TensorRT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; comes into play, an SDK that refines, quantizes, and accelerates deep learning models so they run significantly faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article provides a deep technical overview of converting &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/deep-learning-frameworks-comparison&#34;&gt;PyTorch models&lt;/a&gt; to TensorRT, covering the tools, configurations, and best practices. We&#39;ll also examine how TensorRT reduced latency by more than 70% in an autonomous driving system.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;深度学习模型在计算上可能是昂贵的，尤其是当它们部署在延迟敏感的情况下时。如果您的模型未针对推断进行优化，那么拥有强大的GPU不能保证快速预测。这就是&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/new-tools-and-platforms-to-accelerate-gen-ai-”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; nvidia tensorrt &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;发挥作用，出现在SDK上，一种精炼，量化和加速的SDK，因此它们运行了大量学习模型，因此它们运行了很大程度上可以运行。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文提供了转换&lt;a href =的深度技术概述。我们还将在自主驾驶系统中研究张力如何将潜伏期降低超过70％。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI&#39;s Dilemma: When to Retrain and When to Unlearn?】AI的困境：何时再培训和何时学习？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ais-dilemma-when-to-retrain-and-unlearn</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;A Growing Need for Data Privacy Solutions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In recent times, data privacy has become a central focus, with laws such as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) playing a key role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Organizations are under increasing pressure to comply with user data deletion requests. One significant requirement is the right to data deletion. Where user can request their personal information to be removed from company’s databases.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt;对数据隐私解决方案的需求日益增长&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近，数据隐私已成为核心重点，诸如《通用数据保护法规》（GDPR）和《加利福尼亚州消费者隐私法》（CCPA）扮演关键角色等法律。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;组织的压力越来越大，以符合用户数据删除请求。一个重要的要求是数据删除的权利。用户可以在其中请求其个人信息以从公司的数据库中删除。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Complete Guide to Modern AI Developer Tools】现代AI开发人员工具的完整指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-complete-guide-to-modern-ai-developer-tools</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;1&#34; data-line-start=&#34;0&#34;&gt;Based on my &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-firewall-guardrails-to-address-risks&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;previous articles&lt;/a&gt; exploring AI, machine learning, and generative AI, many developers have reached out to understand how these technologies can enhance their workflows, from improving coding skills and streamlining model training to deploying APIs and beyond. The rapid evolution of artificial intelligence (AI) has led to a surge in specialized tools designed to streamline development, collaboration, and deployment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line-end=&#34;1&#34; data-line-start=&#34;0&#34;&gt;This guide explores the most impactful AI developer tools, highlighting their features, installation steps, strengths, and limitations. Whether you’re training models, deploying APIs, or debugging workflows, this article will help you choose the right tool for your needs.&lt;/p&gt;】基于我的&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/ai-firewall-guardrails-to-dress-to-dress-to-dress-tres---- p data-line-end =“ 1”数据线start =“ 0”&gt;这些技术可以增强其工作流程，从提高编码技能和简化模型培训到部署API及其他方面。人工智能（AI）的快速发展导致了旨在简化开发，协作和部署的专业工具的激增。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line-end =“ 1”数据线启动=“ 0”&gt;本指南探讨了最有影响力的AI开发人员工具，突出了其功能，安装步骤，优势和限制。无论您是培训模型，部署API还是调试工作流程，本文都将帮助您选择适合自己需求的工具。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI’s Role in Everyday Development】AI在日常发展中的作用</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-role-in-everyday-development</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;From automated code generation to intelligent debugging and DevOps optimization, AI-powered tools are enhancing efficiency and improving software quality. As software engineering evolves, developers who leverage AI can significantly reduce development time, minimize errors, and improve productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Can software engineers be really replaced? Let’s explore briefly.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2数据选择 - 段落=“”&gt;简介&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p数​​据选择性 - 段落=“”&gt;从自动代码生成到智能调试和DevOps优化，AI驱动的工具正在提高效率并提高软件质量。随着软件工程的发展，利用AI的开发人员可以大大减少开发时间，最小化错误并提高生产率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA; &lt;p数​​据选择 - 段落=“”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;可以真正更换软件工程师吗？让我们简要探索。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Human Side of Logs: What Unstructured Data Is Trying to Tell You】日志的人类方面：非结构化数据试图告诉您什么</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/human-side-of-logs-unstructured-data-insights</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;It’s Friday afternoon, and your dashboards look great. Charts are green. CPU usage is stable. Database query times are within your SLA. You’re feeling great and ready for the weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;But little do you know, there’s a significant issue being overlooked by all your metrics — and it’s about to ruin your weekend.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;是星期五下午，您的仪表板看起来很棒。图表为绿色。 CPU使用率稳定。数据库查询时间在您的SLA内。您感觉很棒，可以在周末准备好。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir =“ ltr”&gt;，但您几乎不知道，所有指标都忽略了一个重大的问题 - 这将破坏您的周末。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 2: Power BI Embedded Overview】Power BI嵌入式分析 - 第2部分：Power BI嵌入式概述</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/power-bi-embedded-overview</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt;: This article dives into the details of Power BI Embedded. &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;It is a continuation of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-power-bi-authoring-overview&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 1&lt;/a&gt; article, which discusses Power BI Authoring and an introduction to Power BI Embedded Analytics. So, it is recommended that you go through the discussion on that article.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also find Part 3, which presents a Power BI Embedded Demo application, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/powerbi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-3-powerbi-e&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, based on the details presented in this article.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意&lt;/strong&gt;：本文深入介绍了嵌入的Power BI的细节。 &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;It is a continuation of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/introduction-power-bi-authoring-overview&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Power BI Embedded Analytics — Part 1&lt;/a&gt; article, which discusses Power BI Authoring and an introduction to Power BI嵌入式分析。因此，建议您进行该文章的讨论。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您还可以找到第3部分，该部分提出了Power BI嵌入式演示应用程序，&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/poperebi-embedded-analytics-primer-part-3-powrbimer-part-3-powerbi-e----------------- e”</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automatic Code Transformation With OpenRewrite】使用OpenRewrite自动代码转换</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automatic-code-transformation-with-openrewrite</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;Code Maintenance/Refactoring Challenges&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As with most problems in business, the challenge with maintaining code is to minimize cost and maximize benefit over some reasonable amount of time. For software maintenance, costs and benefits largely revolve around two things: the quantity and quality of both old and new code.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Quantity&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/quick-start-witj-sonarqube-for-static-code-analysi&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;SonarQube&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;suggests our organization maintain &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;80 million lines of code&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. That’s a lot, especially if we stay current with security patches and rapid library upgrades.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt;代码维护/重构挑战&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;与业务中的大多数问题一样，维持代码的挑战是在合理的时间内最大程度地降低成本并最大化收益。对于软件维护，成本和收益在很大程度上围绕两件事：旧代码的数量和质量。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt;数量&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/quick-start-witj-sonarqube-for-static-code-analysi&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;SonarQube&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; suggests our organization maintain &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;80 million lines of code&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.这是很多，尤其是如果我们保持安全补丁和快速库升级时。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to Convert XLS to XLSX in Java】如何将XLS转换为Java中的XLSX</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-convert-xls-to-xlsx-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Upgrading XLS to XLSX Is Worth Your Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ask any seasoned Java developer who&#39;s worked with Excel files long enough, and you’ll probably hear a similar refrain: the old XLS Excel format is clunky and annoying. It’s been around since the late ’80s, and while it’s still supported in a lot of systems, it&#39;s not doing us many favors today. &amp;nbsp;It was, after all, replaced with XLSX for a reason.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, there’s still a lot of important data packed in those old binary XLS containers, and some developers are tasked with making clean conversions to XLSX to improve the usability (and security) of that data for the long run.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么将XLS升级到XLSX值得您时间&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;询问任何经验丰富的Java开发人员，他们使用Excel文件足够长的时间，您可能会听到类似的限制：旧的XLS Excel格式笨拙而烦人。自80年代后期以来一直存在，虽然它仍然在许多系统中得到支持，但今天并没有为我们提供很多帮助。  毕竟，它被XLSX取代是有原因的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不幸的是，那些旧的二进制XLS容器中仍然有很多重要数据包装，并且一些开发人员的任务是将其清晰的转换到XLSX，以改善长期数据的可用性（和安全性）。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Immutable Secrets Management: A Zero-Trust Approach to Sensitive Data in Containers】不变的秘密管理：一种用于容器中敏感数据的零信任方法</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/immutable-secrets-management-zero-trust-approach</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This paper presents a comprehensive approach to securing sensitive data in containerized environments using the principle of immutable secrets management, grounded in a Zero-Trust security model. We detail the inherent risks of traditional secrets management, demonstrate how immutability and Zero-Trust principles mitigate these risks, and provide a practical, step-by-step guide to implementation. A real-world case study using AWS services and common DevOps tools illustrates the tangible benefits of this approach, aligning with the criteria for the Global Tech Awards in the DevOps Technology category. The focus is on achieving continuous delivery, security, and resilience through a novel concept we term &#34;ChaosSecOps.&#34;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Executive Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This paper details a robust, innovative approach to securing sensitive data within containerized environments: Immutable Secrets Management with a Zero-Trust approach. We address the critical vulnerabilities inherent in traditional secrets management practices, which often rely on mutable secrets and implicit trust. Our solution, grounded in the principles of Zero-Trust security, immutability, and DevSecOps, ensures that secrets are inextricably linked to container images, minimizing the risk of exposure and unauthorized access.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;摘要&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文提出了一种全面的方法，可以使用不变的秘密管理原理在容器化环境中保护敏感数据，该原则基于零信任的安全模型。我们详细介绍了传统秘密管理的固有风险，证明了不变性和零信任原则如何减轻这些风险，并提供实施实施的实用，逐步指南。使用AWS服务和常见DevOps工具的真实案例研究说明了这种方法的切实好处，与DevOps技术类别中全球技术奖的标准保持一致。重点是通过我们称为“ Chaossecops”的新颖概念来实现持续交付，安全性和韧性。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;strong&gt;执行摘要&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文详细介绍了一种在容器化环境中保护敏感数据的强大而创新的方法：具有零信任方法的不变秘密管理。我们解决了传统秘密管理实践中固有的关键漏洞，这些漏洞通常依赖于可变的秘密和内在的信任。我们的解决方案基于零信托安全性，不变性和DevSecops的原则，可确保秘密密不可分地与容器图像相关，从而最大程度地降低了暴露的风险和未经授权的访问。&lt;/p&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Revolutionizing Financial Monitoring: Building a Team Dashboard With OpenObserve】革命性的财务监控：使用openobserve建立团队仪表板</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/financial-monitoring-build-dashboard-openobserve</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;After a particularly grueling Thursday spent troubleshooting a publish API outage last year, I remember turning to my colleague and saying, &#34;There has to be a better way.&#34; Four years into my software engineering career in fintech, and we were still piecing together information from disparate monitoring tools whenever something went wrong. That frustration kickstarted my two-month journey to build what&#39;s now become our team&#39;s most valuable asset: a comprehensive OpenObserve dashboard that&#39;s transformed how we monitor our services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;img style=&#34;width: 640px;&#34; class=&#34;fr-fic fr-dib lazyload&#34; data-image=&#34;true&#34; data-new=&#34;false&#34; data-sizeformatted=&#34;49.5 kB&#34; data-mimetype=&#34;image/png&#34; data-creationdate=&#34;1741307717964&#34; data-creationdateformatted=&#34;03/07/2025 12:35 AM&#34; data-type=&#34;temp&#34; data-url=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18263964-screenshot-2025-03-06-at-63505pm.png&#34; data-modificationdate=&#34;null&#34; data-size=&#34;49525&#34; data-name=&#34;screenshot-2025-03-06-at-63505pm.png&#34; data-id=&#34;18263964&#34; data-src=&#34;https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18263964-screenshot-2025-03-06-at-63505pm.png&#34; alt=&#34;An image of an office setting.&#34;&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Finding the Right Tool&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After spending a few weekends researching options, I narrowed down our choices to three observability platforms. OpenObserve won out because it offered:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;去年花了特别艰苦的周四进行故障排除来进行故障排除，我记得我曾求助于我的同事说：“必须有更好的方法。”在我在金融科技的软件工程生涯中四年，只要出了点问题，我们仍在从不同的监视工具中拼凑出信息。这种挫败感启动了我为期两个月的旅程，以建立现在成为我们团队最有价值的资产：全面的露天店仪表板，它改变了我们如何监视我们的服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;img style =“ width：640px;” class =“ fr-fic fr-dib lazyload” data-image =“ true” data-new =“ false” data-sizeFormatted =“ 49.5 kb” data-mimetype =“ image/png” data-creationdate =“ 1741307717964” data-creationdateDateDateDateDateFormatted =“ 03/07/07/2025 Am” data-url =“ https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/temp/18263964-screenshot-2025-03-03-06-06-at-63505pm.png“ data-modificationdate =” null null“ data-size size =” 49525“ 49525” 49525“ 49525” data-name =“ screenshot-2025-03-06-AT-63505PM.png” data-id =“ 18263964” data-src =“ https:/ https://dz2cdn1.dzone.com/storage/storage/storage/temp/18263964-screensp/18263964-screenshot-2025-25-06-pp.55-pp--25-06-pp pp- alt =“办公室设置的图像。”&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2&gt; &lt;br&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;找到正确的工具&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;花了几个周末的研究选择后，我将选择范围缩小到了三个可观察性平台。 openobserve赢了，因为它提供了：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>