<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Database Connections and Migrations in Go With GORM and Goose】使用 GORM 和 Goose 在 Go 中构建数据库连接和迁移</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-robust-database-connections-and-migration</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Managing database connections and migrations is crucial for any application. In Go, we can leverage powerful libraries such as GORM for ORM functionality and Goose for database migrations. This article walks you through setting up a robust database client, handling migrations, preloading associations, and querying data efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Tutorial&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Before we dive into the implementation, ensure you have the following installed:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;管理数据库连接和迁移对于任何应用程序都至关重要。在 Go 中，我们可以利用强大的库，例如用于 ORM 功能的 GORM 和用于数据库迁移的 Goose。本文将引导您完成设置强大的数据库客户端、处理迁移、预加载关联以及高效查询数据的过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;教程&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;先决条件&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;在我们深入实施之前，请确保您已安装以下软件：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How To Think Simple In Java】如何在 Java 中思考简单</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-to-think-simple-in-java</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The programming language Java is recognized globally for its versatility, robustness, and user-friendly nature, making it one of the most widely used languages. Despite its popularity, individuals at all levels of expertise, from beginners to seasoned programmers, may face challenges comprehending the intricacies of Java, perceiving it as intricate and overwhelming. This comprehensive guide has been meticulously crafted to address these challenges by presenting lucid explanations, and practical examples, and placing a strong emphasis on the development of straightforward, elegant code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upon completion of this guide, you will have gained a comprehensive understanding of how to simplify the process of &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-tutorial-to-learn-java-programming&#34;&gt;Java programming&lt;/a&gt;. This will enable you to produce code that is not only efficient but also highly readable and easily maintainable.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;编程语言 Java 因其多功能性、稳健性和用户友好性而获得全球认可，使其成为使用最广泛的语言之一。尽管它很受欢迎，但各个专业水平的个人，从初学者到经验丰富的程序员，在理解 Java 的复杂性方面可能会面临挑战，认为它错综复杂且令人难以承受。这本综合指南经过精心编写，通过提供清晰的解释和实际示例来应对这些挑战，并重点强调简单、优雅的代码的开发。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成本指南后，您将全面了解如何简化&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/java-tutorial-to-learn-java-programming&#34;的过程&gt;Java编程&lt;/a&gt;。这将使您能够生成不仅高效而且具有高度可读性和易于维护的代码。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Guide to Security Controls for Risk-Based API Protection】基于风险的 API 保护的安全控制指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/a-guide-to-security-controls-for-risk-based-api</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-id=&#34;f5210838-2a6e-4cd6-9a9c-de7f05f39d47&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;In the interconnected world of today, APIs (Application Programming Interface) are the invisible bridges that let applications talk to one another. But to those that with great power, there must also come great responsibility! They need to be able to secure these APIs in order to protect the privacy of their own data or user information from would-be attackers. In this post, we are going to navigate risk-based API security controls which are essential in helping you construct more solid and tamper-proof APIs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-id=&#34;f5210838-2a6e-4cd6-9a9c-de7f05f39d47&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;1. Threat Modeling for Shift-Left Secure Design Practices&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;a2da6f2d-0aa8-45ee-9b58-03f27070e5d1&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;Just think of construction projects. It would perform well to find these structural flaws in the blueprint stage rather than after you build it, wouldn&#39;t that be even upstanding? Threat modeling is based on the same way of thinking The &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/shifting-security-left-the-innovation-of-devsecops&#34;&gt;shift-left mentality&lt;/a&gt;, in action, is identifying and remediating security flaws at the earliest possible point — prior to deploying APIs.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-id=&#34;f5210838-2a6e-4cd6-9a9c-de7f05f39d47&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;在当今的互联世界中，API（应用程序编程接口）是让应用程序能够互相交谈。但权力越大，责任也越大！他们需要能够保护这些 API 的安全，以保护自己的数据或用户信息的隐私免受潜在攻击者的侵害。在这篇文章中，我们将介绍基于风险的 API 安全控制，这对于帮助您构建更可靠、防篡改的 API 至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 data-id=&#34;f5210838-2a6e-4cd6-9a9c-de7f05f39d47&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;1.左移安全设计实践的威胁建模&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-id=&#34;a2da6f2d-0aa8-45ee-9b58-03f27070e5d1&#34; data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;想想建筑项目。在蓝图阶段而不是在建造之后发现这些结构性缺陷会表现得更好，这不是更正派吗？威胁建模基于相同的思维方式&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/shifting-security-left-the-innovation-of-devsecops&#34;&gt;左移心态&lt;/a&gt;，实际上，就是在部署 API 之前尽早识别并修复安全缺陷。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Topic Tagging Using Large Language Models】使用大型语言模型进行主题标记</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/topic-tagging-using-large-language-models</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Topic Tagging&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Topic tagging is an important and widely applicable problem in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-translation-the-power-of-context-in-n-1&#34;&gt;Natural Language Processing&lt;/a&gt;, which involves tagging a piece of content — like a webpage, book, blog post, or video — with its topic. Despite the availability of ML models like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/topic-modelling-techniques-and-ai-models&#34;&gt;topic models&lt;/a&gt; and Latent Dirichlet Analysis [1], topic tagging has historically been a labor-intensive task, especially when there are many fine-grained topics. There are numerous applications to topic-tagging, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content organization&lt;/strong&gt;, to help users of websites, libraries, and other sources of large amounts of content to navigate through the content&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommender systems&lt;/strong&gt;, where suggestions for products to buy, articles to read, or videos to watch are generated wholly or in part using their topics or topic tags&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data analysis and social media management&lt;/strong&gt; — to understand the popularity of topics and subjects to prioritize&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;Large Language Models&lt;/a&gt; (LLMs) have greatly simplified topic tagging by leveraging their multimodal and long-context capabilities to process large documents effectively. However, LLMs are computationally expensive and require the user to understand the trade-offs between the quality of the LLM and the computational or dollar cost of using them.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;主题标签&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;主题标记是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/transforming-translation-the-power-of-context-in-n-1 中一个重要且广泛适用的问题&#34;&gt;自然语言处理&lt;/a&gt;，涉及用主题标记一段内容（例如网页、书籍、博客文章或视频）。尽管有诸如&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/topic-modelling-techniques-and-ai-models&#34;&gt;主题模型&lt;/a&gt;和潜在狄利克雷分析 [1] 之类的 ML 模型，但主题标记历来是一项劳动密集型任务，尤其是当有许多细粒度主题时。主题标记有许多应用，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;内容组织&lt;/strong&gt;，帮助网站、图书馆和其他大量内容源的用户浏览内容&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;推荐系统&lt;/strong&gt;，其中有关购买产品、阅读文章或观看视频的建议全部或部分使用其主题或主题标签生成&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据分析和社交媒体管理&lt;/strong&gt; - 了解主题的受欢迎程度和优先考虑的主题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-large-language-models&#34;&gt;大型语言模型&lt;/a&gt; (LLM) 大大简化了主题通过利用其多模式和长上下文功能来有效地处理大型文档进行标记。然而，LLM 的计算成本很高，需要用户了解 LLM 的质量与使用它们的计算或美元成本之间的权衡。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Setting Up a Local Development Environment With IntelliJ, DevContainers, and Amazon Linux 2023】使用 IntelliJ、DevContainers 和 Amazon Linux 2023 设置本地开发环境</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/local-development-environment-intellij-devcontainers-linux</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In modern software development, &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/java-containerization&#34;&gt;containerization&lt;/a&gt; offers an isolated and consistent environment, which is crucial for maintaining parity between development and production setups. This guide provides a comprehensive walkthrough on creating a local development environment using IntelliJ IDEA, DevContainers, and Amazon Linux 2023 for &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why Use DevContainers?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;What Are DevContainers?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DevContainers are a feature provided by Visual Studio Code and other IDEs like &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/intellij-idea-update&#34;&gt;IntelliJ IDEA&lt;/a&gt; through extensions. They allow you to define a consistent and reproducible development environment using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker containers&lt;/a&gt;. By encapsulating the development environment, you ensure that all team members work in an identical setup, avoiding the &#34;it works on my machine&#34; problem.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在现代软件开发中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/java-containerization&#34;&gt;容器化&lt;/a&gt;提供了一个隔离且一致的环境，这对于保持开发和生产之间的平衡至关重要设置。本指南提供了有关使用 IntelliJ IDEA、DevContainers 和 Amazon Linux 2023 创建本地开发环境以进行 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 开发的全面演练。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么使用 DevContainers？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;什么是 DevContainer？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;DevContainers 是 Visual Studio Code 和其他 IDE（例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/intellij-idea-update&#34;&gt;IntelliJ IDEA&lt;/a&gt;）通过扩展提供的功能。它们允许您使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/getting-started-with-docker-1&#34;&gt;Docker 容器&lt;/a&gt; 定义一致且可重复的开发环境。通过封装开发环境，您可以确保所有团队成员在相同的设置中工作，避免“它可以在我的机器上运行”问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Variance: The Heartbeat of Agile Metrics】方差：敏捷指标的心跳</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/variance-the-heartbeat-of-agile-metrics</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;When teams get their variance right, everything else falls into place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Variance is a measure of whether teams are doing what they say they are going to do. A team with high variance is over-committing or under-delivering. A team with low variance is delivering on its plans. In this case, stakeholders can feel confident in the team, the team can celebrate at the end of each sprint, and longer-term planning is likely to be accurate.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;当团队正确调整差异时，其他一切都会水到渠成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;方差衡量团队是否按照他们所说的去做。差异较大的团队要么过度投入，要么交付不足。差异较小的团队正在实现其计划。在这种情况下，利益相关者可以对团队充满信心，团队可以在每次冲刺结束时庆祝，并且长期规划可能是准确的。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Deploy Your Data Pipelines With GitHub Actions】使用 GitHub Actions 部署数据管道</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/deploy-your-data-pipelines-with-github-actions</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Automate, customize and execute your software development workflows right in your repository with GitHub Actions. You can discover, create, and share actions to perform any job you&#39;d like, including CI/CD, and combine actions in a completely customized workflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitHub Actions is a powerful tool for automating software development workflows, and it can also be used to automate data pipeline processes. In this post, we will walk through an example of using GitHub Actions to automate a data pipeline for a simple data analysis project.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;使用 GitHub Actions 在您的存储库中自动化、自定义和执行您的软件开发工作流程。您可以发现、创建和共享操作来执行您想要的任何作业（包括 CI/CD），并将操作组合到完全自定义的工作流程中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GitHub Actions 是一个用于自动化软件开发工作流程的强大工具，它还可以用于自动化数据管道流程。在这篇文章中，我们将介绍一个使用 GitHub Actions 自动化简单数据分析项目的数据管道的示例。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AWS CDK: Infrastructure as Abstract Data Types, Part 3】AWS CDK：基础设施作为抽象数据类型，第 3 部分</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastructure-as-abstract-data-types-3</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In this third part of our &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastructure-as-abstract-data-types&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;CDK&lt;/a&gt; series, the project &lt;code&gt;cdk-quarkus-s3&lt;/code&gt;, in the same GIT repository, will be used to illustrate a couple of advanced &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/build-a-java-rest-api-with-quarkus&#34;&gt;Quarkus&lt;/a&gt; to AWS integration features, together with several tricks specific to RESTeasy which is, as everyone knows, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/redhat-3-scale-api-management-for-beginners&#34;&gt;RedHat&lt;/a&gt; implementation of Jakarta REST specifications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s start by looking at the project&#39;s &lt;code&gt;pom.xml&lt;/code&gt; file which drives the Maven build process. You&#39;ll see the following dependency:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在我们的&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/aws-cdk-infrastruct-as-abstract-data-types&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;的第三部分中CDK&lt;/a&gt; 系列，同一 GIT 存储库中的项目 &lt;code&gt;cdk-quarkus-s3&lt;/code&gt; 将用于说明几个高级 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/ articles/build-a-java-rest-api-with-quarkus&#34;&gt;Quarkus&lt;/a&gt; 到 AWS 集成功能，以及 RESTeasy 特有的几个技巧，众所周知，&lt;a href=&#34;https:/ /dzone.com/articles/redhat-3-scale-api-management-for-beginners&#34;&gt;RedHat&lt;/a&gt; Jakarta REST 规范的实现。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们首先查看驱动 Maven 构建过程的项目的 &lt;code&gt;pom.xml&lt;/code&gt; 文件。您将看到以下依赖项：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Test Smells: Cleaning up E2E Tests】测试气味：清理 E2E 测试</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/test-smells-cleaning-up-e2e-tests</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In practical terms, knowing how &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; to write tests might be as important as knowing how to write them. There are some very helpful chapters on test smells in Gerard Meszaros&#39;s &lt;a href=&#34;http://xunitpatterns.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;book about xUnit patterns&lt;/a&gt; — and more great stuff around the internet; however, it&#39;s always helpful to have practical examples for particular tech stacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&#39;ve already shown &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-smells-cleaning-up-unit-tests&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;how to clean up unit tests&lt;/a&gt;; this time, we&#39;ll do JUnit + Selenide end-to-end tests, at the top of the pyramid. We&#39;re assuming you&#39;re familiar with Selenide, but most stuff here is valid for other stacks, too.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;实际上，了解如何&lt;em&gt;不&lt;/em&gt;编写测试可能与了解如何编写测试同样重要。 Gerard Meszaros 的&lt;a href=&#34;http://xunitpatterns.com/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;关于 xUnit 模式的书&lt;/a&gt;中有一些关于测试气味的非常有用的章节 - 还有更多精彩的章节互联网上的东西；但是，针对特定技术堆栈提供实际示例总是很有帮助的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经展示了&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/test-smells-cleaning-up-unit-tests&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;如何清洁进行单元测试&lt;/a&gt;；这次，我们将在金字塔的顶部进行 JUnit + Selenide 端到端测试。我们假设您熟悉 Selenide，但这里的大多数内容也适用于其他堆栈。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microservice Logs Testing in the Cloud: Important but Often Ignored】云中的微服务日志测试：重要但经常被忽视</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/microservice-logs-testing-in-the-cloud-important</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Logs of an application are the initial step to start debugging and analysis of issues, so they are quite an important part of the application. However, they are often ignored during the testing phase. As the world is moving to cloud-based microservices, gaining insights into any customer issue heavily relies on logs. If they are not properly structured or don’t contain enough information to analyze the issue, they can be a significant stumbling block for engineers. In this article, we’ll explore why testing microservice logs is crucial and how engineers can ensure logs are up to the mark.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Why Logs Matter&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Logs are the backbone of debugging, monitoring, and security. They help engineers:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;应用程序的日志是开始调试和分析问题的第一步，因此它们是应用程序非常重要的一部分。然而，它们在测试阶段经常被忽视。随着世界正在转向基于云的微服务，深入了解任何客户问题在很大程度上依赖于日志。如果它们的结构不正确或不包含足够的信息来分析问题，则它们可能成为工程师的重大绊脚石。在本文中，我们将探讨为什么测试微服务日志至关重要，以及工程师如何确保日志符合标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;为什么日志很重要&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;日志是调试、监控和安全的支柱。他们帮助工程师：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>