<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【A Complete Guide to Creating Vector Embeddings for Your Entire Codebase】为整个代码库创建向量嵌入的完整指南</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/vector-embeddings-codebase-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As AI-powered development tools like GitHub Copilot, Cursor, and Windsurf revolutionize how we write code, I&#39;ve been diving deep into the technology that makes these intelligent assistants possible. After exploring &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/mcp-vs-traditional-apis-ai-integration&#34;&gt;how Model Context Protocol is reshaping AI integration beyond traditional APIs&lt;/a&gt;, I want to continue sharing what I&#39;ve learned about another foundational piece of the AI development puzzle: vector embeddings. The magic behind these tools&#39; ability to understand and navigate vast codebases lies in their capacity to transform millions of lines of code into searchable mathematical representations that capture semantic meaning, not just syntax.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, I&#39;ll walk through step-by-step how to transform your entire codebase into searchable vector embeddings, explore the best embedding models for code in 2025, and dig into the practical benefits and challenges of this approach.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为AI驱动的开发工具，例如Github Copilot，Cursor和Windsurf彻底改变了我们编写代码的方式，我一直在深入研究使这些智能助手成为可能的技术。探索&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/mcp-vs-traditional-apis-ai-integration”&gt;模型上下文协议如何重塑AI集成以外的传统APIS &lt;/a&gt;，我想继续分享我对AI开发的基础知识分享AI开发拼图的基础：vector eSuzz embecter：vector ectector：vector：vector。这些工具的理解和导航能力背后的魔力在于它们将数百万行代码转换为可搜索的数学表示的能力，而不仅仅是捕获语义含义，而不仅仅是语法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将逐步走进如何将整个代码库转换为可搜索的向量嵌入，探索2025年代码的最佳嵌入模型，并挖掘这种方法的实际好处和挑战。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ITBench, Part 2: ITBench User Experience – Democratizing AI Agent Evaluation】ITBench，第2部分：ITBench用户体验 - 民主化AI代理评估</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/itbench-part-2-ai-agent-evaluation-guide</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Note: A link to the previous article published in this series can be found at the conclusion of this article.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the first blog post of this series we introduced ITBench, IBM Research&#39;s groundbreaking framework that brings scientific rigor to &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/agile-fine-tuning-ai-agents&#34;&gt;AI agent evaluation&lt;/a&gt; in enterprise IT environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;（注意：可以在本文的结论中找到指向本系列上一篇文章的链接。）&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本系列的第一篇博客文章中，我们介绍了IBM Research的开创性框架，该框架将科学严格的框架带入了&lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/articles/Agile-fine-tuning-ai-ai-agents”&gt; ai代理商评估&lt;/a&gt;在企业环境中&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Meta-Learning: The Key to Models That Can &#34;Learn to Learn&#34;】元学习：可以“学习学习”的模型的关键</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/meta-learning-learn-to-learn-ai-models</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-end=&#34;587&#34; data-start=&#34;525&#34;&gt;Meta-Learning: The Key to Models That Can &#34;Learn to Learn&#34;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1036&#34; data-start=&#34;589&#34;&gt;As artificial intelligence (AI) systems continue to evolve, one of the biggest challenges we face is getting machines to generalize well from limited data. Traditionally, training an AI model for a specific task requires vast amounts of labeled data, a problem that is not only costly but also time-consuming. However, a breakthrough concept known as &lt;strong&gt;m&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;957&#34; data-start=&#34;940&#34;&gt;eta-learning&lt;/strong&gt; or &#34;learning to learn&#34; is quickly changing the way we think about AI training.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;1273&#34; data-start=&#34;1038&#34;&gt;In simple terms, meta-learning aims to train models that can adapt quickly to new tasks with very little data. This technique is poised to make AI systems more flexible and capable of solving a wide range of problems with less effort.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-end =“ 587” data-start =“ 525”&gt;元学习：可以“学会学习” &lt;/h2&gt;的模型的关键&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1036” data-start =“ 589”&gt;随着人工智能（AI）系统的不断发展，我们面临的最大挑战之一就是使机器从有限的数据中概述。传统上，针对特定任务的AI模型训练需要大量的标记数据，这个问题不仅昂贵，而且耗时。但是，一个被称为&lt;strong&gt; m &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong data-end =“ 957” data-start =“ 940”&gt; eta学习&lt;/strong&gt;或“学习学习”的突破概念正在迅速改变我们对AI培训的方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 1273” data-start =“ 1038”&gt;简单的术语，元学习旨在训练可以快速适应新任务的模型。该技术有望使AI系统更加灵活，并能够以更少的精力解决各种问题。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How GitHub Copilot Handles Multi-File Context Internally: A Deep Dive for Developers, Researchers, and Tech Leaders】Github Copilot如何在内部处理多文件的环境：对开发人员，研究人员和技术领导者的深入潜水</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/github-copilot-multi-file-context-internal-architecture</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;GitHub Copilot has evolved from a basic autocomplete engine into an intelligent AI assistant capable of understanding and navigating large-scale codebases. One of the most powerful capabilities it brings to developers is the ability to reason across multiple files in a project. This seemingly magical feature is not a trivial extension of autocomplete — it is the result of sophisticated orchestration involving context retrieval, symbol analysis, vector embeddings, token prioritization, and prompt construction under strict limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article presents a deeply technical examination of how GitHub Copilot internally handles multi-file context. The purpose is to demystify its architectural design, explain its data processing pipeline, and highlight the algorithms and data structures powering its context-aware capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style =“ text-align：left;”&gt; github copilot已从基本的自动完整引擎演变为能够理解和导航大规模代码库的智能AI助手。它给开发人员带来的最强大功能之一是能够在项目中跨多个文件推理。这个看似神奇的功能并不是自动完成的微不足道的扩展，这是涉及上下文检索，符号分析，矢量嵌入，令牌优先级和及时施工的复杂编排的结果。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;本文介绍了Github Copilot如何内部处理多文件背景的深入技术研究。目的是揭开其架构设计，解释其数据处理管道，并突出显示为其上下文感知功能提供动力的算法和数据结构。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MCP Logic: How to Make It 40x Simpler】MCP逻辑：如何使其更简单40倍</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/making-mcp-logic-simpler</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2 data-line=&#34;4&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;Foreword&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line=&#34;6&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;This document presents a real-world A/B comparison of two approaches to implementing the same business logic requirements. We asked AI to generate both a procedural implementation using conventional code, and a declarative implementation using the LogicBank rules engine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line=&#34;8&#34; dir=&#34;auto&#34;&gt;This experiment highlights fundamental differences between the two approaches, and what they mean for building reliable, maintainable systems. It&#39;s important, because business logic typically represents &lt;em&gt;nearly half the effort&lt;/em&gt; in database projects.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2 data-line =“ 4” dir =“ auto”&gt; foreword &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line =“ 6” dir =“ auto”&gt;本文档对实现相同业务逻辑要求的两种方法进行了现实世界中的A/B比较。我们要求AI使用常规代码生成程序实现，又是使用LogicBank规则引擎的声明性实施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-line =“ 8” dir =“ auto”&gt;该实验突出了两种方法之间的基本差异，以及它们对构建可靠，可维护的系统的含义。重要的是，因为业务逻辑通常代表数据库项目中的努力&lt;/em&gt;的一半。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Docker Offload: One of the Best Features for AI Workloads】Docker卸载：AI工作负载的最佳功能之一</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/docker-offload-best-feature-for-ai-workloads</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;As I mentioned in my previous post about&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/docker-model-runner-dotnet-guide&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Docker Model Runner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;background-color: transparent;&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;and why it&#39;s a game-changing feature.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&#34;margin: 0px; padding: 0px;&#34;&gt;I also mentioned that the best is yet to come, and Docker finally announced during the &#34;WeAreDevelopers&#34; event in Berlin, about their new feature, &#34;Docker Offload.&#34;&lt;/span&gt; In this article, I will explain what exactly Docker Offload is and why we need it as developers, and why I say it&#39;s one of the best features released by Docker in recent times.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Docker Offload?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are like me, who struggled to try out those cool AI models or data processing pipelines locally but were unable to do so due to the limitations of not having a GPU or a powerful machine to run them on, then continue reading. I always end up utilizing cloud resources, which often come with a hefty price tag.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span style =“背景 - 彩色：透明;”&gt;正如我在上一篇关于&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/docker-model-model-runner-dotnet-guide” target =“ _&gt; docker型跑步者&lt;/a&gt; dockch &lt;/span parkent-partent a thementparent：the appparenent：功能。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style =“边距：0px;填充：0px;”&gt;我还提到，最好的是要来的，最终在柏林的“佩戴deedevelopers”事件中宣布了有关他们的新功能的“ docker卸载”。时代。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是Docker卸载？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您像我一样，他们努力在本地尝试这些酷炫的AI模型或数据处理管道，但由于没有GPU或强大的机器来运行它们，然后继续阅读，因此无法进行此操作。我总是最终利用云资源，这些资源通常带有高价标签。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software Engineer Archetypes: The 5 Branding Styles That Shape Your Tech Career】软件工程师原型：塑造您的技术职业的5种品牌风格</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/software-engineer-archetypes-the-5-branding-styles</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Some of the most skilled software engineers spend years mastering their craft, contributing to critical systems, and solving complex problems — yet remain invisible outside their immediate circles. Meanwhile, others with average skills gain influence, career momentum, and opportunities. It isn&#39;t just about meritocracy; in practice, there are biases, as well as perceptions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;and positioning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;. In the modern software industry,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;your technical skills must be paired&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;with a strong personal brand to ensure your work is recognized, understood, and valued. Reputation amplifies expertise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Our goal is to take the next step in Personal Branding. To understand the reason, I recommend reading the article&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/personal-branding-for-software-engineers&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&#34;Personal Branding for Software Engineers.&#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;We explored how branding shapes how others perceive your expertise, values, and long-term potential. It&#39;s about communicating your impact clearly and consistently.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;span数据 - 销售服务器空间=“ true”&gt;一些最熟练的软件工程师花了多年的时间来掌握自己的手艺，为关键系统做出贡献并解决复杂的问题 - 但在直接圈子之外仍然看不见。同时，具有平均技能的其他人获得了影响力，职业势头和机会。这不仅仅是精英管理；实际上，存在偏见，以及感知&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span data-pleserver spaces =“ true”&gt;和定位&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;span data data-pleserver spaces =“ true”&gt;。在现代软件行业中，&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;您的技术技能必须配对&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;与强大的个人品牌，以确保您的工作得到认可，理解和重视。声誉放大了专业知识。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;我们的目标是迈出个人品牌的下一步。要了解原因，我建议您阅读文章&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/personal-branding-for-software-wardar-ware--gineers&#39;target =“ _ black”&gt; &lt;span data-proserver-spaces =“ true”&gt;“ true”&gt;“ true”&gt;“ true”个人品牌的软件工程师。感知您的专业知识，价值和长期潜力。这是关于清晰，一致地传达您的影响。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【WAN Is the New LAN!?!?】wan是新的局域网！？！？</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/wan-is-the-new-lan</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;For decades, the&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-does-routing-work&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Local Area Network&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;(LAN) was the heart of enterprise IT. It represented the immediate, high-speed connectivity within an office or campus. But in today&#39;s cloud-first, globally distributed world, the very definition of &#34;local&#34; has expanded. The &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/cleaning-out-the-server-closet-enterprise-sustaina&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Wide Area Network&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; (WAN)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;was considered&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;to be the most expensive link. However, its high agility and intelligent fabric make it more reliable and help make LAN expand globally. The paradigm shift is clear: &#34;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;WAN is the new LAN&#34;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;This transformation hasn&#39;t happened overnight.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;A&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;lot&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;of research hours went into this innovation, and it took more than&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;2&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;decades for&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;the&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;evolution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;It&#39;s a journey that began with the limitations of traditional Multiprotocol Label Switching (MPLS) infrastructure, evolved through the revolutionary capabilities of Software-Defined Wide Area Networking (SD-WAN), and is now culminating in the promise of hyper-scale Cloud WAN.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;For decades, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/how-does-routing-work&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;Local Area Network&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; (LAN) was the heart of enterprise IT.它代表了办公室或校园内的直接高速连通性。但是，在当今的云领先，全球分布的世界中，“本地”的定义已经扩大。 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/cleaning-the-server-closet-closet-enterprise-sustaina”&gt; &lt;span data-proserver-spaces =“ true”&gt;广泛区域网络&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;考虑到&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver空道=“ true”&gt;是最昂贵的链接。但是，其高敏捷性和智能面料使其更可靠，并有助于LAN在全球范围内扩展。范式偏移很明显：“ &lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span数据 - 列表范围=“ true”&gt; wan是新的lan。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span data-preserver spaces =“ true”&gt;这种转换在一夜之间没有发生。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;lot&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; of research hours went into this innovation, and it took more than&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt; 2 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver-spaces=&#34;true&#34;&gt;decades for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-preserver空间=“ true”&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver空间=“ true”&gt;进化。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-proserver spaces =“ true”&gt;这是一个旅程，这是一段旅程，始于传统的多元辅助标签（MPLS）基础结构（MPLS）基础设施，通过革命性的网络范围（又一次的范围）（MPLS）基础结构（MPLS）的范围，并在软件定义的范围内进行了范围，并启动了范围。超级云的承诺&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Feature Flags in Agile Development: Lessons from Scaling Front-End Platform Releases】敏捷开发中的功能标志：从缩放前端平台发行的课程</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/feature-flags-in-agile-development-lessons-from-sc</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-end=&#34;454&#34; data-start=&#34;108&#34;&gt;Let’s start with the basics: what is a feature flag?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end=&#34;454&#34; data-start=&#34;108&#34;&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/feature-flags&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;f&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong data-end=&#34;155&#34; data-start=&#34;139&#34;&gt;eature flag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a technique that allows developers to control the execution of specific features or code blocks at runtime without redeploying the application. As engineering teams accelerate their adoption of agile practices, feature flagging has become a cornerstone of modern front-end deployment strategies.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-end =“ 454” data-start =“ 108”&gt;让我们从基础开始：什么是功能标志？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-end =“ 454” data-start =“ 108”&gt; a &lt;a href =“ https://dzone.com/articles/feature-flags”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong data-end =“ 155” data-start =“ data-start =” 139“ 139”&gt;不允许使用的技术来控制特定的特定特定者，以执行特定的特定特定者。重新部署应用程序。随着工程团队加速他们对敏捷实践的采用，功能标记已成为现代前端部署策略的基石。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-Powered AWS CloudTrail Analysis: Using Strands Agent and Amazon Bedrock for Intelligent AWS Access Pattern Detection】AI驱动的AWS CloudTrail分析：使用Strands Agent和Amazon Bedrock进行智能AWS访问模式检测</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/ai-powered-aws-cloudtrail-analysis-strands-agent-bedrock</link>
      <description>【&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Background/Challenge&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;AWS CloudTrail logs capture a comprehensive history of API calls made within an AWS account, providing valuable information about who accessed what resources and when. However, these logs can be overwhelming to analyze manually due to their volume and complexity. Security teams need an efficient way to:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Identify unusual access patterns&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Detect potential security threats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Understand resource usage patterns&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Generate human-readable reports from technical log data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;My approach combines AWS native services with generative AI to transform raw log data into actionable security insights. By leveraging the power of Amazon Bedrock and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://strandsagents.com/latest/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Strands Agent&lt;/a&gt; framework, I have created a scalable, automated system that significantly reduces the manual effort required for CloudTrail analysis while providing more comprehensive results than traditional methods.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;h2&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span&gt;背景/挑战&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt; AWS CloudTrail日志捕获了AWS帐户中进行的API呼叫的全面历史记录，提供了有关谁访问谁资源和何时访问的有价值的信息。但是，由于它们的体积和复杂性，这些日志可能会令人沮丧。安全团队需要一种有效的方法：&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;标识异常访问模式&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;检测潜在的安全威胁&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;了解资源使用模式&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA; &lt;li&gt; &lt;span&gt;从技术日志数据生成人类可读报告&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;span&gt;我的方法将AWS本机服务与生成AI结合在一起，以将原始日志数据转换为可行的安全性见解。通过利用亚马逊底石的力量和&lt;a href =“ https://strandsagents.com/latest/” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” target =“ _ black”&gt; strands代理&lt;/a&gt;框架&lt;/a&gt; framefork &lt;/a&gt;我已经在提供了一个可扩展的，自动化的系统时，可以更加稳定地进行手动分析。方法。&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>