<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DZone.com Feed</title>
    <link>https://feeds.dzone.com/home</link>
    <description>Recent posts on DZone.com</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Confusion Matrix vs. ROC Curve: When To Use Which for Model Evaluation】混淆矩阵与 ROC 曲线：何时使用哪个进行模型评估</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/confusion-matrix-vs-roc-curve-when-to-use</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Model performance has to be evaluated in &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-beginners-guide-to-machine-learning-what-aspirin&#34;&gt;machine learning and data science&lt;/a&gt; in order to come up with a model that is reliable, accurate, and efficient in making any kind of prediction. Some common tools for this are the Confusion Matrix and the ROC Curve. Both have different purposes and knowing exactly when to use them is critical in robust model evaluation. In this blog, we will go into details of both tools, compare them, and finally provide guidance on when to use either in model evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding Confusion Matrix&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-the-confusion-matrix-a-comprehensive-guid&#34;&gt;Confusion Matrix&lt;/a&gt; is a table used for visualizing how well a classification model is performing. Generally, it breaks the predictions of the model into four classes:&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;模型性能必须在&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/a-beginners-guide-to-machine-learning-what-aspirin&#34;&gt;机器学习和数据科学&lt;/a中进行评估&gt; 为了提出一个可靠、准确且高效的模型来进行任何类型的预测。一些常用的工具是混淆矩阵和 ROC 曲线。两者都有不同的目的，准确了解何时使用它们对于稳健模型评估至关重要。在本博客中，我们将详细介绍这两种工具，对它们进行比较，最后提供有关何时在模型评估中使用这两种工具的指导。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;理解混淆矩阵&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/decoding-the-confusion-matrix-a-compressive-guid&#34;&gt;混淆矩阵&lt;/a&gt;是一个用于可视化分类效果的表格模型正在表演。一般来说，它将模型的预测分为四类：&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Cucumber Data Table to Java Object Mapping in Your Cucumber Tests】在 Cucumber 测试中自动将 Cucumber 数据表映射到 Java 对象</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/automating-cucumber-data-table-to-java-object-mapping</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; developer, using &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/effective-java-application-testing-with-cucumber&#34;&gt;Cucumber for Behavior-Driven Development (BDD)&lt;/a&gt; can be a great way to ensure that your code meets business requirements by writing tests in plain language. One of the most powerful features of Cucumber is the ability to use Data Tables in feature files. However, manually mapping these tables to Java objects can be repetitive and error-prone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To streamline this process, the library &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/deblockt/cucumber-datatable-to-bean-mapping?tab=readme-ov-file#cucumber-datatable-to-bean-mapping&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;cucumber-datatable-to-bean-mapping&lt;/a&gt; aims to automatically map Cucumber Data Tables to Java objects. In this article, I will walk you through the library&#39;s functionality and how you can easily integrate it into your Cucumber projects to save time and &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/removing-boilerplate-code-with-lombok&#34;&gt;reduce boilerplate code&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/core-java&#34;&gt;Java&lt;/a&gt; 开发人员，使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ effective- java-application-testing-with-cucumber&#34;&gt;用于行为驱动开发 (BDD) 的 Cucumber&lt;/a&gt; 是通过用简单语言编写测试来确保代码满足业务需求的好方法。 Cucumber 最强大的功能之一是能够在功能文件中使用数据表。但是，手动将这些表映射到 Java 对象可能会重复且容易出错。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了简化此过程，库 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/deblockt/cucumber-datatable-to-bean-mapping?tab=readme-ov-file#cucumber-datatable-to-bean -mapping&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;cucumber-datatable-to-bean-mapping&lt;/a&gt; 旨在自动将 Cucumber 数据表映射到 Java 对象。在本文中，我将引导您了解该库的功能以及如何轻松地将其集成到您的 Cucumber 项目中以节省时间和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/removing-boilerplate-code-with- lombok&#34;&gt;减少样板代码&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Workload Protection in the Cloud: Why It Matters More Than Ever】云中的工作负载保护：为什么它比以往任何时候都更重要</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/workload-protection-in-the-cloud-why-it-matters</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;The swift progress in cloud technology has made data and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/cloud-native-application-security-1&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;application security&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt; an important requirement rather than just a preference.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;As more customer businesses are moving their operations to the cloud, safeguarding their cloud workloads — referring to all deployed applications and services — has become increasingly essential.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crowdstrike.com/cybersecurity-101/cloud-security/cloud-workload-protection/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;Cloud Workload Protection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;(CWP) is important in this area because it ensures that these workloads remain secure and resilient against a growing range of threats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;Why CWP Is Essential&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;CWP is a necessity that must not be ignored.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;As the adoption of cloud technology grows, the scale and complexity of threats also escalate. Here are the reasons why CWP is critical:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:6,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:6}&#34;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;云技术的飞速进步使得数据和&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https ://dzone.com/refcardz/cloud-native-application-security-1&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;应用程序安全性&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data -contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt; 是一个重要的要求，而不仅仅是一个偏好。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;随着越来越多的客户企业将其运营转移到云端，保护其云工作负载（指所有已部署的应用程序和服务）变得越来越重要。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crowdstrike.com/cybersecurity-101/cloud-security/cloud-workload-protection/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;span 数据-对比=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;云工作负载保护&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt; (CWP) 在此领域非常重要，因为它可确保这些工作负载保持安全并能够抵御越来越多的威胁。&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;335551550&#34;:6,&#34;335551620&#34;:6}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;335551550&#34;:6,&#34;335551620&#34;:6}&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN -IN&#34;&gt;为什么 CWP 至关重要&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p style=&#34;text-align: left;&#34;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;CWP 是不容忽视的必需品。 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;335551550&#34;:6,&#34;335551620&#34;:6}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&#34;auto&#34; lang=&#34;EN-IN&#34;&gt;作为随着云技术的采用不断增长，威胁的规模和复杂性也随之升级。以下是 CWP 至关重要的原因：&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&#34;{&#34;335551550&#34;:6,&#34;335551620&#34;:6}&#34;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing an IaC Platform With Terraform, Ansible, and GitLab】使用 Terraform、Ansible 和 GitLab 实施 IaC 平台</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/implement-an-iac-platform-with-terraform-ansible-gitlab</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;Given the need to create infrastructure across multiple environments while ensuring standardization and effective monitoring, it becomes crucial to provision these environments securely. To achieve this, adopting an immutable infrastructure approach, where environments are provisioned as code, is essential.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;The purpose of this article is to demonstrate a possible approach to achieving this by using GitLab’s structures to enforce templates and standards, Terraform to apply and maintain standards across servers, and Ansible for software provisioning and configuration, utilizing a shared roles model across repositories. To manage the state of machines with Terraform, we use MinIO, as it enables this implementation on-premises.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;鉴于需要跨多个环境创建基础设施，同时确保标准化和有效监控，安全地配置这些环境变得至关重要。为了实现这一目标，采用不可变的基础设施方法（将环境作为代码进行配置）至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p data-selectable-paragraph=&#34;&#34;&gt;本文的目的是演示实现这一目标的可能方法，即使用 GitLab 的结构来强制执行模板和标准，使用 Terraform 跨服务器应用和维护标准，并使用 Ansible 进行软件配置和维护。配置，利用跨存储库的共享角色模型。为了使用 Terraform 管理机器的状态，我们使用 MinIO，因为它可以在本地实现此实现。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bridging the Gap: How Developers and Security Professionals Can Collaborate for Better Cybersecurity】弥合差距：开发人员和安全专业人员如何合作以实现更好的网络安全</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/bridging-the-gap-how-developers-and-security-collaborate</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;In the ever-evolving world of cybersecurity, the relationship between developers and security professionals is crucial. At &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blackhat.com/us-24/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Black Hat 2024&lt;/a&gt;, industry experts shared their insights on how these two groups can work together more effectively to create more secure systems. This article explores key areas where developers and security professionals can improve their collaboration and practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Shifting Left: Security from the Start&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;Several experts emphasized the importance of integrating security earlier in the development process. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/idanplotnik/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Idan Plotnik&lt;/a&gt;, co-founder and CEO of Apiiro, suggests that &#34;developers and security professionals need to focus on integrating &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-firewall-guardrails-to-address-risks&#34;&gt;AI security&lt;/a&gt; into their application security processes.&#34; This approach ensures that security is not an afterthought but an integral part of the development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;在不断发展的网络安全世界中，开发人员和安全专业人员之间的关系至关重要。在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.blackhat.com/us-24/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Black Hat 2024&lt;/a&gt; 上，行业专家分享了他们对这两种技术的见解团队可以更有效地合作来创建更安全的系统。本文探讨了开发人员和安全专业人员可以改进协作和实践的关键领域。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;左移：安全从头开始&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;几位专家强调了在开发过程早期集成安全性的重要性。 Apiiro 联合​​创始人兼首席执行官 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/idanplotnik/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Idan Plotnik&lt;/a&gt; 建议“开发人员和安全专业人员需要专注于将&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/ai-firewall-guardrails-to-address-risks&#34;&gt;人工智能安全&lt;/a&gt;集成到他们的应用程序安全流程中。”这种方法确保安全性不是事后才想到的，而是开发生命周期中不可或缺的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Open Standards for Data Lineage: OpenLineage for Batch and Streaming】数据沿袭的开放标准：用于批处理和流处理的 OpenLineage</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/open-standards-for-data-lineage-openlineage-for-ba</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;One of the greatest wishes of companies is end-to-end visibility in their operational and analytical workflows. Where does data come from? Where does it go? To whom am I giving access to? How can I track data quality issues? The capability to follow the data flow to answer these questions is called &lt;strong&gt;data lineage&lt;/strong&gt;. This blog post explores market trends, efforts to provide an open standard with OpenLineage, and how data governance solutions from vendors such as IBM, Google, Confluent, and Collibra help fulfill the enterprise-wide data governance needs of most companies, including data streaming technologies such as Apache Kafka and Flink.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Data Governance?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data governance refers to the overall management of the availability, usability, integrity, and security of data used in an organization. It involves establishing processes, roles, policies, standards, and metrics to ensure that data is properly managed throughout its lifecycle. Data governance aims to ensure that data is accurate, consistent, secure, and compliant with regulatory requirements and organizational policies. It encompasses activities such as data quality management, data security, metadata management, and compliance with data-related regulations and standards.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;公司最大的愿望之一是其运营和分析工作流程的端到端可见性。数据从哪里来？它去哪里？我向谁授予访问权限？如何跟踪数据质量问题？遵循数据流来回答这些问题的能力称为&lt;strong&gt;数据沿袭&lt;/strong&gt;。这篇博文探讨了市场趋势、通过 OpenLineage 提供开放标准的努力，以及来自 IBM、Google、Confluence 和 Collibra 等供应商的数据治理解决方案如何帮助满足大多数公司的企业级数据治理需求，包括数据流技术例如 Apache Kafka 和 Flink。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是数据治理？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;数据治理是指对组织中使用的数据的可用性、可用性、完整性和安全性的整体管理。它涉及建立流程、角色、政策、标准和指标，以确保数据在其整个生命周期中得到正确管理。数据治理旨在确保数据准确、一致、安全并符合监管要求和组织政策。它涵盖数据质量管理、数据安全、元数据管理以及遵守数据相关法规和标准等活动。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Configuring a Connection Pool】配置连接池</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/configuring-a-connection-pool</link>
      <description>【&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;A connection pooler is a software component that manages database connections. This can help in multiple ways to improve resource utilization, help with load balancing or failover, and can greatly reduce transaction times. In this blog post, we’re going to see what a connection pooler is and how to configure it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What a Connection Pooler Is and Why It’s Useful&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Opening a connection to the database takes many steps. We need to connect to the server and perform the initial handshake, agree on the encryption and connection settings, and then keep the new connection resource across all the layers (network driver, OS layer, database layer, etc.). Each connection consumes memory which size depends on the database engine. For PostgreSQL, this can be even 1.3MB of memory for one connection. Opening a connection also takes time as we need to negotiate the settings of the new connection.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p data-pm-slice=&#34;1 1 []&#34;&gt;连接池程序是管理数据库连接的软件组件。这可以通过多种方式帮助提高资源利用率，帮助实现负载平衡或故障转移，并且可以大大减少事务时间。在这篇博文中，我们将了解什么是连接池以及如何配置它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;什么是连接池以及它为何有用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;打开数据库连接需要许多步骤。我们需要连接到服务器并执行初始握手，同意加密和连接设置，然后在所有层（网络驱动程序、操作系统层、数据库层等）保留新的连接资源。每个连接都会消耗内存，内存大小取决于数据库引擎。对于 PostgreSQL，一个连接甚至可以使用 1.3MB 内存。打开连接也需要时间，因为我们需要协商新连接的设置。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Trust Through &#34;Zero Trust:&#34; Transforming Organizational Security Culture】通过“零信任”建立信任：转变组织安全文化</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/building-security-trust-through-zero-trust</link>
      <description>【&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: The following is an article written for and published in DZone&#39;s 2024 Trend Report,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/link/2024-tr-security-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Enterprise Security: Reinforcing Enterprise Application Defense&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;With organizations increasingly relying on cloud-based services and remote work, the security landscape is becoming more dynamic and challenging than ever before. Cyberattacks and data breaches are on the rise, with high-profile organizations making headlines regularly. These incidents not only cause significant financial loss but also result in irreparable reputational damage and loss of customer trust.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p style=&#34;font-size: 17px;&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;编者注：以下是为 DZone 2024 年趋势报告撰写并发表的文章，&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com /link/2024-tr-security-contributor-article&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;企业安全：加强企业应用程序防御&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;小时&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;随着组织越来越依赖基于云的服务和远程工作，安全形势变得比以往任何时候都更加动态和更具挑战性。网络攻击和数据泄露不断增加，知名组织经常成为头条新闻。这些事件不仅造成重大财务损失，还会造成不可挽回的声誉损害和客户信任的丧失。 &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How We Optimized Read Performance: Readahead, Prefetch, and Cache】我们如何优化读取性能：预读、预取和缓存</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/how-we-optimized-read-performance</link>
      <description>【&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;High-performance computing systems often use all-flash architectures and kernel-mode parallel file systems to satisfy performance demands. However, the increasing sizes of both data volumes and distributed system clusters raise significant cost challenges for all-flash storage and vast operational challenges for kernel clients.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;JuiceFS is a cloud-native distributed file system that operates entirely in user space. It improves I/O throughput substantially through the distributed cache and uses cost-effective object storage for data storage. It’s hence suitable for serving large-scale AI workloads.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;高性能计算系统通常使用全闪存架构和内核模式并行文件系统来满足性能需求。然而，数据量和分布式系统集群规模的不断增加给全闪存存储带来​​了巨大的成本挑战，也给内核客户端带来了巨大的运营挑战。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p dir=&#34;ltr&#34;&gt;JuiceFS 是一个完全在用户空间运行的云原生分布式文件系统。它通过分布式缓存大幅提高I/O吞吐量，并使用经济高效的对象存储进行数据存储。因此，它适合服务大规模人工智能工作负载。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MLOps: How To Build a Toolkit To Boost AI Project Performance】MLOps：如何构建工具包来提高 AI 项目性能</title>
      <link>https://dzone.com/articles/mlops-how-to-build-a-toolkit</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Numerous AI projects launched with promise fail to set sail. This is not usually because of the quality of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;machine learning (ML)&lt;/a&gt; models. Poor implementation and system integration sink &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/mlops-so-ai-can-scale#/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;90% of projects&lt;/a&gt;. Organizations can save their AI endeavors. They should adopt adequate MLOps practices and choose the right set of tools. This article discusses MLOps practices and tools that can save sinking AI projects and boost robust ones, potentially doubling project launch speed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MLOps in a Nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/comparison-of-all-ops&#34;&gt;MLOps&lt;/a&gt; is a mix of machine learning application development (Dev) and operational activities (Ops). It is a set of practices that helps automate and streamline the deployment of ML models. As a result, the entire ML lifecycle becomes standardized.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;众多充满希望的人工智能项目未能起航。这通常不是因为&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/refcardz/machine-learning-predictive&#34;&gt;机器学习 (ML)&lt;/a&gt; 模型的质量。实施和系统集成较差 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mckinsey.com/capability/mckinsey-digital/our-insights/mlops-so-ai-can-scale#/&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; 目标=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;90% 的项目&lt;/a&gt;。组织可以挽救他们的人工智能努力。他们应该采用适当的 MLOps 实践并选择正确的工具集。本文讨论了 MLOps 实践和工具，这些实践和工具可以挽救正在下沉的人工智能项目并促进稳健的项目，从而可能使项目启动速度加倍。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MLOps 概述&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dzone.com/articles/comparison-of-all-ops&#34;&gt;MLOps&lt;/a&gt; 是机器学习应用程序开发 (Dev) 和运营活动 (Ops) 的结合。它是一组有助于自动化和简化 ML 模型部署的实践。因此，整个机器学习生命周期变得标准化。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>