<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>eBPF - The latest news, updates and articles covering eBPF and related topics.</title>
    <link></link>
    <description>eBPF is a revolutionary technology that can run sandboxed programs in the Linux kernel without changing kernel source code or loading a kernel module.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【‍Unleashing the power of frame pointers for profiling pt.2 - Writing a simple profiler】‍释放帧指针的力量进行分析第 2 部分 - 编写一个简单的分析器</title>
      <link>https://blog.maxgio.me/posts/unleashing-power-frame-pointers-writing-simple-continuous-profiler/</link>
      <description>【Learn how to build a simple sampling-based continuous profiler with eBPF】了解如何使用 eBPF 构建简单的基于采样的连续分析器</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍Hello eBPF: A Packet Logger in Pure Java using TC and XDP Hooks (13)】‍Hello eBPF：使用 TC 和 XDP Hooks 的纯 Java 数据包记录器 (13)</title>
      <link>https://levelup.gitconnected.com/part-2-ebpf-map-metrics-prometheus-exporter-fd2e3f12239a</link>
      <description>【The thirteenth installment of the Hello eBPF series. In this part, you’ll learn how to build a packet logger in pure Java using TC and XDP hooks】Hello eBPF 系列的第十三部分。在这一部分中，您将学习如何使用 TC 和 XDP hooks 在纯 Java 中构建数据包记录器</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍How the CrowdStrike Tech Outage Reignited a Battle Over the Heart of Microsoft Systems】‍CrowdStrike 技术中断如何重新点燃了微软系统核心之战</title>
      <link>https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-the-crowdstrike-tech-outage-reignited-a-battle-over-the-heart-of-microsoft-systems-72b62c90</link>
      <description>【Learn how eBPF might have prevented the recent CrowdStrike outage in Windows systems】了解 eBPF 如何阻止最近 Windows 系统中的 CrowdStrike 中断</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍Monitoring Inter-Pod Traffic at the AZ Level with Retina (an eBPF based tool)】‍使用 Retina（基于 eBPF 的工具）监控 AZ 级别的 Pod 间流量</title>
      <link>https://medium.com/@j.aslanov94/monitoring-inter-pod-traffic-at-the-az-level-with-ebpf-based-tool-retina-7a79818e305b</link>
      <description>【Learn what eBPF is, explore the tools available for using it, and implement monitoring for inter-pod traffic using Retina, Kube State Metrics, Prometheus, and Grafana】了解 eBPF 是什么，探索可用于使用它的工具，并使用 Retina、Kube State Metrics、Prometheus 和 Grafana 实施对 Pod 间流量的监控</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍eBPF TLS tracing: The Past, Present and Future】‍eBPF TLS 追踪：过去、现在和未来</title>
      <link>https://blog.px.dev/ebpf-tls-tracing-past-present-future/</link>
      <description>【Explore the TLS tracing tactics used by open source projects, how they&#39;ve evolved to address these unstable user space library interfaces and where the future is headed】探索开源项目使用的 TLS 跟踪策略、它们如何发展以解决这些不稳定的用户空间库接口以及未来的发展方向</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍Challenges and Strategies in eBPF Uprobe Development】‍eBPF Uprobe 开发的挑战与策略</title>
      <link>https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/challenges-strategies-ebpf-uprobe-development-teodor-podobnik-q3vqf/</link>
      <description>【Learn where and how to discover and attach uprobes in the application stack】了解在应用程序堆栈中的位置以及如何发现和附加 uprobe</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍Want to Stop Kernel Panics? Use eBPF】想要阻止内核恐慌吗？使用 eBPF</title>
      <link>https://devops.com/want-to-stop-kernel-panics-use-ebpf/</link>
      <description>【Learn how how eBPF can be used to prevent kernel panics by allowing developers to write kernel-level code that is safer and more controlled】了解如何使用 eBPF 通过允许开发人员编写更安全、更受控制的内核级代码来防止内核恐慌</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍Writing eBPF RawTracepoint Program with Rust Aya】‍用 Rust Aya 编写 eBPF RawTracepoint 程序</title>
      <link>https://yuki-nakamura.com/2024/08/12/writing-ebpf-rawtracepoint-program-with-rust-aya/</link>
      <description>【Learn how to write an eBPF RawTracepoint program using Aya with Rust】了解如何使用 Aya 和 Rust 编写 eBPF RawTracepoint 程序</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍eBPF for Anything!】‍eBPF 无所不能！</title>
      <link>https://isovalent.com/blog/post/ebpf-for-anything/</link>
      <description>【Learn about how eBPF is Turing Complete by implementing Conway’s Game of Life entirely in eBPF】通过完全在 eBPF 中实现康威的生命游戏，了解 eBPF 如何实现图灵完备</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‍eBPF for Security】‍eBPF 安全性</title>
      <link>https://www.sjultra.com/ebpf-for-security/</link>
      <description>【Learn how organizations are using eBPF for security, as a new ubiquitous technology to protect their workloads】了解组织如何使用 eBPF 来确保安全，将其作为一种新的普遍技术来保护其工作负载</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 17:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>