<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</title>
    <link>/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana Labs expands its open source observability community in Japan】Grafana Labs 扩大其在日本的开源可观测性社区</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/26/grafana-labs-expands-its-open-source-observability-community-in-japan/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Whether it&amp;rsquo;s attending community meetups, developing new data sources, or even landing on the moon, the open source observability community in Japan has been an integral part of the larger Grafana community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And with our latest regional expansion, we&amp;rsquo;re excited to see what more the community can achieve. We recently added a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/account-management/regional-availability/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud region in Tokyo&lt;/a&gt; as well as hosted two local meetups — one featuring &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F1BK7H79Gw8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;JAXA&lt;/a&gt; and its successful lunar landing using Grafana and another highlighting the visualization of 130 factories worldwide at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FaarevjZnls&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;DENSO&lt;/a&gt;. Each meetup welcomed more than 100 observability experts and enthusiasts to help foster learning, sharing, and networking within the local open source observability community. The meetups were also streamed online, with hundreds of participants joining in real-time.We&amp;rsquo;ve also updated our website to include resources in Japanese for the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This work aligns with our mission to make Grafana easy to use, no matter where your data (or our users) live. While the magic of open source is that our universal language is code, we are always working on ways to extend our global community, which now has more than 20 million users, and meet them where we are.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But in the end, our real superpower lies in the powerful connections that are made within the open source &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-the-community-behind-the-code/&#34;&gt;Grafana community&lt;/a&gt;. “Every time I have a question or an idea I’ve never tried or Grafana has never tried, we always want to try it together,” says Mikhail Volkov, CEO and founder of Volkov Labs and a longtime Grafana contributor. “You can do whatever you want with Grafana with the help of the community.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When the Grafana community wanted an Amazon CloudWatch data source, it was a community member who responded in 2015. “This was my first time contributing to a big OSS like Grafana,” says Mitsuhiro Tanda, Lead Engineer at GREE, Inc. “The community came together and talked about it together. It was very nice to have built something up together. This is a very Grafana-like way of being a community.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And it has remained that way for &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/02/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-from-one-developers-dream-to-20-million-users-worldwide/&#34;&gt;more than a decade&lt;/a&gt;. When Satoshi Nakahira implemented Grafana into JAXA&amp;rsquo;s systems to help Japan become the fifth country to land on the moon, &amp;ldquo;We were able to build our entire system quite easily and the visualization capability was broad from simple to detailed graphs. We were also able to create dashboards that were well-received and visually impressive,&amp;rdquo; says Satoshi, whose &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/grafana-used-to-monitor-japan-slim-moon-lander/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON session is available to watch on demand&lt;/a&gt;. &amp;ldquo;Thank you very much to the Grafana community.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;无论是参加社区聚会、开发新数据源，甚至登陆月球，日本的开源可观测性社区一直是更大的 Grafana 社区不可或缺的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着我们最新的区域扩张，我们很高兴看到社区能够取得更多成就。我们最近在东京添加了一个 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/account-management/regional-availability/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud 区域&lt;/a&gt;，并举办了两场本地聚会 - 其中一场以 &lt;a href=&#34; https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F1BK7H79Gw8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;JAXA&lt;/a&gt; 及其使用 Grafana 的成功登月，以及另一个重点介绍了全球 130 家工厂的可视化&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FaarevjZnls&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;电装&lt;/a&gt;。每次聚会都会迎来 100 多名可观测性专家和爱好者，帮助促进本地开源可观测性社区内的学习、共享和交流。聚会还在线直播，有数百名参与者实时加入。我们还更新了我们的网站，为社区提供日语资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这项工作符合我们的使命，即让 Grafana 易于使用，无论您的数据（或我们的用户）位于何处。虽然开源的魔力在于我们的通用语言是代码，但我们始终致力于扩展我们的全球社区（该社区现已拥有超过 2000 万用户），并在我们所在的地方与他们见面。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但最终，我们真正的超级力量在于开源内部建立的强大联系&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-the-community -behind-the-code/&#34;&gt;Grafana 社区&lt;/a&gt;。 “每当我有一个问题或一个我从未尝试过的想法或 Grafana 从未尝试过的想法时，我们总是想一起尝试，”Volkov Labs 的首席执行官兼创始人、Grafana 的长期贡献者 Mikhail Volkov 说道。 “在社区的帮助下，你可以使用 Grafana 做任何你想做的事情。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当 Grafana 社区想要 Amazon CloudWatch 数据源时，一位社区成员于 2015 年做出了回应。“这是我第一次为 Grafana 这样的大型 OSS 做出贡献，”GREE, Inc. 的首席工程师 Mitsuhiro Tanda 说道。 “社区聚集在一起，共同讨论这个问题。一起建立一些东西真是太好了。这是一种非常类似于 Grafana 的社区方式。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/02/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-from-one-developers-dream-to-20-million-users- 来说，情况仍然如此-全球/&#34;&gt;十多年&lt;/a&gt;。当 Satoshi Nakahira 在 JAXA 的系统中实施 Grafana 来帮助日本成为第五个登陆月球的国家时，“我们能够非常轻松地构建整个系统，并且可视化功能非常广泛，从简单的图表到详细的图表。我们还能够创建广受好评且视觉效果令人印象深刻的仪表板，”Sat 说道oshi，其&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/grafana-used-to-monitor-japan-slim-moon-lander/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 会议可供点播观看&lt;/a&gt;。 “非常感谢 Grafana 社区。”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana Labs bug bounty: What you need to know about our new partnership with Intigriti】Grafana Labs 漏洞赏金：关于我们与 Intigriti 的新合作伙伴关系，您需要了解哪些信息</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/24/grafana-labs-bug-bounty-what-you-need-to-know-about-our-new-partnership-with-intigriti/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs is happy to announce that we have partnered with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.intigriti.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Intigriti&lt;/a&gt;, a leading bug bounty platform, to expand our &lt;a href=&#34;https://app.intigriti.com/programs/grafanalabs/grafanaossbbp/detail&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;bug bounty program&lt;/a&gt;. This collaboration will enable us to work more effectively with security researchers from around the world in a scalable, sustainable way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moving to a platform that handles initial triage will allow us to focus on valid reports and expand our scope, covering a wider range of Grafana Labs developed products and services. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at how our new partnership with intigriti will work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;faq-what-you-need-to-know&#34;&gt;FAQ: What you need to know&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-scope-of-the-new-program&#34;&gt;What is the scope of the new program?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, the eligible projects are &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/&#34;&gt;Grafana OSS&lt;/a&gt; and our other open source backends (&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/pyroscope/&#34;&gt;Grafana Pyroscope&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/&#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt;), but this relaunch allows us to progressively launch additional programs for new and existing products in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-the-submission-requirements&#34;&gt;What are the submission requirements?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will accept valid security vulnerabilities that exist in the latest released version of the products that are listed in scope. All eligible submissions must prove a security impact, and we reward based on the described impact in the submission provided by the researcher.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any current or former (in the last 12 months) Grafana Labs employees and contractors are not permitted to participate in this program.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-happens-after-i-submit-a-reward-eligible-vulnerability-report&#34;&gt;What happens after I submit a reward-eligible vulnerability report?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Intigriti’s triage team will perform an initial assessment of the submission before we review it, meaning they will verify that the vulnerability is in scope, is not a duplicate, and is reproducible. If those criteria are met, we (Grafana Labs) will perform a second round of reviews. This second round is intended to assess whether we already know about the issue internally or whether it’s intentional functionality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the submission is eligible for a reward, we will assess the severity based on the impact described in the report. We follow the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3.1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CVSS 3.1 scoring system&lt;/a&gt;, so we will map bounties to a calculated CVSS score. If the report is of greater quality, we might offer a bonus bounty to incentivize clear and detailed reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-grafana-labs-response-time-to-submissions&#34;&gt;What is Grafana Labs&amp;rsquo; response time to submissions?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After Intigriti has validated the submission, Grafana Labs will respond within the following timelines:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vulnerability Severity&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time to validate (working days)&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Exceptional&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;2&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Critical&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;2&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;High&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;5&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Medium&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;15&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Low&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;15&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once a submission has been assigned to us, we will typically respond to it within two business days. We will reward on triage, meaning we will send the bounty regardless if the fix is published or not, as long as we have sufficient information to assess the impact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-payment-structure-for-bounties&#34;&gt;What is the payment structure for bounties?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will continue to offer top-tier and market competitive bounties. We used &lt;a href=&#34;https://bountycalculator.intigriti.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Intigriti’s bug bounty calculator&lt;/a&gt; to calculate bounty levels that are above the industry median.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity &lt;/strong&gt;(CVSS 3.1)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Bounty&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maximum Bounty&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Low&lt;/strong&gt; (0.1 - 3.9)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;100 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;500 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Medium&lt;/strong&gt; (3.9 - 6.9)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;500 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;2,000 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High&lt;/strong&gt; (7.0 - 8.9)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;2,000 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;7,500 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Critical&lt;/strong&gt; (9.0 - 9.4)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;7,500 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;10,000 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exceptional&lt;/strong&gt; (9.5 - 10.0)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;10,000 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;15,000 USD&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-are-bounties-paid-out&#34;&gt;How are bounties paid out?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All bounties will be paid out directly via the Intigriti platform. If the researcher wants to transfer the funds to their personal bank account, it usually takes three to five business days, &lt;a href=&#34;https://kb.intigriti.com/en/articles/3379564-payout-lifecycle&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;according to Intigriti.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;will-grafana-labs-still-be-transparent-with-its-program&#34;&gt;Will Grafana Labs still be transparent with its program?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, it is not possible to publish submissions on Intigriti. However, for all open source products that are in scope, we will assign a CVE. That CVE will be published in our &lt;a href=&#34;/security/security-advisories/&#34;&gt;CVE database&lt;/a&gt;, where we will provide detailed information about the vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For all published CVEs, we will continue to ask the researcher if they want to be credited in our &lt;a href=&#34;/security/hall-of-fame/&#34;&gt;Security Hall of Fame&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned-from-self-hosting&#34;&gt;Lessons learned from self-hosting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that you&amp;rsquo;re up to speed on our changes, I want to briefly reflect on our what we learned from self hosting, for the sake of transparency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Initially, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/05/04/introducing-the-grafana-labs-bug-bounty-program/&#34;&gt;we thought self-hosting was the right choice&lt;/a&gt;. We wanted full control from start to finish, allowing us to have generous response times, pay on triage, and build a strong security community. And there were a fair share of positives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was great to build those relationships, and the triage process also helped us understand our scope and products better. As security engineers, we have the best understanding of our products&amp;rsquo; threat models. This insight helped us identify issues that initially seemed out of scope but could still provide significant security improvements for our products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, we ran into a number of issues that ultimately led us to make this change. For starters, there weren&amp;rsquo;t any well-maintained open source bug bounty platforms, so we had to build a bunch of workarounds in GitHub to keep the program running as we scaled. We also spent most of our time triaging reports that were clearly out of scope or invalid, and we lacked the reach of a major bug bounty platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moving the program to Intigriti will help us scale and improve the program going forward. If you have any questions regarding the bug bounty programs, feel free to join our public &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.slack.com/archives/C078V3T4AA0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Slack channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs 很高兴地宣布，我们已与领先的 Intigriti 合作伙伴 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.intigriti.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Intigriti&lt;/a&gt;错误赏金平台，以扩展我们的&lt;a href=&#34;https://app.intigriti.com/programs/grafanalabs/grafanaossbbp/detail&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;错误赏金计划&lt;/a&gt;。此次合作将使我们能够以可扩展、可持续的方式与世界各地的安全研究人员更有效地合作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;迁移到处理初始分类的平台将使我们能够专注于有效报告并扩大我们的范围，涵盖更广泛的 Grafana Labs 开发的产品和服务。让我们看看我们与 intigriti 的新合作伙伴关系将如何运作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;faq-what-you-need-to-know&#34;&gt;常见问题解答：您需要了解的内容&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the-scope-of-the-new-program&#34;&gt;新计划的范围是什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，符合条件的项目是 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/&#34;&gt;Grafana OSS&lt;/a&gt; 和我们的其他开源后端 (&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; 、&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/pyrscope/&#34;&gt;Grafana Pyrscope&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/ &#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt;），但这次重新启动使我们能够在未来逐步为新产品和现有产品推出其他计划。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-the-submission-requirements&#34;&gt;提交要求是什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将接受范围中所列产品的最新发布版本中存在的有效安全漏洞。所有符合条件的提交内容都必须证明具有安全影响，我们将根据研究人员提供的提交内容中所描述的影响进行奖励。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;任何现任或前任（过去 12 个月内）Grafana Labs 员工和承包商均不得参与此计划。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-happens-after-i-submit-a-reward-eligible-vulnerability-report&#34;&gt;提交符合奖励资格的漏洞报告后会发生什么？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Intigriti 的分类团队将在我们审核提交之前对提交的内容进行初步评估，这意味着他们将验证漏洞是否在范围内、不重复且可重现。如果满足这些标准，我们（Grafana Labs）将进行第二轮审核。第二轮旨在评估我们是否已经在内部了解该问题或者它是否是有意的功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果提交的内容有资格获得奖励，我们将根据报告中描述的影响评估其严重性。我们遵循 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.first.org/cvss/calculator/3.1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CVSS 3.1 评分系统&lt;/a&gt;，因此我们将映射赏金计算出的 CVSS 分数。如果报告质量更高，我们可能会提供奖金，以激励清晰详细的报告。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-grafana-labs-response-time-to-submissions&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs 对提交内容的响应时间是多少？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Intigriti 验证提交后上，Grafana Labs 将在以下时间内回复：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;表&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;漏洞严重性&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;验证时间（工作日）&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;出色&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;2&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;严重&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;2&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;高&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;5&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;中&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;15&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;低&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;15&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/表&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将提交内容分配给我们后，我们通常会在两个工作日内予以回复。我们将根据分类进行奖励，这意味着无论修复是否发布，只要我们有足够的信息来评估影响，我们都会发送赏金。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-the- payment-struct-for-bounties&#34;&gt;赏金的支付结构是怎样的？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将继续提供顶级且具有市场竞争力的奖金。我们使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://bountycalculator.intigriti.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Intigriti 的错误赏金计算器&lt;/a&gt;来计算高于行业中位数的赏金水平。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;表&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;严重性&lt;/strong&gt;(CVSS 3.1)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;最低赏金&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;最高赏金&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;低&lt;/strong&gt;（0.1 - 3.9）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;100 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;500 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;中&lt;/strong&gt; (3.9 - 6.9)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;500 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;2,000 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高&lt;/strong&gt; (7.0 - 8.9)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;2,000 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;7,500 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;严重&lt;/strong&gt; (9.0 - 9.4)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;7,500 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;10,000 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;出色&lt;/strong&gt; (9.5 - 10.0)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;10,000 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;15,000 美元&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/表&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-are-bounties-paid-out&#34;&gt;赏金如何支付？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所有赏金将直接通过 Intigriti 平台支付。如果研究人员想将资金转入个人银行账户，通常需要三到五个工作日，&lt;a href=&#34;https://kb.intigriti.com/en/articles/3379564-payout-lifecycle&#34; target= &#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;根据 Intigriti 的说法。&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;will-grafana-labs-still-be-transparent-with-its-program&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs 的计划仍将保持透明吗？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，无法在 Intigriti 上发布提交内容。但是，对于范围内的所有开源产品，我们将分配一个 CVE。该 CVE 将发布在我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/security/security-advisories/&#34;&gt;CVE 数据库&lt;/a&gt;中，我们将在其中提供有关该漏洞的详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于所有已发布的 CVE，我们将继续询问研究人员是否希望被列入我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/security/hall-of-fame/&#34;&gt;安全名人堂&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned-from-self-hosting&#34;&gt;从自托管中学到的经验教训&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;既然您已经了解了我们的变化，为了保持透明度，我想简要回顾一下我们从自托管中学到的东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/05/04/introducing-the-grafana-labs-bug-bounty-program/&#34;&gt;我们认为自托管是正确的选择&lt;/a&gt;。我们希望从开始到结束都有完全的控制权，让我们有足够的响应时间，按分类付费，并建立了一个强大的安全社区，并且取得了相当多的积极成果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;建立这些关系真是太好了，分类流程也帮助我们更好地了解我们的范围和产品。作为安全工程师，我们最了解我们产品的威胁模型。这种洞察帮助我们发现了最初看似超出范围的问题，但仍然可以为我们的产品提供重大的安全改进。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，我们遇到了许多问题，最终导致我们做出了这一改变。对于初学者来说，没有任何维护良好的开源错误赏金平台，因此我们必须在 GitHub 中构建一堆解决方法，以保持程序在我们扩展时运行。我们还花费了大部分时间对明显超出范围或无效的报告进行分类，并且我们缺乏主要的错误赏金平台的覆盖范围。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将该计划转移到 Intigriti 将帮助我们扩展和改进该计划。如果您对错误赏金计划有任何疑问，请随时加入我们的公共 &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.slack.com/archives/C078V3T4AA0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Slack 频道&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Mux cut metrics volume by 60%, increased retention times, and improved developer productivity with Grafana Cloud】Mux 如何利用 Grafana Cloud 将指标量减少 60%、延长保留时间并提高开发人员生产力</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/22/how-mux-cut-metrics-volume-by-60-increased-retention-times-and-improved-developer-productivity-with-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Every time the platform engineering team at San Francisco-based startup &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mux.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Mux&lt;/a&gt; deploys new software, there are two must-have components: proper access controls and observability. But until recently, their observability stack left the team frustrated, reactive, and largely in maintenance mode.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The company operates an API-first video platform designed to give development teams world-class video streaming and analytics capabilities, which means they need to scale dynamically to accommodate the unpredictable usage demands for very compute-, network- and storage-intensive workloads. Couple that with the wide variety of user-generated content on the platform and the unique troubleshooting that comes with it, and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to understand why Mux needs fine-grain visibility into their workloads and a system that properly supports it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1074px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Live video stream sample&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1074&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;566&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*A sample of live video streams routing across Mux&amp;#39;s infrastructure. Grafana’s “single pane of glass” allows Mux to aggregate telemetry from any number of clusters and display it using multiple visualization methods.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Live video stream sample&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1074&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;566&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*A sample of live video streams routing across Mux&amp;#39;s infrastructure. Grafana’s “single pane of glass” allows Mux to aggregate telemetry from any number of clusters and display it using multiple visualization methods.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A sample of live video streams routing across Mux&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure. Grafana’s “single pane of glass” allows Mux to aggregate telemetry from any number of clusters and display it using multiple visualization methods.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;All the clusters need observability; all the applications need observability. Whenever we deploy new infrastructure, the first thing we put in there is access and observability — and that creates the sprawl that multiplied as we continued to grow,&amp;rdquo; says Brian Lieberman, Senior Software Engineer at Mux.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So after struggling for years to maintain an in-house OSS stack (Elasticsearch, Kibana, Prometheus, Jaeger, Grafana), they knew it was time for a change. They went with Grafana Cloud, in part because of their existing familiarity with Grafana OSS, but the payoff has been a lot more than just an easy onramp.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They&amp;rsquo;ve cut their metrics volume by 60% while also greatly expanding their data retention time, going from seven days to 30 days for traces and from 14 days to 13 months for metrics. This has helped Mux reduce noise, improve long-term analysis, and take to a more proactive approach to incident management — all while keeping their costs level and their engineers engaged with more high-impact work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Grafana Cloud probably saves us hundreds of engineering hours a year. Our platform engineers don&amp;rsquo;t have to manage the stack any more, and our product engineers don&amp;rsquo;t have to work through multiple observability tools, which used to really slow down our response times,&amp;rdquo; said Ryan Grothouse, VP, Engineering at Mux.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We recently sat down with members of the Mux platform engineering team to learn more about how they&amp;rsquo;re using Grafana Cloud for metrics, logs, and traces – and how they plan to extend their stack in Grafana Cloud with Grafana Cloud K6, Grafana IRM, Grafana SLOs, and Grafana Cloud Profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 2400px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Head shots of the four interviewees from Mux&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;2400&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1148&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Head shots of the four interviewees from Mux&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;2400&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1148&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can you tell us about the problems you were running into with your previous observability setup?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ryan Grothouse, VP, Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;: Our product engineers were jumping across multiple instances to correlate and pinpoint observability across them. It was not only frustrating, but it often slowed mean time to resolution and probably led to us missing a lot of things because of context switching.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ron Lipke, Senior Engineering Manager&lt;/strong&gt;: Doing anything across products was nearly impossible because that data was so fragmented and we didn&amp;rsquo;t have anything that was federated for our developers to go and get that insight. We were doing stuff like exporting to CSVs and then ingesting them back into Kibana — hacky stuff that was not fun.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What were some of the immediate benefits that stood out when you switched to Grafana Cloud?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ron&lt;/strong&gt;: UX improvement for our developers. Some of the immediate feedback was just like, &amp;ldquo;Wow, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to go across all of these individual URLs and logins. I can just flip a cluster label and I can see all these things!&amp;rdquo; Also, the retention time was mind blowing for everybody because it really allowed us to do more long-term trend analysis and it even helped our incident management postmortems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyle Weaver, Staff Software Engineer:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintenance as well. It would be a lot more toil on our team to ensure the correct scale and configuration on the compute side.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1098px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1098&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;665&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*Being able to see detailed information about a single asset using dynamic dashboard queries allows product teams to quickly address potential performance issues or customer concerns.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1098&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;665&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*Being able to see detailed information about a single asset using dynamic dashboard queries allows product teams to quickly address potential performance issues or customer concerns.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Being able to see detailed information about a single asset using dynamic dashboard queries allows product teams to quickly address potential performance issues or customer concerns.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And you&amp;rsquo;ve relied a lot on &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/metrics/prometheus-cardinality-optimization/&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt;, our cardinality optimization tool, right?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyle:&lt;/strong&gt; Adaptive Metrics is an amazing feature. It not only saves us hundreds of thousands of dollars a year but it&amp;rsquo;s also a forcing function for us to look closely at our metrics to find additional opportunities for time series reduction and cardinality improvements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ron&lt;/strong&gt;: We used to spend a lot of time reacting to alerts, and less time being proactive and thinking about how we use our metrics. Now it&amp;rsquo;s fun to see developers being mindful when they make changes or add a new service and how that will impact metrics for our billing purposes. It&amp;rsquo;s really changed our mentality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At Mux, your team builds most things in-house. How do you weigh decisions about when to invest in a hosted solution instead?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ryan&lt;/strong&gt;: We want to maintain flexibility within our stack so we&amp;rsquo;re not locked in to any given vendor and we can evolve and adapt with the needs of the business. But there are certain areas where that isn&amp;rsquo;t valuable, and observability is one of those. If we can free people from managing those types of problems, then they can dedicate more time to driving business and product value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud was a really natural pivot for us since we were already orchestrated with the open source version, so it was actually a pretty easy transition. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have to do a lot of refactoring. So the decision to go with a hosted solution is really about the cost of doing it ourselves and the pain that that imposes on us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana SLO is another tool in Grafana Cloud that you&amp;rsquo;re looking to adopt. Can you tell us more about that?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ron&lt;/strong&gt;: That&amp;rsquo;s a consolidation effort as well. We use other vendors and moving SLOs in-house to Grafana Cloud just makes sense for us — one, for the cost, and two, it&amp;rsquo;s just easier to use and manage since we&amp;rsquo;re already on the platform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ryan&lt;/strong&gt;: With Grafana SLO, we can leverage the same sort of metrics that we&amp;rsquo;re leveraging elsewhere and just layer SLOs on top of that. We don&amp;rsquo;t have to wire that up in any other way; the tools just naturally perform better together. And there&amp;rsquo;s a common user experience, which makes it a lot easier on everyone involved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve been working in Grafana Cloud for a while, what other benefits have you seen?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ryan&lt;/strong&gt;: We never really quantified MTTR before and after, but the general sentiment is that it has absolutely sped up. Still, I can share one concrete example. With our old retention times, there were many times when we would get a support case and we&amp;rsquo;d have to tell the customer that we no longer had that data to troubleshoot the issue. That wasn&amp;rsquo;t an acceptable answer for our customers, and thankfully that&amp;rsquo;s no longer a problem for us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brian&lt;/strong&gt;: It&amp;rsquo;s allowed us to move away from treading water with our stack. It used to be about keeping it running. And usually we were on old versions of everything; nobody wanted to upgrade because the further you fall behind, the harder it gets and the more time it takes. By allowing developers to move faster, identify problems really quickly, and even proactively do it themselves — that shift allows us all to get to a much better place, and it just makes life better.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;每次旧金山初创公司的平台工程团队 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mux.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Mux&lt;/a&gt; 部署新的软件有两个必须具备的组件：适当的访问控制和可观察性。但直到最近，他们的可观察性堆栈还让团队感到沮丧、反应迟钝，并且很大程度上处于维护模式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该公司运营着一个 API 优先的视频平台，旨在为开发团队提供世界一流的视频流和分析功能，这意味着他们需要动态扩展，以适应计算、网络和存储密集型的不可预测的使用需求工作负载。再加上平台上各种各样的用户生成内容以及随之而来的独特故障排除，就很容易理解为什么 Mux 需要对其工作负载进行细粒度的可见性以及正确支持它的系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1074px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png？w = 320 320w，/media/blog/ mux-success/rtmp-streams.png？w=550 550w，/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png？w=750 750w，/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png？ w=900 900w，/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png？w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png？w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/ mux-成功/rtmp-streams.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-size=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;实时视频流示例&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1074”&#xA;高度=“566”&#xA;title=&#34;*跨 Mux 基础设施路由的实时视频流示例。Grafana 的“单一管理平台”允许 Mux 聚合来自任意数量集群的遥测数据，并使用多种可视化方法显示它。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/mux-success/rtmp-streams.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;实时视频流示例&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1074”&#xA;高度=“566”&#xA;title=&#34;*跨 Mux 基础设施路由的实时视频流示例。Grafana 的“单一管理平台”允许 Mux 聚合来自任意数量集群的遥测数据，并使用多种可视化方法显示它。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;跨 Mux 基础设施路由的实时视频流示例。 Grafana 的“单一管理平台”允许 Mux 聚合来自任意数量集群的遥测数据，并使用多种可视化方法进行显示。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“所有集群都需要可观察性；所有的应用程序都需要可观察性。每当我们部署新的基础设施时，我们首先要做的就是访问和可观察性，这会导致随着我们的不断发展而成倍的蔓延。”Brian 说道Lieberman，Mux 高级软件工程师。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，在努力维护内部 OSS 堆栈（Elasticsearch、Kibana、Prometheus、Jaeger、Grafana）多年之后，他们知道是时候做出改变了。他们选择了 Grafana Cloud，部分原因是他们对 Grafana OSS 已经很熟悉，但回报远不止是一个简单的入门。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他们将指标量减少了 60%，同时还大大延长了数据保留时间，跟踪从 7 天延长到 30 天，指标从 14 天延长到 13 个月。这帮助 Mux 降低了噪音、改进了长期分析，并采取了更主动的事件管理方法，同时保持了成本水平并让工程师参与了更具影响力的工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Grafana Cloud 每年可能为我们节省数百个工程时间。我们的平台工程师不必再管理堆栈，我们的产品工程师也不必使用多种可观察性工具，这些工具过去确实会减慢我们的响应时间，”Mux 工程副总裁 Ryan Grothouse 说道。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们最近与 Mux 平台工程团队的成员进行了座谈，详细了解他们如何使用 Grafana Cloud 来获取指标、日志和跟踪，以及他们计划如何使用 Grafana Cloud K6 扩展 Grafana Cloud 中的堆栈， Grafana IRM、Grafana SLO 和 Grafana Cloud 配置文件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：2400px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=320 320w，/media/blog/ mux-success/mux-team.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png？ w=900 900w，/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png？w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png？w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/ mux-成功/mux-team.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Mux 的四位受访者的头像&#34;&#xA;宽度=“2400”&#xA;高度=“1148”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/mux-success/mux-team.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Mux 的四位受访者的头像&#34;&#xA;宽度=“2400”&#xA;高度=“1148”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您能告诉我们您之前的可观察性设置遇到的问题吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ryan Grothouse，工程副总裁&lt;/strong&gt;：我们的产品工程师跨越多个实例来关联并精确定位它们的可观察性。这不仅令人沮丧，而且常常会减慢解决问题的平均时间，并且可能会因为上下文切换而导致我们错过很多事情。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ron Lipke，高级工程经理&lt;/strong&gt;：跨产品做任何事情几乎是不可能的，因为数据是如此分散，我们没有任何东西可以让我们的开发人员联合起来获得洞察力。我们正在做一些事情，比如导出到 CSV，然后将它们提取回 Kibana - 一些不好玩的黑客行为。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;当您切换到 Grafana Cloud 时，有哪些直接的好处？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ron&lt;/strong&gt;：为我们的开发人员改进用户体验。一些即时反馈就像是，“哇，我不必检查所有这些单独的 URL 和登录信息。我只需翻转一个簇标签，就能看到所有这些东西！”此外，保留时间对每个人来说都是令人兴奋的，因为它确实使我们能够进行更多的长期趋势分析，甚至有助于我们的事件管理事后分析。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyle Weaver，高级软件工程师：&lt;/strong&gt; 维护也是如此。为了确保计算端的正确规模和配置，我们的团队需要付出更多的努力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1098px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png？w = 320 320w，/媒体/博客/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png？w=550 550w，/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png？w=750 750w，/media/blog/mux-成功/ingest-job-logs.png？w=900 900w，/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png？w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-日志.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=“auto”alt=“Grafana 仪表板”&#xA;宽度=“1098”&#xA;高度=“665”&#xA;title=&#34;*能够使用动态仪表板查询查看有关单个资产的详细信息，使产品团队能够快速解决潜在的性能问题或客户担忧。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/mux-success/ingest-job-logs.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1098”&#xA;高度=“665”&#xA;title=&#34;*能够使用动态仪表板查询查看有关单个资产的详细信息，使产品团队能够快速解决潜在的性能问题或客户担忧。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;能够使用动态仪表板查询查看有关单个资产的详细信息，使产品团队能够快速解决潜在的性能问题或客户疑虑。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/图标题&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您非常依赖我们的基数优化工具&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/metrics/prometheus-cardinality-optimization/&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/a&gt;，对吗？&lt;/强&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kyle：&lt;/strong&gt;自适应指标是一项了不起的功能。它不仅每年为我们节省数十万美元，这也是我们仔细研究指标以寻找时间序列缩减和基数改进的其他机会的强制功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ron&lt;/strong&gt;：我们过去花费大量时间对警报做出反应，而很少花时间主动思考如何使用指标。现在，很有趣的是看到开发人员在进行更改或添加新服务时保持警惕，以及这将如何影响我们的计费目的指标。这确实改变了我们的心态。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在 Mux，您的团队在内部构建大部分内容。您如何权衡何时投资托管解决方案？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ryan&lt;/strong&gt;：我们希望保持堆栈的灵活性，这样我们就不会被任何给定的供应商所束缚，并且我们可以根据业务需求进行发展和适应。但在某些领域，这没有价值，可观察性就是其中之一。如果我们能让人们摆脱处理这些类型的问题，那么他们就可以投入更多时间来推动业务和产品价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 对我们来说是一个非常自然的枢纽，因为我们已经使用开源版本进行了精心策划，所以这实际上是一个非常简单的过渡。我们不必进行大量重构。因此，决定采用托管解决方案实际上是考虑到我们自己这样做的成本以及这给我们带来的痛苦。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana SLO 是您希望采用的 Grafana Cloud 中的另一个工具。您能告诉我们更多相关信息吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;罗恩&lt;/strong&gt;：这也是一项整合工作。我们使用其他供应商并将内部 SLO 迁移到 Grafana Cloud 对我们来说很有意义 - 一是为了成本，二是因为我们已经在这个平台上，所以更容易使用和管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ryan&lt;/strong&gt;：借助 Grafana SLO，我们可以利用在其他地方使用的同类指标，并在此基础上叠加 SLO。我们不需要以任何其他方式连接它；这些工具在一起自然会表现得更好。而且有共同的用户体验，这使得每个参与者都更容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;现在您已经在 Grafana Cloud 中工作了一段时间，您还看到了哪些其他好处？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ryan&lt;/strong&gt;：我们从未真正量化过前后的 MTTR，但总体感觉是它绝对加速了。不过，我可以分享一个具体的例子。由于我们以前的保留时间，很多时候当我们收到支持案例时，我们必须告诉客户我们不再有这些数据来解决问题。对于我们的客户来说，这不是一个可以接受的答案，值得庆幸的是，这对我们来说不再是问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brian&lt;/strong&gt;：它让我们摆脱了堆栈的原地踏步。它曾经是为了保持它的运行。通常我们使用的都是旧版本；无人你想要升级，因为你落后得越远，难度就越大，花费的时间也就越多。通过允许开发人员更快地采取行动，快速发现问题，甚至主动自己动手，这种转变让我们所有人都能到达更好的地方，并且让生活变得更美好。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to set up Grafana Mimir using Ansible】如何使用 Ansible 设置 Grafana Mimir</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/23/how-to-set-up-grafana-mimir-using-ansible/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ansible.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gerard van Engelen is a seasoned DevOps engineer who ensures the quality of products by drawing parallels between complex issues and simpler, everyday scenarios. This approach helps in delivering value, ensuring that products are not only built correctly but also offer the right functionalities.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ansible.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Ansible&lt;/a&gt; is popular with system administrators and DevOps professionals who use it for automating IT tasks such as configuration management, application deployment, and orchestration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since 2022, Grafana Labs has supported Ansible users through its&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/infrastructure-as-code/ansible/&#34;&gt; Grafana Ansible collection&lt;/a&gt;. With Grafana, OpenTelemetry Collector, Grafana Alloy, and modules for provisioning Grafana resources, the Ansible collection is there to help Grafana Administrators. And now we’ve added &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt; deployments to support Mimir configurations as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this guide we’ll walk you through how to use the &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; role with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Ansible collection&lt;/a&gt; to deploy and manage Mimir across multiple Linux hosts. We’ll then show you how to explore your data in Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;before-you-begin&#34;&gt;Before you begin&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get started, you should have the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 Linux hosts with SSH access and sufficient permissions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ansible installed on your base system&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;install-the-grafana-ansible-collection&#34;&gt;Install the Grafana Ansible collection&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection/tree/main/roles/mimir&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Mimir role&lt;/a&gt; is available in the Grafana Ansible collection as of the 5.0.0 release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To install the Grafana Ansible collection, run this command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;ansible-galaxy collection install grafana.grafana:4.0.0&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;create-an-ansible-inventory-file&#34;&gt;Create an Ansible inventory file&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, you will set up your hosts and create an inventory file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create an Ansible inventory file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An Ansible inventory, which resides in a file named &lt;code&gt;inventory&lt;/code&gt;, lists each host IP on a separate line, like this (3 hosts shown):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;146.190.208.216 # hostname = mimir-01&#xA;146.190.208.190 # hostname = mimir-02&#xA;146.190.208.190 # hostname = mimir-03&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; If you are copying the above file, remove the comments (#).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create an &lt;code&gt;ansible.cfg&lt;/code&gt; file within the same directory as &lt;code&gt;inventory&lt;/code&gt;, with the following values:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;[defaults]&#xA;inventory = inventory # Path to the inventory file&#xA;private_key_file = ~/.ssh/id_rsa # Path to my private SSH Key&#xA;remote_user=root&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-the-mimir-ansible-role&#34;&gt;Use the Mimir Ansible role&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next you will create an Ansible playbook that calls the &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; role from the &lt;code&gt;grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt; Ansible collection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To use the Mimir Ansible role:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, create a file named &lt;code&gt;deploy-mimir.yml&lt;/code&gt; in the same directory as &lt;code&gt;ansible.cfg&lt;/code&gt; and inventory and add the configuration below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just like other roles, Mimir is now available via &lt;a href=&#34;https://galaxy.ansible.com/ui/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Ansible Galaxy&lt;/a&gt;. You can install the collection using the command below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;ansible-galaxy collection install grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the collection is installed, you can use the &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; role in your playbook like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;- hosts: all&#xA;roles:&#xA;- role: grafana.grafana.mimir&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This way, Ansible knows to look for the &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; role within the &lt;code&gt;grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt; collection. Ensure your Ansible configuration and version support collections, as this feature was introduced in Ansible 2.9.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;configuring-mimir-using-the-ansible-collection&#34;&gt;Configuring Mimir using the Ansible collection&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Mimir role is highly configurable due to the config templating. If you want to run Mimir in HA, just add the following vars to your playbook:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;- name: Install Mimir&#xA;hosts: all&#xA;become: true&#xA;tasks:&#xA;- name: Install Mimir&#xA;ansible.builtin.include_role:&#xA;name: grafana.grafana.mimir&#xA;vars:&#xA;mimir_storage:&#xA;# You can use different object store backends, use Minio for local development&#xA;storage:&#xA;backend: s3&#xA;s3:&#xA;endpoint: {{ endpoint }}&#xA;access_key_id: {{ acces_key_id }}&#xA;secret_access_key: {{ secret_acces_key }}&#xA;insecure: true # False when using https&#xA;bucket_name: mimir&#xA;# Blocks storage requires a prefix when using a common object storage bucket.&#xA;mimir_blocks_storage:&#xA;storage_prefix: blocks&#xA;tsdb:&#xA;dir: &amp;#34;{{ mimir_working_path}}/ingester&amp;#34;&#xA;# Use memberlist, a gossip-based protocol, to enable the 3 Mimir replicas to communicate&#xA;mimir_memberlist:&#xA;join_members:&#xA;- mimir-01:7946&#xA;- mimir-02:7946&#xA;- mimir-03::7946&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The playbook calls the &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; role from the &lt;code&gt;grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt; Ansible collection. The Mimir configuration in this playbook installs Mimir on three hosts, makes sure the hosts communicate with each other, and enables use of the object storage backend.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection/tree/main/roles/mimir#role-variables&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Ansible documentation&lt;/a&gt; to understand the other variables you can pass to the &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To run the playbook, run this command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;ansible-playbook deploy-mimir.yml&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: You can place the &lt;code&gt;deploy-mimir.yml&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;ansible.cfg&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;inventory&lt;/code&gt; files in different directories based on your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;check-that-metrics-are-available-in-mimir&#34;&gt;Check that metrics are available in Mimir&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since we’re running Mimir in HA by replication, you’ll need to set up your own load balancing to be able to use Mimir to its full potential. If you’ve set up load balancing, you’ll be able to add your datasource in Grafana using your selected hostname.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To check metrics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Find the Explore section.&lt;/strong&gt; Look for the Explore icon (it looks like a compass) on the left-side vertical navigation bar in Grafana and click it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Select Your Prometheus data source.&lt;/strong&gt; At the top of the page, there’s a dropdown menu. Use it to pick the Prometheus data source you’ve added.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Run a test query.&lt;/strong&gt; Type in the query&lt;code&gt;{name=&amp;quot;mimir-01&amp;quot;}&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check metrics&lt;/strong&gt;. After running the query, if you see a graph and a table with data (similar to the example shown in the image below), it means your metrics are correctly being fetched and displayed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explore additional metrics.&lt;/strong&gt; Explore other metrics—like CPU load, memory usage, disk I/O, network bandwidth—and create dashboards to gain insights into your system’s performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you don’t see any data, it could mean that metrics aren’t being collected as expected. To troubleshoot, check the status of your Mimir service by running this command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;sudo systemctl status mimir.service&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the Mimir service isn’t running, there might be an issue with the configuration syntax, or you might need to debug further. For help with this, take a look at the documentation available on &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/configure/&#34;&gt;configuring Mimir&lt;/a&gt; correctly.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ansible.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gerard van Engelen 是一位经验丰富的 DevOps 工程师，负责确保质量通过在复杂的问题和更简单的日常场景之间进行比较来分析产品。这种方法有助于交付价值，确保产品不仅能够正确构建，而且能够提供正确的功能。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ansible.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Ansible&lt;/a&gt; 深受系统管理员和 DevOps 专业人员的欢迎，他们使用它来实现 IT 自动化配置管理、应用程序部署和编排等任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自 2022 年以来，Grafana Labs 通过其&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/infrastruct-as-code/ansible/&#34;&gt;Grafana Ansible 集合&lt;/a&gt;为 Ansible 用户提供支持。通过 Grafana、OpenTelemetry Collector、Grafana Alloy 以及用于配置 Grafana 资源的模块，Ansible 集合可以为 Grafana 管理员提供帮助。现在，我们添加了 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt; 部署来支持 Mimir 配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本指南中，我们将引导您了解如何将 &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; 角色与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection&#34; target= 结合使用&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Ansible 集合&lt;/a&gt;，用于跨多个 Linux 主机部署和管理 Mimir。然后，我们将向您展示如何在 Grafana 中探索数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;before-you-begin&#34;&gt;开始之前&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要开始使用，您应该具备以下条件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 台具有 SSH 访问权限和足够权限的 Linux 主机&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ansible 安装在您的基础系统上&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;install-the-grafana-ansible-collection&#34;&gt;安装 Grafana Ansible 集合&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection/tree/main/roles/mimir&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Mimir 角色&lt;/a &gt; 自 5.0.0 版本起可在 Grafana Ansible 系列中使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要安装 Grafana Ansible 集合，请运行以下命令：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;ansible-galaxy 集合安装 grafana.grafana:4.0.0&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;create-an-ansible-inventory-file&#34;&gt;创建 Ansible 库存文件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，您将设置主机并创建清单文件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;创建 Ansible 库存文件。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ansible 清单位于名为 &lt;code&gt;inventory&lt;/code&gt; 的文件中，在单独的行上列出每个主机 IP，如下所示（显示 3 个主机）：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;146.190.208.216 # 主机名 = mimir-01&#xA;146.190.208.190 # 主机名 = mimir-02&#xA;146.190.208.190 # 主机名 = mimir-03&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;如果您要复制上述文件，请删除注释 (#)。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol开始=“2”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在与 &lt;code&gt;inventory&lt;/code&gt; 相同的目录中创建一个 &lt;code&gt;ansible.cfg&lt;/code&gt; 文件，并使用以下值：&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;[默认值]&#xA;inventory = inventory # 库存文件的路径&#xA;private_key_file = ~/.ssh/id_rsa # 我的 SSH 私钥的路径&#xA;Remote_user=root&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-the-mimir-ansible-role&#34;&gt;使用 Mimir Ansible 角色&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，您将创建一个 Ansible playbook，从 &lt;code&gt;grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt; Ansible 集合中调用 &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; 角色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要使用 Mimir Ansible 角色：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，在与 &lt;code&gt;ansible.cfg&lt;/code&gt; 和 inventory 相同的目录中创建一个名为 &lt;code&gt;deploy-mimir.yml&lt;/code&gt; 的文件，并添加以下配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与其他角色一样，Mimir 现在可通过 &lt;a href=&#34;https://galaxy.ansible.com/ui/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Ansible Galaxy&lt;/a&gt; 获得。您可以使用以下命令安装该集合：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;ansible-galaxy 集合安装 grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;安装集合后，您可以在 playbook 中使用 &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; 角色，如下所示：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;复制代码到 clipboard“宽度=“14”高度=“13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;- 主机：全部&#xA;角色：&#xA;- 角色：grafana.grafana.mimir&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;这样，Ansible 就知道在 &lt;code&gt;grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt; 集合中查找 &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; 角色。确保您的 Ansible 配置和版本支持集合，因为此功能是在 Ansible 2.9 中引入的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;configuring-mimir-using-the-ansible-collection&#34;&gt;使用 Ansible 集合配置 Mimir&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于配置模板，Mimir 角色具有高度可配置性。如果您想在 HA 中运行 Mimir，只需将以下变量添加到您的 playbook 中即可：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;- 名称：安装 Mimir&#xA;主办方：全部&#xA;成为：真实&#xA;任务：&#xA;- 名称：安装 Mimir&#xA;ansible.builtin.include_role：&#xA;名称：grafana.grafana.mimir&#xA;变量：&#xA;米米尔存储：&#xA;# 可以使用不同的对象存储后端，使用Minio进行本地开发&#xA;贮存：&#xA;后端：s3&#xA;s3：&#xA;端点：{{端点}}&#xA;access_key_id: {{ access_key_id }}&#xA;秘密访问密钥：{{秘密访问密钥}}&#xA;insecure: true # 使用 https 时为 False&#xA;存储桶名称：mimir&#xA;# 使用普通对象存储桶时，块存储需要前缀。&#xA;mimir_blocks_storage：&#xA;storage_prefix: 块&#xA;tsdb：&#xA;目录：“{{ mimir_working_path}}/ingester”&#xA;# 使用memberlist（一种基于gossip的协议）来使3个Mimir副本能够进行通信&#xA;mimir_memberlist：&#xA;加入成员：&#xA;- 米米尔-01:7946&#xA;- 米米尔-02:7946&#xA;- mimir-03::7946&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;剧本从 &lt;code&gt;grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt; Ansible 集合中调用 &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; 角色。本手册中的 Mimir 配置将 Mimir 安装在三台主机上，确保主机相互通信，并启用对象存储后端。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection/tree/main/roles/mimir#role-variables&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; &gt;Grafana Ansible 文档&lt;/a&gt;，了解可以传递给 &lt;code&gt;mimir&lt;/code&gt; 角色的其他变量。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要运行剧本，请运行以下命令：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__bord呃&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;ansible-playbook deploy-mimir.yml&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意：您可以根据需要将&lt;code&gt;deploy-mimir.yml&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;ansible.cfg&lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt;inventory&lt;/code&gt;文件放置在不同的目录中.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;check-that-metrics-are-available-in-mimir&#34;&gt;检查指标在 Mimir 中是否可用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于我们通过复制在 HA 中运行 Mimir，因此您需要设置自己的负载平衡才能充分利用 Mimir 的潜力。如果您已设置负载平衡，您将能够使用您选择的主机名在 Grafana 中添加数据源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;要检查指标：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;找到“探索”部分。&lt;/strong&gt;在 Grafana 的左侧垂直导航栏中查找“探索”图标（看起来像指南针）并点击它。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;选择您的 Prometheus 数据源。&lt;/strong&gt;页面顶部有一个下拉菜单。用它来选择您添加的 Prometheus 数据源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;运行测试查询。&lt;/strong&gt;输入查询&lt;code&gt;{name=&#34;mimir-01&#34;}&lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;检查指标&lt;/strong&gt;。运行查询后，如果您看到包含数据的图表和表格（类似于下图所示的示例），则意味着您的指标已正确获取和显示。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;探索其他指标。&lt;/strong&gt;探索其他指标（例如 CPU 负载、内存使用情况、磁盘 I/O、网络带宽）并创建仪表板以深入了解系统性能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您没有看到任何数据，则可能意味着未按预期收集指标。要进行故障排除，请运行以下命令检查 Mimir 服务的状态：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;sudo systemctl status mimir.service&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;如果 Mimir 服务未运行，则配置语法可能存在问题，或者您可能需要进一步调试。如需这方面的帮助，请查看有关&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/configure/&#34;&gt;正确配置 Mimir&lt;/a&gt; 的文档。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Monitor these Kubernetes signals to help rightsize your fleet】监控这些 Kubernetes 信号以帮助调整您的车队规模</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/29/monitor-these-kubernetes-signals-to-help-rightsize-your-fleet/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Organizations that run Kubernetes clusters in cloud native environments should do so in a way that&amp;rsquo;s both operationally efficient and cost effective. However, many organizations don&amp;rsquo;t prioritize cost optimization until it becomes a pressing need.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This may be due to a directive from senior leadership, a significant scale-up or migration of Kubernetes clusters, or an unexpected surge in the cloud bill. Regardless of the reason, the mandate to reduce cloud costs can be sudden and urgent, pushing teams to scrutinize their resource usage meticulously.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond just the financial implications, there’s also an environmental impact associated with uncontrolled resource usage. Over-provisioned resources contribute to unnecessary energy consumption and carbon emissions, making it imperative for organizations to optimize not just for cost but for sustainability as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, how do we find that optimal balance with our Kubernetes resources? This post will delve into the signals and indicators to watch for, ensuring that your Kubernetes objects are neither starved nor excessively padded.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;finding-the-middle-ground-with-kubernetes-provisioning&#34;&gt;Finding the middle ground with Kubernetes provisioning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To properly allocate resources in a Kubernetes environment, you have to carefully monitor your setup and make adjustments based on key indicators. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the signals that can help us determine whether our Kubernetes resources are over-provisioned or under-provisioned.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;indicators-of-under-provisioning&#34;&gt;Indicators of under-provisioning&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;high-cpu-or-memory-utilization&#34;&gt;High CPU or memory utilization&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Node level:&lt;/strong&gt; When nodes consistently hit 80% - 90% CPU utilization, it may indicate that the resources are under strain. For some types of workloads—like a non-spiky, non-SLA workload—this would be completely fine. However, this high utilization typically suggests that the nodes are working at or near their capacity, leaving little room for additional workloads or spikes in demand. The same goes for memory resources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod level:&lt;/strong&gt; When pods experience CPU throttling, it can severely impact application performance. CPU throttling occurs when CPU usage and requests begin to overload the pod, causing Kubernetes to restrict the CPU cycles available.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1134px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;CPU usage dashboard in Grafana&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1134&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;605&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*CPU and memory usage times series displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;CPU usage dashboard in Grafana&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1134&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;605&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*CPU and memory usage times series displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;CPU and memory usage times series displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;high-disk-io&#34;&gt;High disk I/O&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Node level:&lt;/strong&gt; High disk read/write latency is a signal of I/O (input/output) bottlenecks. If nodes are consistently experiencing high disk I/O wait times, it could lead to slower data retrieval and storage operations, impacting the performance of all the pods using local disk resources on that node.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod level:&lt;/strong&gt; When pods experience slow disk performance, it can be an indicator of insufficient disk I/O capacity. Applications relying heavily on disk operations will suffer from delays and performance degradation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;high-network-latency&#34;&gt;High network latency&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Node level:&lt;/strong&gt; Network interfaces showing high packet loss or latency are critical signals of under-provisioned network resources. High network latency can slow down communication between services, affecting overall system performance. (Note that some cloud service providers only make higher bandwidth nodes available through VMs with higher CPU, RAM, and disk resources.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod level:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications experiencing slow network responses suggest that the pods&amp;rsquo; network bandwidth is insufficient. This can lead to poor user experiences and/or SLA violations, especially for applications dependent on real-time data exchange.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;frequent-pod-evictions&#34;&gt;Frequent pod evictions&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pods that are evicted often indicate that the cluster cannot support the resource demands of its workloads, leading to instability and service interruptions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Technically, this is more of an issue of underestimating workload specifications than an under-provisioning problem, with workloads not respecting their specific CPU, memory requests, and limits. Still, it&amp;rsquo;s relevant to what we&amp;rsquo;re discussing here, so it&amp;rsquo;s still worth keeping an eye on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;slow-application-performance&#34;&gt;Slow application performance&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Applications showing increased response times or timeout errors typically signal that the resources provided are insufficient to handle the workload. This can lead to poor user experiences and/or SLA violations&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;failed-deployments-and-restarts&#34;&gt;Failed deployments and restarts&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pods failing to start, or restarting frequently due to insufficient resources, can disrupt the deployment process and reduce application availability. This instability can hinder development cycles and impact business operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;insufficient-node-capacity&#34;&gt;Insufficient node capacity&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nodes frequently running out of CPU or memory, causing pods to be stuck in a “pending” status, indicate that the cluster lacks the necessary capacity to handle the current workload. This situation can delay new deployments and scale-up/scale-out operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;indicators-of-over-provisioning&#34;&gt;Indicators of over-provisioning&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;low-cpu-or-memory-utilization&#34;&gt;Low CPU or memory utilization&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Node level:&lt;/strong&gt; Nodes consistently below 20% - 30% CPU utilization suggest that they are over-provisioned. This underutilization means that you are paying for more CPU capacity than needed, leading to wasted resources and higher costs. Likewise for memory resources.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod level:&lt;/strong&gt; Pods using a small fraction of their allocated CPU also indicate over-provisioning. Allocating more CPU than required can lead to inefficient use of resources and unnecessary expenditure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;low-disk-io&#34;&gt;Low disk I/O&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Low disk read/write operations indicate underutilization of disk resources. This scenario suggests that while you may have sufficient disk capacity, your IOPS are not fully utilized. This can lead to inefficient resource usage and potentially higher costs due to the tiered pricing models of cloud providers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;low-network-utilization&#34;&gt;Low network utilization&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Network interfaces showing low bandwidth usage indicate over-provisioned network resources. This underutilization suggests that you are paying for more network capacity than required, leading to unnecessary costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;high-cost-without-proportional-usage&#34;&gt;High cost without proportional usage&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your cloud costs are higher than your workload demands, it suggests inefficiency. If your cloud bills are high, but the resource utilization is low, it’s a clear sign that you are over-provisioning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;unused-or-idle-resources&#34;&gt;Unused or idle resources&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unused capacity in cluster nodes, persistent volumes, IP addresses, or other resources remaining unused indicate over-provisioning. Unused and idle resources still incur costs, contributing to higher cloud bills without any operational benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Navigation menu in Grafana&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1034&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*Idle resources displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Navigation menu in Grafana&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1034&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*Idle resources displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Idle resources displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;best-practices-for-rightsizing-your-fleet&#34;&gt;Best practices for rightsizing your fleet&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To strike the right balance between under and over-provisioning, regular monitoring and adjustment of resource allocations are essential. Here are some best practices to help you optimize your Kubernetes environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;regular-monitoring&#34;&gt;Regular monitoring&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use tools like Prometheus and Grafana to monitor resource usage. They provide valuable insights into your Kubernetes cluster&amp;rsquo;s performance and resource utilization, helping you identify areas of inefficiency and make informed decisions about resource allocation. Or, use Grafana Cloud’s &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Monitoring application&lt;/a&gt; for turnkey resource monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OpIzdlArRMM?rel=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;autoscaling&#34;&gt;Autoscaling&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Implement Horizontal Pod Autoscaler (HPA), Vertical Pod Autoscaler (VPA), and Cluster Autoscaler (CA) to automatically scale resources based on demand. Autoscaling ensures that your cluster can dynamically adjust to workload changes, maintaining optimal resource utilization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;resource-quotas-and-limits&#34;&gt;Resource quotas and limits&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Set appropriate resource requests and limits for your pods to avoid over- or under-allocation. Defining these limits is critical to ensure that resources are used efficiently and that applications have the necessary capacity to perform well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;continuously-optimize-workloads&#34;&gt;Continuously optimize workloads&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Analyze workloads to optimize resource allocation and understand workloads’ resource utilization, remove unnecessary processes, and improve application performance. Optimizing workloads over time will lead to better resource utilization and cost savings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s next&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Cluster panels&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1034&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*Cluster-level data displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Cluster panels&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1034&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*Cluster-level data displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cluster-level data displayed in the Kubernetes Monitoring app&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By keeping a close eye on the signals of under- and over-provisioning and making informed adjustments, you can reach a happy state in your Kubernetes environment that is both cost-effective and environmentally sustainable. To quickly stand up Kubernetes observability and resource monitoring, try out&lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt; Kubernetes Monitoring in Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And check out the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/07/30/understand-your-kubernetes-cost-drivers-and-the-best-ways-to-rein-in-spending/&#34;&gt;second part of this series&lt;/a&gt;, where we&amp;rsquo;ll help you achieve even greater efficiency and cost savings in your Kubernetes clusters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在云原生环境中运行 Kubernetes 集群的组织应该以既高效运营又具有成本效益的方式运行。然而，许多组织并没有优先考虑成本优化，直到它成为迫切需要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这可能是由于高层领导的指示、Kubernetes 集群的大幅扩展或迁移，或者云账单的意外激增。无论出于何种原因，降低云成本的任务可能是突然而紧急的，迫使团队仔细审查其资源使用情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了财务影响之外，不受控制的资源使用还会对环境产生影响。过度配置的资源会导致不必要的能源消耗和碳排放，因此组织不仅必须优化成本，还要优化可持续性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;那么，我们如何找到 Kubernetes 资源的最佳平衡呢？这篇文章将深入研究需要观察的信号和指标，确保您的 Kubernetes 对象既不会匮乏，也不会过度填充。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;finding-the-middle-ground-with-kubernetes-provisioning&#34;&gt;通过 Kubernetes 配置找到中间立场&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要在 Kubernetes 环境中正确分配资源，您必须仔细监控您的设置并根据关键指标进行调整。让我们探讨一下可以帮助我们确定 Kubernetes 资源是否过度配置或配置不足的信号。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;indicators-of-under-provisioning&#34;&gt;配置不足的指标&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;high-cpu-or-memory-utilization&#34;&gt;CPU 或内存利用率高&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;节点级别&lt;/strong&gt;：当节点的 CPU 利用率持续达到 80% - 90% 时，可能表明资源紧张。对于某些类型的工作负载（例如非尖峰、非 SLA 工作负载），这完全没问题。然而，这种高利用率通常表明节点正在以其容量或接近其容量工作，为额外工作负载或需求峰值留下的空间很小。内存资源也是如此。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod 级别&lt;/strong&gt;：当 Pod 遇到 CPU 限制时，可能会严重影响应用程序性能。当 CPU 使用率和请求开始使 Pod 过载时，就会发生 CPU 限制，导致 Kubernetes 限制可用的 CPU 周期。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1134px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=320 320w,/媒体/博客/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=550 550w,/媒体/博客/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png？w=750 750w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png？w=900 900w，/media/blog/kubernetes- optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-用法.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 中的 CPU 使用情况仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1134”&#xA;高度=“605”&#xA;title=&#34;*Kubernetes 监控应用程序中显示的 CPU 和内存使用时间序列*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cpu-usage.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 中的 CPU 使用情况仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1134”&#xA;高度=“605”&#xA;title=&#34;*Kubernetes 监控应用程序中显示的 CPU 和内存使用时间序列*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes 监控应用中显示的 CPU 和内存使用时间序列&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;high-disk-io&#34;&gt;高磁盘 I/O&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;节点级别：&lt;/strong&gt;高磁盘读/写延迟是 I/O（输入/输出）瓶颈的信号。如果节点持续经历较长的磁盘 I/O 等待时间，可能会导致数据检索和存储操作变慢，从而影响该节点上使用本地磁盘资源的所有 Pod 的性能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod 级别：&lt;/strong&gt;当 Pod 遇到磁盘性能缓慢时，可能表明磁盘 I/O 容量不足。严重依赖磁盘操作的应用程序将遭受延迟和性能下降的影响。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;high-network-latency&#34;&gt;网络延迟较高&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;节点级别&lt;/strong&gt;：网络接口出现高数据包丢失或延迟是网络资源配置不足的关键信号。高网络延迟会减慢服务之间的通信速度，从而影响整体系统性能。 （请注意，某些云服务提供商仅通过具有更高 CPU、RAM 和磁盘资源的虚拟机提供更高带宽的节点。）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod 级别&lt;/strong&gt;：应用程序网络响应缓慢表明 Pod 的网络带宽不足。这可能会导致糟糕的用户体验和/或违反 SLA，尤其是对于依赖实时数据交换的应用程序。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;frequent-pod-evictions&#34;&gt;频繁的 Pod 驱逐&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;被驱逐的 Pod 通常表明集群无法支持其工作负载的资源需求，从而导致不稳定和服务中断。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从技术上讲，这更多的是低估工作负载规格的问题，而不是配置不足的问题，即工作负载不尊重其特定的 CPU、内存请求和限制。不过，它与我们在这里讨论的内容相关，因此仍然值得关注。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;slow-application-performance&#34;&gt;应用程序性能缓慢&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;显示响应时间增加或超时错误的应用程序通常表明资源提供的 ces 不足以处理工作量。这可能会导致糟糕的用户体验和/或违反 SLA&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;failed-deployments-and-restarts&#34;&gt;部署和重启失败&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pod 无法启动或由于资源不足而频繁重新启动可能会中断部署过程并降低应用程序可用性。这种不稳定性会阻碍开发周期并影响业务运营。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;insufficient-node-capacity&#34;&gt;节点容量不足&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;节点频繁耗尽 CPU 或内存，导致 Pod 陷入“待处理”状态，表明集群缺乏处理当前工作负载所需的能力。这种情况可能会延迟新的部署和扩展/扩展操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;indicators-of-over-provisioning&#34;&gt;过度配置指标&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;low-cpu-or-memory-utilization&#34;&gt;CPU 或内存利用率低&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;节点级别&lt;/strong&gt;：CPU 利用率持续低于 20% - 30% 的节点表明它们存在过度配置。这种未充分利用意味着您要为超出所需的 CPU 容量付费，从而导致资源浪费和更高的成本。内存资源也是如此。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pod 级别&lt;/strong&gt;：Pod 使用其分配的 CPU 的一小部分也表明存在过度配置。分配超过所需的 CPU 可能会导致资源使用效率低下和不必要的支出。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;low-disk-io&#34;&gt;低磁盘 I/O&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;低磁盘读/写操作表明磁盘资源未充分利用。这种情况表明，虽然您可能有足够的磁盘容量，但您的 IOPS 并未得到充分利用。由于云提供商的分层定价模型，这可能会导致资源使用效率低下，并可能导致更高的成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;low-network-utilization&#34;&gt;网络利用率低&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;显示低带宽使用率的网络接口表明网络资源过度配置。这种未充分利用的情况表明您为超出所需的网络容量支付了费用，从而导致不必要的成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;high-cost-without-proportional-usage&#34;&gt;成本高但不按比例使用&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的云成本高于工作负载需求，则表明效率低下。如果您的云费用很高，但资源利用率很低，则明确表明您存在过度配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;unused-or-idle-resources&#34;&gt;未使用或空闲的资源&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;集群节点中未使用的容量、持久卷、IP 地址或其他未使用的资源表示过度配置。未使用和闲置的资源仍然会产生成本，从而导致更高的云费用，而没有任何运营效益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1999px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=320 320w，/media/blog/ kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png？ w=900 900w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png？w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png？w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/ kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 中的导航菜单&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1034”&#xA;title=&#34;*Kubernetes 监控应用中显示的空闲资源*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/navigation.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 中的导航菜单&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1034”&#xA;title=&#34;*Kubernetes 监控应用中显示的空闲资源*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes 监控应用中显示的空闲资源&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;best-practices-for-rightsizing-your-fleet&#34;&gt;调整车队规模的最佳实践&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了在供应不足和供应过剩之间取得适当的平衡，定期监测和调整资源分配至关重要。以下是一些可帮助您优化 Kubernetes 环境的最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;regular-monitoring&#34;&gt;定期监控&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用 Prometheus 和 Grafana 等工具来监控资源使用情况。它们提供有关 Kubernetes 集群的性能和资源利用率的宝贵见解，帮助您识别效率低下的领域并就资源分配做出明智的决策。或者，使用 Grafana Cloud 的 &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 监控应用程序&lt;/a&gt; 进行交钥匙资源监控。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OpIzdlArRMM?rel=0&#34; style=&#34;位置：绝对；顶部：0；左侧：0；宽度：100%；高度：100%；边框： 0;” allowedfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube 视频&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;autoscaling&#34;&gt;自动缩放&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;实施 Horizo​​ntal Pod Autoscaler (HPA)、Vertical Pod Autoscaler (VPA) 和 Cluster Autoscaler (CA)，以根据需求自动扩展资源。自动缩放可确保您的集群可以动态调整以适应工作负载变化，从而保持最佳的资源利用率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;resource-quotas-and-limits&#34;&gt;资源配额和限制&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为 Pod 设置适当的资源请求和限制，以避免分配过度或不足。定义这些限制对于确保资源得到有效利用以及应用程序具有良好运行所需的能力至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;continuously-optimize-workloads&#34;&gt;持续优化工作负载&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;分析工作负载以优化资源分配并了解工作负载的资源利用率，删除不必要的进程，并提高应用程序性能。随着时间的推移优化工作负载将提高资源利用率并节省成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;下一步是什么&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1999px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png？w = 320 320w，/媒体/博客/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png？w=550 550w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png？w=750 750w，/media/blog/kubernetes- optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster- panel.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-size=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;集群面板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1034”&#xA;title=&#34;*Kubernetes 监控应用中显示的集群级数据*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/cluster-panels.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;集群面板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1034”&#xA;title=&#34;*Kubernetes 监控应用中显示的集群级数据*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes 监控应用中显示的集群级数据&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过密切关注配置不足和过度配置的信号并进行明智的调整，您可以在 Kubernetes 环境中达到既经济高效又环境可持续的良好状态。要快速建立 Kubernetes 可观察性和资源监控，请尝试&lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud 中的 Kubernetes 监控&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;并查看&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/07/30/understand-your-kubernetes-cost-drivers-and-the-best-ways-to-rein-in-spending/&#34;&gt;第二个这是本系列的一部分&lt;/a&gt;，我们将帮助您在 Kubernetes 集群中实现更高的效率并节省成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understand your Kubernetes cost drivers and the best ways to rein in spending】了解 Kubernetes 成本驱动因素以及控制支出的最佳方法</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/30/understand-your-kubernetes-cost-drivers-and-the-best-ways-to-rein-in-spending/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/07/29/monitor-these-kubernetes-signals-to-help-rightsize-your-fleet/&#34;&gt;previous blog post&lt;/a&gt; in this two-part series, we discussed the critical signals you need to monitor in your Kubernetes environment to ensure optimal resource provisioning. These signals include high CPU and memory utilization, frequent pod evictions, slow application performance, and other indicators that your resources are over- or under-provisioned. Monitoring these signals is essential for maintaining an efficient, cost-effective, and environmentally sustainable Kubernetes environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll go a step further by providing actionable information on how to reduce your Kubernetes-related costs. We&amp;rsquo;ll break down what drives these costs, who is responsible for them, and how you can effectively measure and optimize your resource usage. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-drives-kubernetes-costs&#34;&gt;What drives Kubernetes costs?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At its core, the cost associated with running a Kubernetes environment can be summarized with the formula:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Spend = usage × rate&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here, &lt;em&gt;usage&lt;/em&gt; refers to the amount of resources consumed that are either unused or underused. &lt;em&gt;Rate&lt;/em&gt; is the cost per unit of these resources. To manage and reduce costs, you need to focus on both components—reducing unnecessary usage and optimizing the rates you pay for the resources you actually use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1109px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Spend graph in Grafana&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1109&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;394&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*A bar chart shows CPU and memory costs tracked in the Kubernetes Monitoring app in Grafana Cloud.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Spend graph in Grafana&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1109&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;394&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*A bar chart shows CPU and memory costs tracked in the Kubernetes Monitoring app in Grafana Cloud.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A bar chart shows CPU and memory costs tracked in the Kubernetes Monitoring app in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For a deeper discussion on this formula, check out this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8eiLXtL3oLk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;KubeCon 2023 talk&lt;/a&gt; by my colleagues Mark Poko and JuanJo Ciarlante.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, let&amp;rsquo;s break down the resources, actions, and users that drive those costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;resources&#34;&gt;Resources&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compute resources:&lt;/strong&gt; CPU and memory are primary cost drivers. The more you use, the higher your bill.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage:&lt;/strong&gt; Persistent volumes and disk I/O also contribute significantly to costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Networking:&lt;/strong&gt; Data transfer costs can add up, especially for applications with high bandwidth requirements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managed services:&lt;/strong&gt; If you are using managed Kubernetes services like GKE (Google Kubernetes Engine) or EKS (Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service), the service fees will be part of your cost structure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;actions&#34;&gt;Actions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Over-provisioning:&lt;/strong&gt; Allocating more resources than necessary typically leads to unnecessary spending.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Letting resources sit idle:&lt;/strong&gt; Inactive nodes or persistent volumes can still incur costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not setting request limits:&lt;/strong&gt; Applications can rack up unnecessary costs without appropriate consumption guardrails.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unchecked scaling:&lt;/strong&gt; Constantly scaling clusters up without properly scaling them down can lead to inefficiencies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Storage mismanagement:&lt;/strong&gt; Mismanaging storage resources can lead to high costs, especially if you use high-performance storage when you don&amp;rsquo;t need to.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;users&#34;&gt;Users&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DevOps engineers:&lt;/strong&gt; Responsible for managing the Kubernetes clusters, configuring nodes, and setting up auto scaling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developers:&lt;/strong&gt; Write the applications that run on the Kubernetes clusters. Their code and resource requests directly impact usage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud architects:&lt;/strong&gt; Design the overall cloud infrastructure and strategies for resource utilization.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finance teams:&lt;/strong&gt; While these individuals don’t affect how large your bill is, they do monitor and manage cloud spending, often pushing for cost optimization strategies.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned-top-cost-saving-tips-from-grafana-labs&#34;&gt;Lessons Learned: top cost-saving tips from Grafana Labs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve covered what drives Kubernetes costs, let&amp;rsquo;s look at how you can bring those bills down. Optimization involves continuous learning and improvement, and after years of managing Kubernetes at scale internally, we&amp;rsquo;ve learned a thing or two.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our platform team runs a highly reliable and efficient deployment on Grafana Cloud, our SaaS platform, for customers across the globe. Here are our top three takeaways about operating Kubernetes clusters efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Regularly monitor and adjust.&lt;/strong&gt; Use tools like &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/prometheus/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; to keep a close eye on resource utilization. Regularly review and adjust resource requests and limits based on observed usage patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Leverage auto scaling.&lt;/strong&gt; Implement auto scaling tools such as Horizontal Pod Autoscaler (HPA) and Cluster Autoscaler. They help ensure that your cluster scales up and down based on actual demand, preventing over-provisioning and under-utilization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Optimize resource allocation.&lt;/strong&gt; Remove unnecessary processes, fine-tune application performance, and ensure that resource requests and limits are set appropriately. This step helps in making efficient use of available resources and reduces costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;monitor-usage-in-order-to-know-where-to-cut&#34;&gt;Monitor usage in order to know where to cut&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to properly implement any of these strategies, you need to accurately measure usage so you can adjust accordingly. Here are some of the dimensions to observe to help reduce Kubernetes costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Kubernetes overview page in the Kubernetes Monitoring app&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1059&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*The overview page in the Kubernetes Monitoring app provides a high-level look at your system.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Kubernetes overview page in the Kubernetes Monitoring app&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1059&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*The overview page in the Kubernetes Monitoring app provides a high-level look at your system.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The overview page in the Kubernetes Monitoring app provides a high-level look at your system.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nodes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CPU utilization:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensure nodes are not consistently over- or under-utilized.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Memory utilization:&lt;/strong&gt; Monitor memory usage to prevent out-of-memory errors and unnecessary costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disk I/O:&lt;/strong&gt; High disk operations can indicate bottlenecks or inefficient storage usage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workloads&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Application performance metrics:&lt;/strong&gt; Use tools like Prometheus to gather detailed metrics on application performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resource requests and limits:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensure that pods have appropriate resource requests and limits set.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Idle resources&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Underutilized nodes:&lt;/strong&gt; Nodes that consistently show low utilization should be consolidated or scaled down.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Underutilized nodes:&lt;/strong&gt; Nodes that consistently show low utilization should be consolidated or scaled down.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Persistent volumes:&lt;/strong&gt; Check for unused or underutilized persistent volumes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;tuning-the-scheduler&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tuning the scheduler&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re using AWS or Google Cloud, optimizing the Kubernetes scheduler can help in better resource utilization:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;OPTIMIZE_UTILIZATION&lt;/code&gt; in GKE: GKE offers configurations to optimize resource utilization. Tuning these settings can help reduce costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Karpenter on AWS: If using AWS, Karpenter is an open source, flexible, high-performance Kubernetes cluster autoscaler that you can use to improve resource efficiency.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;implement-grafana-for-monitoring&#34;&gt;Implement Grafana for monitoring&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana is a powerful tool for monitoring and visualizing Kubernetes metrics. It integrates well with Prometheus and other data sources, providing a comprehensive view of your cluster’s performance and resource usage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set up dashboards:&lt;/strong&gt; Create dashboards to monitor CPU, memory, disk I/O, and network usage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leverage OpenCost:&lt;/strong&gt; Gain detailed insights into resource usage and costs, enabling more efficient and cost-effective management of your infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alerting:&lt;/strong&gt; Configure alerts for key metrics to proactively manage resource usage and prevent cost overruns.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use Kubernetes Monitoring:&lt;/strong&gt; The Kubernetes Monitoring application provides a managed solution for resource utilization visualizations, metrics, and alerts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OpIzdlArRMM?rel=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a little bit of practice and the right tools, any team can create actionable strategies for reducing Kubernetes-related costs. And don’t forget, all of the tools you need to monitor and optimize their resource utilization are available in Grafana Cloud’s turnkey &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Monitoring application&lt;/a&gt;. This is the easy path to gain insights quickly, and it’s available on all tiers of Grafana Cloud, including our forever-free tier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt; Sign up for free now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/07/29/monitor-these-kubernetes-signals-to-help-rightsize-your-fleet/&#34;&gt;上一篇博客文章&lt;/a&gt;中的这两个-在系列部分中，我们讨论了您需要在 Kubernetes 环境中监控的关键信号，以确保最佳的资源配置。这些信号包括高 CPU 和内存利用率、频繁的 Pod 驱逐、应用程序性能缓慢以及资源过度配置或配置不足的其他指标。监控这些信号对于维持高效、经济高效且环境可持续的 Kubernetes 环境至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将进一步提供有关如何降低 Kubernetes 相关成本的可操作信息。我们将详细分析导致这些成本的原因、谁负责这些成本，以及如何有效地衡量和优化资源使用情况。让我们深入探讨一下。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-drives-kubernetes-costs&#34;&gt;是什么驱动了 Kubernetes 成本？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从本质上讲，与运行 Kubernetes 环境相关的成本可以用以下公式总结：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;支出=使用量×费率&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此处，&lt;em&gt;使用&lt;/em&gt;是指未使用或未充分利用的资源消耗量。 &lt;em&gt;费率&lt;/em&gt;是这些资源的每单位成本。为了管理和降低成本，您需要关注这两个组成部分 - 减少不必要的使用并优化为实际使用的资源支付的费率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1109px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=320 320w，/media/blog/ kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png？ w=900 900w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png？w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png？w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/ kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 中的支出图&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1109”&#xA;高度=“394”&#xA;title=&#34;*条形图显示 Grafana Cloud 中 Kubernetes 监控应用程序中跟踪的 CPU 和内存成本。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/spend.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 中的支出图&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1109”&#xA;高度=“394”&#xA;title=&#34;*条形图显示 Grafana Cloud 中 Kubernetes 监控应用程序中跟踪的 CPU 和内存成本。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;条形图显示 Grafana Cloud 中 Kubernetes 监控应用程序跟踪的 CPU 和内存成本。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;为了更深入有关此公式的讨论，请查看我的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8eiLXtL3oLk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;KubeCon 2023 演讲&lt;/a&gt;同事 Mark Poko 和 JuanJo Ciarlante。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，让我们细分导致这些成本的资源、操作和用户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;resources&#34;&gt;资源&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;计算资源&lt;/strong&gt;：CPU 和内存是主要成本驱动因素。您使用的越多，您的账单就越高。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;存储&lt;/strong&gt;：持久卷和磁盘 I/O 也会显着增加成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;网络&lt;/strong&gt;：数据传输成本可能会增加，特别是对于带宽要求较高的应用程序。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;托管服务&lt;/strong&gt;：如果您使用 GKE (Google Kubernetes Engine) 或 EKS (Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service) 等托管 Kubernetes 服务，服务费将成为您成本结构的一部分。&lt;/li &gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;actions&#34;&gt;操作&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;过度配置：&lt;/strong&gt;分配超过必要的资源通常会导致不必要的支出。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;让资源闲置&lt;/strong&gt;：不活动的节点或持久卷仍然会产生成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;不设置请求限制&lt;/strong&gt;：如果没有适当的消耗防护措施，应用程序可能会产生不必要的成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;未经检查的扩展&lt;/strong&gt;：不断扩展集群而不适当缩小集群可能会导致效率低下。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;存储管理不善&lt;/strong&gt;：存储资源管理不善可能会导致高昂的成本，尤其是在不需要时使用高性能存储的情况下。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;users&#34;&gt;用户&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DevOps 工程师：&lt;/strong&gt;负责管理 Kubernetes 集群、配置节点和设置自动扩展。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;开发人员&lt;/strong&gt;：编写在 Kubernetes 集群上运行的应用程序。他们的代码和资源请求直接影响使用情况。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云架构师：&lt;/strong&gt;设计整体云基础设施和资源利用策略。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;财务团队&lt;/strong&gt;：虽然这些人不会影响您的账单金额，但他们会监控和管理云支出，通常会推动成本优化策略。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned-top-cost- saving-tips-from-grafana-labs&#34;&gt;经验教训：Grafana Labs 提供的最佳成本节省技巧&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在我们已经介绍了 Kubernetes 成本的驱动因素，让我们看看如何降低这些费用。优化涉及持续学习和改进，经过多年内部大规模管理 Kubernetes，我们已经学到了一两件事。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的平台团队在我们的 SaaS 平台 Grafana Cloud 上为全球客户运行高度可靠且高效的部署。以下是我们关于高效运营 Kubernetes 集群的三大要点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;强&gt;1。雷古尔尽早监控和调整。&lt;/strong&gt;使用&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/prometheus/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt等工具=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; 密切关注资源利用率。根据观察到的使用模式定期审查和调整资源请求和限制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;强&gt;2。利用自动扩展。&lt;/strong&gt;实施自动扩展工具，例如 Horizo​​ntal Pod Autoscaler (HPA) 和 Cluster Autoscaler。它们有助于确保您的集群根据实际需求进行扩展和缩减，从而防止过度配置和利用率不足。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;强&gt;3。优化资源分配。&lt;/strong&gt;删除不必要的进程，微调应用程序性能，并确保正确设置资源请求和限制。此步骤有助于有效利用可用资源并降低成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;monitor-usage-in-order-to-know-where-to-cut&#34;&gt;监控使用情况以了解在哪里剪切&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您想正确实施这些策略，则需要准确衡量使用情况，以便进行相应调整。以下是一些需要观察的维度，有助于降低 Kubernetes 成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1999px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=320 320w,/媒体/博客/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png？w=550 550w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png？w=750 750w，/media/blog/kubernetes- optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes- Overview.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Kubernetes 监控应用程序中的 Kubernetes 概述页面&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1059”&#xA;title=&#34;*Kubernetes 监控应用程序中的概述页面提供了系统的高级视图。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/kubernetes-optimization-series/kubernetes-overview.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Kubernetes 监控应用程序中的 Kubernetes 概述页面&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1059”&#xA;title=&#34;*Kubernetes 监控应用程序中的概述页面提供了系统的高级视图。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Kubernetes 监控应用中的概述页面提供了系统的高级视图。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;节点&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CPU利用率：&lt;/strong&gt;确保节点不一致性略微过度或未充分利用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;内存利用率：&lt;/strong&gt;监控内存使用情况，以防止内存不足错误和不必要的成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;磁盘 I/O&lt;/strong&gt;：磁盘操作过多可能表明存在瓶颈或存储使用效率低下。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;工作负载&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;应用程序性能指标&lt;/strong&gt;：使用 Prometheus 等工具收集有关应用程序性能的详细指标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;资源请求和限制&lt;/strong&gt;：确保 Pod 设置了适当的资源请求和限制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;闲置资源&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;未充分利用的节点&lt;/strong&gt;：应整合或缩减始终显示利用率较低的节点。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;未充分利用的节点&lt;/strong&gt;：应整合或缩减始终显示利用率较低的节点。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;持久卷：&lt;/strong&gt;检查未使用或未充分利用的持久卷。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;tuning-the-scheduler&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;调整调度程序&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您使用 AWS 或 Google Cloud，优化 Kubernetes 调度程序有助于提高资源利用率：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;GKE 中的&lt;code&gt;OPTIMIZE_UTILIZATION&lt;/code&gt;：GKE 提供配置来优化资源利用率。调整这些设置有助于降低成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;AWS 上的 Karpenter：如果使用 AWS，Karpenter 是一个开源、灵活、高性能的 Kubernetes 集群自动扩缩器，您可以用它来提高资源效率。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;implement-grafana-for-monitoring&#34;&gt;实施 Grafana 进行监控&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana 是一个用于监控和可视化 Kubernetes 指标的强大工具。它与 Prometheus 和其他数据源完美集成，提供集群性能和资源使用情况的全面视图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;设置仪表板&lt;/strong&gt;：创建仪表板来监控 CPU、内存、磁盘 I/O 和网络使用情况。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;利用 OpenCost&lt;/strong&gt;：详细了解资源使用情况和成本，从而更高效、更具成本效益地管理您的基础架构。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;警报&lt;/strong&gt;：为关键指标配置警报，以主动管理资源使用情况并防止成本超支。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用 Kubernetes 监控&lt;/strong&gt;：Kubernetes 监控应用程序为资源利用率可视化、指标和警报提供托管解决方案。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/OpIzdlArRMM?rel=0&#34; style=&#34;位置：绝对；顶部：0；左侧：0；宽度：100%；高度：100%；边框： 0;” allowedfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube 视频&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过一点点实践和正确的工具，任何团队都可以制定可行的策略来降低 Kubernetes 相关成本。不要忘记，监控和优化资源利用率所需的所有工具都可以在 Grafana Cloud 的统包中使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 监控应用程序&lt;/a&gt;。这是快速获得见解的简单途径，并且在 Grafana Cloud 的所有层级上都可用，包括我们的永久免费层级。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册&lt;/a&gt; ！&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【An overview of Grafana SSO: Benefits, recent updates, and best practices to get started】Grafana SSO 概述：优点、最新更新和入门最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/31/an-overview-of-grafana-sso-benefits-recent-updates-and-best-practices-to-get-started/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Grafana began as an open and composable platform for data visualization. Today, Grafana has evolved into an all-in-one observability platform, providing everything from infrastructure and application performance monitoring to load testing and incident response.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As organizations extend their use of Grafana, efficient and secure authentication and authorization is essential. Fortunately, Grafana provides multiple ways to authenticate users, including&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/ldap/&#34;&gt;Lightweight Directory Access Protocol (LDAP) authentication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/grafana/#basic-authentication&#34;&gt;Basic authentication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/jwt/&#34;&gt;JSON Web Token (JWT) authentication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/&#34;&gt;Single sign-on (SSO)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll provide an overview of Grafana SSO, including how it compares to other authentication methods, its benefits, and recent updates that make it easier to configure SSO in your environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-comparison-of-authentication-methods&#34;&gt;A comparison of authentication methods&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we dive into the details of SSO, specifically, let&amp;rsquo;s compare the supported authentication methods in Grafana. &lt;em&gt;Note: For more information on which methods are supported in Grafana OSS, Grafana Cloud, and Grafana Enterprise, please refer to &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/&#34;&gt;our technical documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Method&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LDAP&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic authentication&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JWT authentication&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Single sign-on (SSO)&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Description&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Allows users to login with their LDAP credentials&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Uses username and password stored locally&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Uses JSON Web Tokens for stateless authentication. Allows Grafana to accept a JWT token provided in the HTTP header.&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Allows for the use of a centralized identity management provider, using OAuth and SAML in Grafana. Built-in support for multiple known identity providers (IdPs), as well as support for setting up Generic OAuth.&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Security level&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;High (centralized and managed externally)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Low (depends on password strength, user input)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Moderate (in certain configurations can lead to the token being exposed – for example, in logs – which leaves room for hijacking)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;High (centralized and managed by the IdP, and allows for the implementation of multi-factor authentication on the IdP side)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;User management&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Centralized (managed in LDAP directory)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Local (managed within Grafana)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Distributed (tokens issued by third-party trusted provider)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Centralized (managed by the IdP)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Ease of setup&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Moderate (requires LDAP server and configuration)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Easy (built-in, minimal setup)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Moderate (requires token generation, validation, and ensuring security)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Moderate to high (depends on the IdP and protocol used)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Scalability&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;High (suitable for large organizations)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;Low (best for smaller setups, or testing)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;High (scales well with stateless tokens)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;High (ideal for large organizations with multiple services)&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, you can configure Grafana to use &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/#anonymous-authentication&#34;&gt;Anonymous authentication&lt;/a&gt;, which allows users to access Grafana without requiring any login.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, your choice of authentication type depends on your organization’s unique requirements. Most of these authentication methods also allow you to sync user permissions from external providers to Grafana and, therefore, easily control access. While this is beyond the scope of this blog post, you can read more in &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/&#34;&gt;our technical documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-use-sso-with-grafana&#34;&gt;Why use SSO with Grafana?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While SSO might not be applicable to all types of organizations and users, it comes with several advantages compared to other forms of authentication, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced security and better compliance&lt;/strong&gt;: Centralized authentication reduces the risk of compromised credentials. It makes it easier to enforce policies and maintain audit trails, and also scales really well.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Better user experience&lt;/strong&gt;: Users can access Grafana resources without needing to log in separately (aka, no password fatigue), and administrators can manage user access and permissions from a centralized place (for example, their IdP).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-new-in-grafana-sso-configuration&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s new in Grafana SSO configuration?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Historically, configuring SSO in Grafana required updating static configuration files and restarting the Grafana instance for the changes to take effect. This process could be cumbersome and disruptive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the Grafana 10 release, we &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/07/27/new-in-grafana-10-a-ui-to-easily-configure-saml-authentication/&#34;&gt;introduced a new UI to easily configure SAML authentication&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks to feedback from our community, we decided to streamline the entire SSO setup process and introduced the following updates, starting with &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-11-release-all-the-new-features/&#34;&gt;Grafana 11&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UI configuration&lt;/strong&gt;: Configure SSO directly through the Grafana user interface.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API support&lt;/strong&gt;: Automate SSO setup and management using Grafana&amp;rsquo;s API. &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/developers/http_api/sso-settings/&#34;&gt;Refer to the documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terraform integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Manage SSO configurations as code with Terraform support. &lt;a href=&#34;https://registry.terraform.io/providers/grafana/grafana/latest/docs/resources/sso_settings&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Refer to the documentation&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;configuration-files-vs-the-uiapi&#34;&gt;Configuration files vs. the UI/API&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Configuring SSO through Grafana configuration files is still supported and might be applicable in certain scenarios, including when there’s limited infrastructure automation. That said, using the UI or API instead of configuration files has the following advantages:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Available in Grafana Cloud&lt;/strong&gt;: Set up SSO inside of your Grafana Cloud instance without needing to file a support request.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-time configuration validation&lt;/strong&gt;: When using the UI or API, all settings are validated in real time, providing immediate feedback on the validity of the configuration.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No need to restart Grafana&lt;/strong&gt;: Using the UI or API eliminates the need to restart Grafana after making changes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RBAC authorization&lt;/strong&gt;: You have the flexibility to authorize specific users to access the UI or API by using role-based access control (RBAC).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is not recommended to mix configuration methods (for example, to define some fields in a config file and some through the API). If, for some reason, configuration has to be done using both options, Grafana will follow a specific precedence order when loading the configuration:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Settings that were configured using the UI/API, or Terraform.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Settings from environment variables.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Settings from the Grafana configuration file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;exploring-the-authentication-user-interface&#34;&gt;Exploring the Authentication user interface&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To access the UI in Grafana or Grafana Cloud, navigate to &lt;strong&gt;Administration &amp;gt; Authentication&lt;/strong&gt; in the navigation menu of your Grafana instance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please note that in order to access this page, a user must have the &lt;em&gt;settings:read&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;settings:write&lt;/em&gt; permissions. By using the *settings:auth.{provider}:** scope with appropriate providers, you can control access by indicating which specific providers a user can set up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload d-inline-block&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-SSO-overview/grafana-SSO-authentication-settings.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the authentication settings page. &#34; width=&#34;1882&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1248&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;best-practices-to-set-up-sso&#34;&gt;Best practices to set up SSO&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Setting up SSO requires knowledge of both identity providers and Grafana. With hundreds of identity providers available, offering built-in support for all of them is not feasible. This is why Grafana supports a Generic OAuth configuration, which can be used to set up SSO with any identity provider that supports OAuth 2.0.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are a few generic guidelines to follow when setting up SSO in Grafana:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understand your identity provider&lt;/strong&gt;: Each IdP has specific requirements and quirks, so consult their documentation thoroughly before moving forward.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Configure redirect Uniform Resource Identifier (URIs) correctly&lt;/strong&gt;: Make sure the redirect URIs configured in your IdP match exactly with those specified in Grafana. Incorrect URIs can cause authentication failures.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Avoid using Generic OAuth if your provider is supported by Grafana&lt;/strong&gt;. If you are using Azure Active Directory, Okta, Google, GitHub or GitLab, use the appropriate configuration for them and avoid Generic OAuth. This approach simplifies setup and is less error-prone. Additionally, configuration is much more fine-grained, as certain functionality won’t be available with Generic OAuth.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When using OAuth, configure &lt;em&gt;allowed_domains, allowed_groups&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;allowed_organizations&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: This will reduce the attack surface for user accounts and create defense in depth (DiD) in case authentication is bypassed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enable &lt;em&gt;use_pkce=true&lt;/em&gt; for OAuth integrations:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://auth0.com/docs/get-started/authentication-and-authorization-flow/authorization-code-flow-with-pkce&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Proof Key for Code Exchange (PKCE)&lt;/a&gt; is an important addition to OAuth and it might be obligatory in future versions of the protocol. Enable it from the start to avoid breakage on IdP updates (it’s been enabled by default since Grafana 10.1).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use request signing when setting up SAML&lt;/strong&gt;: Request signing is a critical security feature in SAML that enhances the overall security of the authentication process. It ensures SAML requests are genuine, unaltered, and originate from a trusted service provider, thereby protecting the system from various threats and ensuring compliance with security standards.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set up auto login&lt;/strong&gt;: Available for OAuth and SAML, this will improve the user experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;troubleshooting-sso-setup&#34;&gt;Troubleshooting SSO setup&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Setting up SSO requires configuration in multiple places, and sometimes, it doesn’t work out the first time. Being prepared and having the right tools for debugging can streamline the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;be-familiar-with-identity-protocols&#34;&gt;Be familiar with identity protocols&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of the authentication protocols involve browser redirects and HTTP requests/responses between several components, so troubleshooting will be easier if you are familiar with the expected sequence of interaction for a particular scenario. Specifically, it will be helpful to know:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The parameters expected by each protocol endpoint&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The responses and error codes returned by each endpoint&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The identity provider APIs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;have-the-right-tools&#34;&gt;Have the right tools&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tools to capture and view &lt;strong&gt;HTTP traces&lt;/strong&gt; are especially helpful to troubleshoot during SSO setup. Most internet browsers offer dev tools with built-in capabilities to capture an HTTP trace in the &amp;ldquo;Network&amp;rdquo; tab. It is also convenient to be able to dump the HTTP trace to an HTTP Archive format (.har file), which will capture everything, including the cleartext value of any secret.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other examples of tools for SSO debugging and troubleshooting include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.postman.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Postman&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://insomnia.rest/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Insomnia&lt;/a&gt; to test API calls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.telerik.com/fiddler/configure-fiddler/tasks/configurefiddler&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Fiddler&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.charlesproxy.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Charlesproxy&lt;/a&gt; to capture and view network traces of backend API calls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jwt.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://jwt.io/&lt;/a&gt; to view and create JWTs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;SAML-tracer, available for &lt;a href=&#34;https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/saml-tracer/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Firefox&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/saml-tracer/mpdajninpobndbfcldcmbpnnbhibjmch?hl=en&amp;amp;pli=1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt;, to inspect SAML requests&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;know-these-debugging-basics&#34;&gt;Know these debugging basics&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When something is not working as expected, especially when it comes to authentication, it’s best to start checking the simple things. For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Check that the identity provider is accessible and not experiencing any issues&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ensure the supplied credentials are correct for the environment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Check that the login account and credentials are not disabled or expired&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Make sure Grafana is using the correct URL for the identity provider&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Verify the client ID matches the one registered in identity provider&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Check the redirect/callback URL&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Read all error messages to see if they provide valuable clues&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;What’s next?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We hope the recent updates we’ve made related to the UI, API, and Terraform enhance your experience with Grafana and simplify the SSO setup process. Looking ahead, we plan to introduce a new UI and API for configuring LDAP, which will make authentication setup even easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, if you want to learn more about how to organize your users and teams in Grafana to ensure optimal security, please refer to &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/03/14/how-to-best-organize-your-teams-and-resources-in-grafana/&#34;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Grafana 最初是一个开放且可组合的数据可视化平台。如今，Grafana 已发展成为一个一体化的可观测平台，提供从基础设施和应用程序性能监控到负载测试和事件响应的一切功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着组织扩展 Grafana 的使用，高效、安全的身份验证和授权至关重要。幸运的是，Grafana 提供了多种对用户进行身份验证的方法，包括&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/ldap/&#34;&gt;轻量级目录访问协议 (LDAP) 身份验证&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/grafana/#basic-authentication&#34;&gt;基本身份验证&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/jwt/&#34;&gt;JSON Web 令牌 (JWT) 身份验证&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/&#34;&gt;单点登录 (SSO)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将概述 Grafana SSO，包括它与其他身份验证方法的比较、其优点以及使您可以更轻松地在环境中配置 SSO 的最新更新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-comparison-of-authentication-methods&#34;&gt;身份验证方法比较&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们深入了解 SSO 的详细信息之前，具体来说，让我们比较一下 Grafana 中支持的身份验证方法。 &lt;em&gt;注意：有关 Grafana OSS、Grafana Cloud 和 Grafana Enterprise 支持哪些方法的更多信息，请参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication /&#34;&gt;我们的技术文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;表&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;方法&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LDAP&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;基本身份验证&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JWT 身份验证&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;单点登录 (SSO)&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;描述&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;允许用户使用其 LDAP 凭据登录&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;使用本地存储的用户名和密码&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;使用 JSON Web 令牌进行无状态身份验证。允许 Grafana 接受 HTTP 标头中提供的 JWT 令牌。&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;允许使用集中式身份管理提供程序，在 Grafana 中使用 OAuth 和 SAML。对多个已知身份提供商 (IdP) 的内置支持，以及对设置通用 OAuth 的支持。&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;安全级别&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;高（集中且外部管理）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;低（取决于密码强度、用户输入）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;中等（在某些配置中可能会导致令牌被暴露——例如，在日志中——这为劫持留下了空间）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;高（由IdP集中管理，并允许在IdP端实施多重身份验证）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;用户管理&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;集中式（在 LDAP 目录中管理）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;洛卡l（在 Grafana 内管理）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;分布式（由第三方可信提供商发行的令牌）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;集中式（由 IdP 管理）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;易于设置&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;中等（需要 LDAP 服务器和配置）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;简单（内置，最少设置）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;中等（需要令牌生成、验证并确保安全）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;中到高（取决于所使用的 IdP 和协议）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;可扩展性&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;高（适合大型组织）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;低（最适合较小的设置或测试）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;高（可与无状态令牌很好地扩展）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;td&gt;高（非常适合提供多种服务的大型组织）&#xA;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;&lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/表&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，您可以将 Grafana 配置为使用&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/#anonymous-authentication&#34;&gt;匿名身份验证&lt;/a&gt;，这允许用户无需任何登录即可访问 Grafana。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终，您选择的身份验证类型取决于您组织的独特要求。大多数身份验证方法还允许您将用户权限从外部提供商同步到 Grafana，因此可以轻松控制访问。虽然这超出了本博文的范围，但您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/&#34;&gt;我们的技术文档&lt;/a&gt;中阅读更多内容。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-use-sso-with-grafana&#34;&gt;为什么将 SSO 与 Grafana 结合使用？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 SSO 可能不适用于所有类型的组织和用户，但与其他形式的身份验证相比，它具有多种优势，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;增强安全性和更好的合规性&lt;/strong&gt;：集中身份验证可降低凭据泄露的风险。它使执行策略和维护审计跟踪变得更加容易，而且扩展性也非常好。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;更好的用户体验&lt;/strong&gt;：用户无需单独登录即可访问 Grafana 资源（也称为无密码疲劳），管理员可以从集中位置管理用户访问和权限（例如，他们的IdP）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-new-in-grafana-sso-configuration&#34;&gt;Grafana SSO 配置有哪些新增功能？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从历史上看，在 Grafana 中配置 SSO 需要更新静态配置文件并重新启动 Grafana 实例才能使更改生效。这个过程可能很麻烦并且具有破坏性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Grafana 10 版本中，我们&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/07/27/new-in-grafana-10-a-ui-to-easily-configure-saml-authentication/&#34;&gt;引入了新的 UI 可轻松配置 SAML 身份验证&lt;/a&gt;。感谢社区的反馈，我们决定简化整个 SSO 设置流程，并引入了以下更新，从 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-11-release-all-the-new-功能/&#34;&gt;Grafana 11&lt;/a&gt;：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UI 配置&lt;/strong&gt;：直接通过 Grafana 用户界面配置 SSO。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API 支持&lt;/strong&gt;：使用 Grafana 的 API 自动化 SSO 设置和管理。 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/developers/http_api/sso-settings/&#34;&gt;请参阅文档&lt;/a&gt;了解更多信息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terraform 集成&lt;/strong&gt;：通过 Terraform 支持将 SSO 配置作为代码进行管理。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://registry.terraform.io/providers/grafana/grafana/latest/docs/resources/sso_settings&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;请参阅文档&lt;/a&gt;更多信息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;configuration-files-vs-the-uiapi&#34;&gt;配置文件与 UI/API&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仍然支持通过 Grafana 配置文件配置 SSO，并且可能适用于某些场景，包括基础设施自动化有限的情况。也就是说，使用 UI 或 API 代替配置文件具有以下优点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在 Grafana Cloud 中提供&lt;/strong&gt;：在 Grafana Cloud 实例内设置 SSO，无需提交支持请求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;实时配置验证&lt;/strong&gt;：使用 UI 或 API 时，所有设置都会实时验证，从而提供有关配置有效性的即时反馈。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;无需重新启动 Grafana&lt;/strong&gt;：使用 UI 或 API 无需在进行更改后重新启动 Grafana。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RBAC 授权&lt;/strong&gt;：您可以使用基于角色的访问控制 (RBAC) 灵活地授权特定用户访问 UI 或 API。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不建议混合配置方法（例如，在配置文件中定义一些字段，而通过 API 定义一些字段）。如果由于某种原因必须使用这两个选项来完成配置，Grafana 在加载配置时将遵循特定的优先顺序：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用 UI/API 或 Terraform 配置的设置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;来自环境变量的设置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Grafana 配置文件中的设置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;exploring-the-authentication-user-interface&#34;&gt;探索身份验证用户界面&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要访问 Grafana 或 Grafana Cloud 中的 UI，请导航至 Grafana 实例的导航菜单中的&lt;strong&gt;管理 &gt; 身份验证&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请注意，要访问此页面，用户必须具有&lt;em&gt;settings:read&lt;/em&gt;和&lt;em&gt;settings:write&lt;/em&gt;权限。通过将 *settings:auth.{provider}:** 范围与适当的提供程序结合使用，您可以通过指示用户可以设置哪些特定提供程序来控制访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;图片&#xA;类=“lazyload d-inline-block”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-SSO-overview/grafana-SSO-authentication-settings.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;身份验证设置页面的屏幕截图。&#34; width=&#34;1882&#34;&#xA;高度=“1248”/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;best-practices-to-set-up-sso&#34;&gt;设置 SSO 的最佳实践&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;设置 SSO 需要了解身份提供商和 Grafana。拥有数百个可用的身份提供商，提供内置为所有这些国家提供支持是不可行的。这就是 Grafana 支持通用 OAuth 配置的原因，该配置可用于与任何支持 OAuth 2.0 的身份提供商设置 SSO。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是在 Grafana 中设置 SSO 时需要遵循的一些通用准则：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;了解您的身份提供商&lt;/strong&gt;：每个 IdP 都有特定的要求和怪癖，因此在继续操作之前请彻底查阅他们的文档。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;正确配置重定向统一资源标识符 (URI)&lt;/strong&gt;：确保 IdP 中配置的重定向 URI 与 Grafana 中指定的重定向 URI 完全匹配。不正确的 URI 可能会导致身份验证失败。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;如果 Grafana 支持您的提供商，请避免使用通用 OAuth&lt;/strong&gt;。如果您使用的是 Azure Active Directory、Okta、Google、GitHub 或 GitLab，请为它们使用适当的配置并避免通用 OAuth。这种方法简化了设置并且不易出错。此外，配置更加细粒度，因为通用 OAuth 无法提供某些功能。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用 OAuth 时，配置&lt;em&gt;allowed_domains、allowed_groups&lt;/em&gt; 或&lt;em&gt;allowed_organizations&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：这将减少用户帐户的攻击面并创建深度防御（ DiD）以防身份验证被绕过。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为 OAuth 集成启用 &lt;em&gt;use_pkce=true&lt;/em&gt;：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://auth0.com/docs/get-started/authentication-and-authorization- flow/authorization-code-flow-with-pkce&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;代码交换证明密钥 (PKCE)&lt;/a&gt; 是 OAuth 的重要补充，在未来版本中可能是强制性的协议的。从一开始就启用它，以避免 IdP 更新中断（自 Grafana 10.1 起默认启用）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;设置 SAML 时使用请求签名&lt;/strong&gt;：请求签名是 SAML 中的一项关键安全功能，可增强身份验证过程的整体安全性。它确保 SAML 请求是真实的、未更改的，并且来自受信任的服务提供商，从而保护系统免受各种威胁并确保符合安全标准。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;设置自动登录&lt;/strong&gt;：适用于 OAuth 和 SAML，这将改善用户体验。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;troubleshooting-sso-setup&#34;&gt;SSO 设置问题排查&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;设置 SSO 需要在多个位置进行配置，有时，第一次可能无法成功。做好准备并拥有正确的调试工具可以简化流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;be-familiar-with-identity-protocols&#34;&gt;熟悉身份协议&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大多数身份验证协议都涉及多个组件之间的浏览器重定向和 HTTP 请求/响应，因此如果您熟悉特定场景的预期交互顺序，故障排除将会更容易。具体来说，了解以下内容会很有帮助：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;李&gt;每个协议端点期望的参数&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;每个端点返回的响应和错误代码&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;身份提供商 API&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;have-the-right-tools&#34;&gt;拥有合适的工具&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用于捕获和查看&lt;strong&gt;HTTP 跟踪&lt;/strong&gt;的工具对于在 SSO 设置期间进行故障排除特别有帮助。大多数互联网浏览器提供的开发工具具有内置功能，可以在“网络”选项卡中捕获 HTTP 跟踪。能够将 HTTP 跟踪转储为 HTTP 存档格式（.har 文件）也很方便，这将捕获所有内容，包括任何秘密的明文值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用于 SSO 调试和故障排除的工具的其他示例包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.postman.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Postman&lt;/a&gt; 或 &lt;a href=&#34;https://insomnia.rest/ &#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Insomnia&lt;/a&gt; 测试 API 调用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.telerik.com/fiddler/configure-fiddler/tasks/configurefiddler&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Fiddler&lt;/a&gt; 或 &lt;a href= &#34;https://www.charlesproxy.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Charlesproxy&lt;/a&gt; 用于捕获和查看后端 API 调用的网络跟踪&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jwt.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://jwt.io/&lt;/a&gt; 查看和创建 JWT&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;SAML 跟踪器，适用于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/saml-tracer/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Firefox &lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://chromewebstore.google.com/detail/saml-tracer/mpdajninpobndbfcldcmbpnnbhibjmch?hl=en&amp;pli=1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Chrome&lt;/a &gt;，检查 SAML 请求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;know-these-debugging-basics&#34;&gt;了解这些调试基础知识&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当某些事情没有按预期工作时，尤其是在身份验证方面，最好开始检查简单的事情。例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;检查身份提供商是否可以访问并且没有遇到任何问题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;确保提供的凭据对于环境而言正确&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;检查登录帐户和凭据是否未停用或过期&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;确保 Grafana 使用正确的身份提供商 URL&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;验证客户端 ID 是否与身份提供商中注册的 ID 匹配&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;检查重定向/回调网址&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;阅读所有错误消息，看看它们是否提供了有价值的线索&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;下一步是什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们希望最近所做的与 UI、API 和 Terraform 相关的更新能够增强您使用 Grafana 的体验并简化 SSO 设置过程。展望未来，我们计划引入用于配置 LDAP 的新 UI 和 API，这将使身份验证设置更加容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同时，如果您想详细了解如何在 Grafana 中组织用户和团队以确保最佳安全性，请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/03/14/how-to-best -组织你的团队和资源-grafana/&#34;&gt;这篇博文&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册&lt;/a&gt;！&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to authenticate with third-party APIs in your Grafana app plugin】如何在 Grafana 应用插件中使用第三方 API 进行身份验证</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/25/how-to-authenticate-with-third-party-apis-in-your-grafana-app-plugin/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Whether they’re for synthetic monitoring, large-language models, or some other use case, Grafana application plugins are a fantastic way to enhance your overall Grafana experience. Data for these custom experiences can come from a variety of sources, including nested data sources. However, they can also come from third-party APIs, which usually require authentication to access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This blog post explains, step by step, how to securely authenticate against third-party APIs when developing your Grafana app plugin. By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll understand how to handle authentication securely, ensuring that sensitive credentials are protected throughout interactions with third-party APIs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: For those new to Grafana, it might be helpful to understand the distinctions between our panel plugins, data source plugins, and application plugins before continuing with this post. Each plugin type serves a unique purpose and has different capabilities within the Grafana ecosystem. You can find a detailed overview of each type in our &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/key-concepts/plugin-types-usage&#34;&gt;developer documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-need-for-secure-authentication-with-third-party-apis&#34;&gt;The need for secure authentication with third-party APIs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When integrating with third-party APIs, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to secure your connection and use authentication credentials to protect sensitive data from unauthorized access. The mishandling of authentication can expose you to several risks, including credential leaks, man-in-the-middle attacks, replay attacks, impersonation, and compliance violations. This could happen, for example, if you simply store your API authentication credentials in plain text, directly inside your frontend components, and then use them to call a third-party API.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To avoid these risks, it’s essential to implement robust security measures for API credentials and ensure encrypted communications with third-party services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;secure-api-authentication-in-grafana-app-plugins&#34;&gt;Secure API authentication in Grafana app plugins&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the following steps will help you securely authenticate against a third-party API within a Grafan app plugin, they can also be used within a backend data source plugin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are several best practices to ensure credentials are handled safely and that plugins do not expose sensitive information, either in transit or at rest:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In transit&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensure you’re using HTTPS at all times to guarantee secure communication.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At rest&lt;/strong&gt;: Use &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/create-a-plugin/extend-a-plugin/add-authentication-for-data-source-plugins#store-configuration-in-securejsondata&#34;&gt;Grafana&amp;rsquo;s SecureJsonData&lt;/a&gt; plugin configuration to securely store sensitive data like API keys.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimize scope of visibility&lt;/strong&gt;: Use the &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/key-concepts/backend-plugins/#resources&#34;&gt;Resources feature&lt;/a&gt; in the Grafana plugin architecture to act as an intermediary for requests to third-party APIs. This lets you securely fetch data in the frontend without exposing credentials to the client.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 917px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A diagram depicting best practices to ensure credentials are handled safely. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;917&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;523&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A diagram depicting best practices to ensure credentials are handled safely. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;917&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;523&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;handling-api-keys&#34;&gt;Handling API keys&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana provides a mechanism to store sensitive information, such as API keys or passwords, using secure JSON data fields within the plugin’s configuration. These credentials are encrypted and can only be accessed server-side, ensuring they are not exposed in the browser.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When bootstrapping your Grafana app plugin, using the &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/#quick-start&#34;&gt;Create Plugin CLI tool&lt;/a&gt;, your app plugin source code will contain a configuration page with an example for storing secure credentials. This can be found in the &lt;code&gt;src/components/AppConfig/AppConfig.tsx&lt;/code&gt; file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 590px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the out-of-the-box Grafana app plugin configuration settings page.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;590&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;273&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*The out-of-the-box Grafana app plugin configuration settings page.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the out-of-the-box Grafana app plugin configuration settings page.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;590&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;273&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*The out-of-the-box Grafana app plugin configuration settings page.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The out-of-the-box Grafana app plugin configuration settings page.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You will see that there are two pieces of data being stored as part of the plugin’s configuration: &lt;code&gt;apiUrl&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;apiKey&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Inside of the configuration page’s source code, you’ll notice the &lt;strong&gt;Submit&lt;/strong&gt; button has an &lt;code&gt;onClick&lt;/code&gt; handler that calls the &lt;code&gt;updatePluginAndReload&lt;/code&gt; function as shown below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;updatePluginAndReload(plugin.meta.id, {&#xA;enabled,&#xA;pinned,&#xA;jsonData: {&#xA;apiUrl: state.apiUrl,&#xA;},&#xA;secureJsonData: state.isApiKeySet&#xA;? undefined&#xA;: {&#xA;apiKey: state.apiKey,&#xA;},&#xA;})&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This call to the &lt;code&gt;updatePluginAndReload&lt;/code&gt; function saves the user’s configuration form input in the plugin’s configuration settings. The &lt;code&gt;apiUrl&lt;/code&gt; is being stored as plain JSON data, while the &lt;code&gt;apiKey&lt;/code&gt; is being stored as secure JSON data. This means the frontend of your app plugin has no way to retrieve the raw value of the &lt;code&gt;apiKey&lt;/code&gt; which can therefore only be used by the backend part of your plugin. This ensures that your API credentials remain private and secure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember to run your development Grafana instance and navigate to your app plugin’s configuration page to update the configuration appropriately with your third-party API credentials.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, for development purposes, you may want to enter default values for your plugin’s configuration via the &lt;code&gt;provisioning/plugins/app.yaml&lt;/code&gt; file, as shown below. This will default your plugin’s configuration to the values entered in this file each time the Docker containers are restarted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 419px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot showing default values for the plugin&amp;#39;s configuration.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;419&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;270&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot showing default values for the plugin&amp;#39;s configuration.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;419&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;270&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As mentioned earlier, it is incredibly important that you use HTTPS to create a secure connection to your API.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;creating-a-resources-endpoint-to-call-the-third-party-api&#34;&gt;Creating a Resources endpoint to call the third-party API&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana plugins can use the Resources functionality to allow the frontend to retrieve arbitrary data from the plugin’s backend. What you decide to expose via the Resources endpoints is entirely up to you as the developer, but in this instance, we will use a Resources endpoint to retrieve data from an authenticated third-party API.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Resources endpoints within your app plugin are configured inside the &lt;code&gt;pkg/plugin/resources.go&lt;/code&gt; file. Inside this file there is a &lt;code&gt;registerRoutes&lt;/code&gt; function that defines which Resources endpoints are available within your app plugin.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To register a new endpoint, define it within the &lt;code&gt;registerRoutes&lt;/code&gt; function, as shown below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;func (a *App) registerRoutes(mux *http.ServeMux) {&#xA;mux.HandleFunc(&amp;#34;/ping&amp;#34;, a.handlePing)&#xA;mux.HandleFunc(&amp;#34;/echo&amp;#34;, a.handleEcho)&#xA;mux.HandleFunc(&amp;#34;/my-new-endpoint&amp;#34;, a.handleMyNewEndpoint) // Newly registered endpoint&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Above we have defined a new Resources endpoint that can be accessed at the Resources location for our plugin by the frontend – for example, &lt;code&gt;/api/plugins/&amp;lt;your-plugin-id&amp;gt;/resources/my-new-endpoint&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This new endpoint is configured to be handled by a new function, &lt;code&gt;a.handleMyNewEndpoint&lt;/code&gt;. We must implement this function, which is a standard Go HTTP handler, in order to return data to the frontend when the endpoint is called.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a look at an example implementation that gets the API URL and API key from your plugin configuration, and then makes an authenticated HTTP request to the third-party API before returning the data to the client.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;func (a *App) handleMyNewEndpoint(w http.ResponseWriter, req *http.Request) {&#xA;// Only allow HTTP GET calls&#xA;if req.Method != http.MethodGet {&#xA;http.Error(w, &amp;#34;method not allowed&amp;#34;, http.StatusMethodNotAllowed)&#xA;return&#xA;}&#xA;// Get the Plugin context&#xA;pCtx := httpadapter.PluginConfigFromContext(req.Context())&#xA;// Get the API Key from the plugin’s secure JSON configuration data&#xA;apiKey, exists := pCtx.AppInstanceSettings.DecryptedSecureJSONData[&amp;#34;apiKey&amp;#34;]&#xA;if !exists {&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;return&#xA;}&#xA;// Get the API URL from the plugin’s standard JSON configuration data&#xA;var config pluginConfig&#xA;if err := json.Unmarshal(pCtx.AppInstanceSettings.JSONData, &amp;amp;config); err != nil {&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;return&#xA;}&#xA;if config.ApiUrl == &amp;#34;&amp;#34; {&#xA;return nil, errors.New(&amp;#34;no api url configured&amp;#34;)&#xA;}&#xA;// Define the full API endpoint to call (in this instance the /profile endpoint of the third-party API)&#xA;apiUrl := fmt.Sprintf(&amp;#34;%s/profile&amp;#34;, config.ApiUrl)&#xA;// Create a new HTTP request to the API&#xA;client := &amp;amp;http.Client{}&#xA;apiReq, err := http.NewRequest(&amp;#34;GET&amp;#34;, apiUrl, nil)&#xA;if err != nil {&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;return&#xA;}&#xA;// Set the Authorization header using the API Key&#xA;apiReq.Header.Set(&amp;#34;Authorization&amp;#34;, fmt.Sprintf(&amp;#34;Bearer %s&amp;#34;, apiKey))&#xA;// Make the request&#xA;apiResp, err := client.Do(apiReq)&#xA;if err != nil {&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;return&#xA;}&#xA;defer apiResp.Body.Close()&#xA;// Read the response body&#xA;body, err := io.ReadAll(apiResp.Body)&#xA;if err != nil {&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;return&#xA;}&#xA;// Write the response body as JSON for the caller to consume&#xA;w.Header().Set(&amp;#34;Content-Type&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;application/json&amp;#34;)&#xA;w.Write(body)&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The above code uses the plugin’s configuration to call out to the authenticated third-party API’s &lt;code&gt;/profile&lt;/code&gt; endpoint and return the data to the client.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember, in order for this new Resources endpoint to take effect, the backend source code of the plugin must be rebuilt using the &lt;code&gt;mage -v build:linux&lt;/code&gt; command and then the Docker containers must be restarted using Docker Compose.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;calling-the-resources-endpoint-from-the-frontend&#34;&gt;Calling the Resources endpoint from the frontend&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your plugin’s frontend can now use the newly created Resources endpoint to retrieve data from the authenticated third-party API.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To call the Resources endpoint, use the &lt;code&gt;getBackendSrv().fetch()&lt;/code&gt; function, which is part of the &lt;code&gt;@grafana/runtime&lt;/code&gt; package. We also use the &lt;code&gt;lastValueFrom&lt;/code&gt; function, which is available as part of the &lt;code&gt;rxjs&lt;/code&gt; package.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An example of this is shown below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;const response = getBackendSrv().fetch({&#xA;url: &amp;#39;api/plugins/myorg-myplugin-app/resources/my-new-endpoint&#xA;});&#xA;const value = await lastValueFrom(response) as any;&#xA;console.log(value);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The above code will make a call to the new Resources endpoint, grab the value from the response, and output it to the browser’s console.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-learn-more&#34;&gt;How to learn more&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By following the steps above, you can securely authenticate against third-party APIs within your Grafana app plugin, ensuring that your integrations are not only powerful, but secure. This method protects sensitive credentials and maintains the integrity and security of your data flows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information on Grafana plugin development and the Resources API, refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/&#34;&gt;Grafana developer portal&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, you can explore &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;our community forums&lt;/a&gt; to learn best practices and get support from other Grafana developers.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;无论是用于综合监控、大型语言模型还是其他用例，Grafana 应用程序插件都是增强 Grafana 整体体验的绝佳方式。这些自定义体验的数据可以来自多种来源，包括嵌套数据源。但是，它们也可以来自第三方 API，这些 API 通常需要身份验证才能访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这篇博文逐步解释了在开发 Grafana 应用插件时如何针对第三方 API 进行安全身份验证。最后，您将了解如何安全地处理身份验证，确保敏感凭据在与第三方 API 的交互过程中受到保护。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：对于 Grafana 的新手来说，在继续本文之前了解我们的面板插件、数据源插件和应用程序插件之间的区别可能会有所帮助。每种插件类型都有其独特的用途，并且在 Grafana 生态系统中具有不同的功能。您可以在我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/key-concepts/plugin-types-usage&#34;&gt;开发人员文档&lt;/a&gt;中找到每种类型的详细概述。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-need-for-secure-authentication-with-third-party-apis&#34;&gt;使用第三方 API 进行安全身份验证的需求&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与第三方 API 集成时，确保连接安全并使用身份验证凭据来保护敏感数据免遭未经授权的访问至关重要。身份验证处理不当可能会让您面临多种风险，包括凭证泄露、中间人攻击、重放攻击、冒充和违反合规性。例如，如果您只是以纯文本形式直接将 API 身份验证凭据存储在前端组件内，然后使用它们调用第三方 API，则可能会发生这种情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了避免这些风险，必须对 API 凭据实施强大的安全措施并确保与第三方服务的加密通信。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;secure-api-authentication-in-grafana-app-plugins&#34;&gt;Grafana 应用插件中的安全 API 身份验证&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然以下步骤将帮助您在 Grafan 应用插件中安全地对第三方 API 进行身份验证，但它们也可以在后端数据源插件中使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有几种最佳实践可以确保安全处理凭证，并且插件不会暴露敏感信息，无论是在传输中还是静态：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;传输中&lt;/strong&gt;：确保您始终使用 HTTPS 以保证安全通信。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;休息时&lt;/strong&gt;：使用&lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/create-a-plugin/extend-a-plugin/add-authentication-for-data-source-plugins# store-configuration-in-securejsondata&#34;&gt;Grafana 的 SecureJsonData&lt;/a&gt; 插件配置，用于安全存储 API 密钥等敏感数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;最小化可见范围&lt;/strong&gt;：使用&lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/key-concepts/backend-plugins/#resources&#34;&gt;Grafana 插件架构中的资源功能&lt;/a&gt;充当第三方 API 请求的中介。这使您可以安全地在前端获取数据，而无需向客户端公开凭据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：917px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png” png?w=320 320w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs- graph.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating- APIs-diagram.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/身份验证-API-diagram.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;描述确保安全处理凭证的最佳实践的图表。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“917”&#xA;高度=“523”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-diagram.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;描述确保安全处理凭证的最佳实践的图表。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“917”&#xA;高度=“523”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;handling-api-keys&#34;&gt;处理 API 密钥&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana 提供了一种在插件配置中使用安全 JSON 数据字段来存储敏感信息（例如 API 密钥或密码）的机制。这些凭据经过加密，只能在服务器端访问，确保它们不会在浏览器中公开。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用&lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/#quick-start&#34;&gt;创建插件 CLI 工具&lt;/a&gt;引导 Grafana 应用插件时，您的应用插件源代码将包含一个配置页面，其中包含存储安全凭证的示例。这可以在 &lt;code&gt;src/components/AppConfig/AppConfig.tsx&lt;/code&gt; 文件中找到。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：590px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings。 png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/authentiating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/ authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/博客/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;开箱即用的 Grafana 应用程序插件配置设置页面的屏幕截图。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“590”&#xA;高度=“273”&#xA;title=&#34;*开箱即用的 Grafana 应用插件配置设置页面。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-settings.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;开箱即用的 Grafana 应用插件配置设置页面的屏幕截图。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“590”&#xA;高度=“273”&#xA;title=&#34;*开箱即用的 Grafana 应用插件配置设置页面。*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;开箱即用的 Grafana 应用插件配置设置页面。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您将看到插件配置中存储了两部分数据：&lt;code&gt;apiUrl&lt;/code&gt; 和 &lt;code&gt;apiKey&lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在配置页面的源代码中，您会注意到&lt;strong&gt;Submit&lt;/strong&gt;按钮有一个&lt;code&gt;onClick&lt;/code&gt;处理程序，它调用&lt;code&gt;updatePluginAndReload&lt;/code&gt;函数，如图所示如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;updatePluginAndReload(plugin.meta.id, {&#xA;启用，&#xA;固定,&#xA;json数据：{&#xA;apiUrl: 状态.apiUrl,&#xA;},&#xA;secureJsonData：state.isApiKeySet&#xA;？不明确的&#xA;：{&#xA;apiKey: 状态.apiKey,&#xA;},&#xA;})&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;对 &lt;code&gt;updatePluginAndReload&lt;/code&gt; 函数的调用会将用户的配置表单输入保存在插件的配置设置中。 &lt;code&gt;apiUrl&lt;/code&gt; 存储为纯 JSON 数据，而 &lt;code&gt;apiKey&lt;/code&gt; 存储为安全 JSON 数据。这意味着您的应用插件的前端无法检索 apiKey 的原始值，因此只能由插件的后端部分使用。这可确保您的 API 凭据保持私密性和安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请记住运行您的开发 Grafana 实例并导航到应用插件的配置页面，以使用您的第三方 API 凭据适当更新配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;或者，出于开发目的s，您可能需要通过 &lt;code&gt;provisioning/plugins/app.yaml&lt;/code&gt; 文件输入插件配置的默认值，如下所示。每次重新启动 Docker 容器时，这都会将插件的配置默认为在此文件中输入的值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：419px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs- default-values.png?w=320 320w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-插件/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/ authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=1240 1240w ，/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;显示插件配置默认值的屏幕截图。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“419”&#xA;高度=“270”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/authenticating-APIs-grafana-plugins/authenticating-APIs-default-values.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;显示插件配置默认值的屏幕截图。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“419”&#xA;高度=“270”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如前所述，使用 HTTPS 创建与 API 的安全连接非常重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;creating-a-resources-endpoint-to-call-the-third-party-api&#34;&gt;创建资源端点以调用第三方 API&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana 插件可以使用资源功能来允许前端从插件的后端检索任意数据。您决定通过资源端点公开什么完全取决于您作为开发人员，但在本例中，我们将使用资源端点从经过身份验证的第三方 API 检索数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;应用插件中的资源端点在 &lt;code&gt;pkg/plugin/resources.go&lt;/code&gt; 文件中配置。该文件内有一个 &lt;code&gt;registerRoutes&lt;/code&gt; 函数，用于定义应用插件中可用的资源端点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要注册新端点，请在 &lt;code&gt;registerRoutes&lt;/code&gt; 函数中定义它，如下所示：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;func (a *App) registerRoutes(mux *http.ServeMux) {&#xA;mux.HandleFunc(&#34;/ping&#34;, a.handlePing)&#xA;mux.HandleFunc(&#34;/echo&#34;, a.handleEcho)&#xA;mux.HandleFunc(&#34;/my-new-endpoint&#34;, a.handleMyNewEndpoint) // 新注册的端点&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;上面我们定义了一个新的资源端点，前端可以在我们的插件的资源位置访问该端点 - 例如，&lt;code&gt;/api/plugins/&lt;your-plugin-id&gt;/resources /我的新端点&lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个新端点配置为由新函数&lt;code&gt;a.handleMyNewEndpoint&lt;/code&gt; 处理。我们必须实现这个函数，它是一个标准的 Go HTTP 处理程序，以便在调用端点时将数据返回到前端。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们看一个示例实现，它从插件配置中获取 API URL 和 API 密钥，然后向第三方 API 发出经过身份验证的 HTTP 请求，然后再将数据返回给客户端。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;func (a *App) handleMyNewEndpoint(w http.ResponseWriter, req *http.Request) {&#xA;// 只允许 HTTP GET 调用&#xA;if req.Method != http.MethodGet {&#xA;http.Error(w, &#34;不允许的方法&#34;, http.StatusMethodNotAllowed)&#xA;返回&#xA;}&#xA;// 获取插件上下文&#xA;pCtx := httpadapter.PluginConfigFromContext(req.Context())&#xA;// 从插件的安全 JSON 配置数据中获取 API 密钥&#xA;apiKey，存在：= pCtx.AppInstanceSettings.DecryptedSecureJSONData[“apiKey”]&#xA;如果！存在{&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;返回&#xA;}&#xA;// 从插件的标准 JSON 配置数据中获取 API URL&#xA;var config 插件配置&#xA;if err := json.Unmarshal(pCtx.AppInstanceSettings.JSONData, &amp;config);错误！=零{&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;返回&#xA;}&#xA;如果 config.ApiUrl == &#34;&#34; {&#xA;return nil, error.New(&#34;没有配置 api url&#34;)&#xA;}&#xA;// 定义要调用的完整 API 端点（在本例中为第三方 API 的 /profile 端点）&#xA;apiUrl := fmt.Sprintf(&#34;%s/profile&#34;, config.ApiUrl)&#xA;// 创建一个新的 API 请求&#xA;客户端 := &amp;http.Client{}&#xA;apiReq, err := http.NewRequest(&#34;GET&#34;, apiUrl, nil)&#xA;如果错误！= nil {&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;返回&#xA;}&#xA;// 使用 API 密钥设置授权标头&#xA;api请求.Header.Set(&#34;授权&#34;, fmt.Sprintf(&#34;承载%s&#34;, apiKey))&#xA;// 发出请求&#xA;apiResp, err := client.Do(apiReq)&#xA;如果错误！= nil {&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;返回&#xA;}&#xA;延迟 apiResp.Body.Close()&#xA;// 读取响应体&#xA;body, err := io.ReadAll(apiResp.Body)&#xA;如果错误！= nil {&#xA;http.Error(w, err.Error(), http.StatusInternalServerError)&#xA;返回&#xA;}&#xA;// 将响应体写入 JSON 供调用者使用&#xA;w.Header().Set(&#34;Content-Type&#34;, &#34;application/json&#34;)&#xA;w.Write（正文）&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;上述代码使用插件的配置来调用经过身份验证的第三方API的&lt;code&gt;/profile&lt;/code&gt;端点并将数据返回给客户端。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请记住，为了使这个新的资源端点生效，必须使用 &lt;code&gt;mage -v build:linux&lt;/code&gt; 命令重建插件的后端源代码，然后必须重新启动 Docker 容器使用 Docker Compose。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;calling-the-resources-endpoint-from-the-frontend&#34;&gt;从前端调用资源端点&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您的插件的前端现在可以使用新创建的资源端点从经过身份验证的第三方 API 检索数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要调用资源端点，请使用 &lt;code&gt;getBackendSrv().fetch()&lt;/code&gt; 函数，该函数是 &lt;code&gt;@grafana/runtime&lt;/code&gt; 包的一部分。我们还使用 &lt;code&gt;lastValueFrom&lt;/code&gt; 函数，该函数作为 &lt;code&gt;rxjs&lt;/code&gt; 包的一部分提供。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下面显示了一个示例：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;常量响应 = getBackendSrv().fetch({&#xA;url: &#39;api/plugins/myorg-myplugin-app/resources/my-new-endpoint&#xA;});&#xA;const value = 等待lastValueFrom(response) as any;&#xA;console.log(值);&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;上面的代码将调用新的资源端点，从响应中获取值，并将其输出到浏览器的控制台。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-learn-more&#34;&gt;如何了解更多信息&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过执行上述步骤，您可以安全地对 Grafana 应用插件中的第三方 API 进行身份验证，确保您的集成不仅强大，而且安全。此方法可以保护敏感凭据并维护数据流的完整性和安全性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关 Grafana 插件开发和资源 API 的更多信息，请参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/&#34;&gt;Grafana 开发者门户&lt;/a&gt;。此外，您还可以探索&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;我们的社区论坛&lt;/a&gt;以获取最佳知识实践并获得其他 Grafana 开发人员的支持。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to set up an open source database monitoring stack with Grafana Cloud】如何使用 Grafana Cloud 设置开源数据库监控堆栈</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/22/how-to-set-up-an-open-source-database-monitoring-stack-with-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;One of the great powers of Grafana is the open source community behind it — a community that provides a breadth of ready-to-use dashboards, plugins, exporters, and instructions that make a million tasks easier. The sheer scale of it all means whatever you need probably already exists somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate this, I want to share an example of how to use these tools as a base for building a comprehensive database monitoring solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a popular use case because proprietary monitoring tools are often expensive and inflexible. This results in organizations limiting access to these tools when more stakeholders could benefit from their use. But by combining Prometheus and &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud//?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;, you can build an ideal replacement as they are both extraordinarily flexible and free.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;addressing-a-real-world-database-observability-issue&#34;&gt;Addressing a real-world database observability issue&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I had the opportunity to show an organization how to combine Grafana and Prometheus to gain insight into the performance of their Oracle database. The main stakeholder was a senior vice president who needed to monitor the data layer of their most profitable software product.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since they deliver software as a service to the financial services industry, they need every transaction to happen at high speed. They previously used a closed-source tool to gather and visualize performance information about their database, in particular information about performance and long-running queries. They had a proprietary agent deployed alongside Oracle and visualized the data in a legacy tool with an inflexible front end. They needed to move off this solution due to cost constraints and lack of flexibility. As Grafana and Prometheus users already, they were perfectly positioned to leverage these tools for Oracle database observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We started our search for a solution using &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/alloy-opentelemetry-collector/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt; and Grafana Cloud. We needed something that was flexible enough to let us create the views we needed but also quick and easy to get started with. For the remainder of this blog, we&amp;rsquo;ll recreate what I did for that user so you can follow along and build your own open source database monitoring stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-pair-alloy-and-grafana-to-monitor-oracle&#34;&gt;How to pair Alloy and Grafana to monitor Oracle&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Alloy&lt;/strong&gt; is an open source, vendor-neutral distribution of the OpenTelemetry (OTel) Collector. Alloy uniquely combines the very best OSS observability signals in the community and is fully compatible with the OTel Collector, Prometheus Agent, and Promtail. In addition, Alloy embeds a wide range of Prometheus collectors. This includes the community open source &lt;a href=&#34;[https://github.com/iamseth/oracledb_exporter]%28https://github.com/iamseth/oracledb_exporter%29&#34;&gt;OracleDB exporter&lt;/a&gt;, which makes it easier to get started since we can deploy a single binary to collect all the relevant signals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/strong&gt; is our cost effective, flexible SaaS offering that&amp;rsquo;s capable of delivering quick time to value. Grafana Cloud will act as both our datastore and our visualization/alerting solution. Using the &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;forever-free tier &lt;/a&gt;lets me iterate quickly without needing to spin up my own metric store and front-end visualization layer of Grafana. I can simply follow the &lt;a href=&#34;[https://grafana.com/docs/alloy/latest/tutorials/get-started/]%28https://grafana.com/docs/alloy/latest/tutorials/get-started/%29&#34;&gt;quick start instructions&lt;/a&gt; to deploy Alloy and start sending Oracle metrics to the cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;whats-in-the-box-initial-iteration&#34;&gt;What’s in the box: initial iteration&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud makes getting the first iteration up and running a breeze. I just need to navigate to &lt;strong&gt;Home&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Connections&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Add new connection&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;OracleDB&lt;/strong&gt; and then click &lt;strong&gt;Configuration Details&lt;/strong&gt; to get a full set of simple instructions to follow that require a few straightforward steps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1914px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Add new connection menu&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1914&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;996&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Add new connection menu&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1914&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;996&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Install Grafana Alloy.&lt;/strong&gt; The interface will lead you through a few interactive selections and generate a single command to run on your target system, which in my case is a CentOS system.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make configuration selections.&lt;/strong&gt; Here you will be asked to decide if you would like to gather extended metrics and if you’d like to send logs. Since I was trying to figure out exactly what was possible, I decided to turn both on. However, I would generally suggest you only turn on the base metrics to begin with and expand from there, if necessary. The decision comes down to cost. Every metric has a real dollar value and it is important to only collect metrics that you will use.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prepare our configuration file (and prepare our target database).&lt;/strong&gt; At this stage, Grafana Cloud provides commands you can copy and paste into Oracle to create a user. Grafana Alloy can then connect that user to Grafana Cloud, and it provides a ready-to-use configuration block you can simply add to your existing Grafana Alloy configuration from step 1.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Restart Grafana Alloy and test configurations.&lt;/strong&gt; The last step is to simply restart Grafana Alloy and test the connection.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1115px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Worfklow diagram with Oracle DB instance, Grafana Alloy, and Grafana Cloud&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1115&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;329&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Worfklow diagram with Oracle DB instance, Grafana Alloy, and Grafana Cloud&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1115&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;329&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this work done, metrics and logs are flowing into Grafana Cloud from my OracleDB and I can view the out-of-the-box dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OracleDB overview dashboard&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1197&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;OracleDB overview dashboard&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1197&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As pictured above, the integration provides many useful views of important system metrics like number of open sessions, number of processes, and wait time information, among other information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;outside-the-box-subsequent-iteration&#34;&gt;Outside the box: subsequent iteration&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the first iteration immediately demonstrated the power of Grafana to deliver value in a short period of time and proved it was a capable solution, we are now free to iterate on that design to deliver flexibility as well. I would recommend following this pattern as the base metrics provide an excellent out-of-the-box experience. Additional queries and metrics can certainly be defined if necessary, but understanding the base capabilities should be your first priority.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first iteration’s architecture relied on the embedded OracleDB exporter to extract metrics from the Oracle database. The embedded exporter, however, does not allow for the inclusion of custom defined metrics; it simply exports a fixed list of metrics as shown here: &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-oracledb//?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#metrics&#34;&gt;OracleDB integration | Grafana Cloud documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more detailed performance data, we need to use the upstream OracleDB exporter to gain the flexibility to define our own custom Oracle queries that yield our own custom metrics. Grafana’s commitment to delivering an open and composable solution means that it is easy for me to simply turn off embedded OracleDB exporter and instead deploy the upstream exporter and configure Alloy to scrape the metrics from its endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To deploy the upstream exporter, visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/iamseth/oracledb_exporter/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://github.com/iamseth/oracledb_exporter/&lt;/a&gt; to pull down the most recent release. We can then place the exporter alongside Alloy and configure it following the instructions from the GitHub repo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1646px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Workflow diagram with OracleDB instance, ORacleDB Exporter, Grafana Alloy, and Grafana Cloud&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1646&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;329&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Workflow diagram with OracleDB instance, ORacleDB Exporter, Grafana Alloy, and Grafana Cloud&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1646&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;329&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this updated architecture, we were then able to define our own custom metrics in a simple yaml file. For example, we can define four metrics with one block like this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt; metrics:&#xA;- context: &amp;#34;tablespace_capacity&amp;#34;&#xA;labels: [&amp;#34;tablespace&amp;#34;]&#xA;metricsdesc:&#xA;used_value: &amp;#34;Gauge amount used&amp;#34;&#xA;free_value: &amp;#34;Gauge amount free&amp;#34;&#xA;total_value: &amp;#34;Gauge total amount&amp;#34;&#xA;pfree_value: &amp;#34;Gauge percentage free&amp;#34;&#xA;request: &amp;#34;SELECT fs.tablespace_name tbspcname,&#xA;( df.totalspace - fs.freespace ) used_value,&#xA;fs.freespace free_value,&#xA;df.totalspace total_value,&#xA;Round(100 * ( fs.freespace / df.totalspace )) pfree_value&#xA;FROM (SELECT tablespace_name,&#xA;Round(Sum(bytes) / 1048576) totalspace&#xA;FROM dba_data_files&#xA;GROUP BY tablespace_name) df,&#xA;(SELECT tablespace_name,&#xA;Round(Sum(bytes) / 1048576) freespace&#xA;FROM dba_free_space&#xA;GROUP BY tablespace_name) fs&#xA;WHERE df.tablespace_name = fs.tablespace_name&amp;#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;And we can define another important needed metric like this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt; - context: &amp;#34;cache_hit_ratio&amp;#34;&#xA;metricsdesc:&#xA;percentage: &amp;#34;Gauge metric with the cache hit ratio.&amp;#34;&#xA;request: &amp;#34;select&#xA;Round((&#xA;(Sum(Decode(a.name, &amp;#39;consistent gets&amp;#39;, a.value, 0))&#xA;&amp;#43; Sum(Decode(a.name, &amp;#39;db block gets&amp;#39;, a.value, 0))&#xA;- Sum(Decode(a.name, &amp;#39;physical reads&amp;#39;, a.value, 0))&#xA;)/&#xA;(Sum(Decode(a.name, &amp;#39;consistent gets&amp;#39;, a.value, 0))&#xA;&amp;#43; Sum(Decode(a.name, &amp;#39;db block gets&amp;#39;, a.value, 0)))) *100,2) as percentage&#xA;FROM v$sysstat a&amp;#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This new architecture gives us the exact flexibility we need to deliver the custom dashboards required.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1694px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for Oracle&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1694&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;759&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for Oracle&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1694&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;759&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1878px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for Oracle&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1878&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;824&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for Oracle&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1878&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;824&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;going-quickly-from-idea-to-solution&#34;&gt;Going quickly from idea to solution&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Combining the speed and power of Grafana Cloud with the breadth and depth of the open source community allows users to quickly deliver observability to a wide range of platforms. In this case, I was able to go from idea to solution in a matter of hours and deliver a powerful solution that met the business requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I strongly believe that Grafana and Prometheus together can deliver the database monitoring capabilities needed. Plus, Grafana Cloud&amp;rsquo;s free tier makes getting started easy, as we&amp;rsquo;ve has wrapped this all up into easy to follow instructions &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/oracle-database/monitor//?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;built directly into the product&lt;/a&gt;. If you have any questions, feel free to ask me in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Community Slack.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;Grafana 的强大功能之一是其背后的开源社区 - 该社区提供了大量即用型仪表板、插件、导出器和指令，使数百万个任务变得更加容易。这一切的庞大规模意味着您需要的任何东西可能已经存在于某个地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了说明这一点，我想分享一个示例，说明如何使用这些工具作为构建全面的数据库监控解决方案的基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一个流行的用例，因为专有监控工具通常昂贵且不灵活。当更多利益相关者可以从这些工具的使用中受益时，这会导致组织限制对这些工具的访问。但是，通过结合 Prometheus 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud//?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;，您可以构建一个理想的替代品，因为它们都非常灵活且免费。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;addressing-a-real-world-database-observability-issue&#34;&gt;解决现实世界的数据库可观察性问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最近，我有机会向一个组织展示如何结合 Grafana 和 Prometheus 来深入了解其 Oracle 数据库的性能。主要利益相关者是一位高级副总裁，他需要监控最赚钱的软件产品的数据层。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于他们向金融服务行业提供软件即服务，因此他们需要每笔交易都高速发生。他们之前使用闭源工具来收集和可视化有关其数据库的性能信息，特别是有关性能和长时间运行的查询的信息。他们与 Oracle 一起部署了专有代理，并在具有不灵活前端的遗留工具中可视化数据。由于成本限制和缺乏灵活性，他们需要放弃该解决方案。作为 Grafana 和 Prometheus 的用户，他们完全可以利用这些工具来实现 Oracle 数据库的可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们开始使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/alloy-opentelemetry-collector/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt; 和 Grafana Cloud 寻找解决方案。我们需要足够灵活的东西来创建我们需要的视图，但又快速且易于上手。在本博客的其余部分中，我们将重新创建我为该用户所做的事情，以便您可以继续构建自己的开源数据库监控堆栈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-pair-alloy-and-grafana-to-monitor-oracle&#34;&gt;如何配对 Alloy 和 Grafana 来监控 Oracle&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Alloy&lt;/strong&gt; 是 OpenTelemetry (OTel) 收集器的开源、供应商中立发行版。 Alloy 独特地结合了社区中最好的 OSS 可观测信号，并与 OTel Collector、Prometheus Agent 和 Promtail 完全兼容。此外，Alloy 还嵌入了广泛的 Prometheus 收集器。这包括社区开源 &lt;a href=&#34;[https://github.com/iamseth/oracledb_exporter]%28https://github.com/iamseth/oracledb_exporter%29&#34;&gt;OracleDB 导出器&lt;/a&gt;，这使得入门变得更容易，因为我们可以部署单个二进制文件来收集所有相关信号。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/strong&gt; 是我们经济高效、灵活的 SaaS 产品，能够快速实现价值。 Grafana Cloud 将充当我们的数据存储和可视化/警报解决方案。使用&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;永久免费层&lt;/a&gt;让我可以快速迭代，而无需启动自己的指标存储Grafana 的前端可视化层。我可以简单地按照 &lt;a href=&#34;[https://grafana.com/docs/alloy/latest/tutorials/get-started/]%28https://grafana.com/docs/alloy/latest/tutorials/get -started/%29&#34;&gt;部署 Alloy 并开始将 Oracle 指标发送到云的快速入门说明&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;whats-in-the-box-initial-iteration&#34;&gt;盒子里有什么：初始迭代&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 使第一次迭代的启动和运行变得轻而易举。我只需导航到&lt;strong&gt;主页&lt;/strong&gt; &gt; &lt;strong&gt;连接&lt;/strong&gt; &gt; &lt;strong&gt;添加新连接&lt;/strong&gt; &gt; &lt;strong&gt;OracleDB&lt;/strong&gt;，然后单击&lt;strong&gt;配置详细信息&lt;/strong&gt;以获得一整套简单的说明，需要遵循一些简单的步骤。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1914px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w= 320 320w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=750 750w , /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=1040 1040w, /媒体/博客/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-size=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;添加新连接菜单&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1914”&#xA;高度=“996”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/Grafana-cloud-ui.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;添加新连接菜单&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1914”&#xA;高度=“996”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安装 Grafana Alloy。&lt;/strong&gt;该界面将引导您完成一些交互式选择，并生成一个在目标系统上运行的命令，在我的例子中是 CentOS 系统。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;进行配置选择。&lt;/strong&gt;此处系统会要求您决定是否要收集扩展指标以及是否要发送日志。由于我试图弄清楚到底什么是可能的，所以我决定将两者都打开。但是，我通常建议您仅从一开始就打开基本指标，并在必要时从那里进行扩展。决定归结为成本。每个指标都有实际的美元价值，仅收集您将使用的指标非常重要。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;准备我们的配置文件（并准备我们的目标数据库）。&lt;/strong&gt;在此阶段，Grafana Cloud 提供了您可以复制并粘贴到 Oracle 中以创建用户的命令。然后，Grafana Alloy 可以将该用户连接到 Grafana Cloud，并提供一个随时可用的配置块，您只需将其添加到第 1 步中的现有 Grafana Alloy 配置中即可。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;重新启动 Grafana Alloy 并测试配置。&lt;/strong&gt;最后一步只需重新启动 Grafana Alloy 并测试连接即可。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1115px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=320 320w,/媒体/博客/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/oss- db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow- 1.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;包含 Oracle 数据库实例、Grafana Alloy 和 Grafana Cloud 的 Worfklow 图表&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1115”&#xA;高度=“329”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-1.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;包含 Oracle 数据库实例、Grafana Alloy 和 Grafana Cloud 的 Worfklow 图表&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1115”&#xA;高度=“329”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成这项工作后，指标和日志将从我的 OracleDB 流入 Grafana Cloud，我可以查看开箱即用的仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1999px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=320 320w, /媒体/博客/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png？w=550 550w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png？w=750 750w，/media/blog/oss- db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-仪表板.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-size=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OracleDB 概述仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1197”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oob-dashboard.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;OracleDB 概述仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1197”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/没有脚本&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如上图所示，集成提供了许多重要系统指标的有用视图，例如打开的会话数、进程数和等待时间信息等信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;outside-the-box-subsequent-iteration&#34;&gt;跳出框框：后续迭代&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然第一次迭代立即展示了 Grafana 在短时间内提供价值的能力，并证明它是一个强大的解决方案，但我们现在可以自由地迭代该设计以提供灵活性。我建议遵循这种模式，因为基本指标提供了出色的开箱即用体验。如有必要，当然可以定义其他查询和指标，但了解基本功能应该是您的首要任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第一次迭代的架构依赖于嵌入式 OracleDB 导出器从 Oracle 数据库中提取指标。然而，嵌入式导出器不允许包含自定义定义的指标；它只是导出固定的指标列表，如下所示： &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/integrations/integration-reference/integration-oracledb//?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt#metrics&#34; &gt;OracleDB集成| Grafana Cloud 文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于更详细的性能数据，我们需要使用上游 OracleDB 导出器来灵活地定义我们自己的自定义 Oracle 查询，从而生成我们自己的自定义指标。 Grafana 致力于提供开放且可组合的解决方案，这意味着我可以轻松关闭嵌入式 OracleDB 导出器，转而部署上游导出器并配置 Alloy 以从其端点获取指标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要部署上游导出器，请访问 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/iamseth/oracledb_exporter/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://github.com/iamseth/ oracledb_exporter/&lt;/a&gt; 来下载最新版本。然后，我们可以将导出器放在 Alloy 旁边，并按照 GitHub 存储库中的说明进行配置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1646px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=320 320w,/媒体/博客/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/oss- db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow- 2.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;包含 OracleDB 实例、ORacleDB Exporter、Grafana Alloy 和 Grafana Cloud 的工作流程图&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1646”高度=“329”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/workflow-2.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;包含 OracleDB 实例、ORacleDB Exporter、Grafana Alloy 和 Grafana Cloud 的工作流程图&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1646”&#xA;高度=“329”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过这个更新的架构，我们能够在一个简单的 yaml 文件中定义我们自己的自定义指标。例如，我们可以像这样用一个块定义四个指标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt; 指标：&#xA;- 上下文：“表空间_容量”&#xA;标签：[“表空间”]&#xA;指标描述：&#xA;used_value: &#34;已使用的量表数量&#34;&#xA;free_value: &#34;免费计量数量&#34;&#xA;total_value: &#34;计量总金额&#34;&#xA;pfree_value：“空闲仪表百分比”&#xA;请求：“SELECT fs.tablespace_name tbspcname，&#xA;( df.totalspace - fs.freespace ) 使用值，&#xA;fs.freespace 自由值，&#xA;df.totalspace 总值，&#xA;Round(100 * ( fs.freespace / df.totalspace )) pfree_value&#xA;FROM (SELECT 表空间名称,&#xA;Round(Sum(字节) / 1048576) 总空间&#xA;来自 dba_data_files&#xA;GROUP BY 表空间名称) df,&#xA;(选择表空间名称,&#xA;Round(总和(字节) / 1048576) 可用空间&#xA;来自 dba_free_space&#xA;GROUP BY 表空间名称) fs&#xA;WHERE df.tablespace_name = fs.tablespace_name&#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;我们可以像这样定义另一个重要的所需指标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt; - 上下文：“cache_hit_ratio”&#xA;指标描述：&#xA;百分比：“缓存命中率的衡量指标。”&#xA;请求：“选择&#xA;圆形的（（&#xA;(Sum(Decode(a.name, &#39;一致获取&#39;, a.value, 0))&#xA;+ Sum(Decode(a.name, &#39;db block gets&#39;, a.value, 0))&#xA;- Sum(Decode(a.name, &#39;物理读取&#39;, a.value, 0))&#xA;)/&#xA;(Sum(Decode(a.name, &#39;一致获取&#39;, a.value, 0))&#xA;+ Sum(Decode(a.name, &#39;db block gets&#39;, a.value, 0)))) *100,2) 作为百分比&#xA;来自 v$sysstat a&#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;这种新架构为我们提供了交付所需的自定义仪表板所需的精确灵活性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1694px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“l”右框链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=320 320w,/媒体/博客/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png？w=550 550w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png？w=750 750w，/media/blog/oss- db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-仪表板.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;适用于 Oracle 的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1694”&#xA;高度=“759”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Oracle 的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1694”&#xA;高度=“759”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1878px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w= 320 320w、/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=550 550w、/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=750 750w , /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png?w=1040 1040w, /媒体/博客/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png？w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png？w=1920 1920w”&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;适用于 Oracle 的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1878”&#xA;高度=“824”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/oss-db-monitoring/oracle-dashboard-2.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Oracle 的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1878”&#xA;高度=“824”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;going-quickly-from-idea-to-solution&#34;&gt;快速从想法转变为解决方案&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将 Grafana Cloud 的速度和功能与开源社区的广度和深度相结合，使用户能够快速向各种平台提供可观察性。在这种情况下，我能够在几个小时内将想法转变为解决方案，并提供满足业务需求的强大解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我坚信 Grafana 和 Prometheus 一起可以提供所需的数据库监控功能。另外，Grafana Cloud 的免费套餐让入门变得简单，因为我们已将这一切融入到易于遵循的说明中 &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/oracle-database/monitor//?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;直接内置到产品中&lt;/a&gt;。如果您有任何疑问，请随时在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Community Slack 中询问我.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Japan&#39;s space agency used Grafana to monitor its first moon landing in real time】日本航天局如何使用 Grafana 实时监控其首次登月</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/08/01/how-japans-space-agency-used-grafana-to-monitor-its-first-moon-landing-in-real-time/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When Japan&amp;rsquo;s space agency, JAXA, set out to make its first lunar landing in January, the goal wasn&amp;rsquo;t just to get its &lt;a href=&#34;https://global.jaxa.jp/projects/sas/slim/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SLIM (Smart Lander for Investigating Moon)&lt;/a&gt; spacecraft on the moon&amp;rsquo;s surface. The plan also called to touch down within 100 meters of its intended target — making for the world&amp;rsquo;s first pinpoint lunar landing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;JAXA&amp;rsquo;s doubly historic moment came on Jan. 19, 2024, as Japan became the fifth country to put a spacecraft on the moon. Back on Earth, the agency&amp;rsquo;s researchers and engineers monitored the operation in real time using &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/dashboards/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana dashboards&lt;/a&gt; that tracked SLIM&amp;rsquo;s critical functions including navigation, heater status, and landing maneuvers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/grafana-used-to-monitor-japan-slim-moon-lander/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2024 presentation&lt;/a&gt;, Satoshi Nakahira, an associate senior researcher at JAXA&amp;rsquo;s Institute of Space and Astronautical Science (ISAS), highlighted some of the agency&amp;rsquo;s work, discussed its observability system, and shared examples of the dashboards used during the lunar landing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana, he said, &amp;ldquo;played an important role in our operation.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: JAXA session from GrafanaCON 2024 is now available to watch on demand. You can check out the full session on YouTube below.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CpHQfwFPvw8?rel=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;system-booster-engaged&#34;&gt;System booster engaged&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;JAXA observes its data with an in-house tool that Nakahira said has several issues. &amp;ldquo;There are many characters, so it is not easy to find certain parameters,&amp;rdquo; he said. On top of that, he added, it was built as monolithic software, so maintaining it or adding in new features was difficult.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adding Grafana helped JAXA observe the different types of telemetry collected by SLIM&amp;rsquo;s scientific probes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira divided the data into two categories:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Housekeeping data&lt;/strong&gt; covers the basic metrics that monitor the spacecraft&amp;rsquo;s real-time health and functionality, such as voltage, current, temperature, attitude, position, velocity, acceleration, status flags, and counts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scientific data&lt;/strong&gt;, including images, spectrograms, and bursted time series, which are analyzed on a slower time scale.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira said that the housekeeping data is &amp;ldquo;similar to what you find in IoT devices,&amp;rdquo; but with one key difference: IoT systems collect a small amount of telemetry from many devices, but JAXA&amp;rsquo;s probes collect a large volume of telemetry from one big device.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The content of the data is still similar, so as a result, inspired by IoTs, we have integrated Grafana to space probe&amp;rsquo;s operations for enhanced observability,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;JAXA used InfluxDB as its data source in Grafana, as well as an API to get calculations for its image generation. In front of InfluxDB, the team built a data receiver written in Python. &amp;ldquo;We were able to build our entire system quite easily and the visualization capability was broad — from simple ones to detailed graphs,&amp;rdquo; he added.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-giant-step-for-jaxaand-its-querying-abilities&#34;&gt;A giant step for JAXA—and its querying abilities&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To go along with the Quick Look System, JAXA built and used more than 10 Grafana dashboards to monitor SLIM&amp;rsquo;s subsystems (e.g., power and navigation) as well as individual ones for three main phases: launch, running, and cruise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Overall, Nakahira said, Grafana gave JAXA broad &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;visualization capabilities&lt;/a&gt; that ranged from simple gauges to xy graphs, time series panels, and bar charts. The dashboards the agency&amp;rsquo;s team created were &amp;ldquo;well-received and visually impressive,&amp;rdquo; he added. Nakahira also said editing dashboards was &amp;ldquo;straightforward — and could be done even during operations.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The real &amp;ldquo;game-changer&amp;rdquo; for the team, he explained, was Grafana&amp;rsquo;s variable feature. It allowed them to easily locate and display specific telemetry data among the thousands of series they collected. They used parameters and two query variables — &lt;strong&gt;textbox&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;query&lt;/strong&gt; — to filter data across multiple graphs in Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=550 550w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=750 750w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=900 900w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A slide showing a Grafana dashboard to show how easy it is to locate and display a specific telemetry&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;900&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A slide showing a Grafana dashboard to show how easy it is to locate and display a specific telemetry&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;900&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;out-of-this-world-dashboards&#34;&gt;Out-of-this-world dashboards&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira shared video from inside of the JAXA control room just before SLIM&amp;rsquo;s lunar landing, highlighting where Grafana dashboards were used. For example, on the wall seen below, a monitor displayed a real-time Grafana dashboard that was live streamed on YouTube during the operation. &amp;ldquo;In this critical phase, the Control Room and the YouTube audience were all looking at the same Grafana dashboard at the same time,&amp;rdquo; Nakahira said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;An image of two people in a control room looking at a wall-mounted monitor with a Grafana dashboard displayed on it.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;870&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;An image of two people in a control room looking at a wall-mounted monitor with a Grafana dashboard displayed on it.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;870&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the dashboards that helped JAXA&amp;rsquo;s team make history:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;navigation-system-during-the-cruise-phase&#34;&gt;Navigation system during the cruise phase&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira said this was easily built by connecting InfluxDB with Grafana. The panels are monitoring:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;System status&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Error or warning status&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Log messages generated by ground processing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Attitude (orientation in space), atmospheric change, and solar angle&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg?w=550 550w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg?w=750 750w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg?w=900 900w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A presentation slide with an image of a Grafana dashboard with panels of graphs displaying information related to the navigation system&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;900&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A presentation slide with an image of a Grafana dashboard with panels of graphs displaying information related to the navigation system&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;900&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;heater-status&#34;&gt;Heater status&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira said this dashboard is important &amp;ldquo;because instruments can be damaged by extremely low temperatures in space.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg?w=550 550w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg?w=750 750w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg?w=900 900w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A presentation slide with a Grafana dashboard featuring several colorful graphs displaying metrics related to heater status&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;900&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A presentation slide with a Grafana dashboard featuring several colorful graphs displaying metrics related to heater status&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;900&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is scrollable and has several pages of information below what he shared. The dashboard allows team members to observe power-related metrics, such as power generation and power usage. The stacked graph in the upper left, he said, &amp;ldquo;provides a clear view for total power consumption for each component.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SLIM has about 50 heaters, which are controlled autonomously, but it is important to monitor its duty cycle, Nakahira explained. He said the state timeline panel (middle-right) made that task easy because it allowed team members to compare it with the graphs in the middle of the screenshot above, which monitor temperature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;thrusters-and-maneuvers&#34;&gt;Thrusters and maneuvers&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=550 550w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=750 750w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=900 900w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A presentation slide with a screenshot of a Grafana dashboard featuring several panels with graphs related to thrusters and maneuvers&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;900&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A presentation slide with a screenshot of a Grafana dashboard featuring several panels with graphs related to thrusters and maneuvers&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;900&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SLIM has two main thrusters and 12 smaller ones, Nakahira said, and the left side of the dashboard is arranged to reflect that layout. The gauges on the upper-right show the remaining fuel of SLIM&amp;rsquo;s thrusters and the battery. Below that, 3D images monitor SLIM&amp;rsquo;s attitude in relation to the sun and Earth. &amp;ldquo;It is implemented by Python API and images are generated by offline rendering by using &lt;a href=&#34;https://trimesh.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;trimesh&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://pyrender.readthedocs.io/en/latest/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;pyrender&lt;/a&gt; libraries,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;landing&#34;&gt;Landing&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below is a snapshot of what the real-time dashboard looked like during the moon landing. (Nakahira&amp;rsquo;s presentation shows the data moving and changing.) It is similar to the dashboard above, but the panel in the bottom right is different. That new graph is charting distance on the horizontal axis and the attitude on the vertical axis. The flight line is SLIM&amp;rsquo;s actual planned trajectory, with the red section highlighting the actual trajectory during the previous five minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a real-time Grafana dashboard that includes a graph displaying SLIM&amp;#39;s actual planned trajectory&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;841&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a real-time Grafana dashboard that includes a graph displaying SLIM&amp;#39;s actual planned trajectory&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;841&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the panel on the right side below, JAXA&amp;rsquo;s team was able to observe SLIM approaching and landing on the moon&amp;rsquo;s surface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard that includes a panel monitoring SLIM approaching and landing on the moon&amp;#39;s surface&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1078&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard that includes a panel monitoring SLIM approaching and landing on the moon&amp;#39;s surface&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1078&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To find out more about JAXA&amp;rsquo;s upcoming missions, launches, and other projects, visit the agency&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;https://global.jaxa.jp/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;official website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to share your Grafana story and dashboards with the community? Drop us a note at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:stories@grafana.com&#34;&gt;stories@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当日本宇宙航空研究开发机构 (JAXA) 于 1 月份开始首次登月时，其目标不仅仅是获得&lt;a href=&#34;https://global.jaxa.jp/projects/sas/slim /&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SLIM（月球调查智能着陆器）&lt;/a&gt; 月球表面上的航天器。该计划还要求在距离预定目标 100 米的范围内着陆，实现世界上首次精确登月。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2024 年 1 月 19 日，JAXA 迎来了双重历史性时刻，日本成为第五个将航天器送上月球的国家。回到地球后，该机构的研究人员和工程师使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/dashboards/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana 仪表板&lt;/a&gt;实时监控运行情况，跟踪 SLIM 的关键功能，包括导航、加热器状态和着陆操纵。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/grafana-used-to-monitor-japan-slim-moon-lander/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2024 演示文稿&lt;/a&gt;中，副高级研究员 Satoshi Nakahira JAXA 空间与宇航科学研究所 (ISAS) 重点介绍了该机构的一些工作，讨论了其可观测系统，并分享了登月期间使用的仪表板示例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他说，Grafana“在我们的运营中发挥了重要作用。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：GrafanaCON 2024 的 JAXA 会议现已可供点播观看。您可以在下面的 YouTube 上查看完整的会议内容。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/CpHQfwFPvw8?rel=0&#34; style=&#34;位置：绝对；顶部：0；左侧：0；宽度：100%；高度：100%；边框： 0;” allowedfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube 视频&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;system-booster-engged&#34;&gt;系统助推器已启用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;JAXA 使用内部工具观察其数据，Nakahira 表示该工具存在几个问题。 “字符很多，所以找到某些参数并不容易，”他说。他补充说，最重要的是，它是作为整体软件构建的，因此维护它或添加新功能很困难。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;添加 Grafana 有助于 JAXA 观察 SLIM 科学探测器收集的不同类型的遥测数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira 将数据分为两类：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;内务数据&lt;/strong&gt;涵盖了监控航天器实时运行状况和功能的基本指标，例如电压、电流、温度、姿态、位置、速度、加速度、状态标志和计数。&lt; /里&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;科学数据&lt;/strong&gt;，包括图像、频谱图和突发时间序列，在较慢的时间尺度上进行分析。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;Nakahira 表示，内务数据“与物联网设备中的数据类似”，但有一个关键区别：物联网系统从许多设备收集少量遥测数据，但 JAXA 的探测器从一台设备收集大量遥测数据大设备。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“数据的内容是仍然相似，因此，受到物联网的启发，我们将 Grafana 集成到太空探测器的操作中，以增强可观测性。”他说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;JAXA 使用 InfluxDB 作为 Grafana 中的数据源，以及用于获取图像生成计算的 API。在InfluxDB前面，团队构建了一个用Python编写的数据接收器。 “我们能够非常轻松地构建整个系统，并且可视化功能非常广泛——从简单的到详细的图表，”他补充道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-giant-step-for-jaxaand-its-querying-bility&#34;&gt;JAXA 及其查询能力的一大进步&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了配合 Quick Look 系统，JAXA 构建并使用了 10 多个 Grafana 仪表板来监控 SLIM 的子系统（例如电源和导航）以及三个主要阶段的各个子系统：发射、运行和巡航。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;总体而言，Nakahira 表示，Grafana 为 JAXA 提供了广泛的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;可视化功能&lt;/a&gt;，从简单的仪表到xy 图表、时间序列面板和条形图。他补充说，该机构团队创建的仪表板“很受欢迎，而且视觉效果令人印象深刻”。 Nakahira 还表示，编辑仪表板“非常简单，甚至可以在操作期间完成。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他解释说，团队真正的“游戏规则改变者”是 Grafana 的可变功能。它使他们能够在收集的数千个系列中轻松定位和显示特定的遥测数据。他们使用参数和两个查询变量（&lt;strong&gt;文本框&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;查询&lt;/strong&gt;）来过滤 Grafana 中多个图表中的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1600px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-查询-USETHIS.jpg？w=320 320w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg？w=550 550w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot- JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg？w=750 750w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg？w=900 900w，/media/blog/ JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=1240 1240w , /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes =“auto”alt =“显示 Grafana 仪表板的幻灯片，以显示定位和显示特定遥测数据是多么容易”&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“900”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/媒体/blog/JAXA-recap/屏幕截图-JAXA-recap-dashboard-querying-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示 Grafana 仪表板的幻灯片，以展示定位和显示特定遥测数据是多么容易&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“900”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;out-of-this-world-dashboards&#34;&gt;超凡脱俗的仪表板&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira 在 SLIM 登月前分享了 JAXA 控制室内部的视频，重点介绍了使用 Grafana 仪表板的位置。例如，在下面看到的墙上，监视器显示了实时 Grafana 仪表板，该仪表板在操作过程中在 YouTube 上进行了直播。 “在这个关键阶段，控制室和 YouTube 观众都在同时查看同一个 Grafana 仪表板，”Nakahira 说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1600px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside- control-room.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/image- JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/ JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=1240 1240w ，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;控制室中两个人看着壁挂式显示器的图像，显​​示器上显示有 Grafana 仪表板。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“870”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/JAXA-recap/image-JAXA-recap-inside-control-room.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;控制室中两个人看着壁挂式显示器的图像，显​​示器上显示有 Grafana 仪表板。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“870”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是一些帮助 JAXA 团队创造历史的仪表板：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;navigation-system-during-the-cruise-phase&#34;&gt;巡航阶段的导航系统&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira 表示，通过将 InfluxDB 与 Grafana 连接起来可以轻松构建这一点。面板正在监控：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;系统状态&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;错误或警告状态&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;地面处理生成的日志消息&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;姿态（空间方向）、大气变化和太阳角&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1600px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div类=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-仪表板导航系统-USETHIS.jpg？w=320 320w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg？w=550 550w，/media/blog/ JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg？w=750 750w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg？ w=900 900w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-仪表板导航系统-USETHIS.jpg？w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg？w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;演示幻灯片，其中包含 Grafana 仪表板的图像，其中的图形面板显示与导航系统相关的信息&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“900”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-navigation-system-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;演示幻灯片，其中包含 Grafana 仪表板的图像，其中的图形面板显示与导航系统相关的信息&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“900”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;heater-status&#34;&gt;加热器状态&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nakahira 说这个仪表板很重要，“因为仪器可能会因太空中极低的温度而损坏。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1600px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-仪表板-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg？w=320 320w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg？w=550 550w，/media/blog/ JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg？w=750 750w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg？ w=900 900w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-仪表板-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg？w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg？w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;带有 Grafana 仪表板的演示幻灯片，其中包含多个彩色图表，显示与加热器状态相关的指标&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“900”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-heater-status-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;带有 Grafana 仪表板的演示幻灯片，其中包含 se显示与加热器状态相关的指标的真实彩色图表”&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“900”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它是可滚动的，并且在他分享的内容下面有几页信息。仪表板允许团队成员观察与电力相关的指标，例如发电量和用电量。他说，左上角的堆叠图“提供了每个组件的总功耗的清晰视图。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SLIM 大约有 50 个加热器，这些加热器是自主控制的，但监控其工作周期非常重要，Nakahira 解释道。他说状态时间线面板（中右）使这项任务变得容易，因为它允许团队成员将其与上面屏幕截图中间监控温度的图表进行比较。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;thrusters-and-maneuvers&#34;&gt;推进器和机动&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1600px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA- recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=320 320w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=550 550w , /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=750 750w, /media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-推进器和操纵-USETHIS.jpg？w=900 900w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg？w=1040 1040w，/media/博客/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-机动-USETHIS.jpg?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;演示幻灯片，其中包含 Grafana 仪表板的屏幕截图，其中包含多个面板，其中包含与推进器和操作相关的图表&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“900”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-thrusters-and-maneuvers-USETHIS.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;演示幻灯片，其中包含 Grafana 仪表板的屏幕截图，其中包含多个面板，其中包含与推进器和操作相关的图表&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“900”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SLIM 有两个主推进器和 12 个较小的推进器，Nakahira 说，仪表板左侧的布置反映了这种布局。右上角的仪表显示 SLIM 推进器和电池的剩余燃料。下面，3D 图像监控 SLIM 相对于太阳和地球的姿态。 “它是通过Python API实现的，图像是使用&lt;a href=&#34;https”离线渲染生成的://trimesh.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;trimesh&lt;/a&gt; 或 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pyrender.readthedocs.io/en/latest/&#34; target=&#34;_blank “ rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;pyrender&lt;/a&gt; 库，”他说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;landing&#34;&gt;着陆&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下面是登月期间实时仪表板的快照。 （Nakahira 的演示显示了数据的移动和变化。）它与上面的仪表板类似，但右下角的面板有所不同。该新图表在水平轴上绘制距离，在垂直轴上绘制姿态。飞行路线是SLIM实际规划的轨迹，红色部分突出了前五分钟的实际轨迹。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1600px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA- recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=320 320w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=550 550w ，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard- lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/博客/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-图-USETHIS.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;实时 Grafana 仪表板的屏幕截图，其中包括显示 SLIM 实际计划轨迹的图表&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“841”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander-in-graph-USETHIS.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;实时 Grafana 仪表板的屏幕截图，其中包括显示 SLIM 实际计划轨迹的图表&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1600”&#xA;高度=“841”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在下面右侧的面板中，JAXA 的团队能够观察到 SLIM 接近并降落在月球表面。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1999px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png png?w=320 320w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard- lander.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-仪表板-lander.png？w = 1040 1040w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png？w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-回顾-仪表板-lander.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板的屏幕截图，其中包括一个监控 SLIM 接近和登陆月球表面的面板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1078”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/JAXA-recap/screenshot-JAXA-recap-dashboard-lander.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板的屏幕截图，其中包括一个监控 SLIM 接近和登陆月球表面的面板&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1999”&#xA;高度=“1078”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关 JAXA 即将执行的任务、发射和其他项目的更多信息，请访问该机构的&lt;a href=&#34;https://global.jaxa.jp/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;官方网站网站&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想要与社区分享您的 Grafana 故事和仪表板吗？请发送邮件至 &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:stories@grafana.com&#34;&gt;stories@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>