<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</title>
    <link>/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Project Bob: The autonomous boat attempting to circle the globe with open source and Grafana】鲍勃项目：试图用开源和格拉法那绕全球绕全球的自主船</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/29/project-bob-the-open-source-boat-attempting-to-circle-the-globe/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Andrew McCalip works with satellites and spacecraft, so he’s no stranger to ambitious engineering challenges. His latest side project may be his boldest yet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.projectbob.xyz/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Project Bob&lt;/a&gt; aims to be the first autonomous boat to circumnavigate the globe. Open source tools will monitor every detail on the 14-foot, solar-powered vessel, from power levels to location and heading, in real time. And it will use onboard cameras, sensors and a Starlink antenna to stream live video and telemetry data to the public via a custom Grafana Cloud dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;McCalip shared the story of Project Bob at his recent &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2025/monitor-project-bob-droneship-with-grafana-and-tailscale/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025 talk&lt;/a&gt;, demonstrating the power of today’s open source software in tackling real-world engineering challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I haven’t really done software in 10 years,” he said. “So I come back, and there’s this whole sprawling ecosystem of wonderful tools that wasn’t there the first time.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqHO0oYW6Ic?si=uUmXbG3Y4iU&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;from-furnace-door-to-open-ocean&#34;&gt;From furnace door to open ocean&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;McCalip is head of research and development at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.varda.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Varda Space Industries&lt;/a&gt;, but he may be better known for the self-proclaimed “weird hobbies” he documents for his 69,000 followers &lt;a href=&#34;https://x.com/andrewmccalip&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;on X&lt;/a&gt;. During his most famous project—attempting to recreate LK-99, a purported room-temperature superconductor—about 15,000 people were glued to a live stream of a furnace door with a Grafana Labs temperature plot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“They gave me the idea, like, ‘Hey, can we do more really boring live streams?’” McCalip recalled. “And so that was kind of the genesis of this idea. Can we do an orbit? Can we do a really boring live stream? And can we engage the public as we build with these cool tools?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He launched a Kickstarter campaign for Project Bob, which met its funding goal in one day. Then he and a group of engineers got to designing a small, rugged drone boat capable of staying at sea for months on its own. That meant it had to be energy efficient, self-sustaining, and able to recover from failure with no human intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Once we send this thing off, there’s no way to ever get to it again,” McCalip said. “We’ve got one chance.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;one-goal-dont-sink&#34;&gt;One goal: ‘Don’t sink’&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team tested two designs—an aerodynamic, fiberglass hull and a rugged (but slow) modified kayak stuffed with batteries and foam—and built them on nights and weekends.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“It’s a little bit of a race between the two designs,” McCalip said. “We’re launching number two first, and then one will catch up later.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As with past projects, he documented the process in public. He installed solar panels on the roof of his workplace, experimented in a makeshift dev environment, and put the vessels out on the water at a local marina.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“The number-one goal was don’t sink, and we did not sink,” McCalip said. “We did hit a few boats. There was some lag, and once we got out of range of the Wi-Fi, we lost Wi-Fi connection to the boat, and it ran away from us. But other than that, it’s been good.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To test the boat’s GPS capabilities, he even monitored a Grafana dashboard from the passenger seat of a truck en route to the marina.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I am sitting in the truck, we’ve got Grafana open, we’re streaming video through Starlink, through Tailscale, back down to the laptop as we drive down the 405 in Los Angeles,” he said. “That was kind of fun. We got a couple strange looks.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x826/d4cdb68f4b/project-bob-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x826/d4cdb68f4b/project-bob-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;Dashboard with boat data: speed, power, heading, graphs, and video of a harbor scene with palm trees. Various gauges and metrics displayed.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x826/d4cdb68f4b/project-bob-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Dashboard with boat data: speed, power, heading, graphs, and video of a harbor scene with palm trees. Various gauges and metrics displayed.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-at-the-helm&#34;&gt;Grafana at the helm&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Project Bob runs on a Raspberry Pi 4 with 14 Docker containers controlling the propulsion system, motors, GPS, accelerometers, magnetometers, IP cameras and more. Each container communicates through Redis, the open source in-memory data store, and collects data with Telegraf, the open source server agent. That data is stored in an onboard InfluxDB instance, and it syncs daily over a Tailscale-secured Starlink connection to a cloud replica hosted on Google Cloud Platform. From there, the team pushes metrics to Grafana Cloud for visualization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x1086/1d64c2f515/project-bob-pipeline-architecture.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x1086/1d64c2f515/project-bob-pipeline-architecture.png&#34;alt=&#34;Flowchart showing a data pipeline from boat to land. Components include Pi4, Redis, Docker, ESP32, Starlink, GCP, InfluxDB, Grafana, and more.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x1086/1d64c2f515/project-bob-pipeline-architecture.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Flowchart showing a data pipeline from boat to land. Components include Pi4, Redis, Docker, ESP32, Starlink, GCP, InfluxDB, Grafana, and more.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those visualizations play a key role in the monitoring and operating of the boat. In particular, a first-person-view dashboard with video and embedded controls allows the team to steer and change speed when needed. Backed by a robust, near-real-time data pipeline, the team is also able to use Open Broadcaster software to create a single streaming video with Grafana dashboards overlaid on top of the boat’s camera footage. This allows viewers on YouTube to see what the boat sees and how it’s performing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;25000-miles-to-go&#34;&gt;25,000 miles to go&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To officially circumnavigate the globe, Project Bob must take a route that crosses the equator twice, passes through the point on Earth directly opposite Los Angeles (a spot in the Indian Ocean off the southern coast of Madagascar) and avoids all canals. If all goes well, the 25,000-mile voyage will see the boat pass around South America, Africa, and Australia before returning home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;McCalip acknowledged that’s a big if. But he and his team are up for the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I don’t think that we’re going to make it the first time, but we’re going to keep trying until we get it,” he said. “This would be a world record if we can pull it off.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;安德鲁·麦卡利普（Andrew McCalip）与卫星和航天器一起工作，因此他对雄心勃勃的工程挑战并不陌生。他的最新侧面项目可能是他最大胆的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://www.projectbob.xyz/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; bob bob &lt;/a&gt;旨在成为第一艘自主船，以绕过全球。开源工具将监视14英尺太阳能驱动的容器上的每个细节，从电源水平到位置和朝向，并实时进行。它将使用自定义Grafana Cloud仪表板将现场视频和遥测数据传输给公众。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; McCalip在他最近的&lt;a href =“/events/grafanacon/2025/Monitor-project-bob-Roneship-with-grafana and-tailscale/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = grafanacon 2025 Talk Talking &lt;/a&gt;上，挑战&lt;/a&gt;，挑战&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;p&gt; McCalip分享了鲍勃项目的故事。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我十年来还没有真正完成软件，”他说。 “所以我回来了，这是第一次没有的整个庞大的奇妙工具生态系统。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“ 560” height =“ 315” src =“ https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqho0oyw6ic?si =图片中的图片; web-share“ referrerpolicy =“ cross-origin”允许floserfullscreen&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“从炉门到开放式海洋&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; McCalip是研究与开发的主管，&lt;a href =“ https://www.varda.com/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; varda space Industries &lt;/a&gt;，但他可能以自称为“怪异的Hebbies”的自称为69,000 clasters &lt; href =“ https://x.com/andrewmccalip” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; on x &lt;/a&gt;。在他最著名的项目中 - 挑战LK-99，是一个声称的室温超导体 - 大约有15,000人被粘在带有Grafana Labs温度图的炉门的现场直播中。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“他们给了我这个主意，例如，‘嘿，我们能做更多真正无聊的直播吗？’”麦卡利普回忆道。 “这就是这个想法的起源。我们可以做一个轨道吗？我们可以做一个真正无聊的现场直播吗？我们可以在使用这些酷工具时吸引公众吗？” &lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他为鲍勃计划发起了一项Kickstarter运动，该活动在一天之内达到了其资金目标。然后，他和一群工程师必须设计一艘崎rug的无人机船，能够独自待在海上几个月。这意味着它必须是节能，自我维持的，并且能够在没有人类干预的情况下从失败中恢复过来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“一旦我们把这东西寄出，就再也无法再解决了，”麦卡利普说。 “我们有机会。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“一球插入”&gt;一个目标：&#39;不要下沉&#39;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;团队测试了两种设计 - 空气动力学，玻璃纤维船体和坚固（但缓慢）的皮划艇装有电池和泡沫，并在夜间和周末建造。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“这两种设计之间有点比赛，”麦卡利普说。 “我们首先发布第二名，然后再赶上。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与过去的项目一样，他在公开场合记录了这一过程。他在工作场所的屋顶上安装了太阳能电池板，在临时开发环境中进行了试验，并将船只放在当地码头的水上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“第一目标不是下沉，我们没有下沉，”麦卡利普说。 “我们确实撞上了几艘船。有一些滞后，一旦我们离开了Wi-Fi范围，我们就失去了Wi-Fi连接到船上，它逃离了我们。但是除此之外，这很好。”​​ &lt;/p&gt;&gt;&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了测试船的GPS功能，他甚至从卡车的乘客座椅上监视了前往码头的乘客座椅。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我坐在卡车上，我们已经开放了Grafana，我们正在通过Starlink，通过Tailscale播放视频，当我们驶向洛杉矶的405时，回到笔记本电脑，”他说。 “那很有趣。我们有几个奇怪的外观。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x826/d4cdb68f4b/project-bob-dashboard.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x826/d4cdb68f4b/project-bob-dashboard.png” alt =“ dashboard with Boat data with Boat data：speed，speed，power，power，power，power，power，power，heading and thrage and the harbor a the harbor a the harbor abore a harbour coble a there toble a the harbor abore coble a the harbor abore coble。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x826/d4cdb68f4b/project-bob-dashboard.png”&#xA;alt =“带有船只数据的仪表板：速度，电源，标题，图形和带有棕榈树的港口场景的视频。显示了各种规模和指标。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ grafana-at-the-helm”&gt; Grafana in Helm &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;项目BOB在Raspberry Pi 4上运行，该Raspberry Pi 4带有14个Docker容器，可控制推进系统，电动机，GPS，加速度计，磁力计，IP摄像机等。每个容器通过开源中内存数据存储Redis进行通信，并使用开源服务器代理Telegraf收集数据。该数据存储在板载InfluxDB实例中，并且每天通过尾部安全的Starlink连接将其同步到Google Cloud Platform上托管的云复制品。从那里开始，团队将指标推向Grafana Cloud以进行可视化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x1086/1d64c2f515/project-bob-pipeline-architecture.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturL”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x1086/1d64c2f515/project-bob-pipeline-architection.png” alt =“ flowchart显示出船上的数据管道到陆地。 Grafana等等。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1938x1086/1d64c2f515/project-bob-pipeline-archituction.png”&#xA;alt =“流程图显示了从船到土地的数据管道。组件包括PI4，Redis，Docker，ESP32，Starlink，GCP，GCP，InfluxdB，Grafana等。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些可视化在船的监视和操作中起着关键作用。特别是，带有视频和嵌入式控件的第一人视仪表板使团队可以在需要时进行转向和更改速度。在坚固的，近实时的数据管道的支持下，该团队还可以使用开放的广播软件来创建一个单个流媒体视频，其中横跨船的摄像机镜头的Grafana仪表板。这使YouTube上的观众可以查看船的表现以及表现方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ 25000英里到go”&gt; 25,000英里&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了正式绕过地球，鲍勃必须采取两次越过赤道的路线，穿过洛杉矶对面（马达加斯加南部海岸附近的印度洋）对面的地球上的地上，并避免了所有运河。如果一切顺利，那么25,000英里的航行将在返回家园之前在南美，非洲和澳大利亚附近通过。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;麦卡利普承认这是一个很大的话。但是他和他的团队正在挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我认为我们不会第一次做到这一点，但是我们将继续尝试，直到我们得到它为止。” “如果我们能实现这一目标，这将是世界纪录。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How should Prometheus handle OpenTelemetry resource attributes?】Prometheus应该如何处理OpenTelemetry资源属性？</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/28/how-should-prometheus-handle-opentelemetry-resource-attributes-a-ux-research-report/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: A version of this post originally appeared on the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/blog/2025/ux-research-prometheus-otel/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry blog.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Victoria Nduka is user experience designer and open source contributor making her way into the cloud native space. She writes about design, accessibility, and open source with the same curiosity she brings to her work.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On May 29, I wrapped up my mentorship with Prometheus through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://mentorship.lfx.linuxfoundation.org/project/36e3f336-ce78-4074-b833-012015eb59be&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Linux Foundation mentorship program&lt;/a&gt;. My project focused on understanding how Prometheus handles OpenTelemetry resource attributes and how that experience could be improved for users. My job was to conduct research to get the user perspective on this challenge. Over three months, I conducted user and stakeholder interviews, ran a survey, and analyzed the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll share how we conducted the research, what we uncovered, and where the communities involved could go from here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-project-background&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The project background&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel) has something called &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/concepts/resources/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;resource attributes&lt;/a&gt;, which are extra information about the source of a metric, such as the service, host, or environment that generated it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prometheus, being a time-series database, uses labels to identify and query metrics. If resource attributes are converted to labels, they can cause what&amp;rsquo;s known as a &amp;ldquo;cardinality explosion,&amp;rdquo; essentially creating too many unique combinations that overwhelm the system. This usually happens if the attributes change often or include a lot of unique values, such as user IDs or pod names.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, there are three main approaches to handling this challenge:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Map all resource attributes to labels&lt;/strong&gt;: This was the original implementation made by the Prometheus community. However, it actually creates cardinality explosion problems, especially for applications with large numbers of attributes or frequently changing attribute values.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Selective promotion&lt;/strong&gt;: Users manually choose which resource attributes are important enough to be converted to labels in Prometheus.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Target info pattern&lt;/strong&gt;: Put all resource attributes in a separate metric called &lt;code&gt;target_info&lt;/code&gt;. When users need to query metrics involving specific resource attributes, they have to perform a &amp;ldquo;join&amp;rdquo; between the target info and their actual metrics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These aren&amp;rsquo;t bad solutions technically, but they don&amp;rsquo;t make for the best user experience. So, we conducted this research to understand what the Prometheus maintainers might be missing about the user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The research objectives were:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand how engineers currently use OpenTelemetry resource attributes with Prometheus&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Identify pain points in the current integration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Discover user expectations for how resource attributes should be represented&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;research-approach&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research approach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My research approach was a mix of qualitative and quantitative research. I started with stakeholder interviews to understand the historical context and assess how open stakeholders were to changes that might result from my research. The stakeholders we spoke to represented a range of roles, from project founders and co-founders to long-time maintainers with historical context, as well as others more directly involved in the ongoing challenges around resource attribute handling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, I conducted user interviews to hear directly from people actually using these tools. After that, I followed up with a survey to reach a broader audience and validate what we heard in interviews.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;stakeholder-interviews-insights&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stakeholder interviews insights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We spoke to six stakeholders—three from each project:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prometheus stakeholders:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Julius Volz (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/juliusv&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://github.com/juliusv&lt;/a&gt;): Prometheus co-founder&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Beorn Rabenstein (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/beorn7&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://github.com/beorn7&lt;/a&gt;): Long-time Prometheus maintainer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Richard Hartmann (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/RichiH&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://github.com/RichiH&lt;/a&gt;):  OpenMetrics co-founder and Prometheus maintainer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry stakeholders:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Juraci Paixão Khröhling (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jpkrohling&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://github.com/jpkrohling&lt;/a&gt;): OpenTelemetry Governance Committee member&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Josh Suereth (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jsuereth&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://github.com/jsuereth&lt;/a&gt;): OpenTelemetry Technical Committee member &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Austin Parker (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/austinlparker&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://github.com/austinlparker&lt;/a&gt;): OpenTelemetry Governance Committee member and co-founder.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our conversations with stakeholders brought several interesting discoveries to light:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Prometheus and OpenTelemetry communities hadn&amp;rsquo;t always communicated well and that prevented them from collaborating early on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Much of the interoperability issues that exist now stem from the different philosophical and technical foundations on which each of the projects is built. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;If we think about exploratory situations or use cases, then we can justify a lot of the design decisions behind OpenTelemetry. And if we think about metrics and scaling, monitoring, for huge infra, then the design decisions for Prometheus are justified as well. So both have very good arguments.&amp;rdquo; - Juraci Paixão Kröhling&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I think one of the biggest [interoperability issues] is the difference between push and pull.” - Julius Volz&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Julius later elaborated that his concern goes beyond the delivery mechanism itself. In his words:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“One of the biggest downsides of using OTLP to push metrics to Prometheus is that you end up throwing away one of the core features of Prometheus as a monitoring system: its pull-based metrics collection model that is based on dynamic service discovery information (so Prometheus always knows which targets should currently exist), and the resulting automatic target health monitoring via the synthetic ‘up’ metric that is generated for each target scrape.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a shared recognition of the importance of putting user needs first, even while maintaining some non-negotiables (e.g., Prometheus keeping its pull model and not alienating existing users).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One key takeaway from the interviews for me was realizing that the current interoperability problems are not failures, but natural consequences of different communities solving different problems at different times. And it’s good to see both projects are working together now to make user experience better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;user-interviews-insights&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User interviews insights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The user interviews were just as revealing as the stakeholder conversations. We aimed to speak with about 10 users (admittedly ambitious) but managed to interview seven, and they all shared incredibly helpful perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most prominent pain point users shared was the complexity of performing joins with the current integration. Another issue mentioned was the mismatch in metric names caused by character set limitations, but I understand that has since been addressed, as recent Prometheus releases &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/11/06/prometheus-3.0-and-opentelemetry-a-practical-guide-to-storing-and-querying-otel-data/#utf-8&#34;&gt;now support UTF-8 characters&lt;/a&gt; (though this introduces the need for the more cumbersome quoted selector syntax in PromQL).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Regarding mental models, many users (both interviewees and survey respondents) don’t distinguish between resource attributes and Prometheus labels. They tend to think of them as the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I would expect resource attributes as a rule to be treated exactly the same way as the attributes attached to the tracer, the metric&amp;hellip; I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t draw a boundary between them.&amp;rdquo; - Interview participant 1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also learned about the various workarounds people use to handle resource attribute issues in their specific use cases. Some promote selected resource attributes to labels; others handle the conversion at the OpenTelemetry level to avoid dealing with it in Prometheus; and a few convert all attributes, though usually only when the number of attributes is small.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;survey-insights&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Survey insights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The survey helped me quantify what I was hearing in interviews and reach a broader audience. At the time of writing, we’ve had 134 responses, with 61 from our target group—people who use OTel and Prometheus together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are the key findings:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users don&amp;rsquo;t conceptualize resource attributes as different from regular labels, yet current implementation treats them as separate metadata.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Complex join syntax is a big barrier to adoption, with average developers unable to write basic queries accessing resource attributes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manual attribute promotion creates operational overhead that scales poorly with team size and complexity.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;78% of respondents find documentation gaps a challenge in their use of resource attributes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/622x494/f6be735f5a/prometheus-research-stats.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/622x494/f6be735f5a/prometheus-research-stats.png&#34;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing challenges with OpenTelemetry in Prometheus. Highlighted: &amp;#39;Documentation gaps&amp;#39; rated as very challenging by 25 respondents.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/622x494/f6be735f5a/prometheus-research-stats.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing challenges with OpenTelemetry in Prometheus. Highlighted: &amp;#39;Documentation gaps&amp;#39; rated as very challenging by 25 respondents.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The survey patterns were consistent with what emerged from my qualitative research. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-we-didnt-expect-to-learn-but-did&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we didn’t expect to learn (but did)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We began this research to understand user pain points with resource attribute handling, but we uncovered some unexpected and important findings. One of the most surprising was the realization that &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-specification/tree/main/specification/resource#telescoping&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry’s resource detection feature&lt;/a&gt; allows users to selectively retain or drop resource attributes based on relevance via a conceptual pattern sometimes referred to as “telescoping.” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Despite its potential, many users and even some members of the Prometheus community seem unaware of it. This lack of awareness may have contributed to the adoption of the &amp;ldquo;join&amp;rdquo; pattern, which has since proven to be problematic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This also highlights a broader issue: &lt;strong&gt;documentation and education gaps&lt;/strong&gt; are a major barrier. In our survey, 78% of respondents cited documentation gaps as a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another key realization is that earlier integration decisions, like the reliance on joins, were made without a full understanding of each tool’s capabilities. This is an unavoidable consequence of the lack of early collaboration and communication between the Prometheus and OpenTelemetry communities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;recommended-solutions&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended solutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Based on conversations with stakeholders and end users, here are some of the proposed solutions, grouped by what&amp;rsquo;s feasible in the short term vs. what&amp;rsquo;s part of a longer-term vision.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;short-term-solutions&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short-term solutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved documentation for attribute handling.&lt;/strong&gt; Since users find it easier to promote attributes than to join on target info, it may be worth de-emphasizing (or even sunsetting) documentation around joins, while making &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/guides/opentelemetry/#promoting-resource-attributes&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;attribute promotion docs&lt;/a&gt; more prominent for those not yet aware of the option. The telescoping pattern of resource detection in OpenTelemetry also deserves more visibility and proper documentation. Additionally, users have suggested creating consolidated Prometheus-OpenTelemetry documentation that clearly explains how both systems handle resource attributes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;long-term-vision&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Long-Term Vision&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entity framework.&lt;/strong&gt; OpenTelemetry’s developing concept of &lt;em&gt;entities&lt;/em&gt; could help Prometheus distinguish between identifying vs. descriptive attributes. This would guide which attributes become labels, and which are stored or filtered out.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metadata storage.&lt;/strong&gt; Stakeholders also discussed the idea of adding first-class metadata support to Prometheus itself. This would allow certain resource attributes to be stored as metadata (not labels), avoiding cardinality costs while keeping the information available for queries or joins.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expanding for exploratory telemetry.&lt;/strong&gt; This might be a stretch, but Prometheus could consider expanding its scope to better support exploratory telemetry use cases. Stakeholders showed openness to change, as long as Prometheus’ core architecture remains intact and existing users aren’t alienated. That suggests there may be room for evolution, especially if new capabilities can complement, rather than replace, current behavior.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-signal correlation.&lt;/strong&gt; Users mention using platforms that can ingest all telemetry types and correlate metrics, traces, and logs within a single system. While Prometheus will likely remain focused on just metrics, it could enable tooling that correlates metrics with telemetry stored in other databases. Prometheus currently supports &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/specs/om/open_metrics_spec/#exemplars&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;exemplars&lt;/a&gt;, which allow linking metrics to traces, but that’s about the extent of their scope. They rely on tracing being present, which makes them less useful in environments where traces aren’t available or instrumented.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This cross-signal correlation is an opportunity for Prometheus to expand its usefulness in modern observability workflows without changing its core focus on metrics storage. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“One of the key innovative things in OpenCensus was… you could divide CPU usage by which requests were using CPU and get a metric that would say, ‘here&amp;rsquo;s CPU usage by request.’ That’s a thing you could accomplish in OpenCensus because it was all contextual-based metrics.” - Josh Suereth&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s still work to be done. The communities will need time to develop and test solutions. But I&amp;rsquo;m proud that this research has provided a user-centered foundation for that work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in the ongoing discussions, proposals, and feedback around these ideas, you can check out the GitHub repository where everything is being documented: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus-community/ux-research/tree/main/prom-otel-research&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry resource attributes in Prometheus UX research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;acknowledgments&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acknowledgments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post would be incomplete if I didn’t acknowledge my incredible mentors from Grafana Labs: Amy Super, Andrej Kiripolsky, and Arthur Silva Sens. Thanks for trusting me to take on this challenging project and for caring so deeply about my professional journey. You’re the real superstars.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To all the stakeholders and users who shared their time and perspectives, thank you for engaging with the research and trusting me with your honest feedback. Your stories and frustrations are what made this research meaningful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And a few words from the Grafanistas:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Thank&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;you,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Victoria, for getting this research to the finish line. You&amp;rsquo;ve shown courage to face your fears and incredible dedication throughout the whole mentorship.&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We&amp;rsquo;d also like to thank Grafana Labs’ culture, which always encourages us to make meaningful contributions to OpenTelemetry, Prometheus, and other open-source communities!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Andrej, Amy, and Arthur&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s next for me&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m excited to continue working at the intersection of UX and cloud native systems. If you have opportunities in this area similar to this mentorship, please reach out to me on &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/victorianduka/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt; or by &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:ndukavictoria7@gmail.com&#34;&gt;email&lt;/a&gt;. I&amp;rsquo;m a hard worker—just ask my mentors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;注意：本文的一个版本最初出现在&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://opentlemetry.io.io/blog/2025/2025/ux-research-prometheus-otel/” target =“ _ rell =” rel =“ rel =” noopener noreferrer&#39;&gt;用户体验设计师和开源贡献者进入云本地空间。她以与她的作品相同的好奇心写了关于设计，可访问性和开源的文章。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 5月29日，我通过&lt;a href =“ https://mentorship.lfx.linuxfoundation.org/project/project/36e3f336-ce78-4074-4074-b833-012012015eb59be targitor =” no ninux Founterrer =“ sllien nin nlinub ninub ninubs nline nliniunl ninubn linirer nin nliniunl ninuber nin verroferer，程序&lt;/a&gt;。我的项目专注于了解Prometheus如何处理OpenTelemetry资源属性以及如何改善用户的体验。我的工作是进行研究，以了解用户对这一挑战的看法。在三个月的时间里，我进行了用户和利益相关者访谈，进行了调查，并分析了调查结果。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本文中，我将分享我们如何进行研究，发现的内容以及所涉及的社区可以从这里去的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ the-project-background”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;项目背景&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenTelemetry (OTel) has something called &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/concepts/resources/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;resource attributes&lt;/a&gt;, which are extra information about the source of a metric, such as the service, host, or environment that generated it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Prometheus是一个时间序列数据库，使用标签来识别和查询指标。如果将资源属性转换为标签，它们可能会导致所谓的“基数爆炸”，从本质上产生了太多的独特组合，使系统不堪重负。如果属性经常更改或包含许多唯一值，例如用户ID或POD名称，通常会发生这种情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目前，处理这一挑战的主要方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;将所有资源属性映射到标签&lt;/strong&gt;：这是普罗米修斯社区的原始实现。但是，它实际上会产生基数爆炸问题，尤其是对于具有大量属性或经常更改属性值的应用程序。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;选择性促销&lt;/strong&gt;：用户手动选择哪些资源属性很重要，可以转换为Prometheus中的标签。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;目标信息模式&lt;/strong&gt;：将所有资源属性放在一个单独的度量标准中，称为&lt;code&gt; target_info &lt;/code&gt;。当用户需要查询涉及特定资源属性的指标时，他们必须在目标信息和实际指标之间执行“加入”。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从技术上讲，这些解决方案不是不良的解决方案，但是它们并不是最佳的用户体验。因此，我们进行了这项研究，以了解普罗米修斯维护者可能缺少什么关于用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;研究目标是：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;了解工程师当前如何使用Prometheus &lt;/li&gt;使用OpenTelemetry资源属性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;确定当前整合中的疼痛点&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;发现用户对应如何表示资源属性的期望&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“研究 - 接触”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;研究方法&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我的研究方法是定性和定量研究的结合。我从利益相关者的访谈开始，以了解历史环境，并评估利益相关者对我研究可能导致的变化的开放式。我们交谈的利益相关者代表了一系列角色，从项目创始人和联合创始人到具有历史背景的长期维护者，以及其他更直接地参与围绕资源属性处理的挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，我进行了用户访谈，直接听取实际使用这些工具的人的意见。之后，我进行了一项调查，以吸引更广泛的受众并验证我们在采访中听到的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“利益相关者 - 访问 -  i-Insights”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;利益相关者采访见解&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们与六个利益相关者进行了交谈 - 每个项目中的三个：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;普罗米修斯利益相关者：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; julius volz（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/juliusv” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; https：//github.com/julius.com/juliusv &lt;/a&gt;）&#xA;&lt;li&gt; beorn rabenstein（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/beorn7” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; https://github.com/beorn7 &lt;/a&gt;）：&#xA;&lt;li&gt; RICHARD HARTMANN（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/richih” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; https://github.com/richih &lt;/a&gt;）&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; OpentElemetry利益相关者：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; juracipaixãoKhröhling（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/jpkrohling” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; https://github.com/jpkrohling &lt;/a&gt;）&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Josh Suereth（&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/jsuereth” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; https://github.com/jsuereth &lt;/a&gt;）&#xA;&lt;li&gt; Austin Parker（&lt;A href =“ https://github.com/austinlparker” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; https://github.com/austinlparker &lt;/a&gt;）&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们与利益相关者的对话带来了一些有趣的发现：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Prometheus和Opentelemetry社区并不总是很好地交流，这阻止了他们早期合作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在存在的许多互操作性问题源于每个项目的建立的不同哲学和技术基础。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“如果我们考虑探索性情况或用例ns在Opentelemetry后面。而且，如果我们考虑庞大的下属的指标和扩展，监视，那么普罗米修斯的设计决策也是合理的。所以两者都有很好的论点。” -JuraciPaixãoKröhling&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我认为最大的[互操作性问题]之一是推动和拉力之间的区别。” -Julius volz &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;朱利叶斯后来阐述了他的关注超出了交付机制本身。用他的话：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“使用OTLP将指标推向Prometheus的最大弊端之一是，您最终将Prometheus作为监控系统的核心特征之一丢弃：其基于拉动的指标收集模型基于动态服务发现信息，因此，Prometheus始终知道当前的目标是自动监控的目标，并且可以通过“自动监控”目标来启动，并通过“启用”目标，并且可以通过“合成”来指示。刮擦。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使维持某些非商品（例如，Prometheus保留其拉力模型而不疏远现有用户），也可以共同认识到将用户放在首位的重要性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对我的采访中的一个关键要点是，意识到当前的互操作性问题不是失败，而是在不同时间解决不同社区的自然后果。很高兴看到这两个项目现在正在共同努力以使用户体验更好。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户访谈与利益相关者对话一样揭示。我们的目的是与大约10位用户交谈（肯定是雄心勃勃），但设法采访了七个，他们都分享了令人难以置信的有用观点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户分享的最突出的疼痛点是与当前集成一起执行连接的复杂性。提到的另一个问题是由字符集限制引起的公制名称的不匹配，但我知道此后已经解决了，因为最近的Prometheus发行&lt;a href =“/blog/blog/2024/2024/11/11/prometheus-3.0--3.0-and-opentelemetry-apentelemetry-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-practical to-practical-a-practical to-practor-to-stoperd-and-querying-querying-querying-portsuts-underted-inding-undert-utff-in/now and ut/ut utf-8介绍了Promql中更繁琐的选择器语法的需求）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;关于心理模型，许多用户（受访者和调查受访者）都没有区分资源属性和普罗米修斯标签。他们倾向于将它们视为同一件事。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我希望将资源属性通常与示踪剂，度量标准的属性完全相同的方式进行处理。我不会在它们之间划界。” - 面试参与者1 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我还了解了人们用来处理特定用例中资源属性问题的各种解决方法。一些将选定的资源属性推向标签；其他人处理转换t opentelemetry级别避免在普罗米修斯（Prometheus）处理它；还有一些转换所有属性，尽管通常仅在属性数很小时才。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“ Survey-Insights”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;调查见解&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这项调查帮助我量化了在采访中听到的内容，并吸引了更广泛的受众。在撰写本文时，我们有134个回复，我们的目标人群有61个 - 将Otel和Prometheus一起使用的人。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是关键发现：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;用户不会将资源属性概念化为与常规标签不同，但是当前的实现将它们视为单独的元数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;复杂的加入语法是采用的巨大障碍，普通的开发人员无法编写基本查询来访问资源属性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;手动属性促销创建的操作开销，随着团队规模和复杂性的缩小范围很差。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; 78％的受访者发现文档差距是他们使用资源属性的挑战。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/622x494/f6be735f5a/prometheus-research-search-stats.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/10222730/6222x494/f6be735f5a/prometheus-research-stats.png” alt =“ Alt =” bar Chart显示出挑战，在Prometheus中与OpenTelemetry中的OpenTelemetry挑战。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/622x494/f6be735f5a/prometheus-research-search-stats.png”&#xA;Alt =“条形图显示Prometheus中的OpenTelemetry的挑战。突出显示：“文档差距”被25位受访者评为非常具有挑战性。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;调查模式与我的定性研究中出现的结果一致。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ What What We Whe-We-didnt-to-to-bearn but-did”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我们没想到（但做过）&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们开始了这项研究，以通过资源属性处理来了解用户痛点，但我们发现了一些意外而重要的发现。最令人惊讶的之一是意识到，&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry/opentelemetry-specification/tree/main/main/specification/mmain/specification/Resource#telescoping/Resource#telescoping” target =“ _ _ vramp =” real =“ relopener noreferrer”&gt; noopener noreFerrer“ propertiber resource resource resource resoutder resouttion tocription”基于通过概念模式的相关性，有时被称为“望远镜”。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管有潜力，但许多用户甚至普罗米修斯社区的某些成员似乎都没有意识到这一点。缺乏意识可能有助于采用“联接”模式，此后事实证明这是有问题的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这也突出了一个更广泛的问题：&lt;strong&gt;文档和教育差距&lt;/strong&gt;是一个主要障碍。在我们的调查中，有78％的受访者将文件差距作为挑战。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一个关键的认识是，早期的集成决策，例如对加入的依赖，在没有完全了解每个工具的功能的情况下做出了。这是普罗米修斯和Opentelemetry社区之间缺乏早期合作和交流的不可避免的结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“推荐溶液”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;推荐解决方案&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基于与利益相关者和最终用户的对话，以下是一些拟议的解决方案，由短期中可行的与长期愿景的一部分进行分组。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“短期溶液”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;短期解决方案&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;改进了属性处理的文档。&lt;/strong&gt;由于用户发现促进属性比加入目标信息更容易促进属性，因此在加入围绕JOIN的同时，它可能值得强调（甚至是日落）文档，同时进行&lt;a href =“ https：///prometheus.io.io.io/docs/guides/guides/guides/guides/guides/guides/guide-prometry-prometry-promomoting-promomoting-promoting-romoting-romoting-romoting-romoting-romoting-rimoting-risting&#39; target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;属性促销文档&lt;/a&gt;对于尚未知道该选项的人来说，更为突出。 Opentelemetry中资源检测的望远镜模式也值得更多可见性和适当的文档。此外，用户建议创建合并的Prometheus-opentelemetry文档，该文档清楚地说明了两个系统如何处理资源属性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“长期视觉”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;长期视觉&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;实体框架。&lt;/strong&gt; opentelemetry的开发&lt;em&gt;实体概念&lt;/em&gt;可以帮助普罗米修斯（Prometheus）区分识别与描述性属性。这将指导哪些属性成为标签，哪些被存储或过滤出来。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;元数据存储。&lt;/strong&gt;利益相关者还讨论了在普罗米修斯本身中添加一流元数据支持的想法。这将允许某些资源属性作为元数据（不是标签）存储，避免了基数成本，同时保持信息可用于查询或加入。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;扩大探索性遥测。&lt;/strong&gt;这可能是一个伸展的范围，但是普罗米修斯可以考虑扩大其范围以更好地支持探索性遥测用例。只要普罗米修斯的核心架构完好无损并且现有用户没有疏远，利益相关者就会表现出开放的变化。这表明可能存在进化的空间，尤其是如果新功能可以补充而不是取代当前行为。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;交叉信号相关性。&lt;/strong&gt;用户提到的是使用可以摄取所有遥测类型并在单个系统中摄入所有遥测类型并将日志相关的平台。虽然普罗米修斯可能只专注于指标，但它可以启用与存储在其他数据库中的遥测相关的工具es。 Prometheus currently supports &lt;a href=&#34;https://prometheus.io/docs/specs/om/open_metrics_spec/#exemplars&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;exemplars&lt;/a&gt;, which allow linking metrics to traces, but that’s about the extent of their scope.他们依靠跟踪存在，这使得它们在没有痕迹或没有仪器的环境中有用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种跨信号相关性是普罗米修斯在现代可观察性工作流程中扩大其实用性的机会，而不会改变其对指标存储的核心关注。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“ OpenCensus中的关键创新性事物之一是……您可以通过请求使用CPU并获得一个指标的CPU用法，并获得‘这是‘这是通过请求使用的CPU用法。’这是您可以在OpenCensus中完成的事情，因为这都是基于上下文的基于上下文的指标。” -Josh Suereth &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仍然有工作要做。社区将需要时间来开发和测试解决方案。但是我为这项研究提供了以用户为中心的基础，我感到自豪。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您对这些想法的正在进行的讨论，建议和反馈感兴趣，则可以查看所有内容都在记录的GitHub存储库中：&lt;a href =“ https://prometheus/prometheus/prometheus-community/ux-community/ux-research/ux-research/tree/tree/tree/main/main/main/prom-prom-prom-prom-prom-prom-prom-prom-prom-prom-otel-research noore =” Prometheus UX研究中的资源属性&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“确认”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; bengrygments &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，如果我不承认Grafana Labs的令人难以置信的导师：Amy Super，Andrej Kiripolsky和Arthur Silva Sens。您是真正的超级巨星。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对分享时间和观点的所有利益相关者和用户，感谢您参与研究并以诚实的反馈来信任我。您的故事和挫败感使这项研究有意义。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和grafanistas的几个单词：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“感谢&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;您，&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; victoria，将这项研究登上了终点线。您已经勇于面对恐惧和令人难以置信的奉献精神。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;我们还要感谢Grafana Labs的文化，这总是鼓励我们为Opentelemetry，Prometheus和其他开源社区做出有意义的贡献！” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt; Andrej，Amy和Arthur &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ What&#39;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我接下来是什么&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我很高兴能继续在UX和云本机系统的交叉点工作。如果您在此领域有与该指导相似的机会，请通过&lt;a href =“ https://www.linkedin.com/in/victorianduka/” target =“ _ _ black” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” noopener noreferrer“&gt;mail.com”&gt;电子邮件&lt;/a&gt;。我是一个勤奋的人 - 只是问我的导师。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimize application performance at the network layer: introducing HTTP Performance Insights in Frontend Observability】优化网络层的应用程序性能：在前端可观察性中引入HTTP性能见解</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/27/optimize-application-performance-at-the-network-layer-introducing-http-performance-insights-in-frontend-observability/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Imagine you’re a frontend engineer monitoring the user experience for an e-commerce app. You notice your checkout flow has a 15% abandonment rate. Your API responses are inconsistent. Your users are frustrated, and you&amp;rsquo;re drowning in data and complex queries trying to figure out why. Sound familiar? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can use real user monitoring (RUM) to determine &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; has happened, looking at page load times, error counts, user sessions, etc. But when performance issues strike, you also need to know &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; they happened and &lt;em&gt;where&lt;/em&gt; to focus your optimization efforts. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is exactly where &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-07-21-http-performance-insights/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;HTTP Performance Insights&lt;/a&gt;, a new feature in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/frontend-observability/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability&lt;/a&gt;, comes in. With HTTP Performance Insights, you can go beyond basic metrics with aggregated views that surface actionable signals, so you can quickly identify and resolve application performance issues at the network layer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here, we’ll explore the key features of HTTP Performance Insights, and offer an early look at the broader performance intelligence platform we’re building out in Frontend Observability. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;http-performance-insights-clear-actionable-data-to-drive-results&#34;&gt;HTTP Performance Insights: clear, actionable data to drive results &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HTTP Performance Insights offers a comprehensive view into your application’s HTTP requests, allowing you to monitor request quality and detect bottlenecks in real time. Instead of reactive firefighting, teams can use HTTP Performance Insights to proactively identify performance issues and address them before they impact the user experience. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;performance-dashboards-that-highlight-the-network-layer&#34;&gt;Performance dashboards that highlight the network layer&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The HTTP Performance Insights interface shows not just raw numbers, but health indicators, color-coding, and other trend analysis features to guide your attention to what matters most. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To start your investigation, navigate to the &lt;strong&gt;HTTP&lt;/strong&gt; tab in Frontend Observability. You can use the metrics across the top of the dashboard — including &lt;strong&gt;total requests&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;error totals&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;error rate&lt;/strong&gt; — to evaluate backend responsiveness, and protectively identify and address issues affecting frontend performance. You can also reference &lt;strong&gt;time to first byte&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;transfer size&lt;/strong&gt; to identify further opportunities for optimization. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1565x784/5cd33a02f1/http-performance-insights-dashboard-1.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1565x784/5cd33a02f1/http-performance-insights-dashboard-1.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud dashboard displaying performance metrics, including response times, requests per second, and error rates.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1565x784/5cd33a02f1/http-performance-insights-dashboard-1.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud dashboard displaying performance metrics, including response times, requests per second, and error rates.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; The actionable breakdowns below those top-level metrics help you identify your biggest problems first. Sortable tables pinpoint your slowest endpoints, largest requests, and most error-prone calls. With this data, you can quickly answer questions like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are image assets causing performance bottlenecks?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is a specific API endpoint generating most user errors?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which domains are consuming the most bandwidth?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The time series visualization lets you track trends and quickly correlate issues with potential causes. You can also look for clusters of errors to correlate issues against deployments, traffic spikes, or external dependencies.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;deep-dives-into-problematic-endpoints&#34;&gt;Deep dives into problematic endpoints &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you identify a problematic endpoint with a high error rate, you can drill down for granular analysis. The &lt;strong&gt;single endpoint&lt;/strong&gt; view provides request-level granularity, showing individual requests, their performance characteristics, and timing breakdowns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1568x599/bf0008c664/https-performance-insights-dashboard-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1568x599/bf0008c664/https-performance-insights-dashboard-2.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud dashboard displaying metrics like response time and data usage for a specific endpoint.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1568x599/bf0008c664/https-performance-insights-dashboard-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud dashboard displaying metrics like response time and data usage for a specific endpoint.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; This level of detail enables precise troubleshooting. You can see exactly which requests are outliers, understand request size patterns, and correlate performance with specific user sessions or geographic regions. The same rich visualization suite applies at this focused level, giving you consistent analytical capabilities whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking at the big picture or investigating a specific issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started-with-http-performance-insights&#34;&gt;Get started with HTTP Performance Insights&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HTTP Performance Insights is available now in public preview. You can access it in Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability by navigating to the &lt;strong&gt;HTTP&lt;/strong&gt; tab. The feature automatically analyzes your existing HTTP request data, so there&amp;rsquo;s no additional instrumentation required.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We recommend first exploring the HTTP overview to identify performance patterns and problematic endpoints. Then, you can use the drill-down capabilities to investigate specific issues and correlate them with user impact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s next&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HTTP Performance Insights represents our first step towards building out a broader set of performance intelligence capabilities within Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability. We’re currently working to add the following features, which will also offer actionable views to help you correlate performance metrics to the user experience:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Page Performance Insights&lt;/strong&gt;: Comprehensive analysis of loading, rendering, and Web Vitals with resource utilization breakdowns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resource Loading Intelligence&lt;/strong&gt;: Deep visibility into static assets, their impact on performance, and optimization opportunities&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrated User Experience Views&lt;/strong&gt;: Timeline-based analysis showing how performance issues affect real user journeys&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are building with user needs in mind — so we welcome your feedback! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about HTTP Performance Insights, please visit our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/http-insights/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;docs.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;想象您是一名前端工程师，监视电子商务应用程序的用户体验。您会注意到您的结帐流量的放弃率为15％。您的API响应不一致。您的用户感到沮丧，您正在淹没数据和复杂的查询，试图弄清楚原因。听起来很熟悉吗？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以使用真实的用户监视（朗姆酒）来确定&lt;em&gt;发生了什么，查看页面加载时间，错误计数，用户会话等。但是，当绩效问题爆发时，您还需要知道&lt;em&gt;为什么会发生&lt;/em&gt;他们会发生&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;才能集中优化工作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这到底是&lt;a href =“/Whats-new/2025-07-21-HTTP-Performance-Insights/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = http绩效见解&lt;/a&gt;可观察性&lt;/a&gt;，进来。使用HTTP性能洞察，您可以超越基本指标，具有表面可操作的信号的汇总视图，因此您可以快速识别并解决网络层的应用程序性能问题。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这里，我们将探讨HTTP性能见解的关键特征，并尽早查看我们在前端可观察性中构建的更广泛的性能智能平台。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ http-performance-ignights-clear-callable-data-to-data-to-drive-results”&gt; http performance Insights：清晰，可行的数据以驱动结果&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; HTTP Performance Insights对应用程序的HTTP请求提供了全面的视图，从而可以监视请求质量并实时检测瓶颈。团队可以使用HTTP绩效见解来主动识别性能问题并在影响用户体验之前解决这些问题，而不是反应性的消防。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“ performance-dashboards-that-that-the-the-the-network-layer”&gt;性能仪表板，突出显示网络层&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; HTTP性能见解界面不仅显示原始数字，还显示健康指标，颜色编码和其他趋势分析功能，以指导您对最重要的关注。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要开始调查，请在前端可观察性中导航到&lt;strong&gt; http &lt;/strong&gt;选项卡。您可以使用仪表板顶部的指标 - 包括&lt;strong&gt;总请求&lt;/strong&gt;，&lt;strong&gt;错误总计&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;错误率&lt;/strong&gt;  - 评估后端响应性，并保护并解决影响前端性能的问题。您还可以参考第一个字节&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;转移大小&lt;/strong&gt;的时间&lt;/strong&gt;，以确定进一步的优化机会。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1565x784/5cd33a02f1/http-performance-intformance-intformance-inlights-intights-dashboards-dashboard-1.png-1.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper w-100p h-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/10222730/1565x784/5cd33a02f1/http-performance-performance-intights-intights-ingights-dashboards-dashboard-dashboard-1.png” alt =“ Alt =” Alt =“ Grafana Cloud cloud cloud cloud cloud dashboard显示响应仪表，包括响应时间，包括响应时间，请求时间，每个要求，每秒，第二个/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1565x784/5cd33a02f1/http-performance-intformance-intformance-interformance-inlights-ingights-dashboard-dashboard-1.png-1.png”&#xA;Alt =“ Grafana Cloud仪表板显示性能指标，包括响应时间，每秒请求和错误率。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figue&gt;在这些顶级指标下方可行的分解可帮助您首先确定最大的问题。可排序表查明您最慢的端点，最大请求和最容易出错的调用。有了这些数据，您可以快速回答以下问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;图像资产是否导致性能瓶颈？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;是生成大多数用户错误的特定API端点吗？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;哪些域消耗最多的带宽？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;时间序列可视化使您可以跟踪趋势并迅速将问题与潜在原因相关联。您还可以寻找错误群，以将问题与部署，流量尖峰或外部依赖关系相关联。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您以高错误率确定有问题的端点时，您可以向下钻取颗粒状分析。 &lt;strong&gt;单端点&lt;/strong&gt;视图提供了请求级粒度，显示单个请求，其性能特征和时机崩溃。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1568x599/bf0008c664/https-performance-istermance-insights-dashboard-dashboard-2.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1568x599/bf0008c664/https-performance-insights-insights-dashboards-dashboard-dashboard-2.png“ alt =” Alt =“ Grafana cloud云仪表板显示响应时间和数据的指标，例如特定的端点，&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1568x599/bf0008c664/https-performance-insights-insights-dashboard-2.png”&#xA;alt =“ grafana云仪表板显示指标，例如响应时间和特定端点的数据使用。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figue&gt;此详细信息可以进行精确的故障排除。您可以准确查看哪些请求是异常值，了解请求大小模式，并将绩效与特定的用户会话或地理区域相关联。相同的丰富可视化套件适用于此重点级别，无论您是查看大局还是调查特定问题，都可以使您保持一致的分析能力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“与http-performance-Insights一起启动”&gt;开始HTTP性能见解&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; HTTP性能见解现已在公共预览中获得。您可以通过导航到&lt;strong&gt; http &lt;/strong&gt;选项卡中的Grafana Cloud Frontend可观察性访问它。该功能会自动分析您现有的HTTP请求数据，因此无需其他仪器。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们建议首先探索HTTP概述，以识别性能模式和有问题的终点。然后，您可以使用钻取功能来研究特定问题并将其与用户影响相关联。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ Whats-Next”&gt;下一步是什么&#xA;&lt;p&gt; HTTP性能见解是我们在Grafana Cloud前端可观察性中建立更广泛的性能智能功能的第一步。我们目前正在努力添加以下功能，该功能还将提供可行的视图，以帮助您将性能指标与用户体验相关联：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;页面绩效见解&lt;/strong&gt;：对负载，渲染和Web生命的全面分析，并具有资源利用分解&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;资源加载智能&lt;/strong&gt;：对静态资产的可见性，对绩效的影响和优化机会&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;集成的用户体验视图&lt;/strong&gt;：基于时间表的分析，显示绩效问题如何影响真正的用户旅程&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在牢记用户需求，因此我们欢迎您的反馈！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关HTTP性能见解的更多信息，请访问我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/http-insights/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = docs。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Inside Grafana Labs’ Voice of Customer program: what’s new and what’s next】内部Grafana Labs的客户计划：什么是新事物和下一步</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/26/inside-grafana-labs-voice-of-customer-program-whats-new-and-whats-next/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;At Grafana Labs, &lt;em&gt;openness&lt;/em&gt; isn’t just our approach to building software — it’s a core company value that reflects how we engage with our community. This includes being transparent about how we collect product feedback, how it’s reviewed, and how it informs what we build.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re always striving to tighten the loop between what our users ask for and what we prioritize in R&amp;amp;D. Our Voice of Customer (VoC) program — a centralized effort to collect, triage, and share product feedback from our user base — is one of the key ways we achieve this. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll unpack what the VoC program is, share real examples of how it’s shaped product direction here at Grafana Labs, and highlight recent updates like our new customer-facing portal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;voc-program-what-it-is-and-why-it-matters&#34;&gt;VoC program: what it is and why it matters&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our VoC program began as a simple spreadsheet that helped us log incoming requests from &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; users. But as feedback grew, so did the need for structure. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We introduced reporting, analysis, regular reviews, and tighter alignment with product and engineering. Today, VoC acts as a structured, reliable signal that helps teams spot patterns, validate use cases, and build with more context.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have a dedicated team focused on this work, with individual team members aligned to specific product areas. This dedicated team reviews and triages every request for our product and engineering teams, and themes and trends are regularly analyzed and shared.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Having a dedicated team means we can keep this process consistent and scalable. It also helps us spot and connect related requests across different areas of our product portfolio — something that’s easy to miss in more fragmented setups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;About 35% of the requests submitted through our Voice of Customer program have been &lt;em&gt;actioned&lt;/em&gt; — meaning they’ve either been accepted and are in progress, or have already resulted in new features or initiatives. While we’ve anecdotally heard estimates like 10–15% from other product teams, we haven’t found any reliable industry benchmarks to compare against. For now, 35% is our current baseline, and we’re focused on improving it as the program grows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;examples-of-voc-impact&#34;&gt;Examples of VoC impact &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Running Grafana Cloud at scale internally gives us a unique perspective, but we know our needs aren’t always the same as our customers’. We strive to meet a broad range of use cases, environments, and operational realities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Voice of the Customer plays a key role in ensuring that we’re not only optimizing for our own experience. It helps us identify patterns across users and build for the widest possible impact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“As our products evolve, we always want to ensure we are building features that align with our customer use cases,” said Ryan Kehoe, Staff Product Manager at Grafana Labs. “VoC has been critical in providing my teams with direct customer feedback through all phases of the software delivery lifecycle so we can build with confidence and pivot if we miss the mark.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a look at some recent product updates — and on-going initiatives — that have been shaped heavily by VoC user feedback:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expanding RBAC across products&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most consistently requested capabilities across VoC feedback is fine-grained access control — not just in one area, but across our stack. Thanks to this signal, we&amp;rsquo;ve shipped RBAC capabilities and improvements across multiple Grafana Cloud features, including &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/rbac/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Frontend Observability&lt;/a&gt;, Alerting (&lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2024-06-06-rule-specific-silences-with-rbac/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;silences&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-01-22-rbac-for-alerting-notifications/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;contact points&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/set-up/configure-rbac/access-folders/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;subfolders&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/dynamic-alerting/rbac/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Dynamic alerting&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-01-22-rbac-for-notification-policies/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;notification policies&lt;/a&gt;), &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-05-20-rbac-for-synthetic-monitoring-is-generally-available/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/manage/users-and-teams/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#role-based-access-control-rbac&#34;&gt;IRM&lt;/a&gt;. This continues to be a major theme for us and we are committed to expanding and refining RBAC support over time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improving cost visibility and control&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cost control and attribution have been a significant theme in user feedback, especially from teams managing multiple environments or stakeholders. In response, we’ve launched several foundational improvements, including updates to our billing dashboards and usage APIs, to help teams understand where the spend is going. We’ve also introduced &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/&#34;&gt;Adaptive Telemetry&lt;/a&gt; to help reduce noise and manage cost without losing critical observability signals. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“It was crucial for our organization to have an in-depth volume and cost breakdown of telemetry for monthly internal chargebacks, and to ensure compliance of cost centers against set budgets. To our delight, Grafana was able to deliver the necessary component,” said Peter Vernigorov, Principal Engineer at Delivery Hero. “They took the time to understand our needs by collaborating with our observability and FinOps engineers, and we really appreciated their quick iterative approach.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Programmatic workflows: Terraform, APIs, and Git Sync&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another recurring theme in user feedback has been the need to manage Grafana programmatically. This shows up across products: requests for more Terraform coverage, better APIs, and Git-based workflows for dashboards and configurations. In response, we continue to &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/observability-as-code-grafana-12/#new-terraform-resource&#34;&gt;expand our Terraform provider&lt;/a&gt; to cover more resources, and &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafana-12-release-all-the-new-features/#git-sync&#34;&gt;introduced Git Sync&lt;/a&gt; — an observability as code tool that brings Git workflows directly into the Grafana UI — in the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafana-12-release-all-the-new-features/&#34;&gt;Grafana 12 release&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secrets management for Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A top request from users running synthetic checks in production environments has been the ability to securely store and inject sensitive values without hardcoding them in scripts. Today, that’s difficult to do safely, which introduces risk and complicates compliance. We’re actively building a secure secrets management flow that allows sensitive data to be stored in a backend secrets store, injected into scripts as environment variables, and fully hidden from the UI and logs. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Secrets management kept coming up again and again in our Voice of the Customer feedback. It was one of the biggest pain points for Synthetic Monitoring users and a real blocker for adoption,” said Mark Meier, Staff Product Manager at Grafana Labs. “Having that VoC data made a huge difference, helping turn user feedback into real momentum.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more updates. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-new-the-voc-customer-facing-portal&#34;&gt;What’s new: the VoC customer-facing portal&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve rolled out a customer-facing Feature Request Portal to make our feedback process more efficient and transparent. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Previously, all feedback would be filtered manually through Grafana Labs account teams. Now, with the new VoC portal, users can see what’s already been requested, vote or comment on those requests with additional context, and track ideas across their organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x800/c005e08f65/voc-portal-screenshot.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x800/c005e08f65/voc-portal-screenshot.png&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the new Voice of Customer portal.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x800/c005e08f65/voc-portal-screenshot.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the new Voice of Customer portal.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; Customers can now:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Submit and view all Grafana Labs feature requests&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Upvote existing feature requests&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Comment to clarify use cases&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Track requests their org has submitted or supported&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When users can easily see and engage with existing ideas, we get a clearer view of which requests are shared and gaining traction. It also allows people to gauge the popularity of something they are interested in compared to other ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re a Grafana Cloud user, you can log in to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.ideas.aha.io/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Feature Request Portal&lt;/a&gt; today to view, vote on, and submit ideas directly to Grafana Labs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next-extending-the-reach-of-voc&#34;&gt;What’s next: extending the reach of VoC&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Voice of Customer program started by focusing on all Grafana Cloud customers. These customers often run our products in complex environments, rely on tightly integrated features, and generate high-signal feedback that’s directly tied to day-to-day workflows. This was a natural starting point as we built out our structure, scale, and process for the VoC program.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But our roots are in open source, and we know that some of our most thoughtful feedback comes from our OSS community. Community input has always been part of the picture — through GitHub issues, forums, Slack, and direct conversations — but it’s often reached teams informally and inconsistently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, we’re working to integrate that feedback more systematically. The next phase of the VoC program involves partnering with teams across Grafana Labs to ensure that input from our open source users is captured, distilled, and represented alongside our cloud customer signals. This isn’t about replacing those processes for collecting feedback, but expanding the scope. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, we want to thank everyone who’s taken the time to share feedback — whether it’s through the feature request portal, GitHub issues, Slack threads, Technical Support, or hallway conversations at an event. You’ve helped shape the products we’re building, and we’re so grateful for your input. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;voice-of-customer-program-faqs&#34;&gt;Voice of Customer program FAQs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the Voice of the Customer program at Grafana Labs?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Voice of Customer (VoC) program is our structured approach to collecting, analyzing, and actioning on product feedback from our users. It serves as a centralized, reliable signal that helps our team spot patterns, validate use cases, and build with more context. While running Grafana Cloud internally gives us deep insight, VoC ensures we are not just building for our own needs, but for the broad range of environments, challenges, and realities our users face.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does Grafana Labs prioritize VoC feature requests?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We prioritize feature requests based on the number of organizations asking for the same thing — not individual votes. A single vote from 10 different companies carries more weight than 10 votes from the same company. This approach helps us ensure that we&amp;rsquo;re investing in features that solve widespread problems. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When will my feature request be reviewed?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In most cases, feature requests are prioritized for review once we see interest from multiple organizations. We look for themes and patterns across our customer base so we can focus on building solutions that have broad impact. That said, there are cases where requests get reviewed earlier, especially if they align with something already on the roadmap or support a strategic initiative. While multi-org interest is the most common trigger, it&amp;rsquo;s not the only one. Every request is captured and visible to our Product team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long does it take from submission &amp;gt; review &amp;gt; launch?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s no guaranteed timeline from submission to review to launch. It depends on several factors: how many customers are asking, how the request aligns with our current strategy and roadmap, and what other work is already in motion. Even if a request is prioritized for review, that doesn’t always mean it will be built. We aim to solve the right problems in the most scalable way, sometimes finding alternate paths or grouping similar feedback.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What about community feedback?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Community feedback has always been valuable to our product improvement. We hear from users through GitHub issues, forums, community Slack, and direct conversations, and that input has shaped many features over the years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those channels aren’t going away. If you&amp;rsquo;re already sharing feedback through GitHub or other public forums, please keep doing what you&amp;rsquo;re doing. That signal is important, and it’s not being replaced.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re working to better connect that feedback to the broader Voice of Customer program so that insights from open source users are captured more consistently and represented alongside what we hear from cloud customers. This will help us spot shared patterns across all users, regardless of how or where they run Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can I learn more about Voice of Customer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can visit the &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.ideas.aha.io/sections/7518058178676519123&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Resources tab&lt;/a&gt; in the VoC portal to find information on using the portal, answers to common questions, and more details on our processes. For any other questions, contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:voc-shared-inbox@grafana.com&#34;&gt;voc-shared-inbox@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在Grafana Labs，&lt;em&gt;开放性&lt;/em&gt;不仅是我们构建软件的方法，而且是反映我们与社区互动的核心公司价值。这包括关于我们如何收集产品反馈，如何审查以及如何告知我们构建的内容的透明度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们一直在努力收紧用户要求的循环以及在研发中优先考虑的循环。我们的客户（VOC）计划的声音是从用户群中收集，分类和分享产品反馈的集中式努力 - 是我们实现这一目标的关键方法之一。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将解开VOC程序是什么，分享Grafana Labs的形状指导方式的真实示例，并重点介绍了诸如我们的新客户门户网站之类的最新更新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的VOC程序始于一个简单的电子表格，它帮助我们从&lt;a href =“/products/cloud/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud cloud &lt;/a&gt;用户记录了传入请求。但是随着反馈的增长，对结构的需求也随之增加。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们介绍了报告，分析，定期审查以及与产品和工程的更严格的一致性。如今，VOC充当一个结构化的，可靠的信号，可帮助团队发现模式，验证用例并使用更多上下文构建。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们有一个专门的团队专注于这项工作，单个团队成员与特定的产品领域保持一致。定期分析和共享这个专门的团队评论和三叶草的每个请求，以及主题和趋势。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;拥有一个专门的团队意味着我们可以保持这一过程一致且可扩展。它还可以帮助我们在产品组合的不同领域发现并连接相关请求 - 在更零散的设置中很容易错过。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过我们的客户计划提交的请求中约有35％是&lt;em&gt;行动&lt;/em&gt;的 - 这意味着他们要么被接受并且正在进行中，要么已经产生了新功能或计划。虽然我们听到其他产品团队的估计值大约为10-15％，但我们尚未发现任何可靠的行业基准可以与之相比。目前，我们目前的基准是35％，随着程序的增长，我们专注于改进它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“ voc-Impact的示例”&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在内部大规模运行Grafana Cloud为我们提供了独特的视角，但我们知道我们的需求与客户的需求并不总是相同的。我们努力满足广泛的用例，环境和操作现实。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;客户的声音在确保我们不仅为自己的经验优化时发挥着关键作用。它可以帮助我们识别用户之间的模式，并为可能的影响带来最广泛的影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“随着我们产品的发展，我们始终希望确保我们建立与客户用例保持一致的功能。”Grafana Labs的员工产品经理N Kehoe。 “ VOC对于通过软件交付生命周期的所有阶段为我的团队提供直接客户反馈至关重要，因此，如果我们错过了商标，我们可以充满信心地构建。” &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一些最近的产品更新（以及正在进行的计划），这些更新是由VOC用户反馈大量塑造的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;扩展RBAC跨产品&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;跨VOC反馈最一致的功能之一是细粒度的访问控制 - 不仅在一个区域，而且在我们的堆栈中。多亏了这个信号，我们已经发货了RBAC功能和改进，包括&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observility/rbac/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt“ href=&#34;/whats-new/2024-06-06-rule-specific-silences-with-rbac/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;silences&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-01-22-rbac-for-alerting-notifications/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;contact points&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/set-up/configure-rbac/access-folders/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;subfolders&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/dynamic-alerting/rbac/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Dynamic alerting&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href =“/whats-new/2025-01-22-rbac-for-notification-policies/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;通知策略&lt;/a&gt;），&lt;a href =“/whats-new/2025-05-20-rbac-for synththetic-monitoring-is-generally-ableable-abailable/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt&#39;&gt;综合监视&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a &lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/nervering-mirm/irm/andm/manage/user-and-teams/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt/＃基于角色的access-access-control-rbac”&gt; irm &lt;/a&gt;。这对我们来说仍然是一个主要主题，我们致力于随着时间的推移扩展和完善RBAC支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提高成本可见性和控制&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成本控制和归因是用户反馈中的重要主题，尤其是管理多个环境或利益相关者的团队。作为回应，我们启动了几个基本改进，包括对我们的计费仪表板和使用API​​的更新，以帮助团队了解支出的去向。我们还引入了&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-is-aptive-telemetry and-how-can-it-it-it-it-it-it-mttr-mttr-noise-and-cost/”&gt;自适应遥测&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;有助于降低噪音并管理噪音而不失去关键可观察性信号而管理噪音并管理成本。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“对于我们的组织来说，要对遥测进行深入销售和成本分解，以确保每月内部拒绝，并确保成本中心符合固定的预算。令我们高兴的是，Grafana能够提供必要的组成部分。 “他们花了一些时间通过与我们的可观察性和Finops工程师合作来了解我们的需求，我们真的很感谢他们快速的迭代方法。” &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;编程工作流程：Terraform，API和Git Sync &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户反馈中的另一个反复出现的主题是需要以编程方式管理格拉法纳。这跨产品显示：要求更多地Terraform覆盖范围，更好的API和用于仪表板和配置的基于GIT的工作流程。作为回应，我们继续&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/05/07/可观察性-scode-as-as-code-grafana-12/＃new-terraform-resource”&gt;扩展我们的Terraform提供商&lt;/a&gt;涵盖更多资源，&lt;a href =“同步&lt;/a&gt;  - 将GIT工作流直接带入Grafana UI的代码工具的可观察性 - 在&lt;a a href =“/blog/2025/05/05/05/07/grafana-12-rease-allease-all lease-all-the-theew-features/”&gt; grafana&gt; grafana 12版本&lt;/a&gt;中。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; grafana云合成监控的秘密管理&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在生产环境中运行合成检查的用户的最高请求是能够在无需硬编码脚本中安全地存储和注入敏感值的能力。今天，这很难安全，这会引入风险并使合规性复杂化。我们正在积极建立一个安全的秘密管理流，该流程允许将敏感数据存储在后端秘密商店中，并将其注入脚本为环境变量，并完全隐藏在UI和日志中。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“秘密管理人员不断地以我们对客户反馈的声音进行一次又一次地出现。这是合成监控用户的最大痛苦点之一，也是采用真正的阻止者，” Grafana Labs的员工产品经理Mark Meier说。 “拥有这些VOC数据产生了巨大的不同，有助于将用户的反馈转化为真实动力。” &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请继续关注更多更新。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ Whats-New-New-the-the-the-the-customer-Facemer-portal”&gt;新事物：面向VOC客户的门户网站&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经推出了面向客户的功能请求门户，以使我们的反馈流程更加高效和透明。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以前，所有反馈将通过Grafana Labs帐户团队手动过滤。现在，借助新的VOC门户网站，用户可以看到已经要求，对这些请求进行了投票或评论，并在其组织中跟踪想法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x800/c005e08f65/voc-portal-screenshot.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x800/c005e08f65/voc-portal-screenshot.png” alt =“ Alt =” ALT =“新声音&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x800/c005e08f65/voc-portal-screenshot.png”&#xA;alt =“客户门户新声音的屏幕截图。”/&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;客户现在可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;提交并查看所有Grafana Labs功能请求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; upvote现有功能请求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;评论要澄清用例&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;轨道请求他们的组织已提交或支持&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当用户可以轻松地看到并与现有想法互动时，我们可以更清楚地了解哪些请求并获得吸引力。与其他想法相比，它还允许人们评估他们感兴趣的事物的普及。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re a Grafana Cloud user, you can log in to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.ideas.aha.io/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Feature Request Portal&lt;/a&gt; today to view, vote on, and submit ideas directly to Grafana Labs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ whats-next-扩展 -  voc”&gt;下一&#xA;&lt;p&gt;客户计划的声音首先关注所有Grafana Cloud客户。这些客户经常在复杂的环境中运行我们的产品，依靠紧密集成的功能，并产生与日常工作流程直接相关的高信号反馈。当我们为VOC程序构建结构，规模和过程时，这是一个自然的起点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，但我们的根源是开源的，我们知道我们最周到的反馈来自OSS社区。通过GitHub问题，论坛，松弛和直接对话，社区的投入一直是图片的一部分 - 但通常会非正式地与团队联系。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，我们正在努力更系统地整合该反馈。 VOC计划的下一个阶段涉及与Grafana Labs的团队合作，以确保我们的开源用户的输入被捕获，蒸馏和与我们的云客户信号一起捕获。这不是要替换收集反馈的过程，而是要扩大范围。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，我们要感谢所有花时间分享反馈的人 - 无论是通过功能请求门户，GitHub问题，Slack Threads，Slack Threads，技术支持还是在活动中进行的对话。您已经帮助塑造了我们正在构建的产品，我们非常感谢您的投入。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“客户语音式 - 绘制式 -  faqs”&gt;客户程序的语音常见问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana Labs的客户计划的声音是什么？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;客户（VOC）程序的声音是我们收集，分析和对用户的产品反馈采取措施的结构化方法。它是一个集中式，可靠的信号，可帮助我们的团队发现模式，验证用例并使用更多上下文构建。在内部运行Grafana Cloud的同时，VOC确保我们不仅为自己的需求而建立，而且还为我们用户所面临的各种环境，挑战和现实。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana Labs如何优先考虑VOC功能请求？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们优先考虑功能e根据要求同一件事的组织数量的要求，而不是个人投票。来自10个不同公司的一次投票比同一公司的10票更重。这种方法有助于我们确保我们投资于解决广泛问题的功能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么时候可以审查我的功能请求？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在大多数情况下，一旦我们看到多个组织的兴趣，就可以将功能请求优先审核。我们在客户群中寻找主题和模式，因此我们可以专注于建立具有广泛影响的解决方案。也就是说，在某些情况下，请求较早地进行了审查，尤其是当它们与路线图上的某些内容保持一致或支持战略计划时。虽然多ORG的兴趣是最常见的触发因素，但这并不是唯一的触发因素。我们的产品团队都会捕获和可见每个请求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;从提交&gt;评论&gt;启动需要多长时间？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从提交到审核到启动的时间表没有保证的时间表。这取决于几个因素：有多少客户要求，请求与我们当前的策略和路线图如何保持一致，以及其他工作已经在进行中。即使优先审核请求，也并不总是意味着它将建立。我们旨在以最可扩展的方式解决正确的问题，有时会找到其他路径或分组类似的反馈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;社区反馈呢？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;社区反馈始终对我们的产品改进很有价值。我们通过GITHUB问题，论坛，社区懈怠和直接对话从用户那里听到，多年来，该输入已塑造了许多功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些频道不会消失。如果您已经通过GitHub或其他公共论坛分享反馈，请继续做您的工作。该信号很重要，并且没有被替换。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在努力更好地将这些反馈与客户程序的更广泛的声音联系起来，以便更加一致地捕获开源用户的见解，并与我们从云客户那里听到的内容一起表示。这将有助于我们在所有用户中发现共享模式，而不管他们如何运行Grafana。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我如何了解有关客户声音的更多信息？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can visit the &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.ideas.aha.io/sections/7518058178676519123&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Resources tab&lt;/a&gt; in the VoC portal to find information on using the portal, answers to common questions, and more details on our processes.有关其他任何问题，请联系&lt;a href =“ mailto：voc-shared-inbox@grafana.com”&gt; voc-shared inbox@grafana.com &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次，并为每个用例都有计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;ahref =“/auth/imp-up/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Canary tokens: Learn all about the unsung heroes of security at Grafana Labs】金丝雀令牌：在Grafana Labs了解所有有关安全英雄的信息</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/25/canary-tokens-learn-all-about-the-unsung-heroes-of-security-at-grafana-labs/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve written at length about a recent security incident tied to a GitHub action, but what we haven&amp;rsquo;t publicized yet is how we found the trail left by the attacker: canary tokens. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To quickly recap the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/15/grafana-security-update-post-incident-review-for-github-workflow-vulnerability-and-whats-next/&#34;&gt;security incident&lt;/a&gt; in question, on April 26 a vulnerable GitHub Action workflow allowed an unauthorized user access to a limited number of tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/15/grafana-security-update-post-incident-review-for-github-workflow-vulnerability-and-whats-next/&#34;&gt;investigation&lt;/a&gt; into the incident concluded May 12, and we confirmed that &lt;strong&gt;there were no code modifications, unauthorized access to production systems, exposure of customer data, or access to personal information.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After the initial incident was triggered (but before our investigation concluded), the attacker deleted their fork, PRs, and workflow runs in an attempt to cover their tracks. This led to unauthorized access to secrets across five public repositories, though this did not impact production systems or customer data either. We disabled affected workflows, rotated all exposed credentials, and audited our repositories with Trufflehog, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/26/how-to-detect-vulnerable-github-actions-at-scale-with-zizmor/&#34;&gt;Zizmor&lt;/a&gt;, and Gato-X. We also conducted a full access log review in Grafana Loki and other data sources. You can read the initial announcement &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/04/27/grafana-security-update-no-customer-impact-from-github-workflow-vulnerability/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and the PIR &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/15/grafana-security-update-post-incident-review-for-github-workflow-vulnerability-and-whats-next/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Without canary tokens and our watchful team, it would have taken longer to detect the attack. In this blog, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain what canary tokens are and show you how they&amp;rsquo;ve helped us. We&amp;rsquo;ll also tell you how they can help you detect intrusions before they become serious security incidents. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-canary-tokens-and-how-do-we-use-them-at-grafana-labs&#34;&gt;What are canary tokens? And how do we use them at Grafana Labs?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Canary tokens are digital tripwires or decoys that look valuable to an intruder but have no legitimate use. If someone finds and uses one you&amp;rsquo;ve deployed, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive an immediate alert. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Named after coal-mining canaries (early warning for toxic gas), these tokens are far lighter than honeypots. They can take many simple forms, such as API keys, files, URLs, or DNS entries, making them fast and easy to deploy across your environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In our case, canary tokens weren’t just an experiment, they were the primary signal that told us an attacker was inside: An AWS API key was validated by the attacker; we got a real-time alert; teams swarmed; and the intrusion was contained within minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are the actionable lessons from that detection and why placement and deployment matter more than the token itself:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Speed wins:&lt;/strong&gt; Canary tokens turn hours of triage into minutes of containment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Placement matters:&lt;/strong&gt; Choose the right token types and place them where attackers actually look.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Precision in pinpointing:&lt;/strong&gt; Utilize organization-level tokens for broad compromise detection and repository-level tokens to identify specific entry points.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metadata is gold:&lt;/strong&gt; Comprehensive reminder text, token names, and locations are crucial for efficient triage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integration is key:&lt;/strong&gt; Canary tokens only shine when paired with clear naming, automated alerting, and integrated response workflows.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iterative scaling:&lt;/strong&gt; Begin with a small-scale placement in high-risk areas. Only then, by refining your response strategy, can you scale use of canary tokens.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-we-built-our-canary-token-infrastructure&#34;&gt;How we built our canary token infrastructure&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are two options for deploying canary tokens:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DIY setup:&lt;/strong&gt; Generate tokens (API keys, fake files, custom URLs) yourself and build or plug into your existing monitoring system to catch any token use. This gives you full control over token behavior and alert handling, making it ideal for custom platforms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated platforms:&lt;/strong&gt; Solutions like &lt;a href=&#34;https://canary.tools/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Thinkst&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://tracebit.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;TraceBit&lt;/a&gt; offer out-of-the-box token creation, monitoring, and notifications across major cloud providers and apps. For any bespoke tokens or corner-case scenarios, you’ll still need to handle monitoring yourself to ensure complete coverage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While a DIY approach could be sufficient for a relatively small environment, we needed something that could scale without manual intervention. So, after experimenting with Thinkst’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/thinkst/canarytokens&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OSS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://canarytokens.org/nest/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;free&lt;/a&gt; editions, we switched to their &lt;a href=&#34;https://canary.tools/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;cloud&lt;/a&gt; version for features missing in OSS, such as undetectable tokens, a robust API, audit-trail logging, and a full authentication/authorization system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To make the most out of our setup, we connected the notifications of the Thinkst platform to Grafana Cloud IRM &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/configure/integrations/webhooks/incoming-webhooks/oncall-webhooks/&#34;&gt;webhooks&lt;/a&gt;, as shown below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x439/562ee4a70e/webhook-feed.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x439/562ee4a70e/webhook-feed.png&#34;alt=&#34;Screenshot of a web page showing a Global Webhooks Feed section with options for managing flocks and installed webhooks.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x439/562ee4a70e/webhook-feed.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Screenshot of a web page showing a Global Webhooks Feed section with options for managing flocks and installed webhooks.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The webhook is then being listened to by the Grafana Cloud IRM integration:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x1009/ae9bb0e4c2/canary-tokens-integration.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x1009/ae9bb0e4c2/canary-tokens-integration.png&#34;alt=&#34;Screenshot of a Canary Tokens configuration page showing HTTP Endpoint, labels schema, templates, and routes options for security alerts.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x1009/ae9bb0e4c2/canary-tokens-integration.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Screenshot of a Canary Tokens configuration page showing HTTP Endpoint, labels schema, templates, and routes options for security alerts.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This setup allows us to route canary tokens’ notifications to Slack (as you can see in the Routes section above) and automate escalation chains (as you can see in the screenshot below). If you&amp;rsquo;d like to do something similar, further details on Grafana Cloud IRM integrations are available &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/configure/integrations/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x424/6cb322bee6/security-oncall.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x424/6cb322bee6/security-oncall.png&#34;alt=&#34;A schedule interface showing five steps with start, wait, and import actions for &amp;#39;Security Oncall&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;Security Managers&amp;#39; notifications.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x424/6cb322bee6/security-oncall.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A schedule interface showing five steps with start, wait, and import actions for &amp;#39;Security Oncall&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;Security Managers&amp;#39; notifications.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;canary-token-lifecycle&#34;&gt;Canary token lifecycle&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We use a simple, four-step lifecycle to operationalize canary tokens and turn them into an actionable detection and response capability:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt;: Generate a unique token, like an AWS API key, PDF link, or DNS subdomain that “phones home” when accessed.  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Place:&lt;/strong&gt; Embed tokens where attackers would look, like code repos, config directories, vaults, cloud consoles, databases, or shared drives.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitor:&lt;/strong&gt; A background service watches for any token use and sends an alert with metadata (timestamp, IP, hostname). Keep in mind: If you’re not using a platform, you must build custom monitoring.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respond:&lt;/strong&gt; Investigate alerts, isolate affected assets, and remediate before any real data is touched. Keep the triggered token for forensics and replace it immediately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;canary-tokens-and-trufflehog-to-the-rescue&#34;&gt;Canary tokens and TruffleHog to the rescue!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We planted AWS API key canary tokens (alongside a few others) in organization- and repository-level secrets. When the attacker exfiltrated the secrets and ran &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/trufflesecurity/trufflehog&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;TruffleHog&lt;/a&gt; to validate them, TruffleHog’s &lt;code&gt;sts:GetCallerIdentity&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.aws.amazon.com/STS/latest/APIReference/API_GetCallerIdentity.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;call&lt;/a&gt; against our tokens triggered the canary, unlike free canary tokens that are automatically detected by TruffleHog &lt;a href=&#34;https://trufflesecurity.com/blog/canaries&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;without calling the AWS API&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because Thinkst was watching those AWS accounts, we got an immediate Slack alert. That one notification, thanks to our strategic token placement, revealed the exact entry point. The Detection &amp;amp; Response team reacted to the notification and raised an incident. Teams across R&amp;amp;D and Security sprang into action to contain and remediate the incident, which, again, resulted in no code modifications, unauthorized access to production systems, exposure of customer data, or access to personal information. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-canary-token-placement-strategy&#34;&gt;Our canary token placement strategy&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Given GitHub&amp;rsquo;s central role as our primary source of truth, safeguarding it with canary tokens is crucial. Specifically, we strategically deploy AWS API key canary tokens within GitHub Secrets by placing the tokens at the organization level (to flag any repo breach) and per repository (to precisely pinpoint intrusions at the repository level). Other platforms get their own flavors. For example, &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.canary.tools/hc/en-gb/articles/360021010497-How-do-I-create-a-Google-Docs-Sheets-Token&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Google Docs&lt;/a&gt; tokens live in shared Google Drive files, email-based tokens in dummy inboxes, and DNS tokens in unused subdomains.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The key is to map out every asset (repos, CI/CD pipelines, cloud consoles, vaults, pods, containers, etc.) and sprinkle a diverse mix of tokens wherever an attacker might snoop. We’ve deployed tens of thousands (or an infinite amount, for that matter), so watch your steps, since there’s a tripwire behind every click.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-you-can-utilize-canary-tokens-in-your-security-setup&#34;&gt;How you can utilize canary tokens in your security setup&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve walked through how we deploy canary tokens, we want to share some tips for how you can utilize them as well. For the purposes of this blog, we&amp;rsquo;ll focus our advice on the same tools we use internally (because we believe in them as tried and tested technologies), but most of the general guidance still applies for other similar tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;shaping-your-placement-strategy-with-team-discussion&#34;&gt;Shaping your placement strategy with team discussion&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some key questions you should consider before deciding on your canary placement and alerting strategy include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;which-token-types-catch-attackers-best&#34;&gt;Which token types catch attackers best?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pick from Thinkst’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.canary.tools/hc/en-gb/articles/4701687447325-What-are-Canarytokens&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;catalog&lt;/a&gt; (over two dozen types) to match your environment and threats. Mix cloud/API keys (AWS, Azure, Slack) with file- or link-based tokens (PDFs, DNS, URLs) so you cover code repos, docs, and networks. Use a variety to broaden detection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-do-you-make-alerts-impossible-to-miss&#34;&gt;How do you make alerts impossible to miss?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tune your alert thresholds and channels to strike the right balance between urgency and noise. Consider:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acknowledge alerts early:&lt;/strong&gt; Acknowledge alerts promptly on the Thinkst platform to avoid grouping subsequent alerts and missing notifications of repeated canary token triggers from different IP addresses.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;METADATA IS IMPORTANT:&lt;/strong&gt; For quicker investigation, ensure every notification includes canary token metadata (name, location, reminder text). The Thinkst platform automates this if the reminder text is correctly configured.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;where-do-alerts-need-to-land&#34;&gt;Where do alerts need to land?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Choose channels your team actually watches:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Immediate channels:&lt;/strong&gt; Slack (with webhooks) or the Grafana Cloud IRM mobile app for 24/7 paging&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary channels:&lt;/strong&gt; Security mailing lists, SIEM, or ticketing (e.g., Splunk) for structured incident tracking&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Map each severity level to the right channel so nothing slips through.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;where-should-tokens-live&#34;&gt;Where should tokens live?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sprinkle tokens in high-risk and high-value spots:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CI/CD pipelines&lt;/strong&gt;: As dummy environment variables, test jobs, or secondary workflows&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Private GitHub/GitLab repositories&lt;/strong&gt;: In config files, comments or branch-specific .env files&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer workstations &amp;amp; build servers&lt;/strong&gt;: In ~/.aws/credentials, hidden directories or registry entries&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud accounts &amp;amp; consoles&lt;/strong&gt;: Nested within IAM policies or metadata documents&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shared network drives &amp;amp; documentation&lt;/strong&gt;: In ordinary looking directories or PDFs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Public GitHub/GitLab repositories&lt;/strong&gt;: Be cautious here! Alert fatigue is a real thing. Limit use of canary tokens in public repositories to avoid false positives from automated secret scanners triggered by inadvertently exposed sensitive information like AWS API keys in Git branches (i.e., obvious places).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-do-you-prevent-accidental-triggers&#34;&gt;How do you prevent accidental triggers?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Educate teams&lt;/strong&gt;: Explain the “what” and “where” of canary tokens.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demo alerts&lt;/strong&gt;: Show how tokens work and what notifications look like.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Announce deployments&lt;/strong&gt;: Share rollout plans in team channels.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Document “off-limits” zones&lt;/strong&gt;: Post common token names and locations in your wiki.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use runbooks&lt;/strong&gt;: Guide responders through investigations to avoid confusion.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You have two communication strategies for canary tokens:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silent&lt;/strong&gt;: No internal notice, which is better for catching insiders but higher false positives.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communicative&lt;/strong&gt;: Teams know about tokens, with fewer false positives but risk tipping off attackers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;who-are-you-trying-to-catch&#34;&gt;Who are you trying to catch?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Identify target adversaries for canary tokens. Understand that advanced attackers use unique methods, so tokens alone are insufficient for full access prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External attackers&lt;/strong&gt; probing repos or cloud assets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated scanners&lt;/strong&gt; hunting for exposed secrets&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insider threats&lt;/strong&gt; snooping on token-laden areas&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supply-chain attackers&lt;/strong&gt; targeting CI/CD&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phishing or social-engineering&lt;/strong&gt; via document or email tokens&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By answering these, you’ll align token types, alerting, and placement with your organization’s risks and tools, thus turning every token into a reliable tripwire.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;best-practices-limitations-and-gotchas&#34;&gt;Best practices, limitations, and gotchas&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Canary tokens provide valuable, high-confidence alerts of compromise, but triggering one means an attacker is already inside your system. While effective, they are not a foolproof solution and have limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provider support varies:&lt;/strong&gt; Not every token type is available on every platform. If you build your own bespoke API or secret-generation service, you’ll need to roll your own monitoring. One way to do that is to log token IDs (never the secret!) into &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt;, set up &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/&#34;&gt;Grafana Alerting alerts&lt;/a&gt; on those IDs, and feed incidents into &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud IRM&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring availability:&lt;/strong&gt; If your token-watching infrastructure goes down, or worse, becomes compromised, you lose visibility entirely. So, secure your infrastructure!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;False positives from insiders:&lt;/strong&gt; Before we formally announced our token rollout, a handful of teammates accidentally tripped tokens simply by poking around. By asking them why they accessed those credentials, we quickly labeled those alerts as benign and moved on.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Obfuscated attacker source:&lt;/strong&gt; VPNs hide real IPs, so location data can be misleading. Some browser-based tokens can add fingerprinting, but that only works for web-triggered tokens.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;API rate limits:&lt;/strong&gt; Even when vendors advertise “unlimited” API calls, their infrastructure typically enforces limitations. Blast too many token creation or update requests at once and you’ll hit throttling or even break the API.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are the key best practices we’ve learnt over time:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use descriptive reminders:&lt;/strong&gt; Leverage Thinkst’s “reminder” text field to tag each token with owner, environment, and location. You can also store JSON in that field and retrieve it later via the UI or API.  That metadata lets you pinpoint precisely what was touched.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One token per location:&lt;/strong&gt; When a token fires, archive it for forensics, since an attacker might reuse or sell it, then replace it ideally with a fresh name that blends in (e.g., AWS_API_CREDS instead of CANARY_TOKEN_AWS).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Group into flocks:&lt;/strong&gt; Organize tokens by environment, team, or platform into &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.canary.tools/hc/en-gb/articles/360012874638-How-do-I-create-a-new-flock&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;flocks&lt;/a&gt; to simplify bulk management.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integrate alerts into incident response:&lt;/strong&gt; Route notifications into your messaging system, your SIEM, and/or ticketing system so that nothing slips through the cracks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mix token types:&lt;/strong&gt; Don’t rely solely on AWS API keys. Deploy file, URL/DNS, email, and command tokens to cover every attacker tactic.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automate placement:&lt;/strong&gt; Use Thinkst’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/thinkst/canary-utils&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;scripts or IaC examples&lt;/a&gt; (Terraform, Ansible, Puppet, and AWS CloudFormation) to ensure consistency. We also worked closely with Thinkst support to master their UI, API, and tooling and learn some best practices.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test your tokens and document actions:&lt;/strong&gt; Trigger a few tokens in a safe environment after deployment to verify alert delivery and downstream automation. This will also enhance your incident response plan. This practice allows you to simulate real-world scenarios and refine your response procedures. Document these simulated incidents and the corresponding steps taken to create comprehensive runbooks. These runbooks will serve as valuable guides when canary tokens are triggered in the future, ensuring a more efficient and effective response and less confusion.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communicate widely and wisely:&lt;/strong&gt; Make your teams (or even your broader community) aware of canary tokens. That transparency reduces accidental triggers and builds security awareness.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By understanding these limitations and following these practices, you’ll keep your canary token deployment lean, reliable, and ready to catch real attacks the moment they unfold. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Canary tokens have been a force multiplier for us, turning every corner of our infrastructure into a potential tripwire and giving us the precious minutes needed to stop a breach before it escalates. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seed your environment with right token types, integrate alerts for automation, and never underestimate the advantage of knowing an adversary is inside before they ever touch your real assets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们详细介绍了最近与Github动作有关的安全事件，但我们尚未公开的是如何找到攻击者留下的小径：金丝雀令牌。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;快速回顾&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/05/15/grafana-security-post-post-cost-indind-fiew-for-github-github-github-workflow-workflow-vulnerability-vulnerability-and-whats-next/”&gt;安全事件&lt;/a&gt;在4月26日，在4月26日，一个脆弱的Github Action Workflow允许使用Une useflimimit conseffe useffe oss usess offe usefter/per po&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/15/grafana-security-update-post-incident-review-for-github-workflow-vulnerability-and-whats-next/&#34;&gt;investigation&lt;/a&gt; into the incident concluded May 12, and we confirmed that &lt;strong&gt;there were no code modifications, unauthorized access to production systems, exposure of customer data, or access to personal信息。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;触发了最初的事件（但在我们的调查结束之前）后，攻击者删除了他们的叉子，PRS和工作流程，以试图掩盖其轨道。这导致未经授权访问五个公共存储库的秘密，尽管这也不会影响生产系统或客户数据。我们禁用受影响的工作流程，旋转所有暴露的凭据，并使用TruffleHog审核我们的存储库，&lt;a href =“/blog/blog/2025/06/26/how-to-to-to-to-detect-vulnerable-github-actions-github-actions-at-scale-at-Scale-at-scale-zizmor/”&gt; Zizmor/“&gt; Zizmor &lt;/a&gt; and Gato-x。我们还在Grafana Loki和其他数据源进行了完整的访问日志审查。您可以阅读初始公告&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/04/27/grafana-security-update-no-customer-impact-impact-from-github-workflow-vulnerability/”&gt;在这里&lt;/a&gt;和pir &lt;a href =“/blog/2025/05/15/grafana-security-update-post-indident-indident-indident-review for-github-workflow-vulnerability-and-vulnerability-and-whats-next/”&gt;在这里&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;没有金丝雀令牌和我们的注意团队，检测攻击将需要更长的时间。在此博客中，我们将解释金丝雀令牌是什么，并向您展示它们如何帮助我们。我们还将告诉您他们如何在成为严重的安全事件之前帮助您检测入侵。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“什么是tokenary-tokens and-do-do-we-us-them-at-at grafana-labs”&gt;什么是金丝雀令牌？我们如何在Grafana Labs使用它们？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;金丝雀代币是数字绊窗或诱饵，看起来对入侵者很有价值，但没有合法使用。如果有人找到并使用了您已部署的，您将立即收到警报。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以煤矿装饰（有毒天然气的预警）命名，这些令牌比蜜罐轻得多。他们可以采用许多简单的表格，例如API键，文件，URL或DNS条目，使它们快速易于在环境中部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们的情况下，金丝雀令牌不仅是一个实验，它们是告诉我们攻击者在里面的主要信号：AWS API密钥已由攻击者验证；我们得到了实时警报；团队蜂拥而至；并在几分钟内包含入侵。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这里e从该检测中的可操作的课程，以及为什么放置和部署比令牌本身更重要：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;速度获胜：&lt;/strong&gt;金丝雀令牌将小时的分类变成遏制分钟。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;放置很重要：&lt;/strong&gt;选择正确的令牌类型，并将其放置在攻击者实际上。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;精确指标的精度：&lt;/strong&gt;利用组织级令牌进行广泛的妥协检测和存储库级令牌以识别特定的入口点。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;元数据是黄金：&lt;/strong&gt;综合提醒文本，象征名称和位置对于有效的分类至关重要。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;集成是关键：&lt;/strong&gt;金丝雀令牌只有在与清晰的命名，自动警报和集成响应工作流程配对时。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;迭代缩放：&lt;/strong&gt;首先在高风险区域的小规模放置开始。只有这样，通过完善您的响应策略，您才能扩展使用金丝雀令牌。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“如何建造 - 您的token-token-Infrasture”&gt;我们如何构建金丝雀令牌基础架构&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;部署金丝雀令牌有两个选项：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; DIY设置：&lt;/strong&gt;自己生成令牌（API键，假文件，自定义URL），并构建或插入现有的监视系统以捕获任何令牌使用。这使您可以完全控制令牌行为和警报处理，使其非常适合自定义平台。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自动化平台：&lt;/strong&gt;解决方案，例如&lt;a href =“ https://canary.tools/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; thinkst &lt;/a&gt;或开箱即用的令牌创建，监视和大量云提供商和应用程序的通知。对于任何定制令牌或角落场景，您仍然需要处理自己的监视以确保完全覆盖。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然DIY方法对于相对较小的环境可能就足够了，但我们需要可以在不手动干预的情况下进行扩展的东西。因此，在尝试了Thinkst的&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/thinkst/canarytokens” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; oss &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ noreferrer&#34;&gt;free&lt;/a&gt; editions, we switched to their &lt;a href=&#34;https://canary.tools/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;cloud&lt;/a&gt; version for features missing in OSS, such as undetectable tokens, a robust API, audit-trail logging, and a full authentication/authorization system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了充分利用我们的设置，我们将Thinkst平台的通知连接到Grafana Cloud Irm &lt;a href =“/docs/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/artering-anding-and-mirm/irm/irm/ configure/integrations/webhooks/inchooks/incoming-webhooks-webhooks-webhooks-webhooks/oncall-webhooks/oncall-webhooks/oncall-webhooks pp/&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http：// schema.org/imageObject“&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x439/562ee4a70e/webhook-feed.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x439/562ee4a70e/webhook-feed.png” Alt =“ Alt =”网上页面的ScreenShot，显示一个全球Webhooks，显示一个全球webhooks fef部分，该部分用于管理植物和安装Web的webhooks。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x439/562ee4a70e/webhook-feed.png”&#xA;Alt =“网页的屏幕截图显示一个全局Webhooks提要部分，其中包含用于管理羊群和已安装的Webhooks的选项。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，webhook被grafana cloud IRM集成聆听：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x1009/ae9bb0e4c2/canary-tokens-integration.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x1009/ae9bb0e4c2/canary-tokens-integration.png&#34;alt=&#34;Screenshot of a Canary Tokens configuration page showing HTTP Endpoint, labels schema, templates, and routes options for security alerts.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x1009/ae9bb0e4c2/canary-tokens-integration.png”&#xA;alt =“金丝雀令牌配置页面的屏幕截图显示HTTP端点，标签架构，模板和路由安全警报的选项。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此设置允许我们将Canary令牌的通知路由放松（如上所述的路线部分所示），并自动化升级链（如下面的屏幕截图所示）。如果您想做类似的事情，请提供有关Grafana Cloud IRM集成的更多详细信息&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-mirm/irm/irm/configure/intementations/&#39;&gt;在这里&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x424/6cb3222bee6/security-oncall.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x424/6cb3222bee6/security-oncall.png” alt =“ Alt =” Alt =“一个时间表接口显示五个步骤，显示了五个步骤，并在开始，等待和导入&#39;安全OnCall OnCall OnCall OnCall OnCall和“安全管理者”的“安全管理器”，“&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x424/6cb3222bee6/security-oncall.png”&#xA;alt =“计划界面显示五个步骤，其中启动，等待和导入操作&#39;安全性OnCall&#39;和&#39;安​​全经理&#39;通知。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“金丝雀token-lifecycle”&gt; canAry令牌生命周期&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们使用一个简单的四步生命周期来操作金丝雀令牌，并将其变成可操作的检测和响应能力：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;创建&lt;/strong&gt;：生成一个独特的令牌，例如AWS API键，PDF链接或DNS子域，该子域在访问时“ home home”。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;地点：&lt;/strong&gt;嵌入代币，攻击者会在其中看，例如代码存储库，配置目录，保险库，云控制台，数据库或共享驱动器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;监视器：&lt;/strong&gt;背景服务手表可用于任何令牌使用，并使用元数据（Timestamp，ip，hostname）发送警报。请记住：如果您不使用平台，则必须构建自定义监视。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;响应：&lt;/strong&gt;调查警报，隔离受影响的资产并在触摸任何实际数据之前进行补救。将触发的令牌保留以进行取证并立即替换。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“金丝雀tokens and trufflehog-to-the-inscue”&gt;金丝雀令牌和Trufflehog进行营救！&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们在组织和存储库水平的秘密中种植了AWS API关键的金丝雀令牌（与其他几个）。当攻击者删除秘密并运行时href =“ https://docs.aws.amazon.com/sts/latest/apireference/api_getCallerItidentity.html” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;呼叫&lt;/a&gt; call &lt;/a&gt;对我们的代币触发的触发，&lt;/a&gt;触发了&lt;/a&gt;，触发了canary truff tike the canary tick &lt; href =“ https://trufflesecurity.com/blog/canaries” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;而无需调用AWS API &lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因为Thinkst在观看这些AWS帐户，所以我们得到了立即的松弛警报。该通知，由于我们的战略代币放置，这一通知揭示了确切的入口点。检测与响应小组对通知做出了反应，并提出了事件。 R＆D和安全性的团队逐渐采取行动，以控制和纠正事件，这再次导致没有代码修改，未经授权访问生产系统，暴露客户数据或访问个人信息。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“我们的式式置换式策略”&gt;我们的金丝雀令牌放置策略&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;鉴于Github作为我们的主要真理来源的核心作用，使用金丝雀令牌保护它至关重要。具体来说，我们通过将令牌放置在组织级别（以标记任何回购漏洞）和每个存储库（以精确的位置在存储库级别上），从而在GitHub Secrets中战略性地部署AWS API关键的金丝雀令牌。其他平台获得了自己的口味。 For example, &lt;a href=&#34;https://help.canary.tools/hc/en-gb/articles/360021010497-How-do-I-create-a-Google-Docs-Sheets-Token&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Google Docs&lt;/a&gt; tokens live in shared Google Drive files, email-based tokens in dummy收件箱，和未使用子域中的DNS令牌。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;关键是要绘制每个资产（存储库，CI/CD管道，云控制台，保险库，吊舱，容器等），并在攻击者可能窥探的任何地方撒上各种代币的混合物。我们已经部署了成千上万的（或无限的金额），因此请注意您的步骤，因为每次点击后都有绊脚线。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ how-you-can-utilize-canary-tokens in your-security-stetup”&gt;如何在安全设置中使用金丝雀令牌&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;既然我们已经浏览了如何部署金丝雀令牌，我们想分享一些技巧，以了解如何利用它们。出于本博客的目的，我们将建议我们的建议上对我们内部使用的相同工具（因为我们认为它们是经过尝试和测试的技术），但是大多数一般指导仍然适用于其他类似的工具。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“塑造自己的平台 - 策略与团队讨论”&gt;通过团队讨论来塑造您的安置策略&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在决定金丝雀放置和警报策略之前，您应该考虑一些关键问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“哪个typty-types-catch-攻击者 -  best”&gt;哪种令牌类型最好地捕捉攻击者？&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从Thinkst的&lt;a href =“ https://help.canary.tools/hc/en-gb/articles/4701687447325-what-what-what-are-canarytokens” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ rel =” noopener noreferrer“&gt;” noopener noreferrer“将云/API键（AWS，Azure，Slack）与基于文件或链接的令牌（PDFS，DNS，URL）混合，因此您涵盖了代码存储库，文档和网络。使用各种范围扩大检测。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“如何做 - 莫克 - 阿特斯 - 无法解决的失误”&gt;如何使警报不可能错过？&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;调整您的警报阈值和通道，以在紧迫性和噪声之间达到适当的平衡。考虑：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;尽早确认警报：&lt;/strong&gt;在ThinkSt平台上及时确认警报，以避免将随后的警报分组，并从不同的IP地址分组重复的金丝雀令牌触发器的通知。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;元数据很重要：&lt;/strong&gt;进行更快的调查，确保每一个通知都包括金丝雀令牌元数据（名称，位置，提醒文本）。如果提醒文本已正确配置，则Thinkst平台将自动化此。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“ do-alerts-need-to-land”&gt;警报需要在哪里登陆？&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;选择团队实际观看的频道：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;即时渠道：&lt;/strong&gt;松弛（带Webhooks）或Grafana Cloud IRM移动应用程序24/7分页&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;辅助渠道：&lt;/strong&gt;安全邮件列表，SIEM或票务（例如Splunk）结构化事件跟踪&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将每个严重性级别映射到正确的通道，因此没有滑动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“在哪里可以放tokens-live”&gt;代币应该在哪里？&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在高风险和高价值斑点中撒上代币：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; CI/CD管道&lt;/strong&gt;：作为虚拟环境变量，测试工作或次要工作FLOWS &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;私有github/gitlab存储库&lt;/strong&gt;：在配置文件，注释或特定于分支的.env文件&lt;/li&gt;中&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;开发人员工作站和构建服务器&lt;/strong&gt;：在〜/.aws/.aws/vertentials，隐藏的目录或注册表条目&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;云帐户和控制台&lt;/strong&gt;：嵌套在IAM策略或元数据文档中&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;共享网络驱动器和文档&lt;/strong&gt;：在普通的外观目录或pdfs &lt;/li&gt;中&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;公共github/gitlab存储库&lt;/strong&gt;：在这里谨慎！警报疲劳是真实的。限制在公共存储库中使用金丝雀令牌，以避免由自动秘密扫描仪造成的误报，这是由无意间暴露的敏感信息触发的，例如GIT分支机构中的AWS API键（即显而易见的位置）。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“如何进行预防措施-Accidental-Triggers”&gt;您如何防止意外触发器？&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;教育团队&lt;/strong&gt;：解释金丝雀令牌的“什么”和“哪里”。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;演示警报&lt;/strong&gt;：显示代币的工作方式以及通知是什么样的。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;宣布部署&lt;/strong&gt;：在团队渠道中分享推出计划。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;文档“禁区”区域&lt;/strong&gt;：在您的Wiki中发布共同的令牌名称和位置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;使用Runbooks &lt;/strong&gt;：通过调查引导响应者避免混乱。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您有两种金丝雀令牌的通信策略：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;沉默&lt;/strong&gt;：没有内部通知，这比捕获内部人士，但误报更高。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;交流&lt;/strong&gt;：团队知道令牌，误报较少，但有可能降低攻击者的风险。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确定金丝雀令牌的目标对手。了解高级攻击者使用独特的方法，因此仅代币不足以预防全面访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;外部攻击者&lt;/strong&gt;探测存储库或云资产&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自动扫描仪&lt;/strong&gt;寻找暴露的秘密&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;内部人士威胁&lt;/strong&gt;在载有代币的地区窥探&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;供应链攻击者&lt;/strong&gt;针对CI/CD &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;网络钓鱼或社交工程&lt;/strong&gt;通过文档或电子邮件令牌&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过回答这些问题，您将使令牌类型与组织的风险和工具保持一致，提醒和放置，从而将每个令牌变成可靠的Tripwire。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“最佳实践限制和gotchas”&gt;最佳实践，限制和gotchas &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;金丝雀令牌提供了有价值的，高信心的妥协警报，但触发攻击者已经在系统内部。虽然有效，但它们不是万无一失的解决方案，并且有局限性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提供者支持各不相同：&lt;/strong&gt;并非每个平台上都可以使用每种令牌类型。如果您建立自己的定制API或秘密生成服务，您需要进行自己的监视。一种方法是将令牌ID（绝不是秘密！）登录到&lt;a href =“/doc/docs/loki/最终/”&gt; grafana loki &lt;/a&gt;，设置&lt;a href =“/doc/docs/docs/grafana/最终/alteral/nevering/” href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/natering-and-inm/irm/“&gt; grafana cloud irm &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;监视可用性：&lt;/strong&gt;如果您的令牌观察基础架构下降，或者更糟的是，您会完全失去可见度。因此，确保您的基础架构！&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;内部人士的误报：&lt;/strong&gt;在我们正式宣布令牌推出之前，少数队友仅通过戳戳而意外地跳闸令牌。通过询问他们为什么访问这些凭据，我们迅速将这些警报标记为良性并继续前进。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;混淆攻击者来源：&lt;/strong&gt; vpns隐藏真实的IP，因此位置数据可能会误导。一些基于浏览器的令牌可以添加指纹印刷，但这仅适用于Web触发的令牌。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; API速率限制：&lt;/strong&gt;即使供应商宣传“无限”的API呼叫，其基础架构通常会实现限制。一次爆炸太多的代币创建或更新请求，您将击中节流甚至打破API。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是我们随着时间的推移学到的关键最佳实践：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;使用描述性提醒：&lt;/strong&gt;利用Thinkst的“提醒”文本字段，将每个令牌标记为所有者，环境和位置。您还可以将JSON存储在该字段中，并以后通过UI或API检索。  那个元数据使您可以精确地指出所触摸的内容。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;每个位置一个令牌：&lt;/strong&gt;当令牌大火时，将其存档以进行取证，因为攻击者可能会重复使用或出售它，然后将其理想地替换为融合的新名称（例如，AWS_API_CREDS，而不是canary_token_aws）。&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;小组成群：&lt;/strong&gt;按环境，团队或平台组织&lt;a href =” https://help.canary.tools/hc/en-gb/articles/360012874638-how-do-do-do-do-do-i-create-create-create-a-new-flock--------12874638- Noreferrer“&gt;羊群&lt;/a&gt;简化批量管理。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;将警报集成到事件响应中：&lt;/strong&gt;路由通知到您的消息传递系统，您的siem和/或票务系统，以便没有任何通过裂缝滑动的。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;混合令牌类型：&lt;/strong&gt;不要仅依靠AWS API键。部署文件，URL/DNS，电子邮件和命令令牌以涵盖每个攻击者策略。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automate placement:&lt;/strong&gt; Use Thinkst’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/thinkst/canary-utils&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;scripts or IaC examples&lt;/a&gt; (Terraform, Ansible, Puppet, and AWS CloudFormation) to ensure consistency.我们还与Thinkst的支持紧密合作，以掌握其UI，API和工具并学习一些最佳实践。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;测试您的令牌和文档操作：&lt;/strong&gt;触发一些令牌部署后的安全环境以验证警报交付和下游自动化。这也将增强您的事件响应计划。这种做法使您可以模拟现实情况并完善您的响应程序。记录这些模拟事件以及为创建全面运行书所采取的相应步骤。当将来触发金丝雀令牌时，这些运行簿将作为有价值的指南，确保更有效，更有效的响应和更少的混乱。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;沟通广泛，明智：&lt;/strong&gt;使您的团队（甚至更广泛的社区）意识到金丝雀令牌。透明度降低了意外触发因素并建立了安全意识。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过了解这些局限性并遵循这些实践，您将保持金丝雀令牌部署精益，可靠，并准备好在展开的那一刻就可以捕捉到真正的攻击。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“结论”&gt;结论&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;金丝雀令牌对我们来说是一种力量乘数，将我们的基础设施的每个角落变成了潜在的绊脚线，并为我们提供了在升级之前停止违规所需的宝贵时间。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用正确的令牌类型播种您的环境，集成自动化警报，并且永远不会低估知道对手在触摸您的真实资产之前就在内部的优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana Mimir: 3 reasons to run the TSDB for Prometheus on bare metal】Grafana Mimir：在裸机上运行Prometheus的TSDB的3个理由</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/22/grafana-mimir-3-reasons-to-run-the-tsdb-for-prometheus-on-bare-metal/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wilfried Roset is an engineering manager who leads an SRE team and he is a Grafana Champion. Wilfried currently works at OVHcloud where he focuses on prioritizing sustainability, resilience, and industrialization to guarantee customers satisfaction.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether it&amp;rsquo;s for efficient resource allocation, flexibility, high availability, or scalability, it makes a lot of sense to run Grafana Mimir on Kubernetes—but it&amp;rsquo;s not the only way to deploy Mimir.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt; is Grafana Labs&amp;rsquo; horizontally scalable, highly available, multi-tenant TSDB for long-term storage for Prometheus metrics, and in this blog post I&amp;rsquo;ll cover three reasons why you might want to run it on virtual machines and/or bare metal instead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;you-dont-have-kubernetes&#34;&gt;You don&amp;rsquo;t have Kubernetes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most obvious reason you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t deploy Mimir on Kubernetes is that you don&amp;rsquo;t have a Kubernetes cluster at hand, so you cannot deploy Mimir—or anything else—on it. If you are in that camp, you might want to use &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/set-up/puppet/&#34;&gt;Puppet&lt;/a&gt; or Ansible to deploy your TSDB. Similar to the guidance in the official &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/installation/debian/&#34;&gt;Grafana documentation&lt;/a&gt;, you could install Mimir in a few commands on a Debian-based system:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;sudo apt-get update&#xA;sudo apt-get install -y apt-transport-https software-properties-common wget&#xA;sudo mkdir -p /etc/apt/keyrings/&#xA;wget -q -O - https://apt.grafana.com/gpg.key | gpg --dearmor | sudo tee /etc/apt/keyrings/grafana.gpg &amp;gt; /dev/null&#xA;echo &amp;#34;deb [signed-by=/etc/apt/keyrings/grafana.gpg] https://apt.grafana.com stable main&amp;#34; | sudo tee -a /etc/apt/sources.list.d/grafana.list&#xA;sudo apt-get update&#xA;sudo apt-get install mimir&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a RHEL-based system, run this command (the full instruction can be found in the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/installation/redhat-rhel-fedora/&#34;&gt;corresponding documentation&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;sudo dnf install wget&#xA;wget -q -O gpg.key https://rpm.grafana.com/gpg.key&#xA;sudo rpm --import gpg.key&#xA;sudo bash -c &amp;#39;cat &amp;lt;&amp;lt; EOF &amp;gt; /etc/yum.repos.d/grafana.repo&#xA;[grafana]&#xA;name=grafana&#xA;baseurl=https://rpm.grafana.com&#xA;repo_gpgcheck=1&#xA;enabled=1&#xA;gpgcheck=1&#xA;gpgkey=https://rpm.grafana.com/gpg.key&#xA;sslverify=1&#xA;sslcacert=/etc/pki/tls/certs/ca-bundle.crt&#xA;EOF&amp;#39;&#xA;sudo dnf install mimir&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;you-want-to-break-circular-dependencies&#34;&gt;You want to break circular dependencies&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Depending on your information system and organization, you could be in a position where you&amp;rsquo;re the service provider to many teams, and you provide an internal metrics service to the Kubernetes/platform team. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this scenario, you probably have at least one critical circular dependency—the ops team running the Kubernetes cluster rely on their metrics, which are stored in the service you provide. An outage on the Kubernetes cluster, even a small one, can have a severe impact on your deployment, which then impacts access to the metrics. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One way to break this circular dependency is to run at least two Kubernetes clusters and two Mimir clusters:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Kubernetes cluster-A hosts Mimir cluster-1.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Kubernetes cluster-B hosts Mimir cluster-2.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mimir cluster-1 hosts the metrics of Kubernetes cluster-B.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mimir cluster-2 hosts the metrics of Kubernetes cluster-A.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this deployment approach, you have broken the circular dependencies, though you have increased the number of Kubernetes clusters run by your ops team. Be mindful that cross-Kubernetes outages exist and you should take that into account when designing your information system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another way to break these circular dependencies is to not run Mimir on Kubernetes at all. In that case, I&amp;rsquo;d recommend following the process outlined in the &amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t have Kubernetes&amp;rdquo; section above. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;you-want-to-learn-the-hard-way&#34;&gt;You want to learn the hard way&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, you might want to run Mimir outside of Kubernetes, just to learn how it works the hard way. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes offers so many features, integrations, and automation that it can sometimes be mistaken for magic. But with a bit of free time you can learn a lot about software without the &lt;em&gt;Kubernetes magic&lt;/em&gt;; Mimir is not different. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for your next metrics TSDB, I recommend spending some time looking at all aspects of your software. You could begin by following the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/get-started/play-with-grafana-mimir/&#34;&gt;getting started guide&lt;/a&gt;, then evaluate your critical dependencies. Once you are ready, you can &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/set-up/helm-chart/&#34;&gt;deploy Mimir on Kubernetes&lt;/a&gt; or on bare metal. If you choose to deploy Mimir on bare metal and you manage your configuration with Puppet like I discussed earlier, we have &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/set-up/puppet/&#34;&gt;the module for you&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;running-mimir-on-kubernetes-vs-bare-metal&#34;&gt;Running Mimir on Kubernetes vs. bare metal&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While running Mimir on Kubernetes can bring many benefits, there are also some potential drawbacks and considerations to be aware of. Ultimately, the decision depends on your specific needs, resources, and expertise. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Weigh the benefits against the potential drawbacks and consider a proof-of-concept deployment to determine the best approach for your use case. More specifically, make sure to have a closer look at the pros and cons of bare metal deployments:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pros:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Can be deployed without a Kubernetes cluster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Allows for breaking of circular dependencies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Opportunity to learn about the software without relying on Kubernetes features and automation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cons:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;May require more manual configuration and management&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Could increase the complexity of deployment and maintenance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want to share your Grafana story and dashboards with the community? Drop us a note at&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:stories@grafana.com&#34;&gt;stories@grafana.com!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; Wilfried Roset是一名工程经理，领导SRE团队，他是Grafana冠军。威尔弗里德（Wilfried）目前在OVHCloud工作，他专注于优先考虑可持续性，韧性和工业化以保证客户满意度。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;是否是用于有效的资源分配，灵活性，高可用性或可扩展性，在Kubernetes上运行Grafana Mimir很有意义，但这并不是部署Mimir的唯一方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“/oss/mimir/”&gt; mimir &lt;/a&gt;是Grafana Labs的水平扩展，高度可用，多租户的TSDB，用于长期存储用于Prometheus指标的长期存储，在此博客文章中，我可能想掩盖三个理由在虚拟机器和/或裸露的金属上使用三个理由。&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ you-dont-have-kubernetes”&gt;您没有kubernetes &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您不会在Kubernetes上部署Mimir的最明显原因是您手头上没有Kubernetes群集，因此您不能在其中部署Mimir（或其他任何东西）。如果您在那个营地，则可能需要使用&lt;a href =“/doc/mimir/最终/set-in-set-up/puppet/”&gt; puppet &lt;/a&gt;或可安排来部署您的TSDB。类似于官方&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最终/setup-grafana/installation/debian/“&gt; grafana文档&lt;/a&gt;，您可以在基于debian的系统上安装mimir：&lt;/p&gt;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class =“ code-snippet code-snippet__mini”&gt; &lt;div class =“ lang-toolbar__mini”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class =“ code-clipboard”&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data =“ app_code_snippet（）” x-init =“ init（）” @click =“ copy（）”&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class =“ code-clipboard__icon” src =“/媒体/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg” alt =“复制代码到剪贴板” width =“ 14”高度=“ 13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class =“代码 - 尼珀代码snippet__border”&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded =“ false”&gt; &lt;code class =“ language-none”&gt; sudo apt-get更新&#xA;sudo apt-get install -y apt-transport-https https软件 - 普罗托斯 - 普通wget&#xA;sudo mkdir -p/etc/apt/keyrings/&#xA;WGET -Q -O -https：//apt.grafana.com/gpg.key | GPG  -  dearmor | sudo tee /etc/apt/keyrings/grafana.gpg&gt;/dev/null&#xA;echo“ deb [signed-by =/etc/apt/keyrings/grafana.gpg] https://apt.grafana.com稳定的main” | sudo tee -a/etc/apt/sources.list.d/grafana.list.list&#xA;sudo apt-get更新&#xA;sudo apt-get安装mimir &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;对于基于RHEL的系统，运行此命令（可以在&lt;a a href =“/docs/grafana/grafana/最新/setup-grafana/installation/redhat-rhel-fedora/”中找到完整的指令&lt;/a&gt;）：&lt;/p&gt;）：&lt;/p&gt;）：&lt;/p&gt;）&#xA;&lt;div class =“ code-snippet code-snippet__mini”&gt; &lt;div class =“ lang-toolbar__mini”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class =“ code-clipboard”&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data =“ app_code_snippet（）” x-init =“ init（）” @click =“ copy（）”&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class =“ code-clipboard__icon” src =“/媒体/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg” alt =“复制代码到剪贴板” width =“ 14”高度=“ 13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class =“代码 - 尼珀代码snippet__border”&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded =“ false”&gt; &lt;code class =“ language-none”&gt; sudo dnf安装wget&#xA;WGET -Q -O GPG.Key https://rpm.grafana.com/gpg.key&#xA;sudo rpm -import gpg.key&#xA;sudo bash -c&#39;cat &lt;&lt; eof&gt; /etc/yum.repos.d/grafana.repo&#xA;[Grafana]&#xA;名称= Grafana&#xA;baseurl = https：//rpm.grafana.com&#xA;repo_gpgcheck = 1&#xA;启用= 1&#xA;gpgcheck = 1&#xA;gpgkey = https：//rpm.grafana.com/gpg.key&#xA;sslverify = 1&#xA;sslcacert =/etc/pki/tls/certs/ca-bundle.crt&#xA;eof&#39;&#xA;sudo dnf安装mimir &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 id =“你想偏向圆形的依赖性”&gt;您想打破循环依赖项&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据您的信息系统和组织，您可以处于许多团队的服务提供商的位置，并且为Kubernetes/Platform团队提供内部指标服务。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这种情况下，您可能至少有一个关键的循环依赖性 - 运行Kubernetes群集的OPS团队依赖于其指标，这些指标存储在您提供的服务中。 Kubernetes群集的中断，即使是一个小的群集，都会对您的部署产生严重影响，从而影响对指标的访问。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;打破这种循环依赖性的一种方法是至少运行两个kubernetes簇和两个mimir簇：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; kubernetes cluster-a主持mimir cluster-1。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; kubernetes cluster-b主机mimir cluster-2。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; mimir cluster-1托管Kubernetes cluster-B。&lt;/li&gt;的指标&#xA;&lt;li&gt; mimir cluster-2托管kubernetes cluster-a的指标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用这种部署方法，您已经打破了循环依赖性，尽管您增加了OPS团队运行的Kubernetes群集的数量。请注意，跨库伯涅特存在存在，在设计信息系统时应考虑到这一点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;打破这些循环依赖性的另一种方法是根本不在kubernetes上运行mimir。在这种情况下，我建议按照上面的“您没有kubernetes”部分概述的过程遵循该过程。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“你是愿意的学习 - 艰难的路”&gt;您想学习困难的方法&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，您可能想在Kubernetes之外运行Mimir，只是为了了解它的工作方式。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes提供了许多功能，集成和自动化，有时可能会误认为魔术。但是，如果没有&lt;em&gt; kubernetes Magic &lt;/em&gt;，您可以在空闲时间里学到很多有关软件的知识；米米尔没有什么不同。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您正在寻找下一个指标TSDB，建议您花一些时间查看软件的各个方面。您可以首先关注&lt;a href =“/doc/mimir/lestest/wet get-started/play-with-with-with-with-with-with-with-with-with-with-with-with-with grafana-mimir/”&gt;入门指南&lt;/a&gt;，然后评估您的关键依赖性。准备就绪后，您可以&lt;a href =“/doc/mimir/最新/设置/helm-chart/”&gt;在kubernetes上部署mimir &lt;/a&gt;或在裸机上。如果您选择在裸金属上部署mimir，并且像我之前讨论的那样用木偶来管理配置，那么我们有&lt;a href =“/docs/mimir/最终/sett/stet/set-up/puppet/“&gt; for you for you &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“跑步mimir-on-kubernetes-vs-bare-metal“&gt; kubernetes上的米米尔与裸机&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Kubernetes上运行Mimir可以带来许多好处，但也有一些潜在的缺点和注意事项需要注意。最终，决定取决于您的特定需求，资源和专业知识。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;权衡收益与潜在缺点，并考虑概念验证的部署，以确定用例的最佳方法。更具体地说，请确保仔细研究裸机部署的利弊：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;专业人士：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可以在没有kubernetes群集的情况下部署&#xA;&lt;li&gt;允许打破圆形依赖关系&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;有机会在不依赖Kubernetes功能和自动化的情况下了解该软件&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; cons：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可能需要更多的手动配置和管理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;可以增加部署和维护的复杂性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;想与社区分享您的Grafana故事和仪表板吗？给我们留言&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“ mailto：story@grafana.com”&gt; story@grafana.com！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to monitor your homelab with Beyla, eBPF, and OpenTelemetry】如何使用beyla，eBPF和OpenTelemetry监视您的Homelab</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/22/how-to-monitor-your-homelab-with-beyla-ebpf-and-opentelemetry/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Goutham Veeramachaneni sees his homelab as a proving ground.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a longtime engineer and product manager here at Grafana Labs, he built the homelab so he could deploy the same tools used in production, face the same observability challenges, and ultimately make monitoring more accessible. But he quickly discovered that the world of self-hosted services is messy, thanks to fragmented metrics, diverse stacks, and inconsistent monitoring. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“For traditional hobbyist use cases, most of the applications have no metrics at all,” Veeramachaneni said. “Even if they do have metrics, there is no consistency between applications. … I need to have a set of alerts and dashboards for each different application, and this is just too hard to manage.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even his own projects—a &lt;a href=&#34;https://thoughts.gouthamve.dev/books&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;homegrown book tracker&lt;/a&gt; and a private microblog—demanded extensive, error-prone manual work if he wanted to instrument them with OpenTelemetry. That’s where &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/beyla-ebpf/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Beyla&lt;/a&gt; came in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyla, the open source eBPF-based, zero-code instrumentation tool, provides application and network observability for any Linux application. And it’s simple to deploy, whether in a homelab or in a production Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Veeramachaneni and Nikola Grcevski, a principal software engineer at Grafana Labs, shared how Beyla, eBPF, and OpenTelemetry combine to make homelab observability easy during their recent &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2025/homelab-observability-with-ebpf-and-opentelemetry/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025 session&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqHO0oYW6Ic?si=W6_wWrfvRIg&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; The same week Veeramachaneni and Grcevski gave their talk, Grafana Labs announced the  &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation/pull/15&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation/pull/15&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;initial code drop&lt;/a&gt; of Beyla to OpenTelemetry, following through on a proposal &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/community/issues/2406&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/community/issues/2406&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;to donate Beyla&lt;/a&gt; to the OpenTelemetry project under the new project name OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation. Beyla will continue to exist as Grafana Labs’ distribution of the upstream OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-beyla-and-ebpf&#34;&gt;Why Beyla and eBPF?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grcevski, a Beyla maintainer, set out to address the persistent gaps in observability tooling: instrumenting legacy, third-party, or simply neglected services where code modification and traditional agents aren’t practical.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;eBPF proved to be a key component. Because it allows small, safe programs to run inside the Linux kernel without risking crashes or instability, Beyla could use it to observe application and network activity directly at the kernel level. That enabled Beyla to collect powerful observability data from any application, overcoming the limitations of traditional instrumentation tools. And it supported Beyla in creating a new class of auto-instrumentation that doesn’t care about frameworks or binaries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“With this technology, we can tap into any aspect of this application stack, and we can extract signals, which we then turn into telemetry,” Grcevski said. “We send them to an OpenTelemetry format, or we can export them directly to &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/getting-started/get-started-grafana-prometheus/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt;. This is how this magic happens.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;simple-deployment-consistent-monitoring&#34;&gt;Simple deployment, consistent monitoring&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For Veeramachaneni’s homelab, Beyla was transformative. With it running as a DaemonSet across his Kubernetes nodes, he was able to collect consistent, OpenTelemetry-compliant rate, error, and duration (RED) metrics and distributed traces—even from uninstrumented, off-the-shelf applications. Beyla’s ability to extract telemetry from HTTP and Redis protocols was especially valuable, because so many modern applications use them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This approach also allowed Beyla to capture this telemetry in a runtime-agnostic manner, collecting important metadata such as Kubernetes labels and zone information for automatic correlation and troubleshooting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“You get full distributed tracing,” Veeramachaneni said. “All of this is coming from Beyla, which I think is really cool.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/2894x1452/f135faac5b/homelab-distributed-tracing.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/2894x1452/f135faac5b/homelab-distributed-tracing.png&#34;alt=&#34;A software trace interface showing a timeline with various colored bars, indicating different processes and their durations.&#34;title=&#34;A screenshot of the distributed tracing demo that was part of the session.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/2894x1452/f135faac5b/homelab-distributed-tracing.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A software trace interface showing a timeline with various colored bars, indicating different processes and their durations.&#34;title=&#34;A screenshot of the distributed tracing demo that was part of the session.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;A screenshot of the distributed tracing demo that was part of the session.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deploying Beyla is mostly straightforward and painless, he said. It requires running a simple Helm install that provides all the necessary functionality out of the box, across multiple languages. (There can be exceptions on specific hardware; Raspberry Pi devices need to recompile the Linux kernel before deployment, for example.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-beyla-compares-to-native-instrumentation&#34;&gt;How Beyla compares to native instrumentation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Although Beyla enables rapid, broad-spectrum telemetry, there are nuances and trade-offs involved. While Beyla can see and correlate protocol-level traffic with almost no code changes, it doesn’t offer the same context-rich telemetry as native, source-level instrumentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, native instrumentation supports extending traces with extra business context, and it provides full details about templated SQL queries. Beyla, however, intentionally avoids exposing full SQL queries and other potentially sensitive data for security reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyla also requires some protocol- and language-specific adjustments; it automatically handles corner cases for some languages—think of Go’s goroutines or the async event loops in Node.js—but other platforms may require minor tweaks. For these reasons, it’s best to think of Beyla as a “fast start” on the journey to full instrumentation, Veeramachaneni said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“It took me several hours to manually instrument a very simple Go application,” he said. “And if you suddenly have 20 applications, you tell your engineers, ‘Now you have to go manually instrument everything,’ they’re just going to go on holiday together. So what Beyla gives you is, within one command, you get 80% of the way. And then you can use your engineering bandwidth to say, ‘Actually, these two applications are the most important. Let’s manually instrument them correctly.’”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;observability-for-everyone&#34;&gt;Observability for everyone&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The same observability fundamentals apply everywhere, from a handful of self-hosted services in a homelab to thousands of orchestrated containers in production. But installing, configuring and maintaining instrumentation across so many languages—or even binaries without source code—has always been daunting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By blending the kernel-powered reach of eBPF with the standards of OpenTelemetry, Beyla eliminates that barrier, making consistent, powerful insights available to everyone. For Veeramachaneni and Grcevski, that’s the future of observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We built it for the community,” Grcevski said. “We built it for everybody to try this.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; goutham veeramachaneni将他的homelab视为遗嘱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为Grafana Labs的长期工程师和产品经理，他建立了Homelab，以便他可以部署与生产中使用的相同工具，面临相同的可观察性挑战，并最终使监视更容易访问。但是他很快发现，由于零散的指标，多样化的堆栈和不一致的监视，自托管服务的世界是混乱的。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“对于传统的业余爱好者用例，大多数应用程序根本没有指标，” Veeramachaneni说。 “即使它们确实有指标，应用程序之间也没有一致性。…我需要为每个不同应用程序都有一组警报和仪表板，这太难管理了。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使是他自己的项目-A &lt;a href =” https：//thoughts.gouthamve.dev/books“ target =“ _ black” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;“ homegrowner book tracker &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;和私人微型blog”，私人的微博 - 备用的，错误的手动手动工作，如果他对他想要的openterlemetry to progence to progence to the He to posenteremetry，则那就是&lt;a href =“/oss/beyla-ebpf/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana beyla &lt;/a&gt;进来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; beyla是基于开源EBPF的零代码仪器工具，可为任何Linux应用程序提供应用程序和网络可观察性。无论是在Homelab还是在Kubernetes群集中部署很容易部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;Grafana Labs的主要软件工程师Nikola Grcevski &lt;p&gt; Veeramachaneni和Grafana Labs的主要软件工程师分享了Beyla，EBPF和OpenTelemetry的结合，使Homelab的可观察性变得容易，在他们的近期&lt;a期间href =“/events/grafanacon/2025/homelab-observability-with-ebpf-and-opentelemetry/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt&#39;&gt; grafanacon 2025 session &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;Iframe width =“ 560”高度=“ 315” src =“ https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqho0oyw6ic?si=w6_wwrffrig” title =“ youtube视频播放器” frameborder =“ 0”图片中的图片; web-share“ referrerpolicy =“ cross-origin”允许floserfullscreen&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;同一周Veeramachaneni和Grcevski进行了交谈，Grafana Labs宣布&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-epentelemetry-ebpf-inmentry-ebpf-inmtrumenta- href =“ https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation/pull/15“ target =” _ black“ rel =” noopener noreferrer“ href =“ https://github.com/open-telemetry/community/issues/2406” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href =“ noreferrer“&gt;将beyla &lt;/a&gt;捐赠给OpenTElemetry项目的新项目名称OpenTelemetry EBPF仪器。 Grafana Labs的上游Opentelemetry EBPF仪器的分布将继续存在。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ Why-beyla and-ebpf”&gt; why beyla和ebpf？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; grcevski，贝拉维护者，着手解决可观察性工具中持续差距：仪器遗产，第三方或仅被忽视的服务，其中代码修改和传统代理不实用。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; EBPF被证明是关键组件。由于它允许小型，安全的程序可以在Linux内核内部运行，而不会冒崩溃或不稳定的风险，因此Beyla可以使用它直接在内核级别观察应用程序和网络活动。这使Beyla能够从任何应用程序中收集强大的可观察性数据，从而克服了传统仪器工具的局限性。它支持Beyla创建一个新的自动启示类别，该类别不在乎框架或二进制文件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“借助这项技术，我们可以利用该应用程序堆栈的任何方面，我们可以提取信号，然后将其变成遥测，” Grcevski说。 “我们将它们发送到opentelemetry格式，或者我们可以将它们直接导出到&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/festall/wets-started/started grafana-prometheus/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt; prometheus &lt;/a&gt;这就是魔术。&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“简单开发符号 - 符合仪式”&gt;简单部署，一致的监视&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于Veeramachaneni的Homelab，Beyla具有变革性。由于它在他的kubernetes节点上作为守护程序运行，他也能够收集一致的，符合opentelemetry的速率，错误和持续时间（红色）指标和分布式痕迹，即使是从未经备案的，未录制的，现成的应用程序中也是如此。 Beyla从HTTP和REDIS协议中提取遥测的能力尤其有价值，因为许多现代应用都使用它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种方法还允许Beyla以运行时不稳定的方式捕获此遥测，收集重要的元数据，例如Kubernetes标签和区域信息，以进行自动相关性和故障排除。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“您会得到完整的分布式跟踪，” Veeramachaneni说。 “所有这些都来自贝拉，我认为这真的很酷。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/2894x1452/f135faac5b/homelab-distributed-tracing.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/2894x1452/f135faac5b/homelab-distributed-tracing.png” alt =“ A alt =”软件跟踪界面，显示了与各种有色的bars，指示各种彩色的bars，指示各种差异化的处理器和录制效果。会话的。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/2894x1452/f135faac5b/homelab-distributed-tracing.png”&#xA;alt =“软件跟踪接口显示具有各种彩色条的时间表，指示不同的过程和Their持续时间。“ title =”会话一部分的分布式跟踪演示的屏幕截图。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ W-100P字幕Text-Gray-13”&gt;是会话一部分的分布式跟踪演示的屏幕截图。&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&gt;&#xA;他说，&lt;p&gt;部署贝拉大多是简单而毫无痛苦的。它需要运行一个简单的头盔安装，该安装可在多种语言中提供所有必要的功能。 （例如，特定硬件可能有例外； Raspberry Pi设备需要在部署前重新编译Linux内核。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管Beyla可以实现快速，广泛的遥测，但仍涉及细微差别和权衡。虽然Beyla可以看到并关联协议级别的流量几乎没有代码更改，但它不会提供与本机源级仪器相同的上下文遥测。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，本机仪器支持以额外的业务环境扩展痕迹，并提供有关模板SQL查询的完整详细信息。但是，出于安全原因，Beyla有意避免暴露完整的SQL查询和其他潜在敏感数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; beyla还需要一些协议和特定于语言的调整；它会自动处理某些语言的角案例（考虑到Go的Goroutines或Node.js中的异步事件循环），但其他平台可能需要较小的调整。由于这些原因，最好将Beyla视为完整乐器旅程中的“快速开始”，Veeramachaneni说。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我花了几个小时来手动进行非常简单的GO应用程序，”他说。 “如果您突然有20次应用程序，您会告诉工程师，‘现在您必须手动启动一切，’他们只会一起度假。因此，贝拉（Beyla）给您的是，在一个命令中，您可以得到80％的方式。然后，您可以使用工程带宽来说，实际上，这两个应用程序是最重要的。让他们的手动仪器是正确的。&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“每个人的可观察性”&gt;每个人的可观察性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;相同的可观察性基本原理在各处适用，从Homelab中的少数自托管服务到数千个精心策划的容器。但是，安装，配置和维护跨许多语言（甚至没有源代码的二进制文件）总是令人生畏的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过将EBPF的内核供电范围与Opentelemetry的标准融合，Beyla消除了障碍，从而使每个人都可以使用一致，强大的见解。对于Veeramachaneni和Grcevski来说，这就是可观察性的未来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们为社区建造了它，”格塞夫斯基说。 “我们为每个人都构建了它。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是t他最简单的方法是从指标，日志，痕迹，仪表板等开始。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visualize Salesforce data in Grafana: flexible query options, powerful data correlations, and more】可视化Grafana中的Salesforce数据：灵活的查询选项，强大的数据相关性等等</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/21/visualize-salesforce-data-in-grafana-flexible-query-options-powerful-data-correlations-and-more/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As part of our big tent philosophy at Grafana Labs, we think you should be able to dig into your data and find meaningful insights — wherever that data happens to live.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For many of our users, that data lives in Salesforce, the cloud-based customer relationship management (CRM) platform. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll take a closer look at how you can use the &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/grafana-salesforce-datasource/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Salesforce Enterprise data source&lt;/a&gt; for Grafana to quickly and easily visualize your Salesforce data using Grafana dashboards. You can also learn more about the data source, and see a demo, in the YouTube video below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqHO0oYW6Ic?si=9GdSAKuyti4&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-a-quick-overview-of-enterprise-data-sources&#34;&gt;First, a quick overview of Enterprise data sources&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Enterprise data sources allow you to connect to external systems and popular proprietary platforms from within Grafana, so you can visualize data from a wide range of sources using the Grafana dashboards you already know and love. While many Grafana data sources are built by our partners or community members, Enterprise data sources are built and maintained by Grafana Labs, and they are only available in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/enterprise/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; and across all &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud tiers&lt;/a&gt;, including our generous &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Cloud free tier&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Salesforce is one of more than 30 Enterprise data sources currently in our catalog, alongside &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/servicenow/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ServiceNow&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/splunk/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Splunk&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/snowflake/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Snowflake&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/datadog/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Datadog&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/dynatrace/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Dynatrace&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/appdynamics/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AppDynamics&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Grafana Enterprise data sources, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/13/grafana-enterprise-data-source-plugins-a-brief-guide-to-what-they-are-and-how-to-get-started/&#34;&gt;recent guide&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-visualize-salesforce-data-in-grafana&#34;&gt;Why visualize Salesforce data in Grafana?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Salesforce Enterprise data source for Grafana allows you to directly query and visualize your Salesforce data within Grafana. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It also enables you to visualize your Salesforce data alongside other data sources, so you can correlate sales and customer data with system metrics, logs, and more — all in a single dashboard. This can help you draw connections between business outcomes and operational metrics like system uptime or application performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode1952s1hbhb-flexibility-in-how-you-query-salesforce-data&#34;&gt;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/940x487/f0050d859e/salesforce-sample-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/940x487/f0050d859e/salesforce-sample-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of an example dashboard for the Salesforce Enterprise data source for Grafana.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/940x487/f0050d859e/salesforce-sample-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of an example dashboard for the Salesforce Enterprise data source for Grafana.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; Flexibility in how you query Salesforce data &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most powerful features of the Salesforce Enterprise data source is that it offers three unique ways to access and query your Salesforce data, based on your use case and familiarity with &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.salesforce.com/docs/atlas.en-us.soql_sosl.meta/soql_sosl/sforce_api_calls_soql_sosl_intro.htm&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Salesforce Object Query Language (SOQL)&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These three methods include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;soql-editor&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SOQL editor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This mode allows you to write native SOQL queries directly in Grafana. The editor supports autocomplete suggestions for entities and fields, making it easier to construct queries even if you’re not fully familiar with the schema. Use &lt;strong&gt;Ctrl+Space&lt;/strong&gt; for suggestions after &lt;code&gt;SELECT&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;WHERE&lt;/code&gt;. This mode is ideal for users comfortable with SOQL and who want more granular control over their queries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;query-builder&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Query builder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This mode offers a user-friendly, point-and-click interface for building SOQL queries without needing to know SOQL syntax.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You select the Salesforce entity (or table), choose fields, add filters, set ordering, and specify limits. The builder can display results as a table, aggregate, or time series. It also provides a SOQL preview, and you can switch to the SOQL editor to further customize the generated query.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;reports-mode&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reports mode&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This method provides a quick and easy way to access Salesforce reports. Simply click the drop-down menu for a list of available reports to view.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information on these three query methods, please visit our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-salesforce-datasource/latest/salesforce-query-editor/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#salesforce-query-editor&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-key-features&#34;&gt;Other key features&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other features of the Salesforce Enterprise data source include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annotations&lt;/strong&gt;: Add contextual &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/build-dashboards/annotate-visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;annotations&lt;/a&gt; to charts for richer analysis.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Templates, variables, and transformations&lt;/strong&gt;: Use Grafana &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/fundamentals/templates/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;templates&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/variables/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;variables&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/query-transform-data/transform-data/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;transformations&lt;/a&gt; to create dynamic, reusable dashboards.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alerting&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/set-up/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Set up alerts&lt;/a&gt; based on Salesforce data directly within Grafana.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authentication&lt;/strong&gt;: Supports both &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-salesforce-datasource/latest/configure-salesforce-data-source/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#connected-app-settings&#34;&gt;credentials-based and JWT-based authentication&lt;/a&gt;, with detailed configuration options for each.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;salesforce-enterprise-data-source-faqs&#34;&gt;Salesforce Enterprise data source FAQs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Salesforce?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Salesforce is a leading, cloud-based customer relationship management platform designed to help you build and improve your customer relationships. To learn more, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.salesforce.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Salesforce website&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is an Enterprise data source for Grafana?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Enterprise data sources allow you to connect to external systems and popular proprietary platforms from within Grafana, so you can visualize data from a wide range of sources using your Grafana dashboards. While many Grafana data sources are built by our partners or community members, Enterprise data sources are built and maintained by Grafana Labs, and they are only available in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/enterprise/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Enterprise&lt;/a&gt; and across all &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud tiers&lt;/a&gt;, including our generous &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Cloud free tier&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Salesforce is one of more than 30 Enterprise data sources currently in our catalog, alongside &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/servicenow/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ServiceNow&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/splunk/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Splunk&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/datadog/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Datadog&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/dynatrace/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Dynatrace&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/appdynamics/visualize/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AppDynamics&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Grafana Enterprise data sources, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/13/grafana-enterprise-data-source-plugins-a-brief-guide-to-what-they-are-and-how-to-get-started/&#34;&gt;recent guide&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the key features of the Salesforce Enterprise data source for Grafana?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As covered above, key features of the Salesforce Enterprise data source for Grafana include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The ability to query, visualize, and correlate Salesforce data alongside other data sources in Grafana&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Flexible querying options, including SOQL editor, query builder, and reports mode  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support for &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/variables/&#34;&gt;Grafana variables&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/fundamentals/templates/&#34;&gt;templates&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/query-transform-data/transform-data/&#34;&gt;transformations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support for &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/build-dashboards/annotate-visualizations/&#34;&gt;annotations&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/&#34;&gt;alerting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced security capabilities, such as support for multiple authentication options&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where can I go to learn more?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the Salesforce Enterprise data source, please check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-salesforce-datasource/latest/&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;. We also have several resources you can use to learn more about Grafana Enterprise data sources, in general, including our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/all-plugins/?enterprise=1&#34;&gt;plugin catalog&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/go/webinar/grafana-plugins-overview-and-demo/&#34;&gt;this webinar&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The easiest way to get started with our Enterprise data source plugins is in&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;We have a generous forever-free tier that includes access to Enterprise data sources for 3 active users. If you haven’t already,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user?pg=plugins&amp;amp;plcmt=grafana-synthetic-monitoring-app&#34;&gt;sign up for free today!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为我们在Grafana Labs的大帐篷理念的一部分，我们认为您应该能够挖掘数据并找到有意义的见解 - 无论数据恰好居住在哪里。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于我们的许多用户，数据属于Salesforce，这是基于云的客户关系管理（CRM）平台。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll take a closer look at how you can use the &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/grafana-salesforce-datasource/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Salesforce Enterprise data source&lt;/a&gt; for Grafana to quickly and easily visualize your Salesforce data using Grafana dashboards.您还可以在下面的YouTube视频中了解有关数据源的更多信息，并查看演示。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“ 560”高=“ 315” src =“ https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqho0oyw6ic?si=9gdsakuyti4” title =“ youtube blaceborder” fiveseborder =“ frameborder =” accelermeter; acceleremer; acceleremer; autoplay; autoplay; clipboard-board-wirite; clipboard-wirite;图片中的图片; web-share“ referrerpolicy =“ cross-origin”允许floserfullscreen&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ first-a-quick-overview-enterprise-data-sources”&gt;首先，快速概述企业数据源&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana Enterprise数据源允许您连接到Grafana内部的外部系统和流行的专有平台，因此您可以使用您已经知道和喜欢的Grafana仪表板可视化广泛源的数据。虽然我们的合作伙伴或社区成员构建了许多Grafana数据来源，但企业数据源是由Grafana Labs构建和维护的，并且仅在&lt;a href =“/products/enterprise/？pg = blog＆plcmt = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana enterprise&#39;&gt; grafana enterprise &lt;/a&gt;以及所有&lt;a href =“层&lt;/a&gt;，包括我们的慷慨&lt;a href =“/auth/auth/nip-up/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;云免费层&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; salesforce与我们目录中的30多个企业数据源之一是&lt;a href =“/solutions/solutions/serviceNow/serviceNow/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; serviceNow &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a a href =“ href =“/solutions/snowflake/？pgg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; snowflake &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“/solutions/datadog/dataDog/vutaminize/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt; datadog &lt;/a&gt; href =“/solutions/dynatrace/dutuarize/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; dynatrace &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“/solutions/solutions/appdynamics/vutamyize/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt = appdynamics &lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Grafana Enterprise data sources, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/13/grafana-enterprise-data-source-plugins-a-brief-guide-to-what-they-are-and-how-to-get-started/&#34;&gt;recent guide&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ Why-visalize-salesforce-data-in-grafana”&gt;为什么在Grafana中可视化Salesforce数据？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana的Salesforce Enterprise数据源使您可以直接查询和可视化Grafana中的Salesforce数据。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它还使您能够与其他数据源一起可视化Salesforce数据，因此您可以将销售联系起来以及带有系统指标，日志等的客户数据 - 全部在一个仪表板中。这可以帮助您在业务成果和操作指标（例如系统启动时间或应用程序性能）之间建立联系。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“ haha​​hugoshortcode1952s1hbhb-flexibility in-her-you-Query-Salesforce-data”&gt; &lt;figie&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/940x487/f0050d859e/salesforce-sample-dasamploble.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/940x487/f0050d859e/salesforce-samples-sample-dasmample-dasmboard.png” alt =“示例示例仪表仪的Salesforce Enterprise Enterprise Data for Grafana source saleseforce Encorment of Grafaana的屏幕截图。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/940x487/f0050d859e/salesforce-sample-dasamplobe.png”&#xA;alt =“ Grafana的Salesforce Enterprise数据源的示例仪表板的屏幕截图。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figus&gt;在查询salesforce数据&lt;/h3&gt;的灵活性&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Salesforce Enterprise Data Source的最强大功能之一是，它提供了三种独特的方法来访问和查询您的Salesforce数据，并根据您的用例并熟悉&lt;a href =“ https://developer.salesforce.com/docs/atlas.en-us.soql_sosl.sosl.meta/soql_sosl/sforce_api_api_calls_soqls_soql_sosl_sosl_sosl_intr_intro.htm （SOQL）&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这三种方法包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“ soql-editor”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; soql编辑器&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此模式使您可以直接在Grafana中编写本机SOQL查询。编辑器支持对实体和字段的自动完整建议，即使您不完全熟悉该架构，也可以更容易构建查询。在&lt;code&gt;之后，使用&lt;strong&gt; ctrl+Space &lt;/strace&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;选择&lt;/code&gt;或&lt;code&gt; whene &lt;/code&gt;。此模式非常适合对SOQL满意的用户，并且想要对其查询进行更多颗粒状的控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ Query-Builder”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;查询构建器&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此模式提供了一个用户友好的点击接口，用于构建SOQL查询，而无需知道SOQL语法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您选择Salesforce Entity（或表），选择字段，添加过滤器，设置订购并指定限制。构建器可以将结果显示为表，聚合或时间序列。它还提供了SOQL预览，您可以切换到SOQL编辑器以进一步自定义生成的查询。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ Reports-Mode”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;报告模式&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此方法提供了一种快速简便的方法来访问Salesforce报告。只需单击下拉菜单以获取可用报告的列表。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关这三种查询方法的更多信息，请访问我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/plugins/grafana-salesforce-datasource/lestest/salesforce-query-editor/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt/＃saLesforce-Query-editor“&gt;技术文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“其他钥匙 - 功能”&gt;其他关键功能&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Salesforce Enterprise Data Source的其他功能包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注释&lt;/strong&gt;：添加上下文&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana/最新/dashboards/build-dashboards/andotate-visualizations/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-plcmt = body-txt = body-txt&#39;&gt; entotations &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;模板，变量和转换&lt;/strong&gt;：使用grafana &lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/grafana/最终/nervering/fullagentals/templates/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt; templates&#39;&gt; templates &lt;/a&gt; href =“/docs/grafana/最新/dashboards/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt&#39;&gt;变量&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/docs/docs/docs/grafana/最终/panels-visualizations-visualizations/query-query-query-trans-trans-trans-trans-trans-trans-trans-data/？可重复使用的仪表板。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;提醒&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最新/witering/setip/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;设置警报&lt;/a&gt;直接基于salesforce数据，直接基于grafana。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authentication&lt;/strong&gt;: Supports both &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-salesforce-datasource/latest/configure-salesforce-data-source/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt/#connected-app-settings&#34;&gt;credentials-based and JWT-based authentication&lt;/a&gt;, with detailed configuration options for each.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ salesforce-enterprise-data-source-faqs”&gt; salesforce企业数据源常见问题&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是Salesforce？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Salesforce是一个主要的，基于云的客户关系管理平台，旨在帮助您建立和改善客户关系。要了解更多信息，请查看&lt;a href =“ https://www.salesforce.com/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; salesforce网站&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是Grafana的企业数据源？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana Enterprise数据源允许您连接到Grafana内部的外部系统和流行的专有平台，因此您可以使用Grafana仪表板从广泛的来源可视化数据。虽然我们的合作伙伴或社区成员构建了许多Grafana数据来源，但企业数据源是由Grafana Labs构建和维护的，并且仅在&lt;a href =“/products/enterprise/？pg = blog＆plcmt = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana enterprise&#39;&gt; grafana enterprise &lt;/a&gt;以及所有&lt;a href =“层&lt;/a&gt;，包括我们的慷慨&lt;a href =“/auth/auth/nip-up/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;云免费层&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; salesforce与我们目录中的30多个企业数据源之一是&lt;a href =“/solutions/solutions/serviceNow/serviceNow/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; serviceNow &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a a href =“ href =“/solutions/datadog/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; datadog &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“/solutions/dynatrace/dynatrace/？p; plcmt = body-txt“&gt; appdynamics &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Grafana Enterprise data sources, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/13/grafana-enterprise-data-source-plugins-a-brief-guide-to-what-they-are-and-how-to-get-started/&#34;&gt;recent guide&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana的Salesforce Enterprise数据源的关键功能是什么？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如上所述，Grafana的Salesforce Enterprise数据源的主要功能包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;能够查询，可视化和将Salesforce数据与Grafana中的其他数据源一起关联的能力&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;灵活的查询选项，包括SOQL编辑器，查询构建器和报告模式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最终/dashboards/variables/“&gt; grafana变量&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =”/docs/docs/grafana/最新/altest/natering/stalling/natering/fullations/fullagates/spemplates/spemplates/“ href =“/docs/grafana/最新/panels-visualizations/query-transform-data/transform-data/”&gt; transformations &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最终/dashboards/build-dashboards/andotate-visualizations/“&gt; nototations &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =”/docs/docs/grafana/最终/altest/witering/&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;增强的安全功能，例如支持多个身份验证选项&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我可以去哪里了解更多？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关Salesforce Enterprise数据源的更多信息，请查看我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/plugins/grafana-salesforce-datasource/最终/”&gt;技术文档&lt;/a&gt;。通常，您还可以使用几种资源来了解有关Grafana Enterprise数据源的更多信息，包括我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/plugins/”&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“/grafana/plugins/all-plafins/all-plugins/？enterprise = 1” href =“/go/webinar/grafana-plugins-overview and-demo/”&gt;此网络研讨会&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;开始使用企业数据源插件的最简单方法是&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud。&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;我们拥有一个宽敞的forever-forever tier，其中包含Enterprise for Enterprise数据供您使用3个活跃的sirce of 3活跃的serifce。如果您尚未，&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/inper-up/create-user？pg = plugins＆plcmt = grafana-synththetic-monoritoring-app”&gt;今天免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Secure credential storage for your observability stack: Introducing secrets management in Grafana Cloud】可观察性堆栈的安全凭证存储：在Grafana Cloud中引入秘密管理</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/20/secure-credential-storage-for-your-observability-stack-introducing-secrets-management-in-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The more your infrastructure grows, the more likely you are to face a familiar challenge: where to safely store the API keys, passwords, and tokens that power your observability stack. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, a common response to this dilemma is to scatter credentials across configurations, making security and management of secrets increasingly complex. The problem is only compounded by modern observability setups that involve distributed services, API integrations, and collaborative teams—all requiring secure access to sensitive information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re launching secrets management in Grafana Cloud. Currently in public preview, it&amp;rsquo;s designed to be the foundation for securing all your credentials in Grafana. And we aren&amp;rsquo;t just adding another feature with secrets management; we&amp;rsquo;re solving the credential management problem that every growing team faces by delivering these key benefits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Centralized credential storage with enterprise-grade encryption&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reference-based secrets access &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Granular access controls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Complete audit trail of secret usage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog, we&amp;rsquo;ll show you how we&amp;rsquo;re starting this rollout with Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring and how you can implement it today. We&amp;rsquo;ll also give you a look behind the scenes to show how we&amp;rsquo;re developing this new functionality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;secrets-management-in-action-public-preview-for-synthetic-monitoring&#34;&gt;Secrets management in action: public preview for Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first product in Grafana Cloud to integrate with our new secrets manager is &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/synthetic-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/a&gt;. This has been a highly requested feature that delivers clear and immediate value for users, so let&amp;rsquo;s look at how this changes what you can do in Synthetic Monitoring.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-old-way-embedded-credentials&#34;&gt;The old way: embedded credentials   &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re running Synthetic Monitoring checks, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely faced this scenario:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;const bearerToken = &amp;#39;abc123-hardcoded-token-visible-to-everyone&amp;#39;;&#xA;const response = http.get(&amp;#39;https://api.example.com/data&amp;#39;, {&#xA;headers: { &amp;#39;Authorization&amp;#39;: `Bearer ${bearerToken}` }&#xA;});&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are several problems with this approach:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Credentials are visible in the checks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Team collaboration requires sharing sensitive values.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;There’s no audit trail of credential usage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-new-way-secret-references&#34;&gt;The new way: secret references&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;const bearerToken = await secrets.get(&amp;#39;my-token&amp;#39;);&#xA;const response = http.get(&amp;#39;https://api.example.com/data&amp;#39;, {&#xA;headers: { &amp;#39;Authorization&amp;#39;: `Bearer ${bearerToken}` }&#xA;});&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;With secrets management in Grafana Cloud, a user can store values in their stack, then anyone can configure a check that references those values by name (e.g., in an API request header). This was inspired by how &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.github.com/en/actions/how-tos/write-workflows/choose-what-workflows-do/use-secrets&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; handles secrets in CI actions. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are several benefits to this approach:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sensitive values are stored securely and separately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multiple checks can reference the same secret.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You get easy credential rotation without touching individual checks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s a full audit trail of which service accessed what and when.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;try-it-today&#34;&gt;Try it today&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we mentioned, secrets management is available now in public preview for all Grafana Cloud customers. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to get started:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Access the feature&lt;/strong&gt;: Log into your Grafana Cloud instance and navigate to &lt;strong&gt;Testing &amp;amp; synthetics&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Synthetics&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Config&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create your first secret&lt;/strong&gt;: Start with an API key or credential you&amp;rsquo;re currently using in Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add the new secrets module to your check&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;code&gt;import secrets from ‘k6/secrets’;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update your checks&lt;/strong&gt;: Replace hardcoded values with secret references using &lt;code&gt;secrets.get(&#39;my-secret&#39;)&lt;/code&gt; syntax&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can see how the process works in the UI below. For more details, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/manage-secrets/&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png&#34;alt=&#34;User creates a secret&#34;title=&#34;User creates a secret&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;User creates a secret&#34;title=&#34;User creates a secret&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;User creates a secret&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1641/e5c813de5c/health-check-editing.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1641/e5c813de5c/health-check-editing.png&#34;alt=&#34;User references the secret from a scripted check&#34;title=&#34;User references the secret from a scripted check&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1641/e5c813de5c/health-check-editing.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;User references the secret from a scripted check&#34;title=&#34;User references the secret from a scripted check&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;User references the secret from a scripted check&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-we-built-this-securely-the-technical-foundation&#34;&gt;How we built this securely: the technical foundation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Building a secrets manager for Grafana Cloud required rethinking security from the ground up. Here&amp;rsquo;s how we designed it to protect your most sensitive data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;encryption-process&#34;&gt;Encryption process&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We encrypt secrets with &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-database-encryption/#envelope-encryption&#34;&gt;envelope encryption&lt;/a&gt; so that they are protected at rest. Envelope encryption uses randomly generated data keys to encrypt secrets using an AES-GCM cipher, then encrypts those data keys with a root key before storing them. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This obfuscates the data and spreads the decryption keys around, making successful attacks harder. Grafana Cloud supports envelope encryption using Key Management Services (KMS) in AWS, Google Cloud, and Microsoft Azure, as well as with Hashicorp Vault or a self-managed key. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1503x828/e131c9d88b/secrets-management-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1503x828/e131c9d88b/secrets-management-diagram.png&#34;alt=&#34;Simple visualization of envelope encryption&#34;title=&#34;Simple visualization of envelope encryption&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1503x828/e131c9d88b/secrets-management-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Simple visualization of envelope encryption&#34;title=&#34;Simple visualization of envelope encryption&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;Simple visualization of envelope encryption&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-security-principles&#34;&gt;Our security principles&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Encryption is just the beginning. We built secrets management in Grafana Cloud around core security principles that protect your data while making the system easier to use and manage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;unified-api-and-storage&#34;&gt;Unified API and storage&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In collaboration with our Application Security team, we designed a central secrets repository that maintains the highest security standards across all services. Services can use secrets without implementing their own envelope encryption or handling secret rotation and re-encryption. Secrets management in Grafana Cloud handles all of this automatically.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;metadata-separation&#34;&gt;Metadata separation&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Secret values are stored completely separately from metadata such as names and descriptions. This enables team collaboration and secret reuse without ever exposing sensitive data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;secrets-can-only-be-decrypted-by-internal-services&#34;&gt;Secrets can only be decrypted by internal services&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users cannot access the sensitive payload. All services making decryption requests are rigorously vetted and validated for authenticity, permissions, and explicit access grants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;adherence-to-encryption-best-practices&#34;&gt;Adherence to encryption best practices&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We continue to protect secrets with envelope encryption, including using popular third-party encryption services such as HashiCorp Vault and AWS Secrets Manager. Encryption keys are regularly rotated and all interactions are audited.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;observable&#34;&gt;Observable&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Grafana Lab, it is a core part of our technical strategy to dogfood our own observability products. As such, secrets management in Grafana Cloud was instrumented for &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2018/08/02/the-red-method-how-to-instrument-your-services/&#34;&gt;RED Method&lt;/a&gt; analysis using logs, traces, and metrics to detect any potential issues. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; For more information on how we maintains high standards of data privacy and security, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/legal/security-compliance/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;security compliance page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;going-beyond-synthetic-monitoring&#34;&gt;Going beyond Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Synthetic Monitoring is just the beginning for secrets management in Grafana Cloud. We&amp;rsquo;re already working on exciting expansions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Third-party secret stores&lt;/strong&gt;: Connect your existing HashiCorp Vault, AWS Secrets Manager, Google Cloud Secret Manager, or Azure Key Vault to Grafana Cloud.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data source credentials&lt;/strong&gt;: Integrate data sources with secrets management in Grafana Cloud and reference secrets stored in your third‑party secret store.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud k6 integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Reference secrets directly in your k6 scripts without embedding credentials in code.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-trust-through-security&#34;&gt;Building trust through security&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Grafana Labs, we understand that secrets are at the core of trust between us and our users. With secrets management in Grafana Cloud, we&amp;rsquo;re not just solving today&amp;rsquo;s credential management challenges—we&amp;rsquo;re building the foundation for secure, scalable secrets management that will grow with your observability needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This represents a significant investment in security infrastructure that will enable new capabilities across the entire Grafana ecosystem. From Synthetic Monitoring to data sources to future integrations we haven&amp;rsquo;t even imagined yet, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a secure, auditable way to manage the credentials that power your observability stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;您的基础架构越多，您就越有可能面临一个熟悉的挑战：在哪里可以安全地存储API键，密码和为可观察力堆栈供电的代币。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不幸的是，对这一难题的共同反应是散布凭证跨配置，使秘密的安全和管理越来越复杂。这个问题仅由涉及分布式服务，API集成和协作团队的现代可观察性设置加剧了，所有这些都需要安全访问敏感信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是为什么我们在Grafana Cloud启动秘密管理。目前在公共预览中，它旨在确保您在Grafana获得所有证书的基础。而且，我们不仅添加了秘密管理的另一个功能；我们正在解决每个成长中的团队通过提供这些关键好处而面对的凭证管理问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;带有企业级加密的集中凭证存储&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;基于参考的秘密访问&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;粒状访问控制&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;秘密用法的完整审计踪迹&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此博客中，我们将向您展示如何使用Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monituning以及如何实施它开始此次推出。我们还将为您提供幕后展示我们如何开发这种新功能的幕后。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“秘密管理 - 行动式播放 - 观察 - 合成 - 仪式”&gt;秘密管理：合成监控的公共预览&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana Cloud中与我们的新秘密经理集成的第一个产品是&lt;a href =“/products/cloud/cloud/synthetic-monitoring/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;综合监视&lt;/a&gt;。这是一项高度要求的功能，可为用户带来清晰而直接的价值，因此，让我们看看这如何改变合成监视的方法。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“老式 - 隔离 - 肯定”&gt;旧方法：嵌入式凭据&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您正在运行合成监视检查，则可能面临此情况：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class =“ code-snippet code-snippet__mini”&gt; &lt;div class =“ lang-toolbar__mini”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class =“ code-clipboard”&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data =“ app_code_snippet（）” x-init =“ init（）” @click =“ copy（）”&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class =“ code-clipboard__icon” src =“/媒体/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg” alt =“复制代码到剪贴板” width =“ 14”高度=“ 13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class =“代码 - 尼珀代码snippet__border”&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded =“ false”&gt; &lt;code class =“ language-none”&gt; const bearertoken =&#39;abc123- hardcoded-token-token-token-token-to-to-everyone&#39;;&#xA;const响应= http.get（&#39;https://api.example.com/data&#39;，{&#xA;标题：{&#39;授权&#39;：`BEARER $ {BERERTOKOK}`}&#xA;}）; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;这种方法有几个问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在支票中可见凭据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;团队协作需要共享敏感的价值。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;有没有凭证使用的审计踪迹。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“ new-way-secret-refertences”&gt;新方法：秘密参考&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class =“ code-snippet code-snippet__mini”&gt; &lt;div class =“ lang-toolbar__mini”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class =“ code-clipboard”&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data =“ app_code_snippet（）” x-init =“ init（）” @click =“ copy（）”&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class =“ code-clipboard__icon” src =“/媒体/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg” alt =“复制代码到剪贴板” width =“ 14”高度=“ 13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class =“代码 - 尼珀代码snippet__border”&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded =“ false”&gt; &lt;code class =“ language-none”&gt; const bearertoken =等待secrets.get（&#39;my-token&#39;）;&#xA;const响应= http.get（&#39;https://api.example.com/data&#39;，{&#xA;标题：{&#39;授权&#39;：`BEARER $ {BERERTOKOK}`}&#xA;}）; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;使用Grafana Cloud中的Secrets Management，用户可以将值存储在其堆栈中，然后任何人都可以配置通过名称引用这些值的支票（例如，在API请求标题中）。这是受到&lt;a href =“ https://docs.github.com/en/actions/how-tos/write-workflows/choose-what-workflows-do/use-secrets” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” noopener noreferrer &lt;/a&gt; ggithub &lt;/a&gt; gertlessection的启发。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种方法有几个好处：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;敏感值可牢固地存储。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多个检查可以引用相同的秘密。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;您可以轻松的凭证旋转而无需触摸个人检查。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;有一个完整的审核步道，其中的服务访问了什么和何时。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“ try-it-today”&gt;今天尝试&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正如我们提到的，秘密管理现已在所有Grafana Cloud客户的公共预览中可用。这是开始的方法：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;访问功能&lt;/strong&gt;：登录Grafana Cloud实例，并导航至&lt;strong&gt;测试和合成&lt;/strong&gt;&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Synthetics &lt;/strong&gt;&gt;&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; config&gt; config&gt; config&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;创建第一个秘密&lt;/strong&gt;：从当前在合成监视中使用的API键或凭据开始&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;将新秘密模块添加到您的检查中&lt;/strong&gt;：&lt;code&gt;从“ K6/Secrets”导入秘密; &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;更新您的支票&lt;/strong&gt;：使用&lt;code&gt; secrets.get（&#39;my-secret&#39;）&lt;/code&gt;语法&lt;/li&gt;，将硬编码值替换为秘密引用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在下面的UI中看到该过程的工作方式。有关更多详细信息，请查看我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monoritoring/create-monoritoring/create-checks/manage-secrets/“&gt; documentation &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png“ alt =”用户创建秘密“ title =”用户创建秘密”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png”&#xA;alt =“用户创建一个秘密” title =“用户创建秘密”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ W-100P字幕Text-Gray-13”&gt;用户创建秘密&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/fig&gt; &lt;figi&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1641/e5c813de5c/health-check-editing.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x1641/e5c813de5c/health-check-editing.png”&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1641/e5c813de5c/health-check-editing.png”&#xA;alt =“用户引用脚本检查中的秘密” title =“用户引用脚本检查中的秘密”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ W-100P字幕text-gray-13”&gt;用户引用了脚本检查中的秘密&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/fige&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“如何建造 - 这是安全的技术基础”&gt;我们如何安全地构建：技术基金会&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;建立Grafana Cloud的秘密经理需要从头开始重新思考安全性。这是我们设计它以保护您最敏感的数据的方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“加密过程”&gt;加密过程&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们使用&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最终/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-database-contryption/＃envelope-contryption”&gt; envelope-convelope &lt;/a&gt;加密秘密。信封加密使用随机生成的数据键使用AES-GCM密码对秘密进行加密，然后在存储它们之前使用root键加密这些数据键。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这使数据混淆并散布了解密键，使成功的攻击更加困难。 Grafana Cloud在AWS，Google Cloud和Microsoft Azure以及Hashicorp Vault或自我管理的密钥中使用密钥管理服务（KMS）支持信封加密。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1503x828/e131c9d88b/secrets-management-management-diagram.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1503x828/e131c9d88b/secrets-management-diagram.pngr.png”&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1503x828/e131c9d88b/secrets-management-diagram.png“&#xA;alt =“信封加密的简单可视化”标题=“信封加密的简单可视化”/&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“我们的安全性 - 原则”&gt;我们的安全原则&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;加密仅仅是开始。我们在Grafana Cloud围绕核心安全原则建立了秘密管理，这些原理可以保护您的数据，同时使系统更易于使用和管理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ Unified-api和存储”&gt;统一的API和存储&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与我们的应用程序安全团队合作，我们设计了一个中央机密存储库，该存储库维护所有服务中最高的安全标准。服务可以使用秘密，而无需实施自己的信封加密或处理秘密旋转和重新加密。 Grafana Cloud中的秘密管理会自动处理所有这些。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“元数据分离”&gt;元数据分离&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;秘密值与元数据（例如名称和描述）完全分开存储。这使团队协作和秘密重复使用而无需揭示敏感数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“仅秘密限制为单位服务”&gt;秘密只能被内部服务解密&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;用户无法访问敏感有效载荷。所有提出解密请求的服务均经过严格审查和验证，以获得真实性，权限和明确的访问赠款。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“遵守对加密 - 最佳实践”&gt;遵守加密最佳实践&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们继续使用信封加密保护秘密，包括使用流行的第三方加密服务，例如Hashicorp Vault和AWS Secrets Manager。定期旋转加密键，并审核所有相互作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“可观察到”&gt;可观察的&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Grafana Lab，它是我们自己的可观察性产品的技术策略的核心部分。因此，Grafana Cloud中的秘密管理是用&lt;a href =“/blog/2018/08/02/the-red-method-how-how-to-to-to-intrument-your-services/“&gt;红色方法&lt;/a&gt;使用日志，痕迹和指标分析来检测任何潜在问题的分析）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;有关我们如何保持高标准数据隐私和安全标准的更多信息，请查看我们的&lt;a href =“/large/security/security-compliance/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;安全合规性页面&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ bey-beyond synthetic-monitoring”&gt;超越合成监控&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;合成监测只是Grafana Cloud中秘密管理的开始。我们已经在进行令人兴奋的扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;第三方秘密商店&lt;/strong&gt;：连接您现有的hashicorp保管库，AWS Secrets Manager，Google Cloud Secret Manager或Azure密钥库与Grafana Cloud。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;数据源凭据&lt;/strong&gt;：将数据源与grafana云中的秘密管理和参考秘密中的秘密整合在一起在您的第三方秘密商店中陷入困境。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana Cloud K6 Integration &lt;/strong&gt;：直接在您的K6脚本中引用秘密，而无需嵌入代码中的凭据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“建筑物信任 - 直觉安全”&gt;通过安全性建筑物信任&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Grafana Labs，我们了解秘密是我们与用户之间信任的核心。借助Grafana Cloud的秘密管理，我们不仅在解决当今的凭证管理挑战 - 我们为安全，可扩展的秘密管理建立了基础，这些管理将随着您的可观察性需求而增长。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这代表了对安全基础架构的重大投资，这将使整个Grafana生态系统的新功能成为现实。从合成监视到数据源到我们甚至还没有想象过的未来集成，您将有一种安全，可审核的方式来管理能够为您的可观察性堆栈供电的凭证。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana Cloud updates: onboard teams with new AI-powered tooling, secrets management for enhanced security, and more】Grafana Cloud更新：具有新的AI驱动工具的机载团队，用于增强安全性的秘密管理以及更多</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/08/20/grafana-cloud-updates-onboard-teams-with-new-ai-powered-tooling-secrets-management-for-enhanced-security-and-more/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We consistently roll out helpful updates and fun features in Grafana Cloud, our fully managed observability platform powered by the open source Grafana LGTM Stack (&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; for logs, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; for visualization, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt; for traces, and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt; for metrics).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In case you missed them, here’s our monthly round-up of the latest and greatest Grafana Cloud updates. You can also read about all the features we add to Grafana Cloud in our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/whats-new/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;What’s New in Grafana Cloud documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And if you’re not a Grafana Cloud user yet, &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;sign up&lt;/a&gt; for an account today! You can try any of these features (and more) for free with our generous Cloud Free plan.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-easier-way-to-get-started-with-grafana-cloud-grafana-assistant-is-now-in-public-preview&#34;&gt;An easier way to get started with Grafana Cloud: Grafana Assistant is now in public preview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here at Grafana Labs, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/&#34;&gt;we believe&lt;/a&gt; that AI is more than just a trend in observability. It’ll be integral to how organizations keep their systems fully operational going forward.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This belief continues to influence the tools that we build. This month, for example, we’re excited to share that Grafana Assistant — an AI-powered agent in Grafana Cloud that helps you query, build, and troubleshoot faster using natural language — is &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-for-grafana-onboarding-get-your-teams-started-quicker-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;now in public preview&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqHO0oYW6Ic?si=UtZkFYUmjrM&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assistant simplifies common workflows like writing PromQL, LogQL, or TraceQL queries, and creating dashboards — all while keeping you in control. It helps reduce toil and improve productivity by enabling you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write and debug queries faster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build and optimize dashboards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Investigate issues and anomalies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand telemetry trends and patterns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Navigate Grafana more intuitively&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simplify onboarding for your teams &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Grafana Assistant features and use cases, please visit our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;secure-credential-storage-secrets-management-in-grafana-cloud-synthetic-monitoring&#34;&gt;Secure credential storage: secrets management in Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The more your infrastructure grows, the more difficult it becomes to safely store the API keys, passwords, and tokens that power your observability stack. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s why, this month, we&amp;rsquo;re &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-08-12-secrets-management-for-synthetic-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;launching secrets management&lt;/a&gt; in Grafana Cloud. Currently in public preview, secrets management provides a centralized location to securely store and manage values such as API keys, passwords, tokens, and credentials. The first product in Grafana Cloud to integrate with our new secrets manager is Synthetic Monitoring. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With secrets management in Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring, you can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create secrets and attach metadata to secrets, such as description and labels.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reference secrets by name in &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/k6/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;k6 scripted&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/k6-browser/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;k6 browser&lt;/a&gt; synthetics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reset and revoke secret values.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Access to create, update, and delete secrets is currently restricted to admin users. However, anyone with permissions to edit checks can use secrets, provided they know the secret name.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the Synthetic Monitoring UI, showing the &amp;#39;Create secret&amp;#39; dialog box on the left and a &amp;#39;Secrets management&amp;#39; section on the right.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the Synthetic Monitoring UI, showing the &amp;#39;Create secret&amp;#39; dialog box on the left and a &amp;#39;Secrets management&amp;#39; section on the right.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; Currently, secrets can only be accessed in scripted and browser checks, but support for more check types will be available in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more, refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/20/secure-credential-storage-for-your-observability-stack-introducing-secrets-management-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/manage-secrets/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;secrets management documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;llm-powered-insights-for-tracing-data-mcp-support-in-grafana-cloud-traces&#34;&gt;LLM-powered insights for tracing data: MCP support in Grafana Cloud Traces &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Distributed tracing data is a unique and powerful observability signal, allowing you to understand how your services interact and the relationships between them. Sometimes it can be difficult, however, to turn raw tracing data into actionable insights. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To help you overcome this challenge, we’ve &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-08-08-access-tracing-data-using-mcp-server-in-grafana-cloud-traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;added direct support&lt;/a&gt; for the Model Context Protocol (MCP) within &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt;, our fully managed distributed tracing system powered by &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/&#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://modelcontextprotocol.io/overview&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP&lt;/a&gt; is a widely adopted protocol, developed by Anthropic, that standardizes how applications provide context to large language models (LLMs). By integrating MCP with Grafana Cloud Traces, you can now leverage LLM-powered tools like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.anthropic.com/claude-code&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Claude Code&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://cursor.com/en&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Cursor&lt;/a&gt; to analyze and derive value from your tracing data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More specifically, you can use this new integration to more easily:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explore services and understand interactions&lt;/strong&gt;: LLMs can be used to teach new developers about service interactions within an application by analyzing tracing data. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diagnose and investigate errors&lt;/strong&gt;: LLMs can help you identify and diagnose errors in your systems. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Optimize performance and reduce latency&lt;/strong&gt;: LLMs can help you identify the causes of latency and guide your optimization efforts. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Setting up an LLM agent with Grafana Cloud Traces requires a Grafana Cloud API token and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/traces/mcp-server/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;configuration&lt;/a&gt;. This feature is currently available in public preview.  To learn more, please check out &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/13/llm-powered-insights-into-your-tracing-data-introducing-mcp-support-in-grafana-cloud-traces/&#34;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/traces/mcp-server/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;our technical docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;secure-queries-for-data-sources-the-tailscale-and-grafana-cloud-integration&#34;&gt;Secure queries for data sources: the Tailscale and Grafana Cloud integration  &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We know our users want to leverage platforms like Grafana Cloud to visualize and gain valuable insights into their data, while also keeping their data sources private and secure. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s exactly what we set out to achieve with our new integration between &lt;a href=&#34;https://tailscale.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Tailscale&lt;/a&gt; and Grafana Cloud. Available now in private preview, the integration lets you query data sources on your Tailscale network (known as a &lt;a href=&#34;https://tailscale.com/kb/1136/tailnet&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;tailnet&lt;/a&gt;) directly from your Grafana Cloud stack using &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/connect-externally-hosted/private-data-source-connect/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Private Data Source Connect&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqHO0oYW6Ic?si=Gqs3whtiZWQ&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Key benefits of the integration include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure and private data access&lt;/strong&gt;: With Tailscale, querying private data sources can remain private — no endpoints need to be opened to the public internet.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified setup and reduced operational overhead&lt;/strong&gt;: Private Data Source Connect with Tailscale is a simpler alternative to running PDC agents. To connect to a data source on a tailnet, you simply need to enter your data source’s tailnet address or machine name using MagicDNS and provide a Tailscale auth key.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Extended observability with Grafana Cloud&lt;/strong&gt;: Grafana Cloud offers advanced observability solutions and greater convenience than a self-hosted stack. You can query data sources in private networks from anywhere, making it ideal for distributed teams and remote work.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the Tailscale and Grafana Cloud integration, and how it works, please visit &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/07/24/securely-query-data-sources-on-your-tailscale-network-using-private-data-source-connect-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/connect-externally-hosted/private-data-source-connect/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Private Data Source Connect documentation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;out-of-the-box-alerting-for-frontend-observability&#34;&gt;Out-of-the-box alerting for Frontend Observability &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/frontend-observability-for-real-user-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability&lt;/a&gt; is our hosted service for real user monitoring (RUM) that provides immediate, clear, actionable insights into the end user experience of web applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And this month, the process for configuring alerting for Frontend Observability became a whole lot easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability out-of-the-box alerting, &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-07-22-frontend-observability-out-of-the-box-alerting/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;now generally available&lt;/a&gt;, we’ve taken the first step towards helping you configure &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/alerting-rules/create-grafana-managed-rule/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana-managed alerts&lt;/a&gt; without needing any previous experience with alerting in Grafana Cloud. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqHO0oYW6Ic?si=8uacjks_ylg&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Using our simple workflows, you can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enable and configure alerts based on your web app’s errors and web vital metrics. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Find and troubleshoot issues faster because alert configuration and rules are handled automatically. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Develop templates to help expand the alerting coverage of your frontend applications. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can visit our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/alerting/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Frontend Observability docs&lt;/a&gt; to learn more. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;enhanced-incident-management-in-grafana-cloud-irm&#34;&gt;Enhanced incident management in Grafana Cloud IRM &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;communicate-incident-status-updates&#34;&gt;Communicate incident status updates &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-07-23-communicate-incident-status-updates-with-grafana-irm/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;now add Status updates&lt;/a&gt; to incidents in &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/03/11/oncall-management-incident-response-grafana-cloud-irm/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud IRM&lt;/a&gt; to help keep your team and stakeholders informed during an incident.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Status updates are structured messages that communicate key information throughout the incident lifecycle. Whether you’re confirming impact, escalating to another team, or resolving the issue, use status updates to help track and share progress in a consistent, high-signal way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can add status updates directly in the UI or by using the following Slack commands in the associated incident channel:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use &lt;code&gt;/grafana incident update add &amp;lt;content&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; to post a new status update from Slack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use &lt;code&gt;/grafana incident update&lt;/code&gt; to view the latest status update.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get started with this feature, which is now generally available, open any incident in Grafana Cloud IRM and locate the &lt;strong&gt;Status updates&lt;/strong&gt; section in the &lt;strong&gt;activity timeline&lt;/strong&gt;. To learn more, please visit &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/use/incident-management/status-updates/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;our docs&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-new-experience-for-incident-webhooks&#34;&gt;A new experience for incident webhooks &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud IRM outgoing webhooks &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-08-07-incident-webhooks-now-available-through-irm-shared-outgoing-webhooks/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;now support incident events&lt;/a&gt;, providing a unified experience for automating alert group and incident workflows. You can configure webhooks from the &lt;strong&gt;Outgoing Webhooks&lt;/strong&gt; tab and trigger requests based on key incident lifecycle events, such as when an incident is declared, updated, or resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this update, you can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Customize webhook requests with support for any HTTP method&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use templated URLs, headers, and request bodies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dynamically reference incident data and prior webhook responses&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;View webhook execution details directly from the incident or alert group timeline&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manage incident-related webhook configurations using Terraform&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The legacy Incident Outgoing Webhooks app and existing configurations will continue to work. However, we recommend migrating to the shared IRM webhook experience, which is now generally available, to take advantage of the latest features and ensure long-term support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn more in &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/configure/integrations/webhooks/outgoing-webhooks/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;our docs.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;extensions-and-version-support-in-grafana-cloud-k6&#34;&gt;Extensions and version support in Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-08-18-extensions-and-version-support-in-grafana-cloud-k6/&#34;&gt;the general availability&lt;/a&gt; of k6 extensions in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/k6/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/a&gt;, the hosted performance testing platform powered by &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/&#34;&gt;Grafana k6&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/extensions/&#34;&gt;k6 extensions&lt;/a&gt; are a way to extend the core functionality of k6. For k6 open source users, they can write custom extensions and then build a new k6 binary to use them locally. For Grafana Cloud k6 users, you can use a subset of these extensions when running your test scripts, without having to build a custom k6 binary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now seamlessly use extensions from both Grafana Cloud and the k6 CLI:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Local execution: &lt;code&gt;k6 run test.js&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cloud execution: &lt;code&gt;k6 cloud run test.js&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Local execution, streaming test results: &lt;code&gt;k6 cloud run test.js --local-execution&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more, please visit &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/k6/author-run/use-k6-extensions/&#34;&gt;our docs&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-latest-enterprise-data-sources-and-integrations-for-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;The latest Enterprise data sources and integrations for Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, here are some new ways you can extend the value of Grafana Cloud through integrations and Enterprise data sources. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;monitor-claude-usage-and-costs-with-the-anthropic-integration&#34;&gt;Monitor Claude usage and costs with the Anthropic integration &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/19/how-to-monitor-claude-usage-and-costs-introducing-the-anthropic-integration-for-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;Anthropic integration for Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; lets you connect directly to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.anthropic.com/en/api/admin-api/usage-cost&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Anthropic Usage and Cost API&lt;/a&gt; from within Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By leveraging usage data from Anthropic — the AI company who developed the Claude large language models (LLMs) — the new integration provides real-time insights into the costs and performance of your Claude LLMs, all within Grafana Cloud. And with a pre-built dashboard and alerts, you can start visualizing and acting on your Claude data right away.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3024x1726/cca55f846c/anthropic-usage-dashboard_1.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3024x1726/cca55f846c/anthropic-usage-dashboard_1.png&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a pre-built Grafana Cloud dashboard showing Anthropic API usage metrics.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3024x1726/cca55f846c/anthropic-usage-dashboard_1.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a pre-built Grafana Cloud dashboard showing Anthropic API usage metrics.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;To learn more about the Anthropic integration for Grafana Cloud, please check out &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-anthropic/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;our documentation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;visualize-jenkins-data&#34;&gt;Visualize Jenkins data&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/grafana-jenkins-datasource/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Jenkins Enterprise data source&lt;/a&gt; allows you to query and visualize metrics from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jenkins.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Jenkins&lt;/a&gt; — the open source automation server used to build and deploy projects as part of Continuous Integration (CI) and Continuous Deployment (CD) pipelines — within Grafana Cloud or Grafana Enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This data source includes two built-in dashboards to help you quickly get started visualizing Jenkins data:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jenkins Overview dashboard:&lt;/strong&gt; provides an overview of the Jenkins instance, including all projects, nodes, executor status and build queue.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jenkins DORA Metrics dashboard:&lt;/strong&gt; provides information on four key metrics used to assess software development team performance: deployment frequency, lead time for changes, change failure rate, and time to restore service. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x901/5520ac54db/jenkins-enterprise-data-source-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x901/5520ac54db/jenkins-enterprise-data-source-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard displaying four graphs: deployment frequency, lead time for changes, change failure rate, and time to restore service over 30 days.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x901/5520ac54db/jenkins-enterprise-data-source-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard displaying four graphs: deployment frequency, lead time for changes, change failure rate, and time to restore service over 30 days.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; To learn more about the Jenkins Enterprise data source, currently in public preview, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-jenkins-datasource/latest/&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们始终在Grafana Cloud中推出有用的更新和有趣的功能，Grafana Cloud是我们由开源Grafana Lgtm stack供电的完全管理的可观察性平台（&lt;a href =“/oss/oss/loki/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt” href =“/oss/grafana/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana &lt;/a&gt;用于可视化，&lt;a href =“/oss/oss/tempo/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt; tempo &lt;/a&gt; href =“/oss/mimir/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; mimir &lt;/a&gt;用于指标）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您错过了他们，这是我们每月对最新，最出色的Grafana Cloud更新的综述。您还可以在&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/whats-new/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;中添加到grafana云中的所有功能，&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，如果您还不是Grafana Cloud用户，则&lt;a href =“/auth/insig-up/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; cign up &lt;/a&gt;今天！您可以通过我们慷慨的无云计划免费尝试任何这些功能（以及更多）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ an-easier to-to-to-get-with-grafana-cloud-cloud-grafana-rassistant-is-now-now-in-now-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-public-preview”&gt;一种更轻松的方法，可以从Grafana Cloud开始：Grafana Assistant现在在公共预览中&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Grafana Labs，&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-at-at grafana-labs-rabs-rabs-mabservibility-easy-and-and-cell-cell-cell-every-everyone/everyone/“ everyone/”&gt;我们相信&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; AI不仅仅是一种趋势的趋势。这对于组织如何使系统全面运行是不可或缺的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种信念继续影响我们构建的工具。例如，我们很高兴分享Grafana Assistant（Grafana Cloud中的AI驱动的代理商，可以帮助您使用自然语言查询，构建和更快地进行故障排除）是&lt;a href =“/href =”/blog/2025/08/08/08/14/ai-for-for-for-for-for-grafana-onboarding-grafana-onboarding-get-get-get-your-teams-your-teams-with-quickeckern-quickern-quickerand/propply/proupper graffaffafafa in&gt;&#xA;&lt;Iframe width =“ 560”高度=“ 315” src =“ https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqho0oyw6ic?si = utzkfyumjrm” title =“ youtube视频玩家”图片中的图片; web-share“ referrerpolicy =“ cross-origin”允许floserfullscreen&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;助手简化了常见的工作流程，例如编写Promql，logQl或TraceQl查询，并创建仪表板，同时使您可以控制自己。它通过使您能够：&lt;/p&gt;来帮助降低辛劳并提高生产率。&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更快地写和调试查询&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;构建和优化仪表板&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;调查问题和异常&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;了解遥测趋势和模式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更直观地导航grafana &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;简化团队的入职&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关Grafana Assistant功能和用例的更多信息，请访问我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/Machine-Learning/Assistant/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ secure-credential-streagendore-screts-in-grafana-cloud synthetic-监视“&gt;安全凭证存储：Grafana Cloud合成监控中的秘密管理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您的基础架构的增长越多，安全存储API键，密码和令牌就越困难，可以为您的可观察性堆栈提供动力。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是为什么，这个月，我们是&lt;a href =“/whats-new/2025-08-12-secrets-secrets-management-for-synththetic-monitoring/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;启动秘密管理&lt;/a&gt;在Grafana云中&lt;/a&gt;。当前在公共预览中，Secrets Management提供了一个集中的位置，以安全地存储和管理API键，密码，令牌和凭据等值。 Grafana Cloud中与我们的新秘密经理集成的第一个产品是合成监视。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借助Grafana Cloud合成监控的秘密管理，您可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;创建秘密并将元数据附加到秘密，例如描述和标签。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/checks/k6/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = k6 scripted &lt;/a&gt; href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/checks/k6-browser/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = k6浏览器&lt;/a&gt; synthetics。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;重置和撤销秘密价值。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;访问创建，更新和删除秘密目前仅限于管理用户。但是，只要知道秘密名称，任何有权编辑检查许可的人都可以使用秘密。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png” alt =“ Alt =”合成ui的筛选器，显示了&#39;sector ui ui scretenshot&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x869/d0a6feeaf9/secrets-management-config.png”&#xA;alt =“合成监视UI的屏幕截图，在左侧显示&#39;创建秘密&#39;对话框以及右侧的“秘密管理”部分。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figue&gt;当前，秘密只能在脚本和浏览器检查中访问，但将来将提供更多检查类型的支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解更多信息，请参阅我们的&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/08/20/secure-credential-credential-storage-your-orserservibility stack-indroducing-indroducing-secrets-management-indroducts-indroducts-management-ingrafana-cloud/” href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/manage-secrets/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;秘密管理文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ llm驱动的 -   - 追溯 -  data-mcp-sup-support in-grafana-cloud-traces”&gt; llm-powe追踪数据的红色见解：Grafana Cloud Traces中的MCP支持&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;分布式跟踪数据是一个独特而强大的可观察性信号，使您可以了解服务方式及其之间的关系。但是，有时很难将原始的跟踪数据转换为可行的见解。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了帮助您克服这一挑战，我们&lt;a href =“/whats-new/2025-08-08-08-Access-cess-tracing-data-- using-used-in-used-rafafana-cloud-traces/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt&#39;&gt;添加了直接支持&lt;/a&gt; for Model Context（mcp）&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; href =“/products/cloud/traces/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana云痕迹&lt;/a&gt;，我们完全管理的分布式跟踪系统由&lt;a href =“/oss/tempo/”&gt; grafaana tempo &lt;/a&gt;提供支持。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://modelcontextprotocol.io/overview” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; mcp &lt;/a&gt;广泛采用的协议，由人类学开发，标准化了如何为大型语言模型（LLMS）提供上下文（LLMS）。通过将MCP与Grafana Cloud Traces整合在一起，您现在可以利用LLM驱动的工具，例如&lt;a href =“ https://www.anththropic.com/claude-code” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” noopener noreferrer“&gt; claude code&gt; claude code &lt;/a&gt; rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;光标&lt;/a&gt;从您的跟踪数据中分析和得出价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更具体地说，您可以更轻松地使用此新集成：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;探索服务并了解交互&lt;/strong&gt;：LLM可用于通过分析跟踪数据来向新开发人员传授应用程序中的服务交互。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;诊断和调查错误&lt;/strong&gt;：LLM可以帮助您识别和诊断系统中的错误。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;优化性能并减少延迟&lt;/strong&gt;：LLM可以帮助您确定延迟的原因并指导优化工作。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用Grafana云轨迹设置LLM代理需要Grafana Cloud API令牌和&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/traces/mcp-server/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;配置&lt;/a&gt;。此功能当前可在公共预览中找到。  要了解更多信息，请访问&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/08/08/13/llm-powered-powered-in-into-into-your-trac-your-tracing-data-indroducing-mcp-support-indroducing-mcp-support-ingrafana-cloud-traces/”&gt; href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/traces/mcp-server/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;我们的技术文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ secure-queries-for-data-sources-tailscale and grafana-cloud-integration”&gt;数据源的安全查询：尾scale和grafana cloud Integration &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们知道我们的用户希望利用Grafana Cloud等平台可视化并获得对数据的宝贵见解，同时还将其数据源保持私密和安全。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这正是我们在&lt;a href =“ https://tailscale.com/之间的新集成中，我们要实现的目标。 Availab现在的LE在私人预览中，该集成使您可以在TailScale网络上查询数据源（称为A &lt;a href =“ https:/ https://tailscale.com/kb/1136/1136/tailnet” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ rel =” noopener noreferrer href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/connect-externelly-data-source-connect/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;私有数据源连接&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;Iframe width =“ 560”高度=“ 315” src =“ https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqho0oyw6ic?si = gqs3Whtizwq” title =“ title =“图片中的图片; web-share“ referrerpolicy =“ cross-origin”允许floserfullscreen&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;集成的关键好处包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;安全和私人数据访问&lt;/strong&gt;：使用尾部，查询私人数据源可以保持私密 - 不需要向公共互联网打开端点。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简化的设置和减少的操作开销&lt;/strong&gt;：私有数据源与尾部连接是运行PDC代理的更简单替代方案。要连接到尾网上的数据源，您只需要使用MagicDNS输入数据源的尾网地址或机器名称，并提供尾巴验证键。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana Cloud的扩展可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;：Grafana Cloud提供了高级可观察性解决方案和更大的便利性，而不是自托管堆栈。您可以从任何地方查询私人网络中的数据源，使其非常适合分布式团队和远程工作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关尾巴和格拉法纳云集成的更多信息，以及它的工作原理，请访问&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/07/24/seary-query-query-query-query-data-sources-on-your-your-your-tailscale-network-network-using-private-private-data-source-data-source-connect-connect-connect-innect-ingrafana-ingrafana-ingrafana-cloud/this Blog this Blog this Blog this Blog pob pob &lt;a&gt; href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/connect-externelly-data-source-connect/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;私有数据源连接文档&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“在盒子外进行 -  for-for-for-for-for-for-observability&#39;&gt;在框外警报，以确保前端可观察性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/frontend-observiability-for-real-user-monitoring/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud cloud frontend可观察性&lt;/a&gt;是我们的托管服务，可用于真实的用户监控（朗姆酒），可直接，清晰，清晰，可行的，可行，可行的最终用户体验的最终用户体验。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;和本月，配置前端可观察性的警报的过程变得更加容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用Grafana Cloud Frontend可观察性，&lt;a href =“/Whats-new/2025-07-22-frontend-observyable-of-the-box-alerting/？pg = pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt =现在，我们通常可以使用&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，我们已经可以使用&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，我们已经为您配置了&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;/a&gt; href =“/docs/grafana/最终/警报/警报规则/create-grafana-managed-rule/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana管理的警报&lt;/a&gt;无需任何以前的经验e在Grafana Cloud中发出警报。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“ 560” height =“ 315” src =“ https://www.youtube.com/embed/cqho0oyw6ic?si = 8Uacjks_ylg” title =“ youtube” Web-share“ referrerpolicy =” cross-Origin“ aLLEFULLSCREEN&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;时，严格的原始物质&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用我们的简单工作流程，您可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;根据您的Web应用程序的错误和Web重要指标启用和配置警报。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;由于警报配置和规则是自动处理的，因此发现并解决问题的速度更快。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;开发模板，以帮助扩大前端应用程序的警报覆盖范围。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以访问我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observipity/artering/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;前端可观察性文档&lt;/a&gt;以了解更多信息。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“增强的incention-incention-management-in-grafana-cloud-imm”&gt; Grafana Cloud Irm &lt;/h2&gt;的增强事件管理&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以&lt;a href =“/whats-new/2025-07-23- communicate-incention-indist-indent-status-updates-with-with-grafana-mirm/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在添加状态更新&lt;/a&gt; href =“/blog/2025/03/11/oncall-management-incident-response-response-grafana-cloud-irm/”&gt; grafana cloud irm &lt;/a&gt;，以帮助您在事件中保持团队和利益相关者的通知。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;状态更新是结构化消息，可以在整个事件生命周期中传达关键信息。无论您是确认影响力，向另一个团队升级还是解决问题，都使用状态更新以一致，高信号的方式跟踪和分享进度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以直接在UI中添加状态更新，也可以使用相关事件通道中的以下Slack命令：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用&lt;code&gt;/grafana事件更新添加&lt;content&gt; &lt;/code&gt;以发布Slack的新状态更新。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用&lt;code&gt;/grafana事件更新&lt;/code&gt;查看最新状态更新。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开始使用此功能，该功能现在通常可用，请在Grafana Cloud IRM中打开任何事件，并在&lt;strong&gt;活动时间表中找到&lt;strong&gt;状态更新&lt;/strong&gt;部分&lt;/strong&gt;。要了解更多信息，请访问&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/nervering-and-inm/irm/irm/use/indist-management/status-updates/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;我们的文档&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“ a-new-beferience for Incident-webhooks”&gt;事件webhooks的新体验&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud IRM outgoing webhooks &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-08-07-incident-webhooks-now-available-through-irm-shared-outgoing-webhooks/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;now support incident events&lt;/a&gt;, providing a unified experience for automating alert group and incident workflows.您可以根据关键事件生命周期事件的&lt;strong&gt; Out Out Webhooks &lt;/strong&gt;选项卡和触发请求配置Webhooks，例如当事件被宣布时ARED，更新或解决。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用此更新，您可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自定义Webhook请求，并支持任何HTTP方法&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用模板的URL，标题和请求尸体&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;动态参考事件数据和先前的Webhook响应&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;查看Webhook执行直接从事件或警报组时间表中&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用Terraform管理与事件相关的Webhook配置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;传统事件即将发出的Webhooks应用程序和现有配置将继续起作用。但是，我们建议迁移到现在通常可用的共享IRM Webhook体验，以利用最新功能并确保长期支持。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/arterging-and-inm/irm/configure/intermations/webhooks/out out-webhooks/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;我们的文档中，了解更多信息。&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ grafana cloud k6 &lt;/h2&gt;中的扩展和s-support-in-support-in-grafana-cloud-k6”&gt;扩展和版本支持&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-08-18-extensions-and-version-support-in-grafana-cloud-k6/&#34;&gt;the general availability&lt;/a&gt; of k6 extensions in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/k6/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/a&gt;, the hosted performance testing platform powered by &lt;a href =“/docs/k6/最终/”&gt; grafana k6 &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“/docs/k6/最新/扩展/”&gt; k6扩展&lt;/a&gt;是扩展K6核心功能的一种方法。对于K6开源用户，他们可以编写自定义扩展名，然后构建一个新的K6二进制文件以在本地使用它们。对于Grafana Cloud K6用户，您可以在运行测试脚本时使用这些扩展名的子集，而无需构建自定义K6二进制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您现在可以无缝使用Grafana Cloud和K6 CLI的扩展：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;本地执行：&lt;code&gt; k6运行test.js &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;云执行：&lt;code&gt; k6云运行test.js &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;本地执行，流测试结果：&lt;code&gt; k6云运行test.js  - 局部 - 执行&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解更多信息，请访问&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/k6/furet-run/use-k6-extensions/“&gt;我们的文档&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“最新的grafana-cloud-cloud-cloud-anderce-indercrise-inderprise-data-source-cloud-cloud”&gt; Grafana Cloud的最新企业数据源和集成&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，您可以通过集成和企业数据源来扩展Grafana Cloud的价值的一些新方法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“与人类融合有关的Monitor-claude-usage-usage-and-Costs and-Costs”&gt;监视器的Claude使用和成本与人为集成&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;新的&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/08/19/how-to-to-to-monitor-claude-usaude-usage and-costs-indroducing-the-themanthropic-inthropic-inthropic-integration-intergration-for-grafana-cloud/&gt; anthropic inthropic inthropic inthropic inthropic inthropic inthropic inthropic inthropic集成href =“ https://docs.anththropic.com/en/api/admin-api/usage-cost” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;人类用法和成本API &lt;/a&gt;来自Grafana Cloud。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过利用人类的使用数据 - 开发C的AI公司LAUDE大语言模型（LLMS） - 新的集成为您的Clafana Cloud中的Claude LLMS的成本和性能提供了实时见解。借助预先构建的仪表板和警报，您可以立即开始可视化和行动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3024x1726/cca555f846c/anththropic-usage-usage-dashboard_1.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3024x1726/cca555f846c/anththropic-usage-usage-dashboard_1.png” alt =“ Alt =” Alt =“ a for-buitt grafana clofana云仪表板显示Anththap&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3024x1726/cca555f846c/anththropic-usage-usage-dashboard_1.png”&#xA;alt =“预先构建的Grafana云仪表板的屏幕截图，显示拟人API使用指标。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/fige&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&#xA;要了解有关Grafana Cloud的拟人集成的更多信息，请访问&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/monitory-infrastructure/intermations/intermations/intempration-referention-reperation-nathropic/pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;我们的文档&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“可视化 - 詹金斯 - 达塔”&gt;可视化詹金斯数据&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;新的&lt;a href =“/grafana/插件/grafana-jenkins-datasource/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; jenkins enthprise数据源&lt;/a&gt;允许您从&lt;a href =“ Noreferrer“&gt; Jenkins &lt;/a&gt;  - 用于构建和部署项目的开源自动化服务器，作为连续集成（CI）和连续部署（CD）管道的一部分 - 在Grafana Cloud或Grafana Enterprise中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此数据源包括两个内置仪表板，以帮助您快速开始可视化Jenkins数据：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Jenkins概述仪表板：&lt;/strong&gt;提供了Jenkins实例的概述，包括所有项目，节点，执行者状态和构建队列。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Jenkins Dora指标仪表板：&lt;/strong&gt;提供有关用于评估软件开发团队绩效的四个关键指标的信息：部署频率，变更的交付时间，变更失败率以及恢复服务的时间。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999901/5520AC54DB/Jenkins-enterprise-data-source-dashboard.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999901/5520AC520AC54DB/JENKINS-ENTERPRISE-DATA-SOURCE-DASE-DASHBOARD.png” ALT =“ ALT =” GrafaNa Dashboard Displays declosplobs decloshots thagre thrage oferenthing four declenshot：t频率，变化的交货时间，变化失败率以及在30天内恢复服务的时间。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999901/5520AC54DB/jenkins-enterprise-data-data-source-dashboard.png”&#xA;Alt =“ Grafana仪表板的屏幕截图，显示四个图：部署频率，更改的交付时间，变化失败率以及在30天内还原服务的时间。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figud&gt;要了解有关Jenkins Enterprise数据源的更多信息，目前在公共预览中，请查看我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/plugins/grafana-jenkins-datasource/最终/最终预览。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>