<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</title>
    <link>/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Show me the (meeting) money: How to monitor the real-time costs of a meeting in Grafana】显示（会议）费用：如何在 Grafana 中监控会议的实时费用</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/17/show-me-the-meeting-money-how-to-monitor-the-real-time-costs-of-a-meeting-in-grafana/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This meeting could’ve been an email.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s a phrase most of us have said (or at least thought) at some point in our careers. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For me, that realization hit years ago while working for a government organization. I’d frequently sit through long, agendaless meetings that seemingly went nowhere. I wasn’t sure why I was there. And because I’m an engineer at heart, I started to wonder: what were these meetings actually costing the organization? Not just in abstract productivity hours, but in actual dollars and cents?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few simple math formulas later, a few colleagues and I got to work on a Perl script to find out. Fast forward to today, and I lead the developer advocacy team here at Grafana Labs, where I recently reimagined that old Perl script as a Grafana dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll walk through that dashboard — called the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/d/bedn3ke4t1uyoa/meeting-cost-calculator&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Meeting Cost Calculator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; — and how it helps you visualize the real-time costs of any business meeting, down to the cent. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Full disclosure: this concept originated as a joke between coworkers. It’s meant to be a fun, lighthearted way to monitor the real-time costs of a meeting. It’s &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; meant to cast judgement on how anyone runs theirs. Mostly, I just hope it’s something you can share with your team to get a good laugh, and maybe learn a thing or two about Grafana along the way. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;that-sync-cost-how-much-a-closer-look-at-how-the-dashboard-works&#34;&gt;That sync cost &lt;em&gt;how much&lt;/em&gt;?! A closer look at how the dashboard works&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the most part, the Meeting Cost Calculator dashboard does exactly what its name suggests: it shows you, in real time, how much your meeting is costing you (under the watchful but tired eye of Peter Gibbons from &lt;em&gt;Office Space&lt;/em&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As common as meetings are, I doubt we’re the only ones who’ve built a way to calculate their costs. The difference here, of course, is that our dashboard uses Grafana to help you quickly and easily track those costs through eye-catching visualizations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1032/53e75e9da6/cost-of-meetings-dashboard-screenshot.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1032/53e75e9da6/cost-of-meetings-dashboard-screenshot.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard showing meeting cost per second, total meeting cost, and a buzzword bingo game.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1032/53e75e9da6/cost-of-meetings-dashboard-screenshot.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard showing meeting cost per second, total meeting cost, and a buzzword bingo game.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To start using the dashboard, you’ll need to first enter two simple inputs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;number of attendees&lt;/strong&gt; in the meeting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;average hourly cost per person&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see in the screenshot above, these values — which are &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/variables/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana variables&lt;/a&gt; — can be filled out in the top bar of the dashboard. The hourly cost of the meeting is the number of attendees times the hourly rate, which we can work out all the way down to a cost per second with simple math.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you don’t know the average hourly cost per person (which you likely won’t), I recommend starting around $200/hour. That might sound high, but it accounts for more than just salary, factoring in things like benefits and office equipment spend. Back in my consulting days, we had a “&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/consulting/comments/1668yqi/comment/jykq89t/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;amp;utm_term=1&amp;amp;utm_content=share_button&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;rule of 3&lt;/a&gt;,” which stated that the actual hourly cost of a person was roughly triple their salary/hourly rate. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To start calculating real-time costs during a meeting, simply click the text that says &lt;strong&gt;Click here to reset the dashboard&lt;/strong&gt;. Then, based on your inputs, the dashboard displays a count of how many seconds you’ve been in the meeting, the meeting cost per second, and the overall meeting cost so far.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve got things displayed the way you want, you can copy and paste the full URL of the dashboard (which includes your variable values) and share with co-workers to live track the meeting you’re all in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Behind the scenes, a microservice calculates the on-going cost, multiplying the per-person, per-second rate by the number of seconds elapsed, and keeping track of when the dashboard was reset (i.e., when the meeting started). Grafana fetches that data as JSON, and the dashboard refreshes every five seconds to keep things dynamic. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This demonstrates a common technique used in many Grafana dashboards: visualizing data from any accessible microservice. Feel free to inspect the panels to get a better sense of how it works! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bonus-panel-business-buzzword-bingo&#34;&gt;Bonus panel: Business Buzzword Bingo&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let’s circle back. Low-hanging fruit. Lots of moving parts.&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Uh… BINGO?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re all guilty of using corporate clichés from time to time, so why not have some fun while we’re at it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Business Buzzword Bingo panel in the Meeting Cost Calculator dashboard lets you do just that, displaying an array of phrases that you can check off on your personal bingo card when you hear them in a meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/838x942/4a535aea1b/meeting-buzzword-bingo-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/838x942/4a535aea1b/meeting-buzzword-bingo-2.png&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the &amp;#39;Meeting Buzzword Bingo&amp;#39; panel with phrases like &amp;#39;low hanging fruit,&amp;#39; &amp;#39;paradigm shift,&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;synergy.&amp;#39;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/838x942/4a535aea1b/meeting-buzzword-bingo-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the &amp;#39;Meeting Buzzword Bingo&amp;#39; panel with phrases like &amp;#39;low hanging fruit,&amp;#39; &amp;#39;paradigm shift,&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;synergy.&amp;#39;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This component isn’t multiplayer (yet), but it’s a fun way to liven up a meeting — and maybe even hold ourselves accountable for saying things like “synergy” one too many times.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;start-tracking-meeting-costs-today&#34;&gt;Start tracking meeting costs today &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Meeting Cost Calculator dashboard is &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/d/bedn3ke4t1uyoa/meeting-cost-calculator&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;available today on Grafana Play&lt;/a&gt;, our public sandbox environment for testing and learning Grafana. We encourage you to inspect the panel definitions and see how it’s built. You can also copy the JSON definition and import it into your own Grafana instance to customize the dashboard however you’d like. Go ahead and adjust the average hourly cost, add your own memes, or even expand the Bingo board with your team’s favorite buzzwords (you know the ones).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you do put your own spin on it, please share it with us in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Community Forum&lt;/a&gt;. We’d love to see what you come up with. And if you’ve created a different meeting cost calculator for your own teams, we’d love to hear about that, too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;这次会议可以是一封电子邮件。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是我们大多数人在职业生涯的某个时刻说过（或至少想到过）的一句话。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对我来说，这种认识是多年前在政府组织工作时实现的。我经常坐着参加冗长、无议程的会议，但这些会议似乎毫无进展。我不确定我为什么在那里。因为我本质上是一名工程师，所以我开始想知道：这些会议实际上给组织带来了哪些成本？不仅是抽象的生产力时间，而且是实际的美元和美分？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;几个简单的数学公式之后，我和几位同事开始编写 Perl 脚本来找出答案。快进到今天，我领导了 Grafana Labs 的开发人员倡导团队，最近我在那里将旧的 Perl 脚本重新构想为 Grafana 仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将详细介绍该仪表板（称为&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/d/bedn3ke4t1uyoa/meeting-cost-calculator&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;会议成本计算器&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;），以及它如何帮助您可视化任何会议的实时成本 商务会议，精确到分。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完全披露：这个概念起源于同事之间的一个笑话。它旨在以一种有趣、轻松的方式来监控会议的实时成本。这&lt;em&gt;无意&lt;/em&gt;对任何人如何管理他们的业务进行判断。大多数情况下，我只是希望你可以与你的团队分享一些东西，让他们开怀大笑，也许还能学到一两点关于 Grafana 的知识。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;that-sync-cost-how-much-a-closer-look-at-how-the-dashboard-works&#34;&gt;同步费用&lt;em&gt;多少&lt;/em&gt;？！仔细看看仪表板的工作原理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在大多数情况下，会议成本计算器仪表板的功能正如其名称所暗示的那样：它实时向您显示您的会议花费了多少费用（在来自 Office Space 的 Peter Gibbons 的警惕但疲惫的目光下）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管会议很常见，但我怀疑我们是唯一建立了计算成本方法的人。当然，这里的区别在于我们的仪表板使用 Grafana 来帮助您通过引人注目的可视化快速轻松地跟踪这些成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1032/53e75e9da6/cost-of-meetings-dashboard-screenshot.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1032/53e75e9da6/cost-of-meetings-dashboard-screenshot.png&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板，显示每秒会议费用、会议总费用和流行词宾果游戏。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1032/53e75e9da6/cost-of-meetings-dashboard-screenshot.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板显示每秒会议费用、总计会议费用，以及流行语宾果游戏。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要开始使用仪表板，您需要首先输入两个简单的输入：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;会议&lt;strong&gt;与会者人数&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;每人平均每小时费用&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正如您在上面的屏幕截图中看到的，这些值（即 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/variables/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana 变量&lt;/a&gt;）可以在仪表板的顶部栏中填写。会议的每小时成本是与会者人数乘以每小时费率，我们可以通过简单的数学计算一直到每秒的成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您不知道每人每小时的平均成本（您可能不知道），我建议从 200 美元/小时左右开始。这听起来可能很高，但它不仅仅只考虑工资，还考虑了福利和办公设备支出等因素。回到我的咨询时代，我们有一个“&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.reddit.com/r/consulting/comments/1668yqi/comment/jykq89t/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;utm_term=1&amp;utm_content=share_button&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;3 规则&lt;/a&gt;”，该规则规定一个人的实际每小时成本大约是其工资/小时费率的三倍。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要在会议期间开始计算实时费用，只需点击&lt;strong&gt;单击此处重置仪表板&lt;/strong&gt;文本即可。然后，根据您的输入，仪表板会显示您参加会议的秒数、每秒的会议费用以及迄今为止的总体会议费用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;按照您想要的方式显示内容后，您可以复制并粘贴仪表板的完整 URL（其中包括您的变量值）并与同事共享，以实时跟踪您参加的会议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在幕后，微服务计算持续成本，将每人每秒的费用乘以经过的秒数，并跟踪仪表板何时重置（即会议开始的时间）。 Grafana 以 JSON 形式获取该数据，仪表板每五秒刷新一次以保持动态。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这演示了许多 Grafana 仪表板中使用的常见技术：可视化来自任何可访问的微服务的数据。请随意检查面板，以更好地了解其工作原理！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bonus-panel-business-buzzword-bingo&#34;&gt;奖励面板：商业流行词宾果游戏&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;让我们回到过去。唾手可得的果实。很多活动部件。&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;呃…宾果游戏？&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们都会时不时地使用公司的陈词滥调，所以为什么不享受其中的乐趣呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;会议成本计算器仪表板中的商业流行语宾果面板可以让您做到这一点，它会显示一系列短语，当您在会议中听到这些短语时，您可以在个人宾果卡上勾选这些短语。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__ligh”tbox w-100p“&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/838x942/4a535aea1b/meeting-buzzword-bingo-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/838x942/4a535aea1b/meeting-buzzword-bingo-2.png&#34;alt=&#34;“Meeting Buzzword Bingo”面板的屏幕截图，其中包含“容易实现的目标”、“范式转变”和“协同作用”等短语。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/838x942/4a535aea1b/meeting-buzzword-bingo-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;“Meeting Buzzword Bingo”面板的屏幕截图，其中包含“容易实现的目标”、“范式转变”和“协同作用”等短语。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个组件还不是多人游戏，但它是一种让会议活跃起来的有趣方式 - 甚至可能让我们自己对多次说“协同”之类的事情负责。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;start-tracking-meeting-costs-today&#34;&gt;立即开始跟踪会议费用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;会议费用计算器仪表板&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/d/bedn3ke4t1uyoa/meeting-cost-calculator&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;今天可在 Grafana Play 上使用&lt;/a&gt;，这是我们用于测试和学习 Grafana 的公共沙箱环境。我们鼓励您检查面板定义并了解它是如何构建的。您还可以复制 JSON 定义并将其导入您自己的 Grafana 实例中，以根据需要自定义仪表板。继续调整平均每小时成本，添加您自己的模因，甚至用您团队最喜欢的流行语（您知道这些）扩展宾果板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您确实对此有自己的看法，请在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana 社区论坛&lt;/a&gt;中与我们分享。我们很想看看您的想法。如果您为自己的团队创建了不同的会议费用计算器，我们也很想听听。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From pillars to rings: How interconnected observability in Grafana Cloud optimizes performance and reduces telemetry waste】从支柱到环：Grafana Cloud 中的互连可观测性如何优化性能并减少遥测浪费</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/16/from-pillars-to-rings-how-interconnected-observability-in-grafana-cloud-optimizes-performance-and-reduces-telemetry-waste/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In observability, we’ve traditionally been taught to think in terms of &lt;em&gt;pillars&lt;/em&gt;, namely logs, metrics, and traces (and more recently, profiles). But pillars are rigid and disconnected. They don’t reflect how modern systems actually work or how we troubleshoot in real time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So let’s change that. Instead of pillars, think in terms of &lt;em&gt;rings&lt;/em&gt;—rings that act as interconnected layers of observability, each building on the other, wrapped around a central concept of opinionated observability solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog, I’ll walk through how we combine metrics, logs, and traces in context to deliver stronger observability outcomes. By connecting these signals, we’re able to build opinionated solutions in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;—solutions built to optimize performance, minimize waste, and help you focus on the data that truly matters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-inner-core-the-three-telemetry-rings&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The inner core: The three telemetry rings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/3d11055c02/three-rings.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/3d11055c02/three-rings.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;Venn diagram with three overlapping circles labeled Logs, Metrics, and Traces, illustrating their interconnectedness.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/3d11055c02/three-rings.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Venn diagram with three overlapping circles labeled Logs, Metrics, and Traces, illustrating their interconnectedness.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Metrics, logs, and traces are not separate tools; they&amp;rsquo;re connected lenses on the same system. But before we dig into how to use them in tandem, let’s quickly define what each signal does.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traces&lt;/strong&gt; reveal the path a request takes through your system. With OpenTelemetry and tools like &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt; (powered by Grafana Tempo), you can have a transaction-level view. Traces can tell you what happened, where it slowed down, and how it connects across services.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Logs&lt;/strong&gt; tell the granular story of events. When structured, centralized, and contextualized with tools like &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Logs&lt;/a&gt; (powered by Grafana Loki), they stop being noisy and start explaining &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; something happened.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metrics&lt;/strong&gt; summarize the system’s current and historical state. Think CPU usage, request latency, error rates. &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Metrics&lt;/a&gt; (powered by Grafana Mimir) supports Prometheus, OTel metrics, and more, giving you the pulse of your system.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each ring serves a unique role, but they are meant to be viewed together, giving your telemetry context to help you drive actions and outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-might-be-wondering-what-about-profiles&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You might be wondering: What about profiles?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/685x782/ff6c81383e/four-rings.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/685x782/ff6c81383e/four-rings.png&#34;alt=&#34;Venn diagram showing overlapping circles labeled Logs, Metrics, and Traces, with Profiles in a dashed circle above.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/685x782/ff6c81383e/four-rings.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Venn diagram showing overlapping circles labeled Logs, Metrics, and Traces, with Profiles in a dashed circle above.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While not traditionally counted among the three core pillars of observability, at Grafana Labs we see &lt;strong&gt;profiles&lt;/strong&gt; as the emerging fourth signal. When used alongside metrics, logs, and traces, profiles add critical depth and help teams get even more value out of their observability stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, this blog will focus on how we use metrics, logs, and traces today since those are the signals organizations are most likely to start with and put in siloes. When you&amp;rsquo;re ready to take that next step on your &lt;a href=&#34;/maturity-model/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;maturity journey&lt;/a&gt;—and we highly recommend you do—check out &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/08/09/grafana-cloud-profiles-for-continuous-profiling/&#34;&gt;this blog on Grafana Cloud Profiles&lt;/a&gt; to learn more on how profiles are becoming part of our out-of-the-box solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;moving-beyond-the-signals-what-happens-when-you-connect-the-rings&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moving beyond the signals: What happens when you connect the rings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/567x576/b029de4bfe/opinionated-slutions.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/567x576/b029de4bfe/opinionated-slutions.png&#34;alt=&#34;Venn diagram with overlapping circles labeled Logs, Metrics, Traces, and Profiles, highlighting &amp;#39;Opinionated Solutions&amp;#39; at the center.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/567x576/b029de4bfe/opinionated-slutions.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Venn diagram with overlapping circles labeled Logs, Metrics, Traces, and Profiles, highlighting &amp;#39;Opinionated Solutions&amp;#39; at the center.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Collecting logs, metrics, and traces is not enough. Many teams stop here, believing they’ve “done observability” because they have dashboards and alerts. But this is just the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, you can build your own dashboards and configure your own alerts. But these tools are raw materials—powerful but unrefined. To evolve beyond dashboards, we combine:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observability best practices&lt;/strong&gt; like structured logging, low-cardinality metrics, distributed tracing, RED metrics, and golden signals&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technology best practices&lt;/strong&gt; like service discovery, container orchestration, cloud architecture patterns, Kubernetes readiness/liveness probes, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When these are integrated and when you know not just &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; to observe, but &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; it matters and &lt;em&gt;what to do&lt;/em&gt; with the insights, then you reach what we call:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;opinionated-observability-in-context&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opinionated observability in context&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An opinionated observability solution delivers automated, context-rich, cost-effective visibility by bundling:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The technology being observed&lt;/strong&gt;: The system context&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operational best practices&lt;/strong&gt;: Guidance on how to keep the system healthy and performant&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Observability best practices&lt;/strong&gt;: Surfacing signal from noise, ingesting only what’s needed (and only when it’s needed), minimizing cost, and enabling automation wherever possible&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/753x628/2e0a2f71c5/opinionated-solutions-questions.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/753x628/2e0a2f71c5/opinionated-solutions-questions.png&#34;alt=&#34;Flowchart with &amp;#39;Opinionated Solutions&amp;#39; leading to three questions: &amp;#39;What to observe?&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Why is it broken?&amp;#39;, and &amp;#39;What to do about it?&amp;#39;.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/753x628/2e0a2f71c5/opinionated-solutions-questions.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Flowchart with &amp;#39;Opinionated Solutions&amp;#39; leading to three questions: &amp;#39;What to observe?&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Why is it broken?&amp;#39;, and &amp;#39;What to do about it?&amp;#39;.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When telemetry rings are connected, and observability is delivered in opinionated, contextual layers, the results are measurable:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Faster resolution (lower MTTR):&lt;/strong&gt; Root cause detection in minutes, not hours&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Greater operational efficiency&lt;/strong&gt;: Fewer false alerts, tighter SLO compliance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lower cloud cost:&lt;/strong&gt; Right-sizing resources with accurate, contextual data&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is not the future. This is happening today! Opinionated observability in context doesn’t just answer, “What’s happening?” It answers three questions every engineering team really needs to know:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should be observed?&lt;/strong&gt; Curated dashboards, alerting rules, SLOs, and telemetry configuration aligned with known best practices (like SRE principles, golden signals, and cloud native patterns).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is it broken?&lt;/strong&gt; Correlation across signals—latency spikes, error rates, degraded SLOs—connected back to trace paths and logs that explain the root cause, not just the symptom.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should you do about it?&lt;/strong&gt; Recommendations, remediations, and playbooks triggered in context not by humans scanning a dozen tabs, but by pre-wired workflows built into the solution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This model is already elevating the standard observability experience through Grafana Cloud solutions: Kubernetes Monitoring, Cloud Provider Observability, Application Observability, and Frontend Observability (powered by our knowledge graph).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;real-examples-of-opinionated-observability-in-context&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real examples of opinionated observability in context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;kubernetes-monitoring&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/kubernetes-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/a&gt; solution provides out-of-the-box dashboards, alerts, and ML recommendations mapped to industry best practices for cluster health, pod behavior, and service performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t just ingest data. It understands Kubernetes, visualizes thresholds, and stitches together logs and metrics across clusters, pods, nodes, workloads, and namespaces. This gives platform teams a complete contextual view without having to build it from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How it answers the three big questions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should be observed?&lt;/strong&gt; CPU, memory, restarts, network and storage usage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is it broken?&lt;/strong&gt; Contextual drilldowns into correlated logs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should you do about it?&lt;/strong&gt; Alerts and dashboards tied to recommended remediations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;cloud-provider-observability&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Provider Observability&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each cloud monitoring solution—whether for &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/cloud-monitoring-aws/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AWS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/cloud-monitoring-microsoft-azure/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Microsoft Azure&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/cloud-monitoring-google-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Google Cloud&lt;/a&gt;—is tailored to the provider&amp;rsquo;s native services. Grafana Cloud connects to APIs and telemetry pipelines to surface logs and metrics from managed services for compute, storage, network, and many more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The value lies in the pre-mapped service context so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to build your own dashboards or alerts. These solutions come preloaded with visuals, thresholds, and correlations that reflect the real architecture of your cloud deployments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How it answers the three big questions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should be observed?&lt;/strong&gt;  Cloud native service metrics and health checks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is it broken?&lt;/strong&gt;  Pre-wired alerting and logs surfaced next to metrics&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should you do about it?&lt;/strong&gt; Runbook guidance based on cloud-specific anomalies (e.g., autoscaling failures, rate limit issues)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grafana-cloud-knowledge-graph&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Knowledge Graph&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/knowledge-graph/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Knowledge Graph&lt;/a&gt; (formerly Asserts) adds a critical layer to the observability stack: automated insight into service health, performance, and reliability using SLO-based analysis. Unlike dashboards that show &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt;, Knowledge Graph surfaces only the relevant context when something’s wrong, helping you focus on what matters most.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By analyzing telemetry, our knowledge graph identifies issues, correlates them to service dependencies, and explains them in plain language. It leverages opinionated thresholds, service boundaries, and historical patterns so you get answers, not alerts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How it answers the three big questions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should be observed?&lt;/strong&gt; Signals, not noise, for every service&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is it broken?&lt;/strong&gt;  Automatic root cause analysis based on dependency mapping&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should you do about it?&lt;/strong&gt;  Direct recommendations and explanations in real time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-final-ring-an-ai-assistant-that-understands-your-systems&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The final ring: an AI assistant that understands your systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/631x812/730c7ae266/assistant-ring.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/631x812/730c7ae266/assistant-ring.png&#34;alt=&#34;Venn diagram titled &amp;#39;Grafana Assistant&amp;#39; showing overlapping circles: Logs, Metrics, and Traces, with &amp;#39;Profiles&amp;#39; in the center, with Assistant wrapped around all four..&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/631x812/730c7ae266/assistant-ring.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Venn diagram titled &amp;#39;Grafana Assistant&amp;#39; showing overlapping circles: Logs, Metrics, and Traces, with &amp;#39;Profiles&amp;#39; in the center, with Assistant wrapped around all four..&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Surrounding the telemetry rings is a new, emerging ring of AI-powered observability. &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; is built for observability workflows in Grafana Cloud, helping teams manage complex systems with automated insights, contextual alerts, and intelligent monitoring recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It interprets telemetry signals in human-readable language, then it can recommend what to do next. This means:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Fewer war rooms&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Less time combing through dashboards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;More confidence in what you’re seeing and why it matters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, AI will only be as good as the data and structure we feed it, which is why opinionated observability solutions are the perfect foundation. They provide clean, curated data that is intentionally tailored to surface the right signals at the right time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-ready-for-whats-next&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get ready for what’s next&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The future of observability isn&amp;rsquo;t just about seeing your systems. It’s about understanding them and acting with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sooner rather than later, this will be the default: telemetry connected by design, observability enriched with best practices, and AI interpreting it all with clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re constantly expanding and improving Grafana Cloud. To keep tabs on all the latest updates, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s New from Grafana Labs&lt;/a&gt; page. And dig into our &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;full list of solutions&lt;/a&gt; to find the one that fits your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The rings are in motion. The next era of observability is connected, contextual, and AI-powered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在可观察性方面，传统上我们被教导要根据&lt;em&gt;支柱&lt;/em&gt;进行思考，即日志、指标和跟踪（以及最近的配置文件）。但支柱是僵硬且不连贯的。它们没有反映现代系统的实际工作方式或我们如何实时排除故障。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所以让我们改变这一点。不用柱子，而是用&lt;em&gt;环&lt;/em&gt;来思考——环充当可观察性的互连层，每个环都建立在另一个之上，围绕固执己见的可观察性解决方案的中心概念。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本博客中，我将介绍如何在上下文中结合指标、日志和跟踪来提供更强的可观察性结果。通过连接这些信号，我们能够在 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 中构建固执己见的解决方案，这些解决方案旨在优化性能、最大限度地减少浪费并帮助您专注于真正重要的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-inner-core-the- Three-telemetry-rings&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;内核：三个遥测环&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/3d11055c02/ Three-rings.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/3d11055c02/third-rings.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;维恩图，其中三个重叠的圆圈标记为日志、指标和跟踪，说明了它们的互连性。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/3d11055c02/三环.jpg”&#xA;alt=&#34;带有三个重叠圆圈的维恩图，标记为日志、指标和轨迹，说明了它们的互连性。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;指标、日志和跟踪不是独立的工具；而是不同的工具。它们是同一系统上的连接镜头。但在我们深入研究如何协同使用它们之前，让我们快速定义每个信号的作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;跟踪&lt;/strong&gt;揭示请求通过您的系统的路径。借助 OpenTelemetry 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt;（由 Grafana Tempo 提供支持）等工具，您可以获得事务级视图。跟踪可以告诉您发生了什么、哪里变慢以及它如何跨服务连接。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;日志&lt;/strong&gt;讲述事件的详细故事。当使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Logs&lt;/a&gt;（由 Grafana Loki 提供支持）等工具进行结构化、集中化和情境化时，他们就不再吵闹，并开始解释为什么会发生某些事情。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;指标&lt;/strong&gt;总结了系统的当前和历史状态。考虑 CPU 使用率、请求延迟、错误率。 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana 云指标&lt;/a&gt;（由 Grafa 提供支持）na Mimir）支持 Prometheus、OTel 指标等，为您提供系统脉搏。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个环都有独特的作用，但它们应该一起查看，为您提供遥测背景，帮助您推动行动和结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-might-be-wondering-what-about-profiles&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您可能想知道：个人资料怎么样？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/685x782/ff6c81383e/four-rings.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/685x782/ff6c81383e/four-rings.png&#34;alt=&#34;维恩图显示标记为日志、指标和跟踪的重叠圆圈，上面的虚线圆圈为配置文件。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/685x782/ff6c81383e/four-rings.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;维恩图显示标记为日志、指标和跟踪的重叠圆圈，上面的虚线圆圈为配置文件。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然传统上不将其视为可观察性的三大核心支柱，但在 Grafana Labs，我们将&lt;strong&gt;配置文件&lt;/strong&gt;视为新兴的第四个信号。当与指标、日志和跟踪一起使用时，配置文件会增加关键深度，并帮助团队从其可观察性堆栈中获得更多价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;也就是说，本博客将重点介绍我们今天如何使用指标、日志和跟踪，因为这些是组织最有可能开始使用并放入孤岛的信号。当您准备好在&lt;a href=&#34;/maturity-model/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;成熟之旅&lt;/a&gt;中迈出下一步时（我们强烈建议您这么做），请查看&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/08/09/grafana-cloud-profiles-for-continuous-profiling/&#34;&gt;此关于 Grafana Cloud Profiles 的博客&lt;/a&gt;，了解更多信息 配置文件如何成为我们开箱即用的解决方案的一部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;moving-beyond-the-signals-what-happens-when-you-connect-the-rings&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;超越信号：连接环时会发生什么&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/567x576/b029de4bfe/opinionated-slutions.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/567x576/b029de4bfe/opinionated-slutions.png&#34;alt=&#34;带有重叠圆圈的维恩图，标记为日志、指标、跟踪和配置文件，突出显示中心的“意见解决方案”。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/567x576/b029de4bfe/opinionated-slutions.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;带有重叠圆圈的维恩图，标记为日志、指标、迹线和 P配置文件，突出显示中心的“固执己见的解决方案”。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仅收集日志、指标和跟踪还不够。许多团队就此止步，认为他们已经“完成了可观察性”，因为他们有仪表板和警报。但这仅仅是开始。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;是的，您可以构建自己的仪表板并配置自己的警报。但这些工具只是原材料——功能强大但未经提炼。为了超越仪表板，我们结合了：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可观测性最佳实践&lt;/strong&gt;，例如结构化日志记录、低基数指标、分布式跟踪、RED 指标和黄金信号&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;技术最佳实践&lt;/strong&gt;，例如服务发现、容器编排、云架构模式、Kubernetes 就绪/活跃度探测等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当这些整合起来时，当您不仅知道要观察什么，而且知道为什么它很重要以及如何利用这些见解做什么时，您就会达到我们所说的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;opinionated-observability-in-context&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;上下文中的主观可观察性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;固执己见的可观察性解决方案通过捆绑提供自动化、上下文丰富、经济高效的可见性：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;正在观察的技术&lt;/strong&gt;：系统上下文&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;运营最佳实践&lt;/strong&gt;：有关如何保持系统健康和高性能的指南&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;可观测性最佳实践&lt;/strong&gt;：从噪声中提取信号、仅提取需要的内容（并且仅在需要时提取）、最大限度地降低成本并尽可能实现自动化&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/753x628/2e0a2f71c5/opinionated-solutions-questions.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/753x628/2e0a2f71c5/opinionated-solutions-questions.png&#34;alt=&#34;带有“固执己见的解决方案”的流程图，引出了三个问题：“要观察什么？”、“为什么会损坏？”和“该怎么办？”。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/753x628/2e0a2f71c5/opinionated-solutions-questions.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;带有“固执己见的解决方案”的流程图，引出了三个问题：“要观察什么？”、“它为什么坏了？”和“该怎么办？”。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当遥测环连接起来，并且可观察性在固执己见的上下文层中提供时，结果是可测量的：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;更快地解决问题（更低的 MTTR）：&lt;/strong&gt;在几分钟（而不是几小时）内即可检测出根本原因&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;更高的运营效率&lt;/strong&gt;：更少的误报，更严格的 SLO 合规性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;降低云成本：&lt;/strong&gt;利用准确的上下文数据调整资源规模&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这不是未来。这就是今天发生的事！上下文中的自以为是的可观察性不仅仅回答“发生了什么？”它回答了每个工程团队真正需要知道的三个问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;应该注意什么？&lt;/strong&gt;精心策划的仪表板、警报规则、SLO 和遥测配置与已知的最佳实践（例如 SRE 原则、黄金信号和云原生模式）保持一致。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么会损坏？&lt;/strong&gt;信号之间的相关性（延迟峰值、错误率、降级的 SLO）连接回跟踪路径和日志，以解释根本原因，而不仅仅是症状。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您应该对此采取什么措施？&lt;/strong&gt;在上下文中触发的建议、补救措施和行动手册不是由人类扫描十几个选项卡，而是由解决方案中内置的预连线工作流程触发。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该模型已经通过 Grafana Cloud 解决方案提升了标准可观测性体验：Kubernetes 监控、云提供商可观测性、应用程序可观测性和前端可观测性（由我们的知识图谱提供支持）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;real-examples-of-opinionated-observability-in-context&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;上下文中固执己见的可观察性的真实示例&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;kubernetes-monitoring&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kubernetes 监控&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/kubernetes-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 监控&lt;/a&gt;解决方案提供开箱即用的仪表板、警报和 ML 建议，这些建议映射到集群运行状况、Pod 行为和服务性能的行业最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它不只是摄取数据。它了解 Kubernetes，可视化阈值，并将跨集群、pod、节点、工作负载和命名空间的日志和指标拼接在一起。这为平台团队提供了完整的上下文视图，而无需从头开始构建。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;它如何回答三大问题：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;应该观察什么？&lt;/strong&gt;CPU、内存、重启、网络和存储使用情况&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么它被破坏了？&lt;/strong&gt;关联日志的上下文深入&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您应该采取什么措施？&lt;/strong&gt;与建议的补救措施相关的警报和仪表板&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;cloud-provider-observability&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;云提供商可观察性&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个云监控解决方案 - 无论是针对 &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/cloud-monitoring-aws/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AWS&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/cloud-monitoring-microsoft-azure/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Microsoft Azure&lt;/a&gt; 还是 &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/cloud-monitoring-google-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Google Cloud&lt;/a&gt; - 针对提供商的原生服务量身定制。 Grafana Cloud 连接到 API 和遥测管道，以显示来自计算、存储、网络等托管服务的日志和指标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;价值在于在预先映射的服务上下文中，因此您不必构建自己的仪表板或警报。这些解决方案预装了视觉效果、阈值和相关性，可反映云部署的真实架构。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;它如何回答三大问题：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;应注意什么？&lt;/strong&gt;云原生服务指标和运行状况检查&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么它被破坏了？&lt;/strong&gt; 预连接的警报和日志出现在指标旁边&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您应该采取什么措施？&lt;/strong&gt;基于特定于云的异常情况（例如自动扩展失败、速率限制问题）的运行手册指南&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grafana-cloud-knowledge-graph&#34;&gt;Grafana 云知识图&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/knowledge-graph/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;知识图&lt;/a&gt;（以前称为断言）为可观察性堆栈添加了一个关键层：使用基于 SLO 的分析自动洞察服务运行状况、性能和可靠性。与显示所有内容的仪表板不同，知识图谱仅在出现问题时显示相关上下文，帮助您专注于最重要的事情。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过分析遥测数据，我们的知识图谱可以识别问题，将其与服务依赖项关联起来，并用简单的语言进行解释。它利用固执己见的阈值、服务边界和历史模式，以便您获得答案，而不是警报。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;它如何回答三大问题：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;应该注意什么？&lt;/strong&gt;每项服务都是信号，而不是噪音&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么会出现问题？&lt;/strong&gt;基于依赖关系映射的自动根本原因分析&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您应该采取什么措施？&lt;/strong&gt; 实时提供直接建议和解释&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-final-ring-an-ai-assistant-that-understands-your-systems&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;最后一环：了解您系统的 AI 助手&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/631x812/730c7ae266/assistant-ring.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/631x812/730c7ae266/assistant-ring.png&#34;alt=&#34;标题为“Grafana Assistant”的维恩图显示重叠的圆圈：日志、指标和跟踪，“配置文件”位于中心，Assistant 包裹在所有四个周围..&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/631x812/730c7ae266/assistant-ring.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;标题为“Grafana Assistant”的维恩图显示重叠的圆圈：日志、指标和跟踪，“配置文件”位于中心，Assistant 围绕所有四个..&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;遥测环周围是一个新兴的人工智能观测环可修复性。 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; 专为 Grafana Cloud 中的可观察性工作流程而构建，可帮助团队通过自动化洞察、上下文警报和智能监控建议来管理复杂的系统。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它以人类可读的语言解释遥测信号，然后它可以建议下一步做什么。这意味着：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;作战室减少&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;减少梳理仪表板的时间&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;对您所看到的内容及其重要性更有信心&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当然，人工智能的好坏取决于我们提供给它的数据和结构，这就是为什么固执己见的可观测性解决方案是完美的基础。它们提供干净、精心策划的数据，这些数据经过专门定制，以便在正确的时间呈现正确的信号。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-ready-for-whats-next&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为接下来的事情做好准备&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可观察性的未来不仅仅是查看您的系统。关键在于理解它们并自信地采取行动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;迟早，这将成为默认：通过设计连接的遥测、通过最佳实践丰富的可观测性以及人工智能清晰地解释这一切。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在不断扩展和改进 Grafana Cloud。要密切关注所有最新更新，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs 的新增功能&lt;/a&gt;页面。深入研究我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;完整解决方案列表&lt;/a&gt;，找到适合您需求的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;环在运动。下一个可观察时代是互联的、情境化的和人工智能驱动的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Baking in site reliability with observability and AI: How SpotOn uses Grafana Assistant to keep restaurants running】通过可观察性和人工智能提高站点可靠性：SpotOn 如何使用 Grafana Assistant 来保持餐厅运营</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/15/baking-in-site-reliability-with-observability-and-ai-how-spoton-uses-grafana-assistant-to-keep-restaurants-running/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When you operate a restaurant, the last thing you want to do is shut your doors and turn away guests and staff because of some technology failure. And if you&amp;rsquo;re the one providing that tech, it&amp;rsquo;s your job to make sure that doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;For us, observability is about a lot more than just dashboards and alerts. &lt;em&gt;Reliability&lt;/em&gt; is really how we make sure our customers are able to operate, because we understand our restaurants depend on us,&amp;rdquo; said Jeremy White, Vice President of Engineering at SpotOn.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SpotOn offers point-of-sale systems and a suite products to help restaurants take orders, process payments, run marketing campaigns, manage employees and tips, and more. They want their customers to focus on their guests, not the underlying tooling, and that&amp;rsquo;s where Grafana comes in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;And the challenge is bigger than just the cloud,&amp;rdquo; White said. &amp;ldquo;We support hardware that&amp;rsquo;s in thousands of restaurants and kitchens across the country. These are places where you deal with a lot of heat, you deal with a lot of grease. The kitchens are basically Faraday cages, so WiFi is not so great. We rely on observability to help us understand and stay ahead of a lot of those problems in order to avoid interrupting their business and their day-to-day operations.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And just last week, during the &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2025/keynote/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025 keynote&lt;/a&gt;, White spoke about how SpotOn has started using &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt;, our context-aware AI agent built for Grafana, to help improve that reliability even further. You can check out his full segment below, or keep reading to see how SpotOn is reaping tangible benefits from Assistant, including faster onboarding, better adoption, and simpler troubleshooting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;gvsSJwFfR3w&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gvsSJwFfR3w?autoplay=1&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;observability-only-works-when-people-are-actually-using-it&#34;&gt;&amp;lsquo;Observability only works when people are actually using it&amp;rsquo;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/&#34;&gt;became generally available last week&lt;/a&gt;, but it was first released in private preview &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/llm-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;back in May&lt;/a&gt;. SpotOn was an early adopter, and one of the first things White noticed was how it increased internal adoption of Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Observability only works when people are actually using it, and this is one of the areas where we found Grafana Assistant really helped us,&amp;rdquo; White said. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from having new engineers stepping in and not being familiar with where our logs and metrics are for all the different services to actively being able to participate in incidents and triaging.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And it&amp;rsquo;s all done through a conversation with an AI agent—no need for additional training or understanding. This has been particularly helpful when dealing with dependencies across diverse systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;As you span into different products and have to understand how different teams have instrumented their systems, Assistant is able to bridge that gap a lot easier for people not familiar with those teams,&amp;rdquo; White said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;no-more-blank-page-problems&#34;&gt;No more blank page problems&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;White has also enjoyed seeing how Assistant is solving the &amp;ldquo;blank sheet of paper problem&amp;rdquo; where new users struggle to know where to start in Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;With Grafana Assistant, we found that some people could go straight from idea to dashboard and then iterate. And that iteration was a lot easier for people to handle as opposed to solving that blank sheet of paper problem,&amp;rdquo; White said. &amp;ldquo;So this has been a huge boost to our participation in observability as well as the speed to value and how quickly we can get to value for our customers.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;White cited the example of a team of network support specialists whose job is to ensure the client networks are operating properly, with zero negative impact on the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Now these are not Grafana experts, not even familiar with the tooling, but they were able to use Grafana Assistant to get started and create dashboards—dashboards that could look at one restaurant and be able to tell all the network devices, all the possible problems we might be seeing, pull it together in one place and allow them to triage those issues a lot faster,&amp;rdquo; he said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the team didn&amp;rsquo;t stop there, despite their lack of familiarity with Grafana Cloud. They used Assistant to help identify groups of customers experiencing issues so they could proactively contact SpotOn&amp;rsquo;s support team to solve the problem—all before the customer ever calls to ask for help. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;This is a great example of where our team can focus on being subject matter experts and focus on solving customer problems, not on the tooling,&amp;rdquo; White said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;blocking-out-the-noise&#34;&gt;Blocking out the noise&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes SpotOn&amp;rsquo;s observability stack generates so many signals that developers get overwhelmed. White used the example of a &lt;code&gt;CrashLoopBackOff&lt;/code&gt; alert, which is common and could have a hundred different causes. His team used Assistant to decorate the alert and add context for why the alert fired, which is particularly helpful for engineers who aren&amp;rsquo;t used to troubleshooting that specific issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We had one case where it even found a null pointer reference during the transformation process in one of our services,&amp;rdquo; White said. &amp;ldquo;[Assistant] noticed right when it happened during the release, and so it made it a lot easier and a lot less time-consuming for us to troubleshoot that issue and ultimately get to a solution.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even when the assistant doesn&amp;rsquo;t pinpoint the exact solution, it still helps the team build confidence about what they should be looking at—and what to rule out—so they can resolve issues faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re really excited with the capabilities of Grafana Assistant,&amp;rdquo; White said. &amp;ldquo;Ultimately, it&amp;rsquo;s allowed us to really focus on solving customer problems and getting to customer outcomes rather than the underlying tooling. So if anyone else is interested in accelerating their observability adoption, I&amp;rsquo;d encourage you to take a look at Grafana Assistant.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;faq-grafana-cloud-ai--assistant&#34;&gt;FAQ: Grafana Cloud AI &amp;amp; Assistant&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Grafana Assistant?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant is an AI-powered agent in Grafana Cloud that helps you query, build, and troubleshoot faster using natural language. It simplifies common workflows like writing PromQL, LogQL, or TraceQL queries, creating dashboards, and performing guided root cause analysis — all while keeping you in control. Learn more in our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Grafana Assistant Investigations?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assistant investigations is an SRE agent built directly into Grafana Assistant. It helps you find root causes faster by analyzing your observability stack, uncovering anomalies, and connecting signals across your system. You get clear, guided recommendations for remediation — and because it’s embedded in Assistant, it provides a seamless, end-to-end workflow for resolving complex incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does Grafana Cloud use AI in observability?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud’s AI features support engineers and operators throughout the observability lifecycle — from detection and triage to explanation and resolution. We focus on explainable, assistive AI that enhances your workflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What problems does Grafana Assistant solve?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant helps reduce toil and improve productivity by enabling you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write and debug queries faster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build and optimize dashboards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Investigate issues and anomalies with Assistant Investigations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand telemetry trends and patterns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Navigate Grafana more intuitively&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Grafana Labs&amp;rsquo; approach to building AI into observability?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We build around:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Human-in-the-loop interaction for trust and transparency&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Outcome-first experiences that focus on real user value&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-signal support, including correlating data across metrics, logs, traces, and profiles&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does Grafana OSS have AI capabilities?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, Grafana OSS doesn’t include built-in AI features found in Grafana Cloud, but you can enable AI-powered workflows using the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM app plugin&lt;/a&gt;. This open source plugin connects to providers like OpenAI or Azure OpenAI securely, allowing you to generate queries, explore dashboards, and interact with Grafana using natural language. It also provides a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP (Model Context Protocol) server&lt;/a&gt;, which allows you to grant your favourite AI application access to your Grafana instance. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why isn’t Assistant open source?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant runs in Grafana Cloud to support enterprise needs and manage infrastructure at scale. We’re committed to OSS and continue to invest heavily in it — including open sourcing tools like the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM plugin&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP server&lt;/a&gt;, so the community can build their own AI-powered experiences into Grafana OSS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does Grafana Cloud’s AI capabilities take actions on its own?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we focus on human-in-the-loop workflows that keep engineers in control while reducing toil. But as AI systems mature and prove more reliable, some tasks may require less oversight. We&amp;rsquo;re building a foundation that supports both: transparent, assistive AI now, with the flexibility to evolve into more autonomous capabilities where it makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where can I learn more about Grafana’s AI strategy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Check out our blog post&lt;/a&gt; to hear directly from our engineers.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the difference between AI in observability and AI observability?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI in observability&lt;/em&gt; applies AI to operate your systems better and refers to the use of AI as part of a larger observability strategy. This could include agents baked into a platform (e.g., Grafana Assistant in Grafana Cloud) or other integrations that help automate and accelerate the ways teams observe their systems. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI observability&lt;/em&gt; is the use of observability to track the state of an AI system, such as an LLM-based application. It&amp;rsquo;s a subset of observability focused on a specific use case, similar to database observability for databases or application observability for applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud does both: AI that helps you operate, and observability for your AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当您经营一家餐厅时，您最不想做的就是因为某些技术故障而关门并拒绝客人和员工。如果您是提供该技术的人，那么您的工作就是确保这种情况不会发生。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“对我们来说，可观察性不仅仅是仪表板和警报。可靠性实际上是我们确保客户能够运营的方式，因为我们知道我们的餐厅依赖于我们，”SpotOn 工程副总裁 Jeremy White 说道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SpotOn 提供销售点系统和套件产品，帮助餐厅接受订单、处理付款、开展营销活动、管理员工和小费等。他们希望客户关注他们的客人，而不是底层工具，这就是 Grafana 的用武之地。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“挑战不仅仅是云，”怀特说。 “我们为全国数千家餐厅和厨房的硬件提供支持。这些地方需要处理大量热量，处理大量油脂。厨房基本上都是法拉第笼，因此 WiFi 不是很好。我们依靠可观察性来帮助我们了解并领先于许多此类问题，以避免中断他们的业务和日常运营。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;就在上周，在 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2025/keynote/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025 主题演讲&lt;/a&gt;期间，White 谈到了 SpotOn 如何开始使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; 是我们为 Grafana 构建的上下文感知 AI 代理，可帮助进一步提高可靠性。您可以在下面查看他的完整部分，或者继续阅读以了解 SpotOn 如何从 Assistant 中获得切实的好处，包括更快的入门、更好的采用和更简单的故障排除。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“gvsSJwFfR3w”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gvsSJwFfR3w?autoplay=1&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;observability-only-works-when-people-are-actually-using-it&#34;&gt;“可观察性仅在人们实际使用时才起作用”&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/&#34;&gt;上周正式发布&lt;/a&gt;，但它&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/llm-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;早在 5 月份&lt;/a&gt;就以私人预览版形式首次发布。 SpotOn 是早期采用者，White 注意到的第一件事就是它如何提高 Grafana Cloud 的内部采用率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“可观察性只有在人们实际使用时才起作用，这是我们发现 Grafana Assistant 真正帮助我们的领域之一，”White 说。 “我们已经不再有新工程师介入，而且不熟悉我们的日志和指标在所有不同的位置耳鼻喉科服务，以便能够积极参与事件和分类。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这一切都是通过与 AI 代理对话来完成的，无需额外的培训或理解。这在处理不同系统之间的依赖关系时特别有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“当你跨越不同的产品并必须了解不同的团队如何仪表化他们的系统时，Assistant 能够为不熟悉这些团队的人更轻松地弥合这一差距，”怀特说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;no-more-blank-page-problems&#34;&gt;不再出现空白页问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;White 还很高兴看到 Google Assistant 如何解决新用户在 Grafana 中不知道从哪里开始的“白纸问题”。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“通过 Grafana Assistant，我们发现有些人可以直接从想法转到仪表板，然后进行迭代。与解决白纸问题相比，这种迭代对于人们来说要容易得多，”White 说。 “因此，这极大地促进了我们对可观察性的参与，以及实现价值的速度以及我们为客户实现价值的速度。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;White 举了一个网络支持专家团队的例子，他们的工作是确保客户端网络正常运行，对业务的负面影响为零。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“现在他们不是 Grafana 专家，甚至不熟悉工具，但他们能够使用 Grafana Assistant 开始并创建仪表板 - 仪表板可以查看一家餐厅并能够告诉所有网络设备，我们可能会看到的所有可能的问题，将其集中在一个地方，使他们能够更快地分类这些问题，”他说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;尽管团队对 Grafana Cloud 不熟悉，但他们并没有就此止步。他们使用 Assistant 来帮助识别遇到问题的客户群体，以便他们可以主动联系 SpotOn 的支持团队来解决问题，而这一切都在客户致电寻求帮助之前进行。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“这是一个很好的例子，说明我们的团队可以专注于成为主题专家并专注于解决客户问题，而不是工具，”怀特说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;blocking-out-the-noise&#34;&gt;屏蔽噪音&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有时，SpotOn 的可观测性堆栈会生成如此多的信号，导致开发人员不知所措。 White 使用了 CrashLoopBackOff 警报的示例，该警报很常见，可能有一百种不同的原因。他的团队使用 Assistant 来装饰警报并添加警报触发原因的上下文，这对于不习惯解决特定问题的工程师特别有帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们遇到过一种情况，它甚至在我们的一项服务的转换过程中发现了空指针引用，”怀特说。 “[助理]在发布过程中就注意到了这一点，所以它做到了我们可以更轻松、更省时地解决该问题并最终找到解决方案。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使助理没有指出确切的解决方案，它仍然可以帮助团队建立对他们应该关注什么以及应该排除什么的信心，以便他们能够更快地解决问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们对 Grafana Assistant 的功能感到非常兴奋，”White 说。 “最终，它使我们能够真正专注于解决客户问题并获得客户结果，而不是底层工具。因此，如果其他人有兴趣加速其可观察性的采用，我鼓励您看看 Grafana Assistant。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;faq-grafana-cloud-ai--assistant&#34;&gt;常见问题解答：Grafana Cloud AI 和助手&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是 Grafana 助手？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 是 Grafana Cloud 中的人工智能代理，可帮助您使用自然语言更快地查询、构建和排除故障。它简化了常见的工作流程，例如编写 PromQL、LogQL 或 TraceQL 查询、创建仪表板以及执行指导性根本原因分析，同时让您保持掌控。请参阅我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;博文&lt;/a&gt;了解更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是 Grafana 助理调查？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;助理调查是直接内置于 Grafana Assistant 中的 SRE 代理。它通过分析可观测性堆栈、发现异常并连接整个系统的信号，帮助您更快地找到根本原因。您可以获得清晰的指导性补救建议，而且由于它嵌入在 Assistant 中，因此它提供了一个无缝的端到端工作流程来解决复杂事件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud 如何在可观测性中使用 AI？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 的 AI 功能在整个可观测性生命周期（从检测和分类到解释和解决）为工程师和操作员提供支持。我们专注于可解释的辅助人工智能，以增强您的工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Assistant 解决了哪些问题？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 可以帮助您减少劳累并提高工作效率：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更快地编写和调试查询&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;构建和优化仪表板&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过助理调查来调查问题和异常情况&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;了解遥测趋势和模式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更直观地浏览 Grafana&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Labs 将人工智能构建为可观察性的方法是什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们围绕：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;人机交互以实现信任和透明度&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;注重实际用户价值的结果优先体验&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多信号支持，包括跨指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件关联数据&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana OSS有AI功能吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认情况下，Grafana OSS 不包含Grafana Cloud 中内置了 AI 功能，但您可以使用&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM 应用插件&lt;/a&gt;启用 AI 支持的工作流程。此开源插件安全地连接到 OpenAI 或 Azure OpenAI 等提供商，允许您生成查询、探索仪表板并使用自然语言与 Grafana 交互。它还提供 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP（模型上下文协议）服务器&lt;/a&gt;，允许您授予您最喜爱的 AI 应用程序对 Grafana 实例的访问权限。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么 Google 助理不开源？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 在 Grafana Cloud 中运行，以支持企业需求并大规模管理基础设施。我们致力于 OSS 并继续对其进行大力投资 - 包括 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM 插件&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP 等开源工具 服务器&lt;/a&gt;，以便社区可以在 Grafana OSS 中构建自己的人工智能体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud 的 AI 功能会自行采取行动吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们专注于人机交互工作流程，让工程师保持控制，同时减少辛苦。但随着人工智能系统的成熟并证明更加可靠，某些任务可能需要更少的监督。我们正在建立一个支持两者的基础：现在是透明的辅助人工智能，并且可以在有意义的情况下灵活地发展为更加自主的功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在哪里可以了解有关 Grafana 人工智能策略的更多信息？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;查看我们的博文&lt;/a&gt;，直接听取我们工程师的意见。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;人工智能的可观察性和人工智能的可观察性有什么区别？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;可观察性中的人工智能&lt;/em&gt;应用人工智能来更好地操作系统，并指将人工智能用作更大的可观察性策略的一部分。这可能包括嵌入到平台中的代理（例如 Grafana Cloud 中的 Grafana Assistant）或其他集成，以帮助自动化和加速团队观察其系统的方式。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI 可观察性&lt;/em&gt;是利用可观察性来跟踪 AI 系统的状态，例如基于 LLM 的应用程序。它是专注于特定用例的可观察性的子集，类似于数据库的数据库可观察性或应用程序的应用程序可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 兼具以下两点：帮助您操作的 AI 以及 AI 的可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Managing observability costs at scale: A look at the latest cost management features in Grafana Cloud】大规模管理可观测性成本：Grafana Cloud 中最新的成本管理功能一览</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/14/managing-observability-costs-at-scale-a-look-at-the-latest-cost-management-features-in-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The benefits of observability are clear: deep visibility into system health, faster troubleshooting, and improved reliability (to name a few). But what’s equally clear is that, as organizations scale and evolve their observability strategies, they need a way to tap into these benefits without runaway costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&#34;/observability-survey/2025/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs&amp;rsquo; 2025 Observability Survey&lt;/a&gt;, 74% of respondents say cost is a top priority for selecting tools. Another &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/06/the-observability-maturity-curve-how-it-leaders-are-shifting-from-tools-to-outcomes/&#34;&gt;survey of 150 IT executives&lt;/a&gt; found that 41% of organizations increased their observability spending in the past year, with 55% predicting their spending will continue to grow in the next 12 months. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Recognizing this challenge, we’re always exploring new ways to help our users manage and optimize observability costs in Grafana Cloud. This means using technology to actively reduce your bill and foregoing &amp;ldquo;clever pricing,&amp;rdquo; according to Tom Wilkie, CTO of Grafana Labs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We are one of the few, if not the only, observability companies out there to really prioritize this,” Wilkie said during the &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2025/keynote/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025 keynote&lt;/a&gt; this month.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From a centralized cost management app to our end-to-end Adaptive Telemetry suite, here are some of the Grafana Cloud features we’ve rolled out recently to help you control and optimize costs, especially as your observability strategy scales. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;reduce-costs-and-noise-across-all-observability-pillars-adaptive-telemetry&#34;&gt;Reduce costs and noise across all observability pillars: Adaptive Telemetry &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A common culprit behind ballooning observability costs is storing large, and often unnecessary, volumes of telemetry data. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Observability costs and the volume of telemetry have really been rising exponentially,” Wilkie said. “And the common 80/20 rule applies: you&amp;rsquo;re not actually using 80% of the data you&amp;rsquo;re sending to your observability systems.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Enter &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/&#34;&gt;Adaptive Telemetry&lt;/a&gt;, a suite of features in Grafana Cloud designed to optimize observability data and costs by ensuring only the most valuable telemetry, spanning metrics, logs, traces, and profiles, is stored and surfaced. It uses intelligent classification and prioritization techniques to analyze how telemetry is used, and then automatically recommends actions like aggregating, sampling, dropping, or reducing low-value data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The suite started with Adaptive Metrics and Adaptive Logs and, as of this month, now includes &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;Adaptive Traces and Adaptive Profiles&lt;/a&gt;. This means Grafana Cloud users can extend the adaptive model across their end-to-end observability stacks. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;JJH7S-hdcNg&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JJH7S-hdcNg?autoplay=1&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a closer look at each feature:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(general availability)&lt;/strong&gt;: Helps you identify and eliminate unused or partially used time series data through aggregation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Logs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(general availability)&lt;/strong&gt;: Reduces log volume and associated costs by automatically identifying and removing low-value logs that are rarely or never used.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Traces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(general availability)&lt;/strong&gt;: Uses tail sampling to automatically identify and retain your most valuable traces, ensuring you get the critical performance insights you need (and nothing you don’t).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Profiles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;(private preview)&lt;/strong&gt;: Dynamically adjusts data collection based on workload behavior, allowing you to deploy continuous profiling more broadly across your infrastructure without incurring excessive costs. (Interested in joining the Adaptive Profiles private preview? Please complete &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeIFky5ut3g3tvhIOApTqV1yyuZ6i0Cv_Vg2G0wTbS6r98elQ/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt; and we’ll be in touch.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So far, our users &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/12/why-companies-choose-adaptive-metrics-and-how-they-save-time-and-a-lot-of-money/&#34;&gt;have seen some pretty powerful results&lt;/a&gt; with Adaptive Telemetry, from reduced alert fatigue to significantly lower storage and processing costs. For example, on average, organizations using Adaptive Metrics see a &lt;strong&gt;30%-50% reduction in telemetry costs&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Adaptive Telemetry and how it works, please check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;technical documentation&lt;/a&gt; and this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dz5XLSPTpWA&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;overview video&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;centralized-control-of-your-observability-spend-cost-management-and-billing-app&#34;&gt;Centralized control of your observability spend: Cost Management and Billing app&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When multiple teams across your org are generating telemetry data, it can be difficult to know who, exactly, is accountable for the costs — and even more difficult to get a big-picture view of your total spend.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the Cost Management and Billing app in Grafana Cloud, you get complete, centralized visibility into your Grafana Cloud usage and spend so you can stay in control of your observability budget. It can help underpin your organization’s &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/06/why-observability-needs-finops-and-vice-versa-the-vantage-integration-with-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;FinOps strategy&lt;/a&gt; by offering transparency around overall spend, and establishing cost accountability across departments and teams.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a dashboard in the Cost Management and Billing app, showing monthly costs for metrics, logs, and traces, and a detailed attributions breakdown.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a dashboard in the Cost Management and Billing app, showing monthly costs for metrics, logs, and traces, and a detailed attributions breakdown.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Key features include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost attribution&lt;/strong&gt;: Break down costs by label, such as a team or project, for better accountability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Usage-based alerts&lt;/strong&gt;: Set usage alerts to detect spikes early and prevent unexpected charges.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Invoice management&lt;/strong&gt;: View and download monthly invoices directly in the app.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spend insights&lt;/strong&gt;: Track costs across metrics, logs, traces, and other observability data, all in one place. Compare month-over-month spending trends to identify changes and optimize spend.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Cost Management and Billing app is generally available in Grafana Cloud. To learn more, please visit our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/understand-usage-cost/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;docs.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-existing-csp-discounts-and-credits-grafana-bring-your-own-cloud&#34;&gt;Use existing CSP discounts and credits: Grafana Bring Your Own Cloud &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We know many of our users have existing discounts and credits with cloud service providers (CSPs), and want them to be able to leverage those discounts while using Grafana Cloud. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Bring Your Own Cloud (BYOC) is a deployment option that allows you to do just that by running Grafana Cloud within your own AWS or Google Cloud Platform (GCP) account (Azure support is currently available on a case-by-case basis). You pay the infrastructure bill directly, so you can take advantage of any discounts, credits, or commitments you’ve already negotiated with your CSP. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“BYOC provides mega-scale customers a fundamentally new economic model for when traditional SaaS pricing stops making sense,” Wilkie said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to being cost effective, Grafana BYOC offers the following benefits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data residency&lt;/strong&gt;: All Grafana Cloud services are run in your account, so you know all your observability data stays there, too.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managed service&lt;/strong&gt;: Our team handles operations, scaling, and upgrades so your engineers can focus on more important things, like delivering business value.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feature parity&lt;/strong&gt;: You get to benefit from rapid feature releases and all the latest enhancements in Grafana Cloud, including Adaptive Telemetry, running in your environment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana BYOC is designed for large enterprises with high telemetry volumes and complex observability needs. To learn more, please visit our &lt;a href=&#34;/products/bring-your-own-cloud-byoc/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;BYOC page.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;apply-open-standards-to-cloud-cost-management-the-focus-specification&#34;&gt;Apply open standards to cloud cost management: The FOCUS specification&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Grafana Labs, we often say that open source is in our DNA. Earlier this year, we extended that philosophy to cost management by &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/02/simple-cloud-cost-management-grafana-labs-integrates-open-standard-focus-specification-for-cloud-billing-data/&#34;&gt;adopting the FinOps Open Cost and Usage Specification (FOCUS)&lt;/a&gt;, a community-driven, open specification that standardizes cost and usage data across cloud vendors to reduce complexity for FinOps practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Supported by the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.finops.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;FinOps Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, which is a project of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linuxfoundation.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;The Linux Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://focus.finops.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;FOCUS&lt;/a&gt; is designed to give organizations a consistent, vendor-neutral way to understand and analyze their cloud costs. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Access to standardized usage and cost data makes it easier for Grafana Cloud users to integrate their billing data into existing FinOps reporting, and to proactively identify optimization opportunities across their observability workloads. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“As FinOps is being applied to new scopes, especially to software as a service, a unifying billing format is becoming essential for streamlined cost management,&amp;quot; said Lorant Kiss, Senior FinOps Manager at Delivery Hero. “Grafana Labs’ adoption of the open source FOCUS billing specification will enable incremental efficiency gains via more timely, detailed, and standardized cost information.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FOCUS billing data is currently available in private preview in Grafana Cloud. If you’d like early access, please complete this &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/bLu5y6X9Gy7jtbnCA&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;FOCUS interest form&lt;/a&gt; or talk to your Grafana Labs account representative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-tools-and-tips-to-optimize-grafana-cloud-costs&#34;&gt;Other tools and tips to optimize Grafana Cloud costs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the new features outlined above, here are some other tools and practices you can use to control observability costs as you scale:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/simplified-exploration/profiles/concepts/what-is-profiling/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Continuous profiling&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Continuous profiling tools, like &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/profiles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Profiles&lt;/a&gt;, provide code-level visibility to identify performance bottlenecks, optimize resource use, and reduce infrastructure costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/kubernetes-monitoring/manage-costs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#cost-overview&#34;&gt;Cost Overview tab in Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Providing a detailed view of your total compute costs, average cost per pod, and average pod count, the Cost Overview tab in &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/a&gt; gives you greater control over your Kubernetes infrastructure spending.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visibility into&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/understand-usage-cost/metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#data-points-per-minute-billing&#34;&gt;data points per minute (DPM)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: DPM helps you understand how much data you’re sending to Grafana Cloud — and whether it’s more than you need. Here are &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/11/data-points-per-minute-in-grafana-cloud-what-you-need-to-know-about-dpm/&#34;&gt;some best practices&lt;/a&gt; for investigating and reducing high DPM. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;可观察性的好处是显而易见的：深入了解系统运行状况、更快地排除故障以及提高可靠性（仅举几例）。但同样清楚的是，随着组织扩展和发展其可观察性策略，他们需要一种方法来利用这些好处而不失失控的成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据 &lt;a href=&#34;/observability-survey/2025/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs 2025 年可观测性调查&lt;/a&gt;，74% 的受访者表示成本是选择工具的首要考虑因素。另一项&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/06/the-observability-maturity-curve-how-it-leaders-are-shifting-from-tools-to-outcomes/&#34;&gt;对 150 名 IT 高管进行的调查&lt;/a&gt;发现，41% 的组织在过去一年中增加了可观察性支出，其中 55% 的组织预测他们的支出将在未来 12 个月内继续增长。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;认识到这一挑战，我们一直在探索新方法来帮助我们的用户管理和优化 Grafana Cloud 中的可观测性成本。 Grafana Labs 首席技术官 Tom Wilkie 表示，这意味着使用技术来积极减少账单并放弃“明智的定价”。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们是少数（即使不是唯一）真正优先考虑这一问题的可观测性公司之一，”Wilkie 在本月的&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2025/keynote/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025 主题演讲&lt;/a&gt;中说道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从集中式成本管理应用程序到我们的端到端自适应遥测套件，以下是我们最近推出的一些 Grafana Cloud 功能，可帮助您控制和优化成本，特别是在您的可观测性策略扩展时。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;reduce-costs-and-noise-across-all-observability-pillars-adaptive-telemetry&#34;&gt;降低所有可观测性支柱的成本和噪音：自适应遥测&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可观测性成本不断膨胀的一个常见罪魁祸首是存储大量且通常是不必要的遥测数据。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“可观测性成本和遥测数据量确实呈指数级增长，”威尔基说。 “常见的 80/20 规则适用：您实际上并没有使用发送到可观测系统的 80% 的数据。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;引入&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/&#34;&gt;自适应遥测&lt;/a&gt;，这是 Grafana Cloud 中的一套功能，旨在通过确保仅提供最有价值的遥测、涵盖指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件来优化可观测性数据和成本， 被存储并浮出水面。它使用智能分类和优先级技术来分析遥测的使用方式，然后自动建议聚合、采样、删除或减少低价值数据等操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该套件从自适应指标和自适应日志开始，截至本月，现在包括&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;自适应跟踪和自适应配置文件&lt;/a&gt;。这意味着 Grafana Cloud 用户可以扩展跨端到端可观测性堆栈的自适应模型。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“JJH7S-hdcNg”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JJH7S-hdcNg?autoplay=1&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是对每个功能的详细介绍：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;（一般可用性）&lt;/strong&gt;：通过聚合帮助您识别和消除未使用或部分使用的时间序列数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应日志&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;（一般可用性）&lt;/strong&gt;：通过自动识别和删除低价值日志来减少日志量和相关成本 很少或从未使用过。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应跟踪&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;（一般可用性）&lt;/strong&gt;：使用尾部采样自动识别和保留最有价值的跟踪，确保您获得关键性能 您需要的见解（而不是您不需要的见解）。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应配置文件&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;（私有预览版）&lt;/strong&gt;：根据工作负载行为动态调整数据收集，使您能够在整个基础架构中更广泛地部署连续分析，而不会产生任何影响 成本过高。 （有兴趣加入自适应配置文件私人预览版吗？请填写&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeIFky5ut3g3tvhIOApTqV1yyuZ6i0Cv_Vg2G0wTbS6r98elQ/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;此表格&lt;/a&gt;，我们会与您联系。）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;到目前为止，我们的用户&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/12/why-companies-choose-adaptive-metrics-and-how-they-save-time-and-a-lot-of-money/&#34;&gt;已经通过自适应遥测看到了一些非常强大的结果&lt;/a&gt;，从减少警报疲劳到显着降低存储和处理成本。例如，平均而言，使用自适应指标的组织&lt;strong&gt;遥测成本降低了 30%-50%&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要详细了解自适应遥测及其工作原理，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;技术文档&lt;/a&gt;和此&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dz5XLSPTpWA&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;概述视频&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;centralized-control-of-your-observability-spend-cost-management-and-billing-app&#34;&gt;集中控制您的可观察性支出：成本管理和计费应用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当组织中的多个团队生成遥测数据时，可能很难确切地知道谁负责成本 - 而且更难以全面了解您的总支出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借助 Grafana Cloud 中的成本管理和计费应用，您可以全面、集中地了解 Grafana Cloud 使用情况和支出，以便您可以控制可观察性预算。它可以通过提供总体支出透明度以及跨部门和团队建立成本问责制来帮助巩固组织的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/06/why-observability-needs-finops-and-vice-versa-the-vantage-integration-with-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;FinOps 战略&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;alt=&#34;成本管理和计费应用程序中仪表板的屏幕截图，显示指标、日志和跟踪的每月成本以及详细的归因 故障。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;成本管理和计费应用程序中仪表板的屏幕截图，显示指标、日志和跟踪的每月成本以及详细的归因细分。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主要功能包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;成本归因&lt;/strong&gt;：按团队或项目等标签细分成本，以便更好地承担责任。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;基于使用情况的警报&lt;/strong&gt;：设置使用情况警报以及早检测峰值并防止意外收费。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;发票管理&lt;/strong&gt;：直接在应用中查看和下载每月发票。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;支出洞察&lt;/strong&gt;：跨指标、日志、跟踪和其他可观察性数据跟踪成本，全部集中在一处。比较逐月支出趋势，以确定变化并优化支出。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;成本管理和计费应用程序通常可在 Grafana Cloud 中使用。要了解更多信息，请访问我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/understand-usage-cost/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-existing-csp-discounts-and-credits-grafana-bring-your-own-cloud&#34;&gt;使用现有的 CSP 折扣和积分：Grafana 自带云&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们知道许多用户都拥有云服务提供商 (CSP) 的现有折扣和积分，并希望他们在使用 Grafana Cloud 时能够利用这些折扣。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana 自带云 (BYOC) 是一种部署选项，允许您通过在自己的 AWS 或 Google Cloud Platform (GCP) 帐户中运行 Grafana Cloud 来实现此目的（目前可根据具体情况提供 Azure 支持）。您直接支付基础设施账单，因此您可以利用与 CSP 协商的任何折扣、积分或承诺。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“当传统 SaaS 定价不再有意义时，BYOC 为超大规模客户提供了一种全新的经济模式，”Wilkie 说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了具有成本效益之外，Grafana BYOC 还具有以下优势：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据驻留&lt;/strong&gt;：所有 Grafana Cloud 服务都在您的帐户中运行，因此您知道所有可观测性数据也都保留在那里。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;托管服务&lt;/strong&gt;：我们的团队负责处理运营、扩展和升级，以便您的工程师可以专注于更重要的事情，例如交付业务价值。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;功能对等&lt;/strong&gt;：您可以从快速功能发布以及 Grafana Cloud 中的所有最新增强功能（包括在您的环境中运行的自适应遥测）中受益。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana BYOC 专为具有高遥测量和复杂可观测性需求的大型企业而设计。要了解更多信息，请访问我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/products/bring-your-own-cloud-byoc/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;BYOC 页面。&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;apply-open-standards-to-cloud-cost-management-the-focus-specification&#34;&gt;将开放标准应用于云成本管理：FOCUS 规范&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Grafana Labs，我们经常说开源已融入我们的 DNA。今年早些时候，我们通过&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/02/simple-cloud-cost-management-grafana-labs-integrates-open-standard-focus-specation-for-cloud-billing-data/&#34;&gt;采用 FinOps 开放成本和使用规范 (FOCUS)&lt;/a&gt; 将这一理念扩展到成本管理，这是一个社区驱动的开放规范，可标准化跨云的成本和使用数据 供应商降低 FinOps 从业者的复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.finops.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;FinOps 基金会&lt;/a&gt;支持，该基金会是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linuxfoundation.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;The Linux 基金会&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://focus.finops.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;FOCUS&lt;/a&gt; 旨在为组织提供一种一致的、供应商中立的方式来了解和分析其云成本。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过访问标准化使用情况和成本数据，Grafana Cloud 用户可以更轻松地将其计费数据集成到现有的 FinOps 报告中，并主动识别其可观察性工作负载的优化机会。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“随着 FinOps 被应用于新的领域，特别是软件即服务，统一的计费格式对于简化成本管理变得至关重要，”Delivery Hero 高级 FinOps 经理 Lorant Kiss 说道。 “Grafana Labs 采用开源 FOCUS 计费规范将通过更及时、详细和标准化的成本信息来提高效率。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FOCUS 账单数据目前可在私人预付款中获取在 Grafana 云中查看。如果您想提前访问，请填写此&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/bLu5y6X9Gy7jtbnCA&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;FOCUS 兴趣表&lt;/a&gt;或与您的 Grafana Labs 客户代表联系。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-tools-and-tips-to-optimize-grafana-cloud-costs&#34;&gt;优化 Grafana Cloud 成本的其他工具和技巧&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了上面概述的新功能之外，您还可以使用以下一些其他工具和实践来控制扩展时的可观测性成本：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/simplified-exploration/profiles/concepts/what-is-profiling/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;持续分析&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：持续分析工具，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/profiles/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud 配置文件&lt;/a&gt;，提供代码级可见性，以识别性能瓶颈、优化资源使用并降低基础设施成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/kubernetes-monitoring/manage-costs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt/#cost-overview&#34;&gt;Kubernetes 监控中的“成本概览”选项卡&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：提供总计算成本、每个 Pod 的平均成本和平均 Pod 数量的详细视图， &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/a&gt; 中的“成本概览”选项卡可让您更好地控制 Kubernetes 基础设施支出。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;了解&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/understand-usage-cost/metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt/#data-points-per-month-billing&#34;&gt;每分钟数据点 (DPM)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：DPM 可帮助您了解发送到 Grafana 的数据量 云——以及它是否超出您的需要。以下是用于调查和降低高 DPM 的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/11/data-points-per-minute-in-grafana-cloud-what-you-need-to-know-about-dpm/&#34;&gt;一些最佳实践&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A serverless approach to CI/CD observability with GitLab and Grafana】使用 GitLab 和 Grafana 实现 CI/CD 可观察性的无服务器方法</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/10/a-serverless-approach-to-ci-cd-observability-with-gitlab-and-grafana/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced development environment, it&amp;rsquo;s critical that you understand what&amp;rsquo;s happening in your CI/CD pipeline. And yet, many teams struggle with fragmented tooling that makes it difficult to get a holistic view of their dev lifecycle. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, if you&amp;rsquo;re using GitLab for CI/CD and Grafana for observability, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably faced this challenge: how do you bring your GitLab events into your existing observability and alerting infrastructure?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s exactly the problem I set out to solve when I created &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danifitz/gitlab-logs-grafana-loki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;lambda-gitlab-loki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;—a lightweight, serverless open source project that bridges GitLab webhooks with &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Logs&lt;/a&gt;, which is powered by &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt;, our open source log aggregation system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem-with-isolated-cicd-visibility&#34;&gt;The problem with isolated CI/CD visibility&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most development teams today use different tools for different aspects of their workflow. GitLab excels at source control and CI/CD, while Grafana provides unparalleled observability dashboards and alerting. However, these tools often operate in silos.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When issues arise, teams find themselves switching between multiple interfaces:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Checking GitLab for pipeline status&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Looking at application metrics in Grafana&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reviewing infrastructure logs in yet another tool&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manually correlating deployment events in Gitlab with performance changes in Grafana &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This fragmentation reduces visibility into your CI/CD pipeline trends and patterns and slows incident response because you can&amp;rsquo;t quickly correlate deployment events with system behavior. You&amp;rsquo;re also left making manual correlations between code changes and system metrics, and you&amp;rsquo;ll likely end up with alert fatigue from all these disconnected monitoring systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-unified-observability-bridges-the-gap&#34;&gt;How unified observability bridges the gap&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lambda-gitlab-loki leverages the strengths of both platforms while connecting them seamlessly. By using GitLab webhooks and Grafana Cloud, we can create a unified observability experience that provides a number of benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;real-time-pipeline-monitoring&#34;&gt;Real-time pipeline monitoring&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every GitLab event—from pushes and merge requests to pipeline completions and deployments—flows directly into Loki as structured logs. This means you can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Monitor pipeline success/failure rates in real-time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Track deployment frequency and timing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Correlate code changes with system performance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set up alerts for failed builds or unusual deployment patterns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;powerful-logql-queries&#34;&gt;Powerful LogQL queries&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With GitLab events stored in Grafana Cloud, you can use LogQL to slice and dice your CI/CD data:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;logql&#xA;sum by (project_name) (&#xA;count_over_time(&#xA;{job=&amp;#34;gitlab-webhook&amp;#34;}&#xA;| json&#xA;| object_kind=&amp;#34;pipeline&amp;#34;&#xA;| object_attributes_status=&amp;#34;success&amp;#34;[24h]&#xA;)&#xA;)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;contextual-dashboards&#34;&gt;Contextual dashboards&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also create Grafana dashboards that combine application metrics with CI/CD events. Imagine seeing:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Application response times with deployment markers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Error rates correlated with specific commits&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resource usage trends alongside release velocity&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Team productivity metrics derived from GitLab activity&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I chose AWS Lambda for this integration for several reasons:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost efficiency:&lt;/strong&gt; Most GitLab webhooks are infrequent events. With Lambda&amp;rsquo;s pay-per-execution model, you only pay for actual webhook processing. For typical development teams, this often means costs under $1 per month.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zero infrastructure management:&lt;/strong&gt; No servers to maintain, no scaling concerns, no security patches to apply. Lambda handles all the operational overhead, letting you focus on deriving insights from your data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Built-in reliability:&lt;/strong&gt; Lambda provides automatic retry logic, scaling, and monitoring. Your webhook processing becomes as reliable as AWS&amp;rsquo; infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easy Integration:&lt;/strong&gt; The serverless approach makes integration straightforward—just point your GitLab webhook at an API Gateway endpoint, and you&amp;rsquo;re done.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;improve-alerting-trend-analysis-incident-response-and-compliance&#34;&gt;Improve alerting, trend analysis, incident response, and compliance&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once your GitLab events flow into Grafana Cloud, a world of possibilities opens up:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advanced alerting:&lt;/strong&gt; Set up alerts in Grafana Alerting for pipelines that fail repeatedly, unusually long build times, deployment frequency dropping below thresholds, and specific types of GitLab events (like force pushes to main).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trend analysis:&lt;/strong&gt; Understand your development patterns, such as team activity, changes in deployment frequency, the busiest times of day for CI/CD activity, and variations in pipeline durations by project.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident response:&lt;/strong&gt; Quickly correlate data to resolve incidents faster. For example, you could combine data that pertains to when your last successful deployment was, which commits were included in your recent releases, which pipelines failed around the incident, and how current metrics compare to previous deployment periods.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance and reporting:&lt;/strong&gt; Generate reports on deployment frequency for audit purposes, change failure rates and recovery times, developer productivity metrics, release cadence across different projects, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-get-started&#34;&gt;How to get started&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The beauty of this approach lies in its simplicity. You can have GitLab events flowing into Grafana Cloud in under 30 minutes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;Deploy the Lambda function&lt;/strong&gt; with your Grafana Cloud credentials.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;Create an API Gateway&lt;/strong&gt; endpoint to receive webhooks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;Configure GitLab webhooks&lt;/strong&gt; to point to your endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;Start building dashboards&lt;/strong&gt; with your new GitLab data stream.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The entire solution consists of just 69 lines of Python code, yet it unlocks powerful observability capabilities that would otherwise require complex, expensive enterprise solutions. (You can find the full step-by-step instructions &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danifitz/gitlab-logs-grafana-loki?tab=readme-ov-file#setup&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: I recommend using Grafana Cloud with Lambda-gitlab-loki because you don&amp;rsquo;t have to manage any of the underlying infrastructure. We even have a generous &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;forever-free tier&lt;/a&gt;. However, the steps outlined here can be used with open source Loki, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned-and-the-future-of-cicd-observability&#34;&gt;Lessons learned, and the future of CI/CD observability&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Building this integration taught me several important lessons about modern observability:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webhooks are powerful:&lt;/strong&gt; GitLab&amp;rsquo;s webhook system is incredibly comprehensive, providing detailed payloads for virtually every action in your development workflow. This richness makes it an ideal data source for observability tools.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Structured logging wins:&lt;/strong&gt; By treating CI/CD events as structured logs rather than traditional metrics, we gain the flexibility to query and aggregate data in ways that weren&amp;rsquo;t predefined. Loki&amp;rsquo;s label-based approach makes this particularly powerful.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serverless fits perfectly:&lt;/strong&gt; Event-driven architectures like webhook processing are perfect fits for serverless computing. The natural mapping between webhooks and function invocations creates an elegant, scalable solution.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This integration represents a broader trend toward unified observability. As development teams adopt cloud-native practices, the lines between application monitoring, infrastructure observability, and CI/CD tracking continue to blur.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By connecting GitLab and Grafana, we&amp;rsquo;re not just solving a technical integration challenge—we&amp;rsquo;re enabling a more holistic approach to understanding our development process. When CI/CD events become first-class citizens in our observability stack, we can build more reliable systems, respond to incidents faster, and make data-driven decisions about our development practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;try-it-yourself&#34;&gt;Try it yourself&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re troubleshooting CI/CD issues, wanting better visibility into your development process, or looking to correlate deployments with system behavior, this open source project provides a solid foundation for CI/CD observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re ready to try it out, start small—set up the basic webhook integration and create a simple dashboard showing pipeline success rates. Then expand from there by adding alerts, correlating with application metrics, and building the solution your team needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The lambda-gitlab-loki project is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danifitz/gitlab-logs-grafana-loki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;available on GitHub&lt;/a&gt; with complete setup instructions, deployment guides, and example dashboards. Join the growing community of teams using Grafana and GitLab together for better CI/CD observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for more ways to use Grafana with GitLab, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-gitlab-datasource/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;enterprise plugin&lt;/a&gt; for tracking GitLab statistics or our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-gitlab/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;integration&lt;/a&gt; with pre-built alerts and a dashboard for monitoring GitLab. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在当今快节奏的开发环境中，了解 CI/CD 管道中发生的情况至关重要。然而，许多团队都在与分散的工具作斗争，这使得很难全面了解他们的开发生命周期。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，如果您使用 GitLab 进行 CI/CD 并使用 Grafana 进行可观察性，您可能会面临这样的挑战：如何将 GitLab 事件引入现有的可观察性和警报基础设施？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这正是我在创建&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danifitz/gitlab-logs-grafana-loki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;lambda-gitlab-loki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;时要解决的问题——一个连接 GitLab 的轻量级、无服务器开源项目 带有 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Logs&lt;/a&gt; 的 webhook，该日志由我们的开源日志聚合系统 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; 提供支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem-with-isolated-cicd-visibility&#34;&gt;隔离 CI/CD 可见性的问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如今，大多数开发团队针对工作流程的不同方面使用不同的工具。 GitLab 擅长源代码控制和 CI/CD，而 Grafana 提供无与伦比的可观察性仪表板和警报。然而，这些工具通常在孤岛中运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当问题出现时，团队发现自己在多个界面之间切换：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;检查 GitLab 的管道状态&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;查看 Grafana 中的应用指标&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在另一个工具中查看基础架构日志&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;手动将 Gitlab 中的部署事件与 Grafana 中的性能变化关联起来&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种碎片化降低了对 CI/CD 管道趋势和模式的可见性，并减慢了事件响应速度，因为您无法快速将部署事件与系统行为关联起来。您还需要在代码更改和系统指标之间进行手动关联，并且您可能最终会因所有这些断开连接的监控系统而感到警报疲劳。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-unified-observability-bridges-the-gap&#34;&gt;统一可观测性如何弥合差距&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lambda-gitlab-loki 利用两个平台的优势，同时无缝连接它们。通过使用 GitLab webhooks 和 Grafana Cloud，我们可以创建统一的可观察性体验，从而提供许多好处。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;real-time-pipeline-monitoring&#34;&gt;实时管道监控&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个 GitLab 事件（从推送和合并请求到管道完成和部署）都会作为结构化日志直接流入 Loki。这意味着您可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;实时监控管道成功/失败率&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;跟踪部署频率和时间&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将代码更改与系统性能关联起来&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;为失败的构建或异常部署模式设置警报&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;powerful-logql-queries&#34;&gt;强大的 LogQL 查询&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;W通过存储在 Grafana Cloud 中的 GitLab 事件，您可以使用 LogQL 对 CI/CD 数据进行切片和切块：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;logql&#xA;总和（项目名称）（&#xA;计数时间（&#xA;{job=&#34;gitlab-webhook&#34;}&#xA;| json&#xA;| object_kind=“管道”&#xA;| object_attributes_status=&#34;成功&#34;[24h]&#xA;）&#xA;）&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;contextual-dashboards&#34;&gt;上下文仪表板&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您还可以创建将应用程序指标与 CI/CD 事件相结合的 Grafana 仪表板。想象一下看到：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;带有部署标记的应用响应时间&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;错误率与特定提交相关&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;资源使用趋势与发布速度&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;源自 GitLab 活动的团队生产力指标&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我选择 AWS Lambda 进行此集成有几个原因：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;成本效率&lt;/strong&gt;：大多数 GitLab Webhook 都是不常见的事件。通过 Lambda 的按执行付费模型，您只需为实际的 Webhook 处理付费。对于典型的开发团队来说，这通常意味着每月的成本低于 1 美元。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;零基础设施管理：&lt;/strong&gt;无需维护服务器，无需考虑扩展问题，无需应用安全补丁。 Lambda 处理所有运营开销，让您能够专注于从数据中获取见解。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;内置可靠性&lt;/strong&gt;：Lambda 提供自动重试逻辑、扩展和监控。您的 Webhook 处理变得与 AWS 基础设施一样可靠。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;轻松集成：&lt;/strong&gt;无服务器方法使集成变得简单 - 只需将您的 GitLab Webhook 指向 API 网关端点即可完成。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;improve-alerting-trend-analysis-incident-response-and-compliance&#34;&gt;改进警报、趋势分析、事件响应和合规性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦您的 GitLab 事件流入 Grafana Cloud，就会打开一个充满可能性的世界：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;高级警报&lt;/strong&gt;：在 Grafana Alerting 中针对重复失败、构建时间异常长、部署频率低于阈值以及特定类型的 GitLab 事件（例如强制推送到主线程）的管道设置警报。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;趋势分析&lt;/strong&gt;：了解您的开发模式，例如团队活动、部署频率的变化、CI/CD 活动一天中最繁忙的时间以及项目的管道持续时间的变化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;事件响应&lt;/strong&gt;：快速关联数据以更快地解决事件。例如，您可以合并与您上次登录时间相关的数据成功的部署是，哪些提交包含在您最近的版本中，哪些管道因事件而失败，以及当前指标与之前的部署周期相比如何。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;合规性和报告：&lt;/strong&gt;生成有关用于审计目的的部署频率、更改故障率和恢复时间、开发人员生产力指标、不同项目的发布节奏等的报告。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-get-started&#34;&gt;如何开始&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种方法的优点在于它的简单性。您可以在 30 分钟内让 GitLab 事件流入 Grafana Cloud：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.使用您的 Grafana Cloud 凭据&lt;strong&gt;部署 Lambda 函数&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;创建 API 网关&lt;/strong&gt;端点以接收 Webhook。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;配置 GitLab webhooks&lt;/strong&gt; 以指向您的端点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4.使用新的 GitLab 数据流&lt;strong&gt;开始构建仪表板&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;整个解决方案仅由 69 行 Python 代码组成，但却释放了强大的可观察功能，否则需要复杂、昂贵的企业解决方案。 （您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danifitz/gitlab-logs-grafana-loki?tab=readme-ov-file#setup&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;找到完整的分步说明。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意：我建议将 Grafana Cloud 与 Lambda-gitlab-loki 结合使用，因为您无需管理任何底层基础设施。我们甚至还提供慷慨的&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;永久免费套餐&lt;/a&gt;。但是，此处概述的步骤也可以与开源 Loki 一起使用。 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lessons-learned-and-the-future-of-cicd-observability&#34;&gt;经验教训以及 CI/CD 可观察性的未来&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;构建这种集成教会了我关于现代可观察性的几个重要教训：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webhook 功能强大：&lt;/strong&gt;GitLab 的 Webhook 系统非常全面，几乎可以为开发工作流程中的每个操作提供详细的有效负载。这种丰富性使其成为可观察性工具的理想数据源。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;结构化日志记录的胜利：&lt;/strong&gt;通过将 CI/CD 事件视为结构化日志而不是传统指标，我们可以灵活地以未预定义的方式查询和聚合数据。 Loki 基于标签的方法使其特别强大。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;无服务器完美契合&lt;/strong&gt;：Webhook 处理等事件驱动架构非常适合无服务器计算。 Webhook 和函数调用之间的自然映射创建了一个优雅的、可扩展的解决方案。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种集成代表了统一可观测性的更广泛趋势。随着开发团队采用云原生实践，应用程序监控、基础设施可观察性和 CI/CD 跟踪之间的界限继续模糊。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过连接 GitLab 和 Grafana，我们不仅仅是解决技术集成挑战，我们还提供一种更全面的方法来理解我们的开发流程。当 CI/CD 事件成为我们的可观察性堆栈中的一等公民时，我们可以构建更可靠的系统，更快地响应事件，并就我们的开发实践做出数据驱动的决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;try-it-yourself&#34;&gt;亲自尝试一下&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是在解决 CI/CD 问题、希望更好地了解开发流程，还是希望将部署与系统行为关联起来，这个开源项目都为 CI/CD 可观察性提供了坚实的基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您准备好尝试，请从小处开始 - 设置基本的 Webhook 集成并创建一个简单的仪表板来显示管道成功率。然后通过添加警报、与应用程序指标关联以及构建团队所需的解决方案来进行扩展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;lambda-gitlab-loki 项目&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/danifitz/gitlab-logs-grafana-loki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;可在 GitHub 上获取&lt;/a&gt;，其中包含完整的设置说明、部署指南和示例仪表板。加入不断增长的团队社区，同时使用 Grafana 和 GitLab，以实现更好的 CI/CD 可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您正在寻找将 Grafana 与 GitLab 结合使用的更多方法，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-gitlab-datasource/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;企业插件&lt;/a&gt;，用于跟踪 GitLab 统计信息或我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/integrations/integration-reference/integration-gitlab/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;与预构建警报和用于监控 GitLab 的仪表板集成&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maximize data value and cut costs: Adaptive Telemetry for metrics, logs, traces, and profiles in Grafana Cloud】最大化数据价值并降低成本：Grafana Cloud 中指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件的自适应遥测</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When it comes to observability, more data doesn’t always mean more clarity. In fact, as telemetry volumes grow, it only becomes more difficult to discern the signals from the noise and to keep overall costs in check.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is exactly why we built &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/&#34;&gt;Adaptive Telemetry,&lt;/a&gt; a suite of features in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; that analyzes how your telemetry is used and then automatically recommends actions like aggregating, sampling, dropping, or reducing low-value data. You can easily pinpoint the critical signals you need to keep your systems running smoothly, while reducing observability costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our Adaptive Telemetry suite started with &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Logs&lt;/a&gt; — and our users have seen some pretty incredible results from both of these solutions, from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wz2a4hxt2c4&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;improved productivity&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZGquwsXt1C0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;reducing their observability costs by 50%&lt;/a&gt; (without losing visibility).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, at &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt;, we’re excited to share that our Adaptive Telemetry suite is evolving, with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Traces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;now generally available&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Profiles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;in private preview&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this end-to-end Adaptive Telemetry suite, you can extend the benefits of the adaptive model across all core pillars of your observability strategy, ensuring every piece of telemetry you store is truly worth the investment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;adaptive-traces-retain-only-your-most-valuable-traces&#34;&gt;Adaptive Traces: Retain only your most valuable traces &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In modern distributed systems, tracing provides visibility into how requests move across services, exposing bottlenecks and interdependencies. But once tracing expands beyond a few services, costs rise, dashboards grow noisy, and teams often abandon the practice altogether — not due to lack of value, but because successful requests generate large volumes of redundant data that’s expensive to store.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, there’s a better way. With Adaptive Traces in Grafana Cloud, you can ensure that only valuable traces, such as those with errors, high latency, or other critical signals, are stored, leading to faster insights and optimized costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Before Adaptive Tracing, we had two bad options: send everything and blow our budget, or send so little we couldn’t get meaningful insight,” said Geoff Schultz, Manager, Infrastructure Engineering at Auditboard. “Now tracing is actually usable — we can dial sampling up or down as needed, keep costs in check, and still give teams the visibility they need.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Traces achieves this using &lt;strong&gt;tail sampling&lt;/strong&gt;, a technique where the decision to sample (aka, keep) or drop a trace is made after collecting all or most of its spans, rather than at the start of the trace. This allows for light sampling during normal operations, and then more targeted retention when issues arise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;custom-policy-management-for-fine-grained-control&#34;&gt;Custom policy management for fine-grained control&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Traces offers out-of-the-box recommendations, while also allowing you to &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/create-policies/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;define flexible and customizable sampling policies&lt;/a&gt; to capture only the tracing data you need. For example, you might configure rules to ingest all traces with an error status from a particular service, or to capture a random 5% of traces from another.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1722x706/5f2b9fb513/adaptive-traces-policies.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1722x706/5f2b9fb513/adaptive-traces-policies.png&#34;alt=&#34;Flowchart showing recommendations and policies for trace capturing, including probabilistic sampling, status code, and latency-based sampling.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1722x706/5f2b9fb513/adaptive-traces-policies.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Flowchart showing recommendations and policies for trace capturing, including probabilistic sampling, status code, and latency-based sampling.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By automatically filtering out noise while retaining the traces that matter most, Adaptive Traces allows you to debug more effectively and get deeper, more meaningful insights into system performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;anomaly-detection-to-capture-traces-of-interest&#34;&gt;Anomaly detection to capture traces of interest &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Traces’ &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/manage-recommendations/investigate-anomalies/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;anomaly detection feature&lt;/a&gt; automatically identifies anomalies in your tracing data, and then adjusts sampling decisions and policies on-the-fly, based on those observed anomalies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To do this, Adaptive Traces analyzes your past data to establish a baseline for “normal” system behavior, such as the typical latency for a specific database query. It then monitors incoming traces for significant changes, like a latency spike, from that established baseline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/1a1ecffd85/adaptive-traces-anomaly-detection.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/1a1ecffd85/adaptive-traces-anomaly-detection.png&#34;alt=&#34;A diagram depicting the anomaly detection feature in Adaptive Traces, including graphs of span latency and sampled traces per minute for HTTP GET requests.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/1a1ecffd85/adaptive-traces-anomaly-detection.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A diagram depicting the anomaly detection feature in Adaptive Traces, including graphs of span latency and sampled traces per minute for HTTP GET requests.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When a trace is identified as an anomaly, it’s retained rather than dropped, helping you more easily identify issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;closed-loop-investigations-with-traces-drilldown&#34;&gt;Closed-loop investigations with Traces Drilldown &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Traces &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/manage-recommendations/investigate-anomalies/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#drilldown-and-analysis&#34;&gt;now integrates&lt;/a&gt; directly with &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/08/traces-drilldown-generally-available/&#34;&gt;Grafana Traces Drilldown&lt;/a&gt;, an application within our broader &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/20/grafana-drilldown-apps-the-improved-queryless-experience-formerly-known-as-the-explore-apps/&#34;&gt;Grafana Drilldown suite&lt;/a&gt; that allows you to quickly investigate and visualize your tracing data through a simplified, queryless experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When an anomaly is detected, click &lt;strong&gt;Drilldown&lt;/strong&gt; within the anomaly policy view to instantly jump to relevant traces within the time range the issue occurred. This provides a closed-loop investigative workflow that allows you to quickly find root causes and reduce time to recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1784x605/9a7ae43a32/adaptive-traces-drilldown.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1784x605/9a7ae43a32/adaptive-traces-drilldown.png&#34;alt=&#34;An interface showing a list of HTTP trace data with columns for start time, service, duration, and trace details.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1784x605/9a7ae43a32/adaptive-traces-drilldown.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;An interface showing a list of HTTP trace data with columns for start time, service, duration, and trace details.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;adaptive-profiles-the-power-of-continuous-profiling-without-runaway-costs&#34;&gt;Adaptive Profiles: The power of continuous profiling without runaway costs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/09/30/how-to-boost-observability-roi-with-continuous-profiling-and-grafana-drilldown/&#34;&gt;Continuous profiling&lt;/a&gt; is a critical piece of any observability strategy, providing deep insights into how your application uses resources, like CPU and memory, in production. Because data is collected continuously, you get a holistic and uninterrupted view of your application&amp;rsquo;s behavior over time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And now, with Adaptive Profiles, teams can deploy continuous profiling more broadly across their infrastructure, maximizing the value of their data without the risk of cost overruns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Profiles dynamically adjusts the detail and frequency of data collection based on workload behavior, then generates insights to help your developers optimize their services’ performance and cost. It ensures you capture critical, high-resolution data to generate performance insights when you need them, and then reduces data to a cost-effective baseline during normal operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To try Adaptive Profiles in Grafana Cloud, please fill out this &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeIFky5ut3g3tvhIOApTqV1yyuZ6i0Cv_Vg2G0wTbS6r98elQ/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;private preview interest form.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;rounding-out-the-suite-adaptive-metrics-and-adaptive-logs&#34;&gt;Rounding out the suite: Adaptive Metrics and Adaptive Logs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Traces and Adaptive Profiles can work alongside two other powerful features in Grafana Cloud — &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/12/why-companies-choose-adaptive-metrics-and-how-they-save-time-and-a-lot-of-money/&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/24/introducing-adaptive-logs/&#34;&gt;Adaptive Logs&lt;/a&gt; — to help you filter out noise and reduce observability costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Metrics continuously analyzes how your metrics are being used across dashboards, alerts, recording rules, and queries, and provides recommendations for aggregating underutilized metrics into lower-cardinality versions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Logs, meanwhile, is a cost optimization feature that analyzes log data at scale, identifies commonly ingested log patterns, and generates customized recommendations for dropping unused or low-value logs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about both features, and how they’ve benefitted our users, in &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/#get-the-most-from-your-logs-and-metrics&#34;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started-with-adaptive-telemetry-today&#34;&gt;Get started with Adaptive Telemetry today&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can easily get started today with Adaptive Traces, Adaptive Logs, and Adaptive Metrics in all tiers of Grafana Cloud, including in our &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;free tier&lt;/a&gt;. Simply navigate to &lt;strong&gt;Adaptive Telemetry&lt;/strong&gt; within the Grafana Cloud UI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in the Adaptive Profiles private preview, please complete &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeIFky5ut3g3tvhIOApTqV1yyuZ6i0Cv_Vg2G0wTbS6r98elQ/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this form&lt;/a&gt; and we’ll be in touch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To read all the news from ObservabilityCON 2025, check out our&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/observabilitycon-2025-announcements/&#34;&gt;blog post recapping all the big announcements!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;faq-adaptive-telemetry-in-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;FAQ: Adaptive Telemetry in Grafana Cloud&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Adaptive Telemetry?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Telemetry is a suite of features in Grafana Cloud designed to optimize observability data by ensuring that only the most valuable telemetry — such as metrics, logs, traces, and profiles — is stored and surfaced. It uses intelligent classification and prioritization techniques to analyze how telemetry is used (e.g., in dashboards, alerts, or queries) and then automatically recommends actions like aggregating, sampling, dropping, or reducing low-value data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This approach helps organizations filter out noise, reduce costs, and maintain the insights needed for effective monitoring and troubleshooting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is included in the Adaptive Telemetry suite?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Adaptive Telemetry suite in Grafana Cloud consists of four features, spanning all core pillars of observability:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Helps you identify and eliminate unused or partially used time series data through aggregation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Logs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Reduces log volume and associated costs by automatically identifying and removing low-value logs that are rarely or never used.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Traces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Uses tail sampling to automatically identify and retain your most valuable traces, ensuring you get the critical performance insights you need.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Profiles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Dynamically adjusts data collection based on workload behavior, allowing you to deploy continuous profiling more broadly across your infrastructure without incurring excessive costs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the key benefits of Adaptive Telemetry?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Telemetry is especially beneficial for high-cardinality and dynamic environments, helping teams maintain visibility while controlling costs. Here are some of the highlights:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keeping only what’s valuable&lt;/strong&gt;: Adaptive Telemetry classifies telemetry based on actual usage, system behavior, and human inputs, prioritizing signals that power alerts, dashboards, or are frequently queried, while identifying and optimizing away less useful data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost and noise reduction&lt;/strong&gt;: By focusing on valuable telemetry, Adaptive Telemetry reduces alert fatigue and significantly lowers storage and processing costs. For example, on average, organizations using Adaptive Metrics see a &lt;strong&gt;30% - 50% reduction in telemetry costs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated and flexible optimization&lt;/strong&gt;: The system continuously learns from usage patterns and adapts its recommendations. You can review and implement optimizations in minutes based on your requirements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fine-grained control&lt;/strong&gt;: With features like &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/create-exemptions/&#34;&gt;exemptions in Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt;, you can be sure critical data and signals are always retained.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where can I learn more about Adaptive Telemetry?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can learn more about Adaptive Telemetry in our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt;, this &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;, and this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dz5XLSPTpWA&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;overview video&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;就可观察性而言，更多数据并不总是意味着更清晰。事实上，随着遥测量的增长，从噪声中辨别信号并控制总体成本只会变得更加困难。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这正是我们在 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 中构建&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/&#34;&gt;自适应遥测&lt;/a&gt;功能的原因 分析遥测数据的使用方式，然后自动建议聚合、采样、删除或减少低价值数据等操作。您可以轻松查明保持系统平稳运行所需的关键信号，同时降低可观测性成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的自适应遥测套件始于&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应日志&lt;/a&gt; - 我们的用户已经从这两种解决方案中看到了一些非常令人难以置信的结果，来自 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wz2a4hxt2c4&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;提高工作效率&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZGquwsXt1C0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;将可观察性成本降低 50%&lt;/a&gt;（不失去可见性）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，在 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; 上，我们很高兴与大家分享，我们的自适应遥测套件正在不断发展，&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应跟踪&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;现在普遍可用&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应配置文件&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;私人预览版&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借助这款端到端自适应遥测套件，您可以将自适应模型的优势扩展到可观测性策略的所有核心支柱，确保您存储的每一项遥测数据都真正值得投资。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;adaptive-traces-retain-only-your-most-valuable-traces&#34;&gt;自适应痕迹：仅保留最有价值的痕迹&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在现代分布式系统中，跟踪可以让您了解请求如何跨服务移动，从而暴露瓶颈和相互依赖关系。但是，一旦跟踪扩展到少数服务之外，成本就会上升，仪表板会变得嘈杂，团队通常会完全放弃这种做法 - 不是因为缺乏价值，而是因为成功的请求会生成大量冗余数据，而这些数据的存储成本很高。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;幸运的是，有更好的方法。借助 Grafana Cloud 中的自适应跟踪，您可以确保仅有价值的跟踪，例如那些存在错误、高延迟或其他关键信号的跟踪存储，从而更快地获得洞察并优化成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“在自适应跟踪之前，我们有两个糟糕的选择：发送所有内容并超出我们的预算，或者发送太少，我们无法获得有意义的见解，”Auditboard 基础设施工程经理 Geoff Schultz 说道。 “现在跟踪实际上是可用的 - 我们可以根据需要向上或向下调整采样，控制成本，并且仍然为团队提供他们所需的可见性。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应跟踪使用&lt;strong&gt;尾部采样&lt;/strong&gt;来实现这一点，这是一种技术，在收集所有或大部分跨度之后而不是在跟踪开始时做出采样（也称为保留）或删除跟踪的决定。这样可以在正常操作期间进行光采样，然后在出现问题时进行更有针对性的保留。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;custom-policy-management-for-fine-grained-control&#34;&gt;用于细粒度控制的自定义策略管理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应跟踪提供开箱即用的建议，同时还允许您&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/create-policies/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;定义灵活且可自定义的采样策略&lt;/a&gt;以仅捕获您需要的跟踪数据。例如，您可以配置规则以从特定服务中提取所有具有错误状态的跟踪，或者从另一个服务中捕获随机 5% 的跟踪。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1722x706/5f2b9fb513/adaptive-traces-policies.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1722x706/5f2b9fb513/adaptive-traces-policies.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示跟踪捕获的建议和策略的流程图，包括概率采样、状态代码和基于延迟的采样。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1722x706/5f2b9fb513/adaptive-traces-policies.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示跟踪捕获的建议和策略的流程图，包括概率采样、状态代码和基于延迟的采样。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过自动滤除噪音，同时保留最重要的跟踪，自适应跟踪使您能够更有效地进行调试，并对系统性能获得更深入、更有意义的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;anomaly-detection-to-capture-traces-of-interest&#34;&gt;异常检测以捕获感兴趣的痕迹&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Traces 的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/manage-recommendations/investigate-anomalies/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;异常检测功能&lt;/a&gt;会自动识别跟踪数据中的异常情况，然后即时调整采样决策和策略， 基于那些观察到的异常。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为此，Adaptive Traces 会分析您过去的数据以建立一个数据库seline 用于“正常”系统行为，例如特定数据库查询的典型延迟。然后，它会监控传入跟踪是否存在与已建立的基线相比的重大变化，例如延迟峰值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/1a1ecffd85/adaptive-traces-anomaly-detection.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/1a1ecffd85/adaptive-traces-anomaly-detection.png&#34;alt=&#34;描述自适应跟踪中的异常检测功能的图表，包括 HTTP GET 请求的跨度延迟和每分钟采样跟踪的图表。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/1a1ecffd85/adaptive-traces-anomaly-detection.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;描述自适应跟踪中的异常检测功能的图表，包括 HTTP GET 请求的跨度延迟和每分钟采样跟踪的图表。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当跟踪被识别为异常时，它会被保留而不是被删除，从而帮助您更轻松地识别问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;close-loop-investigations-with-traces-drilldown&#34;&gt;通过跟踪深入进行闭环调查&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应跟踪&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/manage-recommendations/investigate-anomalies/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt/#drilldown-and-analysis&#34;&gt;现在直接与&lt;a集成&lt;/a&gt; href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/08/traces-drilldown-generally-available/&#34;&gt;Grafana Traces Drilldown&lt;/a&gt;，我们更广泛的 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/20/grafana-drilldown-apps-the-improved-queryless-experience-known-as-the-explore-apps/&#34;&gt;Grafana 中的应用程序 深入分析套件&lt;/a&gt;可让您通过简化的无查询体验快速调查和可视化跟踪数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当检测到异常时，点击异常策略视图中的&lt;strong&gt;深入分析&lt;/strong&gt;即可立即跳转到问题发生时间范围内的相关跟踪。这提供了闭环调查工作流程，使您能够快速找到根本原因并缩短恢复时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1784x605/9a7ae43a32/adaptive-traces-drilldown.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1784x605/9a7ae43a32/adaptive-traces-drilldown.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示 HTTP 跟踪数据列表的界面，其中包含开始时间、服务、持续时间和跟踪详细信息的列。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1784x605/9a7ae43a32/adaptive-traces-drilldown.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示 HTTP 跟踪数据列表的界面，其中包含开始时间、服务、持续时间和跟踪详细信息的列。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;adaptive-profiles-the-power-of-continuous-profiling-without-runaway-costs&#34;&gt;自适应配置文件：持续分析的强大功能，无需失控成本&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/09/30/how-to-boost-observability-roi-with-continuous-profiling-and-grafana-drilldown/&#34;&gt;持续分析&lt;/a&gt;是任何可观察性策略的关键部分，可以深入了解应用程序在生产中如何使用资源（例如 CPU 和内存）。由于数据是连续收集的，因此您可以全面、不间断地了解应用程序随时间的行为。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，借助自适应配置文件，团队可以在其基础架构中更广泛地部署连续分析，从而最大限度地提高数据价值，而无需承担成本超支的风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应配置文件根据工作负载行为动态调整数据收集的细节和频率，然后生成见解以帮助您的开发人员优化其服务的性能和成本。它可确保您捕获关键的高分辨率数据，以便在需要时生成性能见解，然后在正常操作期间将数据减少到具有成本效益的基线。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要在 Grafana Cloud 中尝试自适应配置文件，请填写此&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeIFky5ut3g3tvhIOApTqV1yyuZ6i0Cv_Vg2G0wTbS6r98elQ/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;私人预览兴趣表。&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;rounding-out-the-suite-adaptive-metrics-and-adaptive-logs&#34;&gt;完善套件：自适应指标和自适应日志&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应跟踪和自适应配置文件可以与 Grafana Cloud 中的另外两个强大功能一起使用 - &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/12/why-companies-choose-adaptive-metrics-and-how-they-save-time-and-a-lot-of-money/&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/24/introducing-adaptive-logs/&#34;&gt;自适应日志&lt;/a&gt; - 帮助您过滤噪音并降低可观察性成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应指标持续分析您的指标在仪表板、警报、记录规则和查询中的使用情况，并提供将未充分利用的指标聚合到较低基数版本中的建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同时，自适应日志是一项成本优化功能，可大规模分析日志数据、识别常见摄取的日志模式，并生成删除未使用或低价值日志的定制建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/#get-the-most-from-your-logs-and-metrics&#34;&gt;这篇博文&lt;/a&gt;中详细了解这两项功能以及它们如何使我们的用户受益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started-with-adaptive-telemetry-today&#34;&gt;立即开始使用自适应遥测&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您今天就可以轻松开始使用 Adaptive Traces、Adaptive LGrafana Cloud 所有层级中的 ogs 和自适应指标，包括我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;免费层级&lt;/a&gt;。只需导航到 Grafana Cloud UI 中的&lt;strong&gt;自适应遥测&lt;/strong&gt;即可。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您对自适应配置文件私人预览版感兴趣，请填写&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeIFky5ut3g3tvhIOApTqV1yyuZ6i0Cv_Vg2G0wTbS6r98elQ/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;此表格&lt;/a&gt;，我们会与您联系。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;要阅读 ObservabilityCON 2025 的所有新闻&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/observabilitycon-2025-announcements/&#34;&gt;博客文章回顾了所有重大公告！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;faq-adaptive-telemetry-in-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;常见问题解答：Grafana Cloud 中的自适应遥测&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是自适应遥测？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应遥测是 Grafana Cloud 中的一套功能，旨在通过确保仅存储和显示最有价值的遥测（例如指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件）来优化可观测性数据。它使用智能分类和优先级技术来分析遥测的使用方式（例如，在仪表板、警报或查询中），然后自动建议聚合、采样、删除或减少低价值数据等操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种方法可以帮助组织过滤噪音、降低成本并保持有效监控和故障排除所需的洞察力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自适应遥测套件包含哪些内容？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 中的自适应遥测套件包含四个功能，涵盖可观测性的所有核心支柱：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：帮助您通过聚合识别和消除未使用或部分使用的时间序列数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应日志&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：通过自动识别和删除很少或从未使用的低价值日志，减少日志量和相关成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应跟踪&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：使用尾部采样自动识别和保留最有价值的跟踪，确保您获得所需的关键性能洞察。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应配置文件&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：根据工作负载行为动态调整数据收集，使您能够在整个基础架构中更广泛地部署连续分析，而不会产生过多成本。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自适应遥测的主要优点是什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应电话emetry 对于高基数和动态环境特别有益，可以帮助团队在控制成本的同时保持可见性。以下是一些亮点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;仅保留有价值的内容&lt;/strong&gt;：自适应遥测根据实际使用情况、系统行为和人工输入对遥测进行分类，优先考虑为警报、仪表板或频繁查询提供动力的信号，同时识别和优化不太有用的数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;降低成本和噪音&lt;/strong&gt;：通过专注于有价值的遥测，自适应遥测可减少警报疲劳并显着降低存储和处理成本。例如，平均而言，使用自适应指标的组织的遥测成本&lt;strong&gt;降低了 30% - 50%。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自动且灵活的优化&lt;/strong&gt;：系统不断从使用模式中学习并调整其建议。您可以根据自己的要求在几分钟内查看并实施优化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;细粒度控制&lt;/strong&gt;：借助&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/create-exemptions/&#34;&gt;自适应指标中的豁免&lt;/a&gt;等功能，您可以确保始终保留关键数据和信号。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在哪里可以了解有关自适应遥测的更多信息？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/&#34;&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;（此&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/&#34;&gt;博客）中了解有关自适应遥测的更多信息 帖子&lt;/a&gt;，以及这个&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Dz5XLSPTpWA&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;概述视频&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI-powered observability: Resolve incidents faster, reduce alert fatigue, and expand access】AI 支持的可观察性：更快地解决事件、减少警报疲劳并扩大访问范围</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When an incident lands in your lap, you&amp;rsquo;ll often start with a lot of questions: &lt;em&gt;Why is latency so high? What&amp;rsquo;s causing this outage? How much money are we losing at this very moment?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The uncertainty—and the pressure to quickly find answers—has always been one of the more nerve wracking parts of being an on-call engineer, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be that way any more. Instead of scrambling to make sense of all your observability data at once, simply take a deep breath, open Grafana Cloud, and ask Grafana Assistant: “What’s going on with my service and how could it impact revenue?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/strong&gt;, a context-aware AI agent built for Grafana, will take that request, launch an investigation that&amp;rsquo;s tailored to your stack, and start exploring data for you—and with you. Whenever an investigation surfaces something new, the assistant will share the relevant context and point you to the right places in your stack so you can quickly get your service running properly again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s an exciting change in the way you can interact with your data in Grafana Cloud, and at &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to reveal the next step in that evolution, as we announce the general availability of &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; and the public preview of &lt;strong&gt;Grafana&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Assistant Investigations&lt;/strong&gt;, an &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/introduction/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AI-powered feature&lt;/a&gt; that extends Grafana Assistant to accelerate multi-step incident investigations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taken collectively, these tools will help you speed up root cause analysis, reduce alert fatigue, and make observability accessible to users at any skill level.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-more-from-assistant-with-our-latest-improvements&#34;&gt;Get more from Assistant with our latest improvements &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can think of Assistant as an AI co-pilot for all your users. Embedded directly into the Grafana Cloud UI (simply click on the sparkle icon in the top-right corner to open the chat window), it helps you:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write and debug queries faster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build and optimize dashboards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Investigate issues and anomalies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand telemetry trends and patterns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Navigate Grafana more intuitively, using natural language&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddddc/assistant-ga-ui.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddddc/assistant-ga-ui.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A GIF showing Assistant responding to a request for help writing a LogQL query&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddddc/assistant-ga-ui.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A GIF showing Assistant responding to a request for help writing a LogQL query&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve seen a ton of excitement and engagement since we first announced Assistant at &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/llm-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/a&gt;, and early users are already seeing measurable benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“One of the biggest use cases for us is reducing the cognitive load on engineers,” said Neil Wilson, Director of Software Engineering, LexisNexis Risk Solutions. “Grafana Assistant helps us get to root cause faster—without needing deep expertise in every part of our complex system. That lowers training time and reduces risk if one of our experts leaves.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And with the general availability release, we&amp;rsquo;re pleased to share some additional enhancements:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profiles support&lt;/strong&gt;: Assistant now supports all your telemetry signals, so you can analyze profiles and automatically generate and refine queries in PromQL, LogQL, and TraceQL based on plain-language prompts—no syntax knowledge required.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-product guides:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;ve added tutorials and built-in prompting guides to help you unlock value quickly and expand adoption. By giving non-observability teams self-service access, you can also reduce dependency on already stretched SREs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MCP server support:&lt;/strong&gt; Connect to any remote MCP of your choice to bring in organizational knowledge and tooling. The assistant can then draw from that server and correlate the knowledge with your observability data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enterprise-ready access controls:&lt;/strong&gt; Building on existing RBAC in Grafana Cloud, Grafana Assistant now offers &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/privacy-and-security/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Assistant-specific roles and permissions&lt;/a&gt;. Admins can configure access to features such as rules, Assistant Investigations, and MCP server management at a granular level, ensuring teams can align observability workflows with enterprise security and compliance requirements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re also excited to share the private preview of our Slack integration with Assistant (&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/BNGFj8nf8ELoviSF9&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt; for access.) Now you can take Assistant with you wherever you go. Plus, you can do most of the Assistant tasks directly in Slack—no context switching needed! Stay tuned for more on this soon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x450/7095988630/assistant-slack-integration.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x450/7095988630/assistant-slack-integration.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A GIF showing someone use Slack to use Grafana Assistant&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x450/7095988630/assistant-slack-integration.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A GIF showing someone use Slack to use Grafana Assistant&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;autonomous-multi-step-incident-investigations-introducing-assistant-investigations&#34;&gt;Autonomous, multi-step incident investigations: Introducing Assistant Investigations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If Assistant is your AI co-pilot for finding answers in Grafana Cloud, you can think of Assistant Investigations as your support staff for narrowing down context during incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Incidents can happen for all sorts of reasons. And if you&amp;rsquo;re the one who&amp;rsquo;s on call, one of your most important tasks is figuring out what &lt;em&gt;isn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/em&gt; causing the problem. Chasing down all those leads and crossing off all your dead-ends is time consuming, but that&amp;rsquo;s where Assistant Investigations comes in, as it can look at multiple possibilities all at once.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It coordinates specialized agents to analyze your observability stack, diving into your metrics, logs, traces, and profiles to find anomalies and build up a picture of your system. It will collect evidence in parallel, generate findings and hypotheses, then provide actionable recommendations for mitigation and remediation. And since it&amp;rsquo;s embedded directly into Assistant, you get a seamless, guided workflow for resolving complex incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can ask Grafana Assistant at any time to pull in Assistant Investigations context and vice-versa. Found something that should be considered? Just tell the assistant to update your investigation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The feature will roll out automatically to all Grafana Cloud customers that have access to Grafana Assistant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-get-started-with-assistant-investigations&#34;&gt;How to get started with Assistant Investigations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The next time you receive an alert, you can kick off an investigation from the chat window and our agents will start exploring your stack to uncover root causes, find correlations, and to guide you as you remedy the incident.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Getting started is simple: Hit the &lt;strong&gt;Deep Investigation&lt;/strong&gt; button in Assistant and ask a question. For example: “Why do I have high latency in my payment service?” Assistant Investigations will then build a plan to investigate your problem; you can consult the progress at any time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x493/39e1435195/assistant-investigations-ui.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x493/39e1435195/assistant-investigations-ui.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A GIF showing someone typing questions into Grafana Assistant and clicking the &amp;#39;deep invesgiration&amp;#39; button&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x493/39e1435195/assistant-investigations-ui.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A GIF showing someone typing questions into Grafana Assistant and clicking the &amp;#39;deep invesgiration&amp;#39; button&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-were-building-ai-tooling-differently-at-grafana-labs&#34;&gt;How we&amp;rsquo;re building AI tooling differently at Grafana Labs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We realize this is a space with a lot of hype and some well-deserved hesitation. That&amp;rsquo;s why it’s important to us that we build features that feel seamless and integrate well with what users do in Grafana. Bottom line: We want to make your observability journey simpler.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re doing that by embedding AI directly into the heart of your observability workflows, redefining how your team interacts with its data. We&amp;rsquo;ve also designed these systems with the “human in the loop” concept in mind. Assistant and Assistant Investigations adapt to your input, learning from your cues to make each step more efficient and aligned with the way you work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And we&amp;rsquo;re not only developing this technology—&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/09/11/debug-query-and-build-faster-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;we&amp;rsquo;re using it internally&lt;/a&gt;. We get the struggles engineers face, because we face them, too. For example, we understand the need for flexibility, which is why we think our Slack and MCP server integrations will help you get work done faster, regardless of the time or your tooling. And we&amp;rsquo;ll continue to build and improve AI-powered capabilities that can be tailored to fit your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about our philosophy about building AI into observability, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/&#34;&gt;recent blog post on the topic&lt;/a&gt;. And for more information on Assistant and Assistant Investigations, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/&#34;&gt;corresponding docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To learn about all the news from ObservabilityCON 2025, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/observabilitycon-2025-announcements/&#34;&gt;blog post recapping all the big announcements&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;faq-grafana-cloud-ai--assistant&#34;&gt;FAQ: Grafana Cloud AI &amp;amp; Assistant&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Grafana Assistant?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant is an AI-powered agent in Grafana Cloud that helps you query, build, and troubleshoot faster using natural language. It simplifies common workflows like writing PromQL, LogQL, or TraceQL queries, creating dashboards, and performing guided root cause analysis —&amp;ndash; all while keeping you in control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Grafana Assistant Investigations?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assistant investigations is an SRE agent built directly into Grafana Assistant. It helps you find root causes faster by analyzing your observability stack, uncovering anomalies, and connecting signals across your system. You get clear, guided recommendations for remediation &amp;mdash; and because it’s embedded in Assistant, it provides a seamless, end-to-end workflow for resolving complex incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does Grafana Cloud use AI in observability?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud’s AI features support engineers and operators throughout the observability lifecycle —&amp;ndash; from detection and triage to explanation and resolution. We focus on explainable, assistive AI that enhances your workflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What problems does Grafana Assistant solve?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant helps reduce toil and improve productivity by enabling you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write and debug queries faster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build and optimize dashboards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Investigate issues and anomalies with Assistant Investigations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand telemetry trends and patterns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Navigate Grafana more intuitively&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Grafana Labs&amp;rsquo; approach to building AI into observability?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We build around:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Human-in-the-loop interaction for trust and transparency&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Outcome-first experiences that focus on real user value&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-signal support, including correlating data across metrics, logs, traces, and profiles&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does Grafana OSS have AI capabilities?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, Grafana OSS doesn’t include built-in AI features found in Grafana Cloud, but you can enable AI-powered workflows using the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM app plugin&lt;/a&gt;. This open source plugin connects to providers like OpenAI or Azure OpenAI securely, allowing you to generate queries, explore dashboards, and interact with Grafana using natural language. It also provides a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP (Model Context Protocol) server&lt;/a&gt;, which allows you to grant your favourite AI application access to your Grafana instance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why isn’t Assistant open source?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant runs in Grafana Cloud to support enterprise needs and manage infrastructure at scale. We’re committed to OSS and continue to invest heavily in it —&amp;ndash; including open sourcing tools like the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM plugin&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP server&lt;/a&gt;, so the community can build their own AI-powered experiences into Grafana OSS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does Grafana Cloud’s AI capabilities take actions on its own?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we focus on human-in-the-loop workflows that keep engineers in control while reducing toil. But as AI systems mature and prove more reliable, some tasks may require less oversight. We&amp;rsquo;re building a foundation that supports both: transparent, assistive AI now, with the flexibility to evolve into more autonomous capabilities where it makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where can I learn more about Grafana’s AI strategy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Check out our blog post&lt;/a&gt; to hear directly from our engineers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the difference between AI in observability and AI observability?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI in observability&lt;/em&gt; applies AI to operate your systems better and refers to the use of AI as part of a larger observability strategy. This could include agents baked into a platform (e.g., Grafana Assistant in Grafana Cloud) or other integrations that help automate and accelerate the ways teams observe their systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI observability&lt;/em&gt; is the use of observability to track the state of an AI system, such as an LLM-based application. It&amp;rsquo;s a subset of observability focused on a specific use case, similar to database observability for databases or application observability for applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud does both: AI that helps you operate, and observability for your AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当事件发生时，您通常会首先提出很多问题：&lt;em&gt;为什么延迟如此之高？是什么导致了这次中断？此时此刻我们损失了多少钱？&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不确定性以及快速找到答案的压力一直是作为一名待命工程师最令人紧张的部分之一，但现在不必再这样了。无需急于立即理解所有可观测性数据，只需深吸一口气，打开 Grafana Cloud，然后询问 Grafana 助手：“我的服务发生了什么情况，它会对收入有何影响？”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/strong&gt; 是一款专为 Grafana 构建的上下文感知 AI 代理，它将接受该请求，启动针对您的堆栈量身定制的调查，并开始为您探索数据，并与您一起探索数据。每当调查发现新的情况时，助手就会共享相关上下文，并将您指向堆栈中的正确位置，以便您可以快速让服务再次正常运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是您在 Grafana Cloud 中与数据交互方式的一个令人兴奋的变化，在 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; 上，我们很高兴地揭示这一演变的下一步，因为我们宣布全面推出 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;strong&gt;Grafana&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Assistant Investigations&lt;/strong&gt; 的公共预览版，&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/introduction/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AI 驱动的功能&lt;/a&gt;，可扩展 Grafana Assistant 以加速多步骤事件调查。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;总的来说，这些工具将帮助您加快根本原因分析，减少警报疲劳，并使任何技能水平的用户都可以进行观察。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-more-from-assistant-with-our-latest-improvements&#34;&gt;通过我们的最新改进，让 Google 助理发挥更多作用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以将 Assistant 视为所有用户的 AI 副驾驶。直接嵌入到 Grafana Cloud UI 中（只需单击右上角的闪光图标即可打开聊天窗口），它可以帮助您：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更快地编写和调试查询&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;构建和优化仪表板&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;调查问题和异常情况&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;了解遥测趋势和模式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用自然语言更直观地浏览 Grafana&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddd​​dc/assistant-ga-ui.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddd​​dc/assistant-ga-ui.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A GIF显示 Assistant 响应编写 LogQL 查询的帮助请求&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddd​​dc/assistant-ga-ui.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A GIF，显示 Assistant 响应编写 LogQL 查询的帮助请求&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自从我们在 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/llm-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; 上首次发布 Assistant 以来，我们看到了巨大的兴奋和参与度，早期用户已经看到了可衡量的好处。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“对我们来说最大的用例之一是减少工程师的认知负担，”LexisNexis Risk Solutions 软件工程总监 Neil Wilson 说道。 “Grafana Assistant 帮助我们更快地找到根本原因，而无需在复杂系统的每个部分都拥有深厚的专业知识。这样可以缩短培训时间，并降低我们的一位专家离开时的风险。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着正式发布，我们很高兴与大家分享一些额外的增强功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;配置文件支持&lt;/strong&gt;：Google 助理现在支持您的所有遥测信号，因此您可以分析配置文件，并根据简单语言提示在 PromQL、LogQL 和 TraceQL 中自动生成和优化查询，无需语法知识。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;产品内指南&lt;/strong&gt;：我们添加了教程和内置提示指南，以帮助您快速释放价值并扩大采用范围。通过为不可观察性团队提供自助服务访问权限，您还可以减少对已经捉襟见肘的 SRE 的依赖。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MCP 服务器支持：&lt;/strong&gt;连接到您选择的任何远程 MCP，以引入组织知识和工具。然后，助手可以从该服务器获取知识，并将知识与您的可观察性数据关联起来。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;企业级访问控制&lt;/strong&gt;：Grafana Assistant 以 Grafana Cloud 中的现有 RBAC 为基础，现在提供&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/privacy-and-security/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;特定于 Google Assistant 的角色和权限&lt;/a&gt;。管理员可以精细地配置对规则、助理调查和 MCP 服务器管理等功能的访问权限，确保团队能够使可观察性工作流程与企业安全和合规性要求保持一致。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还很高兴与大家分享 Slack 与 Assistant 集成的私人预览版（&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/BNGFj8nf8ELoviSF9&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;在此处注册&lt;/a&gt;以获取访问权限。）现在，您可以随身携带 Assistant。另外，您可以直接在 Slack 中完成大部分 Assistant 任务，无需上下文切换！请继续关注有关此内容的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x450/7095988630/assistant-slack-integration.gif&#34;&#xA;项目专业p=&#34;内容网址&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x450/7095988630/assistant-slack-integration.gif&#34;alt=&#34;显示某人使用 Slack 来使用 Grafana Assistant 的 GIF&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x450/7095988630/assistant-slack-integration.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示某人使用 Slack 来使用 Grafana Assistant 的 GIF&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;autonomous-multi-step-incident-investigations-introducing-assistant-investigations&#34;&gt;自主、多步骤事件调查：引入助理调查&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果 Assistant 是您在 Grafana Cloud 中寻找答案的 AI 副驾驶，您可以将 Assistant 调查视为您在事件期间缩小背景范围的支持人员。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;事故的发生可能有多种原因。如果您是值班人员，那么您最重要的任务之一就是找出导致问题的原因。追查所有这些线索并消除所有死胡同非常耗时，但这就是助理调查的用武之地，因为它可以同时查看多种可能性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它协调专门的代理来分析您的可观察性堆栈，深入研究您的指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件，以查找异常情况并构建系统图景。它将并行收集证据，生成调查结果和假设，然后提供可行的缓解和补救建议。由于它直接嵌入到 Assistant 中，因此您可以获得一个无缝的引导式工作流程来解决复杂事件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以随时要求 Grafana Assistant 引入 Assistant Investigations 上下文，反之亦然。发现了应该考虑的事情？只需告诉助理更新您的调查即可。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该功能将自动向所有有权访问 Grafana Assistant 的 Grafana Cloud 客户推出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-get-started-with-assistant-investigations&#34;&gt;如何开始使用助理调查&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下次收到警报时，您可以从聊天窗口开始调查，我们的代理将开始探索您的堆栈，以发现根本原因、查找相关性并指导您纠正事件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;入门很简单：点击 Google 助理中的&lt;strong&gt;深度调查&lt;/strong&gt;按钮并提出问题。例如：“为什么我的支付服务延迟很高？”然后，调查助理将制定一个计划来调查您的问题；您可以随时查询进度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x493/39e1435195/assistant-investigations-ui.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;c拉斯=“懒加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x493/39e1435195/assistant-investigations-ui.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A GIF 显示某人在 Grafana Assistant 中输入问题并单击“深度调查”按钮&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x493/39e1435195/assistant-investigations-ui.gif”&#xA;alt=&#34;GIF 显示某人在 Grafana Assistant 中输入问题并单击“深度调查”按钮&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-were-building-ai-tooling- Differently-at-grafana-labs&#34;&gt;我们如何在 Grafana Labs 构建不同的 AI 工具&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们意识到这是一个充满炒作和一些当之无愧的犹豫的空间。这就是为什么我们构建的功能感觉无缝并与用户在 Grafana 中所做的事情很好地集成，这对我们很重要。底线：我们希望让您的可观察之旅变得更简单。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们通过将人工智能直接嵌入到可观察性工作流程的核心来实现这一目标，重新定义您的团队与其数据交互的方式。我们在设计这些系统时还考虑到了“人在回路”的概念。助理和助理调查会适应您的输入，从您的提示中学习，使每个步骤更加高效并与您的工作方式保持一致。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们不仅在开发这项技术，&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/09/11/debug-query-and-build-faster-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;我们还在内部使用它&lt;/a&gt;。我们了解工程师面临的困境，因为我们也面临着它们。例如，我们了解灵活性的需求，这就是为什么我们认为我们的 Slack 和 MCP 服务器集成将帮助您更快地完成工作，无论时间或工具如何。我们将继续构建和改进人工智能驱动的功能，这些功能可以根据您的需求进行定制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要详细了解我们将 AI 融入可观察性的理念，请查看我们&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/&#34;&gt;最近关于该主题的博文&lt;/a&gt;。有关助理和助理调查的更多信息，请查看&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/&#34;&gt;相应文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;要了解 ObservabilityCON 2025 的所有新闻，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/observabilitycon-2025-announcements/&#34;&gt;博客文章回顾所有重大公告&lt;/a&gt;！&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;faq-grafana-cloud-ai--assistant&#34;&gt;常见问题解答：Grafana Cloud AI 和助手&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是 Grafana 助手？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 是 Grafana Cloud 中的人工智能代理，可帮助您使用自然语言更快地查询、构建和排除故障。它简化了常见的工作流程，例如编写 PromQL、LogQL 或 TraceQL 查询、创建仪表板以及执行引导式根本原因分析 — — 所有这些都让您保持掌控。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么是 Grafana 助理调查？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;助理调查是直接内置于 Grafana Assistant 中的 SRE 代理。它通过分析可观测性堆栈、发现异常并连接整个系统的信号，帮助您更快地找到根本原因。您可以获得清晰的指导性补救建议，而且由于它嵌入在 Assistant 中，因此它提供了一个无缝的端到端工作流程来解决复杂事件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud 如何在可观测性中使用 AI？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 的 AI 功能在整个可观测性生命周期（从检测和分类到解释和解决）为工程师和操作员提供支持。我们专注于可解释的辅助人工智能，以增强您的工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Assistant 解决了哪些问题？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 可以帮助您减少劳累并提高工作效率：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更快地编写和调试查询&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;构建和优化仪表板&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过助理调查来调查问题和异常情况&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;了解遥测趋势和模式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更直观地浏览 Grafana&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Labs 将人工智能构建为可观察性的方法是什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们围绕：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;人机交互以实现信任和透明度&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;注重实际用户价值的结果优先体验&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多信号支持，包括跨指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件关联数据&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana OSS有AI功能吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认情况下，Grafana OSS 不包含 Grafana Cloud 中的内置 AI 功能，但您可以使用&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM 应用插件&lt;/a&gt;启用 AI 驱动的工作流程。此开源插件安全地连接到 OpenAI 或 Azure OpenAI 等提供商，允许您生成查询、探索仪表板并使用自然语言与 Grafana 交互。它还提供了一个 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP（模型上下文协议）服务器&lt;/a&gt;，它允许您授予您最喜爱的 AI 应用程序对 Grafana 实例的访问权限。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为什么 Google 助理不开源？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 在 Grafana Cloud 中运行，以支持企业需求并大规模管理基础设施。我们致力于 OSS 并继续大力投资 —– 包括 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM 插件&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP 等开源工具 服务器&lt;/a&gt;，以便社区可以在 Grafana OSS 中构建自己的人工智能体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud 的 AI 功能会自行采取行动吗？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们专注于人机交互工作流程，让工程师保持控制，同时减少辛苦。但作为人工智能随着系统成熟并被证明更加可靠，某些任务可能需要更少的监督。我们正在建立一个支持两者的基础：现在是透明的辅助人工智能，并且可以在有意义的情况下灵活地发展为更加自主的功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在哪里可以了解有关 Grafana 人工智能策略的更多信息？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;查看我们的博文&lt;/a&gt;，直接听取我们工程师的意见。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;人工智能的可观察性和人工智能的可观察性有什么区别？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;可观察性中的人工智能&lt;/em&gt;应用人工智能来更好地操作系统，并指将人工智能用作更大的可观察性策略的一部分。这可能包括嵌入到平台中的代理（例如 Grafana Cloud 中的 Grafana Assistant）或其他有助于自动化和加速团队观察其系统的方式的集成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;AI 可观察性&lt;/em&gt;是利用可观察性来跟踪 AI 系统的状态，例如基于 LLM 的应用程序。它是专注于特定用例的可观察性的子集，类似于数据库的数据库可观察性或应用程序的应用程序可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 兼具以下两点：帮助您操作的 AI 以及 AI 的可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ObservabilityCON 2025: A guide to all the announcements from Grafana Labs】ObservabilityCON 2025：Grafana Labs 所有公告指南</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/08/observabilitycon-2025-announcements/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Today at &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; in London, we unveiled a number of exciting announcements and updates to Grafana Cloud that reimagine SaaS economics, simplify the complexity of running your observability stack at scale, and provide AI tooling that&amp;rsquo;s actually useful. (Root cause analysis via chatbot? Yes, please!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2025/keynote/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;keynote&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about how we&amp;rsquo;re helping you do more with the open observability cloud, and read on for a quick recap of all the news from ObservabilityCON 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3114x1750/fb19122e27/obscon-25-announcements-release-summary.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3114x1750/fb19122e27/obscon-25-announcements-release-summary.png&#34;alt=&#34;Infographic titled &amp;#39;The Open Observability Cloud&amp;#39; with three sections: SaaS Economics, Complexity Simplified, and Actually Useful AI, each listing features.&#34;title=&#34;All the Grafana Cloud updates announced at ObservabilityCON 2025&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3114x1750/fb19122e27/obscon-25-announcements-release-summary.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Infographic titled &amp;#39;The Open Observability Cloud&amp;#39; with three sections: SaaS Economics, Complexity Simplified, and Actually Useful AI, each listing features.&#34;title=&#34;All the Grafana Cloud updates announced at ObservabilityCON 2025&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;All the Grafana Cloud updates announced at ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;actually-useful-ai&#34;&gt;Actually useful AI&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve integrated AI-powered capabilities into Grafana Cloud to help you resolve incidents faster, lower operational overhead, and make observability accessible to users of any skill level.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;now generally available&lt;/a&gt;) is a context-aware AI agent that helps you:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write and debug queries faster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build and optimize dashboards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Investigate issues and anomalies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand telemetry trends and patterns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Navigate Grafana more intuitively, using natural language&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At ObservabilityCON, the team also revealed that Assistant now supports profiles and MCP servers; provides in-product guides; and offers &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/privacy-and-security/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;tailored RBAC controls&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x957/6f0b6be1ab/obscon-25-announcements-assistant.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x957/6f0b6be1ab/obscon-25-announcements-assistant.png&#34;alt=&#34;Screenshot of Grafana Assistant interface, featuring a text input box with a dark theme and colorful outline, and various menu options.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x957/6f0b6be1ab/obscon-25-announcements-assistant.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Screenshot of Grafana Assistant interface, featuring a text input box with a dark theme and colorful outline, and various menu options.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve seen a ton of excitement and engagement since we first announced Assistant at &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/llm-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/a&gt;, and early users are already seeing measurable benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“One of the biggest use cases for us is reducing the cognitive load on engineers,” said Neil Wilson, Director of Software Engineering, LexisNexis Risk Solutions. “Grafana Assistant helps us get to root cause faster—without needing deep expertise in every part of our complex system. That lowers training time and reduces risk if one of our experts leaves.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And now we&amp;rsquo;re taking it a step further with &lt;strong&gt;Assistant Investigations&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/introduction/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;in public preview&lt;/a&gt;), which uses specialized agents to analyze your observability stack, find anomalous behavior, and build a broader picture of your system. It provides actionable recommendations for mitigation and remediation, and since it&amp;rsquo;s embedded directly into Assistant, you get a seamless, guided workflow for resolving complex incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To learn more, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview&#34;&gt;blog post on Assistant and Assistant Investigations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;saas-economics-reimagined&#34;&gt;SaaS economics reimagined&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s a frustrating and familiar challenge: observability costs keep rising, but the value of your telemetry data doesn’t keep pace. That’s why we made several announcements at ObservabilityCON intended to help you optimize observability costs, maximize the value of your data, and reduce operational complexity in cloud environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-expanded-adaptive-telemetry-suite-cut-costs-keep-all-the-value&#34;&gt;The expanded Adaptive Telemetry suite: cut costs, keep all the value&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As telemetry volumes grow, it gets harder to separate signals from noise, and to control costs. That’s why we built Adaptive Telemetry in Grafana Cloud: a suite of features that analyze how your telemetry is used and automatically suggest actions like aggregating, sampling, dropping, or reducing low-value data. This helps you focus on the critical signals to keep systems running smoothly while lowering observability costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our suite started with &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Logs&lt;/a&gt;, and now we’re excited to share the general availability of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Traces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and private preview of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Profiles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adaptive Traces: Maximize the value of your tracing data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In modern distributed systems, tracing helps reveal bottlenecks and dependencies, but as it scales, costs climb and dashboards fill with redundant data from successful requests. Adaptive Traces in Grafana Cloud solves this with tail sampling—a technique where the decision to sample or drop a trace is made after collecting all or most of its spans—to ensure you only retain the insights that truly matter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With custom policy management, anomaly detection, and an integration with &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/simplified-exploration/traces//?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Traces Drilldown&lt;/a&gt;, Adaptive Traces provides a powerful, closed-loop experience to cut through the noise and accelerate root cause analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/9ae6d01953/obscon-25-announcements-adaptive-traces.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/9ae6d01953/obscon-25-announcements-adaptive-traces.png&#34;alt=&#34;Graph showing span latency and sampled traces for HTTP GET service, with actual and predicted values. Labels: Policy, Detection, Intake.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/9ae6d01953/obscon-25-announcements-adaptive-traces.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Graph showing span latency and sampled traces for HTTP GET service, with actual and predicted values. Labels: Policy, Detection, Intake.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adaptive Profiles: scalable continuous profiling without runaway costs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Profiles in Grafana Cloud lets you scale continuous profiling across your infrastructure without the worry of cost overruns. By automatically dialing data collection up based on workload behavior, it delivers critical performance insights when they matter most while keeping everyday monitoring efficient and affordable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn more about Adaptive Traces and Adaptive Profiles—and the Adaptive Telemetry suite, as a whole—in&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;this blog post.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;centralized-control-over-your-observability-spend&#34;&gt;Centralized control over your observability spend &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the &lt;strong&gt;Cost Management and Billing&lt;/strong&gt; app in Grafana Cloud (&lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-10-06-cost-management-and-billing-application/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;now generally available&lt;/a&gt;), admins get a centralized suite of tools to manage, control, and optimize their observability spend. By centralizing billing and usage information in one place, Cost Management and Billing is your one-stop-shop for attributing costs to teams and projects, managing invoices, and setting proactive usage alerts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;alt=&#34;Dashboard showing cost management and billing for October 2025, with metrics for cost, logs, and traces, and a detailed attributions breakdown.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Dashboard showing cost management and billing for October 2025, with metrics for cost, logs, and traces, and a detailed attributions breakdown.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To learn more, please visit our Cost Management and Billing &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grafana-bring-your-own-cloud-byoc-leverage-existing-csp-discounts&#34;&gt;Grafana Bring Your Own Cloud (BYOC): Leverage existing CSP discounts&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We realize many of our users have existing discounts and credits with cloud service providers (CSPs) like AWS and Google Cloud. With &lt;strong&gt;Grafana BYOC&lt;/strong&gt;, you can tap into all the benefits of Grafana Cloud, while still taking advantage of the special pricing agreements you have with your CSP.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To read more, please check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/products/bring-your-own-cloud-byoc/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Bring Your Own Cloud webpage&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grafana-federal-cloud-secure-and-reliable-observability&#34;&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud: secure and reliable observability&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;/products/fedramp-federal-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;now generally available&lt;/a&gt;) is authorized at FedRAMP High and DoD Impact Level 5 (IL5), making the fully managed, highly scalable observability platform available to U.S. government agencies and contractors operating in highly regulated environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud offers organizations secure and reliable cloud-based monitoring for their infrastructure, applications, and services, ensuring data protection and compliance with stringent security standards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please visit our&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/federal-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;to learn more.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;complexity-simplified&#34;&gt;Complexity simplified&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Observability has historically been costly, siloed, and difficult to scale, which is why we&amp;rsquo;re adding new capabilities to help every engineer, from developers to SREs, reduce complexity and deliver reliability for enterprise workloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;full-stack-observability-powered-by-the-the-knowledge-graph&#34;&gt;Full-stack observability, powered by the the knowledge graph&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With today&amp;rsquo;s complex systems, you can&amp;rsquo;t monitor applications or infrastructure in isolation—you need observability across your entire stack. That’s where the &lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud Knowledge Graph&lt;/strong&gt; (formerly Asserts) comes in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1616x963/daa3e9ed8a/obscon-25-announcements-knowledge-graph.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1616x963/daa3e9ed8a/obscon-25-announcements-knowledge-graph.png&#34;alt=&#34;A complex network graph with interconnected nodes and lines, displaying services and relationships in a dark-themed interface.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1616x963/daa3e9ed8a/obscon-25-announcements-knowledge-graph.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A complex network graph with interconnected nodes and lines, displaying services and relationships in a dark-themed interface.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge Graph (&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/knowledge-graph/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;generally available&lt;/a&gt;) connects metrics, logs, traces, and profiles across &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/application-observability/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Application Observability&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Frontend Observability&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/kubernetes-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/a&gt; solutions in Grafana Cloud and combines the telemetry into a single intelligent map of a system&amp;rsquo;s apps, databases, nodes, and more. The knowledge graph then provides you with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unified, intelligent workflows:&lt;/strong&gt; Automatically discover and map services and dependencies, surfacing curated dashboards and real-time health insights without needing deep PromQL expertise.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Faster root cause analysis:&lt;/strong&gt; Consolidates anomalies, dependencies, and timelines into a single view. It&amp;rsquo;s also integrated with Grafana Assistant, so teams can turn 30-minute war rooms into three-minute diagnoses.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Out-of-the-box insights:&lt;/strong&gt; When used alongside Application Observability, the knowledge graph provides built-in intelligence for Kubernetes, databases, and cloud services, reducing alert fatigue, shortening MTTR, and empowering engineers to troubleshoot effectively.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Centralized knowledge for your whole team:&lt;/strong&gt; Integrate existing dashboards, alerts, and even tags from metrics directly into the knowledge graph so everyone in your team has shared understanding of system behavior and state during RCA.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To learn more about Grafana Cloud Knowledge Graph, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/knowledge-graph/&#34;&gt;check out our docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;service-center-a-service-first-view-of-system-health&#34;&gt;Service Center: A service-first view of system health&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the context of observability, a &lt;em&gt;service&lt;/em&gt; is an individual or set of software functions. These services are dynamically derived from metric labels, but they can become difficult to track in distributed systems because those labels often differ once they&amp;rsquo;re split across microservices, clusters, or regions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But with &lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud Service Center&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/service-center/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;generally available&lt;/a&gt;), you can define your own static service label definitions, giving your team one view to organize and support a given service. This helps you define ownership and track service health and performance better. With Service Center, you get:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inventory:&lt;/strong&gt; This landing page contains all Grafana Cloud resources related to the specific service, with links to jump into the pre-filtered view of those product areas.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operational review:&lt;/strong&gt; Teams can view historical summary information based on SLOs, alerts, incidents, and Grafana Cloud IRM pages. They can then use the data to gauge service performance over a set period of time to help continuously improve operations and reliability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1427x872/95970a1394/obscon-25-announcements-service-center.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1427x872/95970a1394/obscon-25-announcements-service-center.png&#34;alt=&#34;Dashboard showing incident details, SLOs, and alerting data. Includes error budget, burn rate, alert instances, and event timeline graph.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1427x872/95970a1394/obscon-25-announcements-service-center.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Dashboard showing incident details, SLOs, and alerting data. Includes error budget, burn rate, alert instances, and event timeline graph.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The latest updates to Service Center include a historical view of firing alert rules and alert instances. We&amp;rsquo;ve also added historical views of mean time to resolve, mean time to respond, alert group ownership by user, and pages by data source.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To learn more, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/service-center/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Service Center docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;coming-soon-in-public-preview-database-observability-and-instrumentation-hub&#34;&gt;Coming soon in public preview: Database Observability and Instrumentation Hub&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The majority of application performance issues start in the database, yet traditional tools stop at “the database is slow.” But with &lt;strong&gt;Database Observability&lt;/strong&gt; in Grafana Cloud, you can break open the black box and get query-level visibility and AI-powered optimization so database troubleshooting is faster and easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/9ba4a0137e/obscon-25-announcements-db-observability.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/9ba4a0137e/obscon-25-announcements-db-observability.png&#34;alt=&#34;Dashboard displaying database performance metrics: duration, errors, rate, cumulative wait events, and schema details with various graphs.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/9ba4a0137e/obscon-25-announcements-db-observability.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Dashboard displaying database performance metrics: duration, errors, rate, cumulative wait events, and schema details with various graphs.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can use Database Observability to track every query across your databases and easily correlate queries with app and infrastructure signals. Plus, you can drill into execution plans, schema details, and indexes to pinpoint inefficiencies, and you get AI-powered recommendations with ready-to-run code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Database Observability will be available in public preview soon.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/VeoxhXqSMkrHULQH9&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Join the waitlist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;to be notified when it’s available.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also coming soon: &lt;strong&gt;Instrumentation Hub&lt;/strong&gt;, a point-and-click experience that allows you to automatically discover instrumentation gaps and deploy observability coverage at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdiA40upSyEzu-xh0MZ9jTQPzLHpMfvr18kV-Z-z42XxHF_Sg/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;to sign up for early access.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;celebrating-grafana-labs-partners&#34;&gt;Celebrating Grafana Labs partners&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year at ObservabilityCON we held our first-ever &lt;strong&gt;Grafana Labs Partner Summit&lt;/strong&gt;, where we celebrated the incredible impact of our partner ecosystem with our inaugural Grafana Labs Partner Awards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 2025 awards recognized excellence across revenue impact, new customer acquisition, sales collaboration, enablement, and customer success, spotlighting the partners who have truly set the bar in delivering value alongside Grafana Labs and helping shape the future of observability. You can check out the winners in each category in the image below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e3a224b88e/obscon-25-announcements-partner-summit.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e3a224b88e/obscon-25-announcements-partner-summit.png&#34;alt=&#34;Orange background with text: &amp;#39;Grafana Labs Partner Summit&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;Partner Award Winners&amp;#39; alongside logos and award categories for AHEAD, Lidd, Softcat, dnx.solutions, HCLTech, and AWS.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e3a224b88e/obscon-25-announcements-partner-summit.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Orange background with text: &amp;#39;Grafana Labs Partner Summit&amp;#39; and &amp;#39;Partner Award Winners&amp;#39; alongside logos and award categories for AHEAD, Lidd, Softcat, dnx.solutions, HCLTech, and AWS.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Partner Summit also provided a dedicated forum to strengthen alignment with our partners by sharing strategic updates, upcoming initiatives, and new opportunities for co-marketing and go-to-market collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can learn more about partnership opportunities with Grafana Labs by visiting &lt;a href=&#34;/partnerships/&#34;&gt;this page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;And check out the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025 homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;for all the latest from Grafana Labs&amp;rsquo; flagships observability event!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;今天，在伦敦举行的 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; 上，我们发布了许多令人兴奋的 Grafana Cloud 公告和更新，这些公告和更新重新构想了 SaaS 经济学，简化了大规模运行可观测性堆栈的复杂性，并提供了真正有用的 AI 工具。 （通过聊天机器人进行根本原因分析？是的，请！）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查看&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2025/keynote/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;主题演讲&lt;/a&gt;，详细了解我们如何帮助您利用开放可观测性云做更多事情，并继续阅读以快速回顾 ObservabilityCON 2025 的所有新闻。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接标题”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3114x1750/fb19122e27/obscon-25-announcements-release-summary.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“lazyload mb-0”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3114x1750/fb19122e27/obscon-25-announcements-release-summary.png&#34;alt=&#34;标题为“开放可观测性云”的信息图，包含三个部分：SaaS 经济学、简化的复杂性和实际有用的 AI，每个部分都列出了功能。&#34;title=&#34;All ObservabilityCON 2025 上宣布的 Grafana Cloud 更新&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/3114x1750/fb19122e27/obscon-25-announcements-release-summary.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;标题为“开放可观测性云”的信息图，包含三个部分：SaaS 经济学、简化的复杂性和实际有用的人工智能，每个部分都列出了功能。&#34;title=&#34;ObservabilityCON 2025 上宣布的所有 Grafana 云更新&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p title text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025 上宣布的所有 Grafana Cloud 更新&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;actually-useful-ai&#34;&gt;真正有用的人工智能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已将 AI 驱动的功能集成到 Grafana Cloud 中，以帮助您更快地解决事件、降低运营开销，并使任何技能水平的用户都可以进行观察。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/strong&gt;（&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;现已全面推出&lt;/a&gt;）是一款上下文感知 AI 代理，可帮助您：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更快地编写和调试查询&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;构建和优化仪表板&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;调查问题和异常情况&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;了解遥测趋势和模式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用自然语言更直观地浏览 Grafana&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 ObservabilityCON 上，团队还透露 Assistant 现在支持配置文件和 MCP 服务器；提供产品内指南；并提供&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/privacy-and-security/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;定制的 RBAC 控制&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x957/6f0b6be1ab/obscon-25-announcements-assistant.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x957/6f0b6be1ab/obscon-25-announcements-assistant.png&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Assistant 界面的屏幕截图，具有深色主题和彩色轮廓的文本输入框以及各种菜单选项。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x957/6f0b6be1ab/obscon-25-announcements-assistant.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana Assistant 界面的屏幕截图，具有深色主题和彩色轮廓的文本输入框，以及各种菜单选项。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自从我们在 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/llm-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; 上首次发布 Assistant 以来，我们看到了巨大的兴奋和参与度，早期用户已经看到了可衡量的好处。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“对我们来说最大的用例之一是减少工程师的认知负担，”LexisNexis Risk Solutions 软件工程总监 Neil Wilson 说道。 “Grafana Assistant 帮助我们更快地找到根本原因，而无需在复杂系统的每个部分都拥有深厚的专业知识。这样可以缩短培训时间，并降低我们的一位专家离开时的风险。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，我们通过&lt;strong&gt;助理调查&lt;/strong&gt;（&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/introduction/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;公共预览版&lt;/a&gt;）更进一步，它使用专门的代理来分析您的可观测性堆栈、查找异常行为并构建更广泛的系统概况。它提供了缓解和补救措施的可行建议，并且由于它直接嵌入到 Assistant 中，因此您可以获得解决复杂事件的无缝引导工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;要了解更多信息，请查看我们&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview&#34;&gt;有关助理和助理调查的博客文章&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;saas-economics-reimagined&#34;&gt;重新构想 SaaS 经济学&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一个令人沮丧且熟悉的挑战：可观测性成本不断上升，但遥测数据的价值却没有跟上。因此，我们在 ObservabilityCON 上发布了多项公告，旨在帮助您优化可观测性成本、最大限度地提高数据价值并降低云环境中的操作复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-expanded-adaptive-telemetry-suite-cut-costs-keep-all-the-value&#34;&gt;扩展的自适应遥测套件：削减成本，保留所有价值&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着遥测量的增长，将信号与噪声分离以及控制成本变得越来越困难。这就是我们在 Grafana Cloud 中构建自适应遥测的原因：一套功能可以分析遥测的使用方式并自动执行通常建议采取聚合、采样、删除或减少低价值数据等操作。这有助于您专注于关键信号，以保持系统平稳运行，同时降低可观测性成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的套件始于&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应日志&lt;/a&gt;，现在我们很高兴与大家分享&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-traces/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应跟踪&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a的私人预览 href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应配置文件&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自适应跟踪：最大化跟踪数据的价值&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在现代分布式系统中，跟踪有助于揭示瓶颈和依赖关系，但随着规模的扩大，成本会上升，仪表板会充满来自成功请求的冗余数据。 Grafana Cloud 中的自适应跟踪通过尾部采样解决了这个问题，该技术是在收集所有或大部分跨度后做出采样或删除跟踪的决定的技术，以确保您只保留真正重要的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过自定义策略管理、异常检测以及与&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/simplified-exploration/traces//?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;跟踪深入分析&lt;/a&gt;的集成，自适应跟踪提供了强大的闭环体验，可消除干扰并加速根本原因分析。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/9ae6d01953/obscon-25-announcements-adaptive-traces.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/9ae6d01953/obscon-25-announcements-adaptive-traces.png&#34;alt=&#34;图表显示 HTTP GET 服务的跨度延迟和采样跟踪，以及实际值和预测值。标签：策略、检测、摄入。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/988x816/9ae6d01953/obscon-25-announcements-adaptive-traces.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;图表显示 HTTP GET 服务的跨度延迟和采样跟踪，以及实际值和预测值。标签：策略、检测、摄入。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自适应配置文件：可扩展的连续分析，无需失控成本&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 中的自适应配置文件可让您在整个基础架构中扩展连续分析，而无需担心成本超支。通过根据工作负载行为自动拨号数据收集，它提供了关键的性能在保持日常监控高效且经济实惠的同时，在最重要的时候提供洞察。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;了解有关自适应跟踪和自适应配置文件以及整个自适应遥测套件的更多信息&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;这篇博文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;centralized-control-over-your-observability-spend&#34;&gt;集中控制您的可观察性支出&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借助 Grafana Cloud 中的&lt;strong&gt;成本管理和计费&lt;/strong&gt;应用（&lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-10-06-cost-management-and-billing-application/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;现已全面推出&lt;/a&gt;），管理员可以获得一套集中的工具来管理、控制和优化其可观察性支出。通过将计费和使用信息集中在一处，成本管理和计费成为您将成本分配给团队和项目、管理发票以及设置主动使用警报的一站式服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;alt=&#34;仪表板显示 2025 年 10 月的成本管理和计费，包含成本、日志和跟踪指标以及详细的归因细分。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1614x936/73fc8f11e9/obscon-25-announcements-cost-management.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;仪表板显示 2025 年 10 月的成本管理和计费，包含成本、日志和跟踪指标以及详细的归因细分。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;要了解更多信息，请访问我们的成本管理和计费&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grafana-bring-your-own-cloud-byoc-leverage-existing-csp-discounts&#34;&gt;Grafana 自带云 (BYOC)：利用现有的 CSP 折扣&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们意识到，我们的许多用户都拥有 AWS 和 Google Cloud 等云服务提供商 (CSP) 的现有折扣和积分。借助 &lt;strong&gt;Grafana BYOC&lt;/strong&gt;，您可以充分利用 Grafana Cloud 的所有优势，同时仍可利用与 CSP 签订的特殊定价协议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;要了解更多信息，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/products/bring-your-own-cloud-byoc/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自带云网页&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;grafana-federal-cloud-secure-and-reliable-observability&#34;&gt;Grafana 联邦云：安全可靠的可观测性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud&lt;/strong&gt;（&lt;a href=&#34;/products/fedramp-federal-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;现已全面发布&lt;/a&gt;）已在 FedRAMP Hi 授权gh 和国防部影响级别 5 (IL5)，使在高度监管环境中运营的美国政府机构和承包商可以使用完全托管、高度可扩展的可观测平台。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud 为组织的基础设施、应用程序和服务提供安全可靠的基于云的监控，确保数据保护并符合严格的安全标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;请访问我们的&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/federal-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud 文档&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;了解更多信息。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;complexity-simplified&#34;&gt;简化复杂性&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可观测性历来成本高昂、孤立且难以扩展，这就是为什么我们添加新功能来帮助从开发人员到 SRE 的每位工程师降低复杂性并为企业工作负载提供可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;full-stack-observability-powered-by-the-the-knowledge-graph&#34;&gt;由知识图谱提供支持的全栈可观察性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于当今复杂的系统，您无法单独监控应用程序或基础设施 - 您需要整个堆栈的可观察性。这就是 &lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud 知识图&lt;/strong&gt;（以前称为 Asserts）的用武之地。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1616x963/daa3e9ed8a/obscon-25-announcements-knowledge-graph.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1616x963/daa3e9ed8a/obscon-25-announcements-knowledge-graph.png&#34;alt=&#34;具有互连节点和线路的复杂网络图，在深色主题界面中显示服务和关系。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1616x963/daa3e9ed8a/obscon-25-announcements-knowledge-graph.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;具有互连节点和线路的复杂网络图，在深色主题界面中显示服务和关系。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;知识图（&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/knowledge-graph/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;普遍可用&lt;/a&gt;）连接&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/application-observability/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;应用程序中的指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件 可观察性&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;前端可观察性&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/kubernetes-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud 中的 Kubernetes 监控解决方案，并将遥测数据合并到系统应用程序、数据库、节点等的单个智能地图中。然后知识图为您提供：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;统一、智能nt 工作流程：&lt;/strong&gt;自动发现并映射服务和依赖项，呈现精心策划的仪表板和实时健康见解，而无需深厚的 PromQL 专业知识。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;更快的根本原因分析：&lt;/strong&gt;将异常、依赖性和时间线整合到一个视图中。它还与 Grafana Assistant 集成，因此团队可以将 30 分钟的作战室变成三分钟的诊断。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;开箱即用的见解&lt;/strong&gt;：当与应用程序可观察性一起使用时，知识图谱可为 Kubernetes、数据库和云服务提供内置智能，从而减少警报疲劳、缩短 MTTR，并帮助工程师有效排除故障。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;为整个团队提供集中知识&lt;/strong&gt;：将现有的仪表板、警报，甚至指标中的标签直接集成到知识图中，以便团队中的每个人都能在 RCA 期间共享对系统行为和状态的理解。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;要了解有关 Grafana Cloud 知识图的更多信息，&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/knowledge-graph/&#34;&gt;查看我们的文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;service-center-a-service-first-view-of-system-health&#34;&gt;服务中心：系统运行状况的服务优先视图&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在可观察性的背景下，&lt;em&gt;服务&lt;/em&gt;是一个单独的或一组软件功能。这些服务是从指标标签动态派生的，但在分布式系统中它们可能会变得难以跟踪，因为这些标签一旦跨微服务、集群或区域划分，通常会有所不同。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但借助 &lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud Service Center&lt;/strong&gt;（&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/service-center/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;普遍可用&lt;/a&gt;），您可以定义自己的静态服务标签定义，为您的团队提供一个组织和支持给定服务的视图。这有助于您更好地定义所有权并跟踪服务运行状况和性能。通过服务中心，您可以获得：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;库存&lt;/strong&gt;：此着陆页包含与特定服务相关的所有 Grafana Cloud 资源，以及可跳转到这些产品区域的预过滤视图的链接。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;操作审核&lt;/strong&gt;：团队可以查看基于 SLO、警报、事件和 Grafana Cloud IRM 页面的历史摘要信息。然后，他们可以使用这些数据来衡量一段时间内的服务性能，以帮助不断改进运营和可靠性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1427x872/95970a1394/obscon-25-announcements-service-center.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1427x872/95970a1394/obscon-25-announcements-service-center.png&#34;alt=&#34;Dashboard 显示事件详细信息、SLO 和警报数据。包括错误预算、消耗率、警报实例和事件时间线图。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1427x872/95970a1394/obscon-25-announcements-service-center.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示事件详细信息、SLO 和警报数据的仪表板。包括错误预算、消耗率、警报实例和事件时间线图。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;服务中心的最新更新包括触发警报规则和警报实例的历史视图。我们还添加了平均解决时间、平均响应时间、用户警报组所有权以及数据源页面的历史视图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;要了解更多信息，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/service-center/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;服务中心文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;coming-soon-in-public-preview-database-observability-and-instrumentation-hub&#34;&gt;即将推出公共预览版：数据库可观测性和检测中心&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大多数应用程序性能问题都是从数据库开始的，而传统工具却止于“数据库速度慢”。但借助 Grafana Cloud 中的&lt;strong&gt;数据库可观察性&lt;/strong&gt;，您可以打破黑匣子并获得查询级可见性和人工智能支持的优化，从而更快、更轻松地进行数据库故障排除。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/9ba4a0137e/obscon-25-announcements-db-observability.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/9ba4a0137e/obscon-25-announcements-db-observability.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示数据库性能指标的仪表板：持续时间、错误、速率、累积等待事件和带有各种图表的架构详细信息。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/9ba4a0137e/obscon-25-announcements-db-observability.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示数据库性能指标的仪表板：持续时间、错误、速率、累积等待事件以及带有各种图表的架构详细信息。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以使用数据库可观察性来跟踪数据库中的每个查询，并轻松将查询与应用和基础设施信号关联起来。此外，您还可以深入研究执行计划、架构详细信息和索引来查明效率低下的地方，并通过可立即运行的代码获得人工智能支持的建议。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Database Observability 即将推出公共预览版。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/VeoxhXqSMkrHULQH9&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;加入候补名单&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;在可用时收到通知。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即将推出：&lt;strong&gt;Instrumentation Hub&lt;/strong&gt;，一种点击式体验，可让您自动刻录弥补仪器差距并大规模部署可观测性覆盖范围。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdiA40upSyEzu-xh0MZ9jTQPzLHpMfvr18kV-Z-z42XxHF_Sg/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;点击 在此&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;注册抢先体验。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;celebating-grafana-labs-partners&#34;&gt;庆祝 Grafana Labs 合作伙伴&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年，我们在 ObservabilityCON 上举办了首届 &lt;strong&gt;Grafana Labs 合作伙伴峰会&lt;/strong&gt;，会上我们颁发了首届 Grafana Labs 合作伙伴奖，以庆祝我们的合作伙伴生态系统所产生的令人难以置信的影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2025 年奖项表彰了在收入影响、新客户获取、销售协作、支持和客户成功方面的卓越表现，重点关注与 Grafana Labs 一起真正树立了价值交付标准并帮助塑造可观测性未来的合作伙伴。您可以在下图中查看每个类别的获奖者：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e3a224b88e/obscon-25-announcements-partner-summit.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e3a224b88e/obscon-25-announcements-partner-summit.png&#34;alt=&#34;橙色背景，文字：“Grafana Labs 合作伙伴峰会”和“合作伙伴奖获奖者”以及 AHEAD、Lidd、Softcat 的徽标和奖项类别， dnx.solutions、HCLTech 和 AWS。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e3a224b88e/obscon-25-announcements-partner-summit.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;橙色背景，文字：“Grafana Labs 合作伙伴峰会”和“合作伙伴奖获奖者”，以及 AHEAD、Lidd、Softcat、dnx.solutions、HCLTech 和 AWS 的徽标和奖项类别。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;合作伙伴峰会还提供了一个专门的论坛，通过分享战略更新、即将推出的举措以及联合营销和上市合作的新机会，加强与合作伙伴的协调。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;您可以访问&lt;a href=&#34;/partnerships/&#34;&gt;此页面&lt;/a&gt;了解有关与 Grafana Labs 合作机会的更多信息。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;并查看&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025主页&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;了解 Grafana Labs 旗舰可观测性活动的所有最新动态！&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The observability maturity curve: How IT leaders are shifting from tools to outcomes】可观察性成熟度曲线：IT 领导者如何从工具转向成果</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/06/the-observability-maturity-curve-how-it-leaders-are-shifting-from-tools-to-outcomes/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Observability has come a long way from its origins in monitoring logs and metrics. Today, it sits on a maturity curve: Organizations move from fragmented tool stacks to unified platforms to proactive engineering practices that tie reliability to business outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To better understand where IT leaders are on this curve, Grafana Labs surveyed 150 decision-makers across industries in advance of &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt;. The findings reveal a true progression: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Teams are starting with unified platforms,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wrestling with consolidation,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Adopting SLOs for accountability,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Experimenting with AI-assisted insights,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And increasingly tying observability to business value. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, these milestones map out a key trend that shows not just where the industry is—but where it’s headed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-were-entering-the-era-of-unified-observability&#34;&gt;1. We’re entering the era of unified observability&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nearly three-quarters of executives have either implemented (44%) or are actively transitioning to (29%) unified observability platforms. Only a small fraction (3%) reported having no defined strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x828/8368431998/etr-observability-approach.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x828/8368431998/etr-observability-approach.png&#34;alt=&#34;Bar chart of organizational observability approaches: 44% unified, 24% siloed, 29% transitioning, 3% no strategy.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x828/8368431998/etr-observability-approach.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Bar chart of organizational observability approaches: 44% unified, 24% siloed, 29% transitioning, 3% no strategy.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This marks the starting point on the maturity curve: breaking down silos. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s for faster incident resolution or better developer experience, unified observability is no longer a &amp;ldquo;nice to have&amp;rdquo;—it&amp;rsquo;s the foundation of modern operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our take:&lt;/strong&gt; Vendor-neutral platforms like &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; are poised to lead this shift. As organizations unify tools and data sources, open and composable ecosystems offer the flexibility enterprises need without lock-in—a foundational move for scaling maturity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-tool-consolidation-is-a-strategic-priority-but-still-a-work-in-progress&#34;&gt;2. Tool consolidation is a strategic priority, but still a work in progress&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, most executives are in agreement that unified observability is the best path forward, but their ability to execute and get value from that consolidation remains a work in progress. For example, 77% of respondents rated tool consolidation as important, but only 14% consider their consolidation efforts very successful. Two-thirds are somewhere in the middle: on the journey but not yet at the destination.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/92906ee8e2/etr-consolidated-observability.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/92906ee8e2/etr-consolidated-observability.png&#34;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing importance of tool consolidation in observability: 1% (1), 3% (2), 19% (3), 55% (4), 22% (5).&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/92906ee8e2/etr-consolidated-observability.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing importance of tool consolidation in observability: 1% (1), 3% (2), 19% (3), 55% (4), 22% (5).&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This reflects the growing pains of the maturity curve. Merging complex telemetry pipelines while supporting multiple teams and legacy systems isn’t trivial. Yet the momentum is there, and both cost pressures and operational clarity are driving it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our take:&lt;/strong&gt; This is an opportunity for observability platforms to offer more out-of-the-box integrations, intelligent defaults, and better UX to reduce the cost of context switching and tool overload. The platforms that win will be open and composable, giving organizations the flexibility to unify tools at their own pace while avoiding lock-in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-slos-are-changing-the-way-teams-work-even-if-theyre-not-fully-mature&#34;&gt;3. SLOs are changing the way teams work, even if they’re not fully mature&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Service level objectives (SLOs) are internal reliability targets like uptime and latency, which are quickly becoming a standard practice. 86% of organizations reported &amp;ldquo;basic&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;broad&amp;rdquo; adoption of SLOs, mainly to track service level agreements (SLAs), alerting, and leadership reporting. While SLO adoption is growing, only a little over a third (39%) use SLOs to prioritize engineering work, which points to the fact that many organizations are still in the early stages of maturity, using SLOs for reactive reporting rather than as a proactive driver of engineering priorities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x874/9ead6d1cf0/etr-slo-implementation.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x874/9ead6d1cf0/etr-slo-implementation.png&#34;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing SLO implementation maturity: 11% no SLOs, 42% basic adoption, 44% broad adoption, 3% advanced and automated.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x874/9ead6d1cf0/etr-slo-implementation.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing SLO implementation maturity: 11% no SLOs, 42% basic adoption, 44% broad adoption, 3% advanced and automated.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This stage represents the maturing middle of the curve: moving from visibility to accountability. Still, teams that have embraced SLOs report real impact; 56% said SLOs significantly changed how they operate, particularly in accountability, visibility, and data-driven decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/bc0e0215f0/etr-slo-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/bc0e0215f0/etr-slo-workflow.png&#34;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing responses to how SLOs changed team work: 1 (3%), 2 (6%), 3 (36%), 4 (49%), 5 (7%).&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/bc0e0215f0/etr-slo-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing responses to how SLOs changed team work: 1 (3%), 2 (6%), 3 (36%), 4 (49%), 5 (7%).&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“We&amp;rsquo;re a data-centric company. SLOs allow us to hold people accountable with data. It also points to performance directly. It helps change the culture to more of a results-oriented one.” – C-level executive at a midsized consulting firm on the benefits of SLOs&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our take:&lt;/strong&gt; SLOs are the bridge between technical reliability and business alignment. But they need to be actionable—not just a set of unattended goals highlighted on a dashboard. We see a future where AI-powered SLO insights help teams shift from reactive firefighting to proactive engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-ai-in-observability-is-on-everyones-radar-but-its-still-early&#34;&gt;4. AI in observability is on everyone’s radar, but it&amp;rsquo;s still early&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As organizations mature their observability strategies, many are looking beyond dashboards and alerts to the next frontier: AI. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So far, only 3% of organizations have deployed AI for observability in production to help reduce alert fatigue, detect anomalies earlier, and guide incident response. However, more than 80% are actively exploring or piloting use cases. Most prefer to purchase rather than build solutions, and voluntary experimentation drives adoption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x986/e5fd10a8b5/etr-ai-in-use.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x986/e5fd10a8b5/etr-ai-in-use.png&#34;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing AI adoption stages: 51% investigating use cases, 33% in pilot phase, 13% not exploring, 3% in production.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x986/e5fd10a8b5/etr-ai-in-use.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing AI adoption stages: 51% investigating use cases, 33% in pilot phase, 13% not exploring, 3% in production.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Top use cases? Incident detection, reducing alert fatigue, root cause analysis, and SLO tracking. But notably, root cause analysis ranked lower—perhaps a sign that teams still trust human intuition for postmortems, or that the state of the art has not yet reached the point where it can be trusted—at least not yet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x1227/34420b7ed0/etr-ai-benefit.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x1227/34420b7ed0/etr-ai-benefit.png&#34;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing AI benefits: Incident detection 71%, Alert noise reduction 47%, Root cause analysis 43%, SLO tracking 21%, Capacity planning 17%.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x1227/34420b7ed0/etr-ai-benefit.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing AI benefits: Incident detection 71%, Alert noise reduction 47%, Root cause analysis 43%, SLO tracking 21%, Capacity planning 17%.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the cutting edge of the maturity curve: using AI not to replace human intuition but to amplify it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our take:&lt;/strong&gt; The next wave of observability won’t just surface more data, it will help teams understand what matters. At Grafana Labs, we believe &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AI should act as a co-pilot&lt;/a&gt;, not a black box. That’s why our approach to AI-assisted observability prioritizes transparency, explainability, and user control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-the-end-goal-measurable-business-impact&#34;&gt;5. The end goal: measurable business impact&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Only 14% of respondents quantify observability ROI in financial terms. Most use operational metrics like uptime, incident frequency, and mean time to resolution. And while business leaders increasingly rely on observability for proactive issue management and strategic decisions, cost optimization ranked surprisingly low.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1838x1227/16fd50bf2a/etr-value-observability.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1838x1227/16fd50bf2a/etr-value-observability.png&#34;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing responses on communicating observability value: Operational efficiency (37%) to SLA and compliance management (3%).&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1838x1227/16fd50bf2a/etr-value-observability.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Bar chart showing responses on communicating observability value: Operational efficiency (37%) to SLA and compliance management (3%).&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“We look at how observability helps reduce MTTD and MTTR incidents. Shorter detection and resolution times mean less downtime, fewer service disruptions, and more consistent user satisfaction. That’s a clear sign of value, even if we’re not attaching a price tag to it.” – C-level executive at a consulting firm on how they assign value to observability outcomes without a specific dollar value&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the summit of the maturity curve: when observability becomes a business driver, not just an engineering tool. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our take:&lt;/strong&gt; Teams are underselling the impact of observability because of that gap between the real value observability delivers and the way it’s currently measured. As observability matures, we expect more teams to tie performance to business outcomes such as customer experience, developer productivity, or revenue protection. Eventually, observability will be seen as more than just an operational tool and become a strategic business driver.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;observabilitys-next-chapter&#34;&gt;Observability’s next chapter&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The survey confirms what we see every day at Grafana Labs: Observability is no longer just the purview of infrastructure teams; it&amp;rsquo;s critical to the success of data-driven businesses. With 41% of organizations increasing observability spending in the past year and 55% expecting to invest even more in the year ahead, the message is clear: the value of observability is only growing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But unlocking that value means progressing along the maturity curve. It starts with unifying platforms, advances through tool consolidation and disciplined SLO practices, and looks ahead to AI-assisted insights and measurable business impact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s the future we’re building toward. Whether you’re consolidating tools, scaling SLOs, or experimenting with AI, Grafana Labs is helping turn data into insight—and insight into impact.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;methodology&#34;&gt;Methodology&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This research was conducted in partnership with market research firm &lt;a href=&#34;https://etr.ai/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Enterprise Technology Research&lt;/a&gt;, which surveyed 150 IT decision-makers from around the world for this study. The survey took place in July 2025. Respondents spanned multiple industries, including financial services, healthcare, IT, manufacturing, education, retail, government, and more. To qualify, all respondents had to be at the Director level or above and have responsibility and visibility into their organization’s observability and monitoring practices, as well as a high level of familiarity with the technology stacks used, related budgets, and purchasing decisions. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Last updated Oct. 6th 2025&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;可观察性从监控日志和指标的起源到现在已经取得了很大的进步。如今，它正处于成熟度曲线上：组织从分散的工具堆栈转向统一的平台，再转向将可靠性与业务成果联系起来的主动工程实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了更好地了解 IT 领导者在这条曲线上的位置，Grafana Labs 在 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; 之前对各行业的 150 名决策者进行了调查。研究结果揭示了真正的进展：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;团队从统一平台开始，&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;努力整合，&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;采用 SLO 进行问责，&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;尝试利用人工智能辅助的见解，&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;并且越来越多地将可观察性与商业价值联系起来。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;总而言之，这些里程碑勾勒出一个关键趋势，不仅表明了行业的现状，而且表明了行业的发展方向。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-were-entering-the-era-of-unified-observability&#34;&gt;1.我们正在进入统一可观测时代&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;近四分之三的高管已经实施 (44%) 或正在积极过渡到 (29%) 统一的可观察性平台。只有一小部分 (3%) 表示没有明确的策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x828/8368431998/etr-observability-approach.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x828/8368431998/etr-observability-approach.png&#34;alt=&#34;组织可观察性方法的条形图：44% 统一，24% 孤立，29% 过渡，3% 无策略。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x828/8368431998/etr-observability-approach.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;组织可观察性方法的条形图：44% 统一，24% 孤立，29% 过渡，3% 无策略。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这标志着成熟度曲线的起点：打破孤岛。无论是为了更快地解决事件还是更好的开发人员体验，统一的可观察性不再是“有就有之”，而是现代运营的基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我们的看法：&lt;/strong&gt;像 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 这样的供应商中立平台已准备好引领这一转变。随着组织统一工具和数据源，开放且可组合的生态系统提供了企业所需的灵活性，而无需锁定——这是扩展成熟度的基础举措。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-tool-consolidation-is-a-strategic-priority-but-still-a-work-in-progress&#34;&gt;2.工具整合是战略重点，但仍在进行中&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;是的，大多数高管都认为统一的可观察性是最好的前进道路，但是他们执行整合并从整合中获取价值的能力仍然是一项正在进行的工作。例如，77% 的受访者认为工具整合很重要，但只有 14% 的受访者认为他们的整合工作非常成功。三分之二的人处于中间位置：正在旅途中，但尚未到达目的地。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/92906ee8e2/etr-consolidated-observability.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/92906ee8e2/etr-consolidated-observability.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示工具整合在可观测性中的重要性的条形图：1% (1)、3% (2)、19% (3)、55% (4)、22% (5)。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/92906ee8e2/etr-consolidated-observability.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;显示工具整合在可观察性方面的重要性的条形图：1% (1)、3% (2)、19% (3)、55% (4)、22% (5)。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这反映了成熟度曲线的成长阵痛。合并复杂的遥测管道，同时支持多个团队和遗留系统并非易事。然而，势头确实存在，成本压力和运营清晰度都在推动这一势头。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我们的看法：&lt;/strong&gt;对于可观察性平台来说，这是一个提供更多开箱即用集成、智能默认设置和更好的用户体验的机会，以降低上下文切换和工具过载的成本。获胜的平台将是开放且可组合的，使组织能够按照自己的节奏灵活地统一工具，同时避免锁定。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-slos-are-changing-the-way-teams-work-even-if-theyre-not-complete-mature&#34;&gt;3. SLO 正在改变团队的工作方式，即使它们尚未完全成熟&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;服务级别目标 (SLO) 是内部可靠性目标，例如正常运行时间和延迟，这些目标正在迅速成为标准做法。 86% 的组织表示“基本”或“广泛”采用了 SLO，主要是为了跟踪服务级别协议 (SLA)、警报和领导力报告。虽然 SLO 的采用率不断增长，但只有略多于三分之一 (39%) 的人使用 SLO 来确定工程工作的优先级，这表明许多组织仍处于成熟的早期阶段，使用 SLO 进行被动报告，而不是作为工程优先级的主动驱动因素。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x874/9ead6d1cf0/etr-slo-implementation.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;数据-src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x874/9ead6d1cf0/etr-slo-implementation.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示 SLO 实施成熟度的条形图：11% 无 SLO、42% 基本采用、44% 广泛采用、3% 高级和自动化。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x874/9ead6d1cf0/etr-slo-implementation.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示 SLO 实施成熟度的条形图：11% 无 SLO、42% 基本采用、44% 广泛采用、3% 高级和自动化。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这个阶段代表了曲线的成熟中间阶段：从可见性转向问责制。尽管如此，接受 SLO 的团队报告了真正的影响； 56% 的受访者表示，SLO 显着改变了他们的运营方式，特别是在问责制、可见性和数据驱动的决策方面。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/bc0e0215f0/etr-slo-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/bc0e0215f0/etr-slo-workflow.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示对 SLO 如何改变团队工作的响应的条形图：1 (3%)、2 (6%)、3 (36%)、4 (49%)、5 (7%)。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x991/bc0e0215f0/etr-slo-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示对 SLO 如何改变团队工作的回应的条形图：1 (3%)、2 (6%)、3 (36%)、4 (49%)、5 (7%)。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“我们是一家以数据为中心的公司。SLO 使我们能够让人们对数据负责。它还直接指向绩效。它有助于将文化转变为更加注重结果的文化。” – 一家中型咨询公司的 C 级高管介绍 SLO 的好处&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我们的看法：&lt;/strong&gt;SLO 是技术可靠性和业务一致性之间的桥梁。但它们需要具有可操作性，而不仅仅是仪表板上突出显示的一组无人关注的目标。我们看到，未来人工智能驱动的 SLO 洞察将帮助团队从被动应对转向主动工程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-ai-in-observability-is-on-everyones-radar-but-its-still-early&#34;&gt;4.可观察性人工智能受到每个人的关注，但还处于早期阶段&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着组织的可观察性策略日趋成熟，许多组织将目光从仪表板和警报转向下一个前沿领域：人工智能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;到目前为止，只有 3% 的组织在生产中部署了用于可观察性的 AI，以帮助减少警报疲劳、及早检测异常并指导事件响应。然而，超过 80% 正在积极探索或试点用例。大多数人更喜欢购买而不是构建解决方案，自愿实验推动了采用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;class=&#34;灯箱链接&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x986/e5fd10a8b5/etr-ai-in-use.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x986/e5fd10a8b5/etr-ai-in-use.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示人工智能采用阶段的条形图：51% 正在调查用例，33% 处于试点阶段，13% 未探索，3% 处于生产阶段。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x986/e5fd10a8b5/etr-ai-in-use.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示人工智能采用阶段的条形图：51% 正在调查用例，33% 处于试点阶段，13% 未探索，3% 正在生产。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主要用例？事件检测、减少警报疲劳、根本原因分析和 SLO 跟踪。但值得注意的是，根本原因分析排名较低——这也许表明团队仍然相信人类的事后直觉，或者表明现有技术尚未达到可以信任的程度——至少目前还没有。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x1227/34420b7ed0/etr-ai-benefit.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x1227/34420b7ed0/etr-ai-benefit.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示 AI 优势的条形图：事件检测 71%、警报噪音降低 47%、根本原因分析 43%、SLO 跟踪 21%、容量规划 17%。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x1227/34420b7ed0/etr-ai-benefit.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示 AI 优势的条形图：事件检测 71%、警报降噪 47%、根本原因分析 43%、SLO 跟踪 21%、容量规划 17%。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是成熟度曲线的最前沿：使用人工智能不是取代人类直觉，而是放大它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我们的看法：&lt;/strong&gt;下一波可观察性不仅会呈现更多数据，还将帮助团队了解重要的事情。在 Grafana Labs，我们相信&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;人工智能应该充当副驾驶&lt;/a&gt;，而不是黑匣子。这就是为什么我们的人工智能辅助可观察性方法优先考虑透明度、可解释性和用户控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-the-end-goal-measurable-business-impact&#34;&gt;5.最终目标：可衡量的业务影响&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;只有 14% 的受访者从财务角度量化可观察性投资回报率。大多数使用正常运行时间、事件频率和平均解决时间等运营指标。尽管企业领导者越来越依赖可观察性来进行主动问题管理和战略决策，但成本优化的排名却出奇地低。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;它emprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1838x1227/16fd50bf2a/etr-value-observability.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1838x1227/16fd50bf2a/etr-value-observability.png&#34;alt=&#34;显示对传达可观察性价值的响应的条形图：运营效率 (37%) 到 SLA 和合规性管理 (3%)。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1838x1227/16fd50bf2a/etr-value-observability.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;显示对传达可观察性价值的响应的条形图：运营效率 (37%) 到 SLA 和合规性管理 (3%)。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“我们研究可观察性如何帮助减少 MTTD 和 MTTR 事件。更短的检测和解决时间意味着更少的停机时间、更少的服务中断以及更一致的用户满意度。这是一个明显的价值标志，即使我们没有为其贴上价格标签。” – 一家咨询公司的 C 级高管，讲述如何在没有具体美元价值的情况下为可观察性结果分配价值&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是成熟度曲线的顶峰：可观察性成为业务驱动因素，而不仅仅是工程工具。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;我们的看法：&lt;/strong&gt;团队低估了可观察性的影响，因为可观察性提供的实际价值与当前衡量方式之间存在差距。随着可观察性的成熟，我们期望更多的团队将性能与业务成果（例如客户体验、开发人员生产力或收入保护）联系起来。最终，可观察性将不仅仅被视为一种运营工具，而且成为战略业务驱动力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;observabilitys-next-chapter&#34;&gt;可观察性的下一章&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这项调查证实了我们每天在 Grafana 实验室看到的情况：可观测性不再只是基础设施团队的职责；这对于数据驱动型企业的成功至关重要。 41% 的组织在过去一年中增加了可观察性支出，55% 的组织预计在未来一年进行更多投资，这一信息很明确：可观察性的价值只会不断增长。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但释放这一价值意味着沿着成熟曲线前进。它从统一平台开始，通过工具整合和严格的 SLO 实践取得进展，并展望人工智能辅助的见解和可衡量的业务影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是我们正在努力建设的未来。无论您是要整合工具、扩展 SLO 还是尝试 AI，Grafana Labs 都可以帮助您将数据转化为洞察，并将洞察转化为影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;methodology&#34;&gt;方法论&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这项研究是与市场研究公司 &lt;a href=&#34;https://etr.ai/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Enterprise Technology Research&lt;/a&gt; 合作进行的，该公司调查了来自世界各地的 150 名 IT 决策者参与了这项研究。该调查于 2025 年 7 月进行。受访者跨越多个行业，包括金融服务、医疗保健、IT、制造、教育、零售、政府等。为了符合资格，所有受访者都必须是总监或更高级别，并且对其组织的可观察性和监控实践有责任和可见性，并且高度熟悉所使用的技术堆栈、相关预算和采购决策。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;最后更新时间为 2025 年 10 月 6 日&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Taylor Swift (Grafana’s Version): How to track and visualize data related to pop’s biggest superstar】泰勒·斯威夫特（Grafana 版本）：如何跟踪和可视化与流行音乐巨星相关的数据</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/10/03/taylor-swift-grafanas-version-how-to-track-and-visualize-data-related-to-pop-s-biggest-superstar/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;It’s official: Taylor has entered her data visualization era. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, the pop icon and global superstar dropped &lt;em&gt;The Life of a Showgirl&lt;/em&gt;, her 12th studio album. And in the lead-up to this monumental event, a group of Swifties here at Grafana Labs had a thought: what better way to celebrate than with a Grafana dashboard?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From there, the group got to work and used &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; — an AI-powered agent in Grafana Cloud that helps you query and build dashboards faster using natural language — to create one of the most dazzling dashboards we’ve seen to date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So go grab your favorite cardigan and settle in, because in this post, we dive into &lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/a2000410bf714aac8103b9705a0b507e&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;a new Grafana Cloud dashboard&lt;/a&gt; that helps you track career milestones, analyze album vibes (is &lt;em&gt;Lover&lt;/em&gt; really more danceable than &lt;em&gt;1989&lt;/em&gt;?!), and visualize all the eras of the one and only Taylor Swift. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-a-quick-look-at-our-dashboard-creators-and-why-they-chose-assistant&#34;&gt;First, a quick look at our dashboard creators (and why they chose Assistant)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the reasons Grafana Assistant is so powerful is that it &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-for-grafana-onboarding-get-your-teams-started-quicker-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;enables a wide range of users&lt;/a&gt;, observability experts and novices alike, to more easily navigate to the right places in Grafana and build beautiful dashboards. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is exactly why the team of Grafanistas shown below — Ivana, Sven, Belyn, and Maggie —  chose Grafana Assistant for this Taylor-themed project: to ensure ease of use and that they’d all be empowered to contribute and create, regardless of their roles or experience levels with Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x628/f35975424a/taylor-dashboard-creators.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x628/f35975424a/taylor-dashboard-creators.png&#34;alt=&#34;A graphic introducing the Grafana Labs team behind the Taylor Swift dashboard, featuring four team members with favorite eras listed.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x628/f35975424a/taylor-dashboard-creators.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A graphic introducing the Grafana Labs team behind the Taylor Swift dashboard, featuring four team members with favorite eras listed.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in learning more about Assistant, and how our own engineering and product teams are using it to debug, query, and build faster, check out &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/09/11/debug-query-and-build-faster-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;this blog post&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;are-you-ready-for-it-a-tour-of-the-taylor-swift-dashboard&#34;&gt;Are You Ready For It? A tour of the Taylor Swift dashboard&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team used Assistant to build virtually every component of their Swift-acular dashboard, ranging from simple text panels to dynamic, data-driven charts. The process was highly iterative; they often started with an auto-generated dashboard and then refined it using natural language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The end result is a vibrant dashboard consisting of four distinct tabs, each offering a unique view into Taylor’s prolific career.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tab-1-profile-and-career-stats-&#34;&gt;Tab 1: Profile and career stats 🏆&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/a2000410bf714aac8103b9705a0b507e&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;first tab&lt;/a&gt; is designed to feel like an introduction to Taylor (every Swiftie has to start somewhere, right?). Using an array of static text panels, it offers a high-level snapshot of her career milestones — including a timeline of her eras and how many times she’s won a Grammy — along with some fun facts about her personal life. All of the text and data seen in these panels was generated by the built-in knowledge of Grafana Assistant&amp;rsquo;s LLM.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/f0df038850/eras-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/f0df038850/eras-gif.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A gif scrolling through colorful text panels representing Taylor Swift&amp;#39;s different musical eras.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/f0df038850/eras-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A gif scrolling through colorful text panels representing Taylor Swift&amp;#39;s different musical eras.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the lead-up to &lt;em&gt;The Life of a Showgirl&lt;/em&gt; release, this tab also included a live countdown to the Oct. 3 release date, created using Grafana’s clock panel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tab-2-musical-characteristics-and-song-analysis-&#34;&gt;Tab 2: Musical characteristics and song analysis 🎵&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/269a9b866c4d43f29a55854328e15596&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;second tab of the dashboard&lt;/a&gt; dives deeper into the music itself, using &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/grafana-bigquery-datasource/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Google BigQuery&lt;/a&gt; as the data source. The team imported a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/jarredpriester/taylor-swift-spotify-dataset&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Kaggle data set&lt;/a&gt; that’s built off a Spotify API to visualize key details and characteristics of Taylor’s end-to-end discography (including her re-recorded songs, &lt;em&gt;of course&lt;/em&gt;). Some of these characteristics include danceability, energy, and acousticness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/9796cd5fe0/musical-characteristics-tab.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/9796cd5fe0/musical-characteristics-tab.png&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the second tab in the Taylor Swift dashboard, displaying various analytics for her music, including valence, acoustics, tempo graphs, and a list of top-rated songs.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/9796cd5fe0/musical-characteristics-tab.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the second tab in the Taylor Swift dashboard, displaying various analytics for her music, including valence, acoustics, tempo graphs, and a list of top-rated songs.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The resulting panels help you visually track the evolution of Taylor’s musical style over the years, surfacing insights that are bound to spark discussion (and no doubt some debate) among fans. Some of the these insights include: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;“I Think He Knows” (&lt;em&gt;Lover&lt;/em&gt;) is the most danceable track&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;“Shake It Off” (&lt;em&gt;1989&lt;/em&gt;) is the track with the most valence (aka, conveys the most positivity)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;“Haunted” (&lt;em&gt;Speak Now&lt;/em&gt;) is the most energetic &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fun fact: the panels in this tab (and throughout much of the dashboard) follow the same color scheme that’s often used to denote Swift’s different albums and eras. &lt;em&gt;Midnights&lt;/em&gt; blue, anyone?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tab-3-eras-tour-analytics-&#34;&gt;Tab 3: Eras Tour analytics 🎤&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The friendship bracelets. The bodysuits. That iconic bridge from &lt;em&gt;Cruel Summer&lt;/em&gt;. The Eras Tour was epic in oh-so-many ways, and our team of Grafanistas knew their dashboard had to rep it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x813/c9962111a7/eras-tour-geomap-panel.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x813/c9962111a7/eras-tour-geomap-panel.png&#34;alt=&#34;A geomap panel from the third tab of the Taylor Swift dashboard, showing concert locations and attendance numbers for the Eras Tour.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x813/c9962111a7/eras-tour-geomap-panel.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A geomap panel from the third tab of the Taylor Swift dashboard, showing concert locations and attendance numbers for the Eras Tour.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s why they built the &lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/a38ed56984834dc794f4e1d209fb869d&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;third tab&lt;/a&gt;, which uses data to convey the incredible reach and impact of Taylor’s recent global tour. Like the Musical characteristics and song analysis tab, this one uses BigQuery and a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/tymonbot/taylor-swift-eras-toure&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Kaggle data set&lt;/a&gt; behind the scenes. Some of its highlights include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A geomap panel (shown above) that plots every tour stop by latitude and longitude, complete with attendance numbers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A ranking of the top cities by attendance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lists of opening acts for each show.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A pie chart and tables breaking down surprise performances.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tab-4-the-life-of-a-showgirl-&#34;&gt;Tab 4: The Life of a Showgirl ✨&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since Taylor’s new album inspired this project, the &lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/6eac2dfe57674a7280eaa78dfb9d9f5f&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;fourth and final tab&lt;/a&gt; is dedicated, of course, to &lt;em&gt;The Life of a Showgirl&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/e40b9ced61/life-of-a-showgirl-tab.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/e40b9ced61/life-of-a-showgirl-tab.png&#34;alt=&#34;The fourth tab of the Taylor Swift dashboard, displaying data related to The Life of Showgirl album, including a track duration analysis bar chart and a content advisory breakdown.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/e40b9ced61/life-of-a-showgirl-tab.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;The fourth tab of the Taylor Swift dashboard, displaying data related to The Life of Showgirl album, including a track duration analysis bar chart and a content advisory breakdown.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This tab provides a visual overview of the album, including a track listing and duration analysis, stats about the production team, and special features, like the Sabrina Carpenter collab. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bonus-a-grafana-assistant-easter-egg&#34;&gt;Bonus: A Grafana Assistant “Easter egg”&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the Swiftie-verse, an “Easter egg” refers to a hidden clue or detail that Taylor plants in her work to suggest something big (like a new album) is coming. Naturally, the Grafana Labs masterminds behind our new dashboard created a little Easter egg of their own.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1716x1766/300e583a8b/shake-it-off-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1716x1766/300e583a8b/shake-it-off-gif.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A gif showing the &amp;#39;Easter egg&amp;#39; planted in Grafana Assistant that makes the UI shake.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1716x1766/300e583a8b/shake-it-off-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A gif showing the &amp;#39;Easter egg&amp;#39; planted in Grafana Assistant that makes the UI shake.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you open Grafana Assistant in Grafana Cloud, you can type the name of a certain song (see above) into the chatbox, and the UI will give you a delightful little &lt;em&gt;shake… shake… shake&lt;/em&gt;. (Don’t have a Grafana Cloud account yet? You can &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;sign up for a free one&lt;/a&gt; today and start exploring with Assistant.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;build-the-dashboards-of-your-wildest-dreams&#34;&gt;Build the dashboards of your Wildest Dreams &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To all the Swifties out there, happy &lt;em&gt;The Life of a Showgirl&lt;/em&gt; release day. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We hope you’ll explore this new dashboard to track Taylor’s career milestones, musical evolution, and more. And if you haven’t already, give Grafana Assistant a try. The new AI-powered agent makes it easier and faster to build dashboards in Grafana Cloud — whether you’re monitoring system uptime or the world’s biggest pop star. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;官方消息：泰勒已进入数据可视化时代。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，这位流行偶像和全球巨星推出了她的第 12 张录音室专辑《The Life of a Showgirl》。在这场具有里程碑意义的活动之前，Grafana 实验室的一群 Swifties 想到了：还有什么比使用 Grafana 仪表板更好的庆祝方式呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从那时起，该团队开始工作并使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt;（Grafana Cloud 中的人工智能代理，可帮助您使用自然语言更快地查询和构建仪表板）创建了我们迄今为止见过的最令人眼花缭乱的仪表板之一。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所以，去拿上你最喜欢的羊毛衫，安顿下来吧，因为在这篇文章中，我们将深入探讨&lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/a2000410bf714aac8103b9705a0b507e&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;新的 Grafana Cloud 仪表板&lt;/a&gt; 它可以帮助您追踪职业里程碑、分析专辑氛围（&lt;em&gt;Lover&lt;/em&gt; 真的比 &lt;em&gt;1989&lt;/em&gt; 更适合跳舞吗？！），并可视化唯一泰勒·斯威夫特 (Taylor Swift) 的所有时代。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-a-quick-look-at-our-dashboard-creators-and-why-they-chose-assistant&#34;&gt;首先，快速浏览一下我们的信息中心创建者（以及他们选择 Google 助理的原因）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 如此强大的原因之一是它&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-for-grafana-onboarding-get-your-teams-started-quicker-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;让广泛的用户&lt;/a&gt;（可观察性专家和新手）能够更轻松地导航到 Grafana 中的正确位置并构建漂亮的仪表板。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这正是下面所示的 Grafanista 团队（Ivana、Sven、Belyn 和 Maggie）为这个 Taylor 主题项目选择 Grafana Assistant 的原因：确保易用性，并且无论他们在 Grafana 中的角色或经验水平如何，他们都有权做出贡献和创造。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x628/f35975424a/taylor-dashboard-creators.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x628/f35975424a/taylor-dashboard-creators.png&#34;alt=&#34;介绍 Taylor Swift 仪表板背后的 Grafana Labs 团队的图片，其中有四名团队成员，并列出了最喜欢的时代。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1200x628/f35975424a/taylor-dashboard-creators.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;该图介绍了 Taylor Swift 仪表板背后的 Grafana Labs 团队，其中包括四名团队成员，并列出了最喜欢的时代。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您有兴趣了解有关 Assistant 的更多信息，以及我们自己的工程和产品团队如何使用它来更快地调试、查询和构建，请查看出&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/09/11/debug-query-and-build-faster-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;这篇博文&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;are-you-ready-for-it-a-tour-of-the-taylor-swift-dashboard&#34;&gt;您准备好了吗？泰勒·斯威夫特仪表板之旅&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该团队使用 Assistant 构建了 Swift-aclar 仪表板的几乎所有组件，从简单的文本面板到动态的数据驱动图表。这个过程是高度迭代的；他们通常从自动生成的仪表板开始，然后使用自然语言对其进行完善。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最终结果是一个充满活力的仪表板，由四个不同的选项卡组成，每个选项卡都提供了泰勒多产职业生涯的独特视图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tab-1-profile-and-career-stats-&#34;&gt;标签 1：个人资料和职业统计数据🏆&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/a2000410bf714aac8103b9705a0b507e&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;第一个选项卡&lt;/a&gt;的设计感觉就像是对 Taylor 的介绍（每个 Swiftie 都必须从某个地方开始，对吧？）。它使用一系列静态文本面板，提供了她职业生涯里程碑的高级快照 - 包括她的时代时间表和她赢得格莱美奖的次数 - 以及有关她个人生活的一些有趣的事实。这些面板中看到的所有文本和数据都是由 Grafana Assistant 的法学硕士的内置知识生成的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/f0df038850/eras-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/f0df038850/eras-gif.gif&#34;alt=&#34;滚动浏览代表泰勒·斯威夫特不同音乐时代的彩色文本面板的 gif。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/f0df038850/eras-gif.gif”&#xA;alt=&#34;滚动浏览代表泰勒·斯威夫特不同音乐时代的彩色文本面板的 gif。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在《The Life of a Showgirl》发布之前，此选项卡还包含使用 Grafana 时钟面板创建的 10 月 3 日发布日期的实时倒计时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tab-2-musical-characteristics-and-song-analysis-&#34;&gt;标签 2：音乐特征和歌曲分析🎵&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/269a9b866c4d43f29a55854328e15596&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;仪表板的第二个选项卡&lt;/a&gt;使用&lt;a更深入地了解音乐本身 href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/grafana-bigquery-datasource/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Google BigQuery&lt;/a&gt; 作为数据源。该团队导入了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/jarredpriester/taylor-swift-spotify-dataset&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Kaggle 数据集&lt;/a&gt;，该数据集基于 Spotify API 构建，用于可视化关键详细信息和ch泰勒端到端唱片的特征（当然包括她重新录制的歌曲&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;）。其中一些特征包括舞蹈性、活力和声学性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/9796cd5fe0/musical-characteristics-tab.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/9796cd5fe0/musical-characteristics-tab.png&#34;alt=&#34;Taylor Swift 仪表板中第二个选项卡的屏幕截图，显示她音乐的各种分析，包括效价、声学、节奏图和列表 评分最高的歌曲。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/9796cd5fe0/musical-characteristics-tab.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;泰勒·斯威夫特仪表板中第二个选项卡的屏幕截图，显示她音乐的各种分析，包括效价、声学、节奏图和评分最高的歌曲列表。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由此产生的面板可帮助您直观地跟踪多年来泰勒音乐风格的演变，提出必然会引发歌迷之间讨论（无疑是一些辩论）的见解。其中一些见解包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;“I Think He Knows”（&lt;em&gt;Lover&lt;/em&gt;）是最适合跳舞的歌曲&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;“Shake It Off”（&lt;em&gt;1989&lt;/em&gt;）是最具效价的歌曲（也就是传达最多的积极性）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;“闹鬼”（&lt;em&gt;立即发言&lt;/em&gt;）是最有活力的&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有趣的事实：此选项卡中的面板（以及整个仪表板的大部分内容）遵循相同的配色方案，通常用于表示 Swift 的不同专辑和时代。 &lt;em&gt;午夜&lt;/em&gt;蓝色，有人吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tab-3-eras-tour-analytics-&#34;&gt;标签 3：Eras Tour 分析 🎤&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;友谊手镯。连体衣。 《残酷夏天》中的那座标志性桥梁。 Eras Tour 在很多方面都是史诗般的，我们的 Grafanista 团队知道他们的仪表板必须代表它。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x813/c9962111a7/eras-tour-geomap-panel.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x813/c9962111a7/eras-tour-geomap-panel.png&#34;alt=&#34;Taylor Swift 仪表板第三个选项卡中的地理地图面板，显示 Eras 巡演的音乐会地点和出席人数。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x813/c9962111a7/eras-tour-geomap-panel.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;泰勒·斯威夫特仪表板第三个选项卡中的地理地图面板，显示音乐会地点和出席者Eras 巡演的编号。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就是为什么他们构建了&lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/a38ed56984834dc794f4e1d209fb869d&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;第三个选项卡&lt;/a&gt;，该选项卡使用数据来传达 Taylor 最近的令人难以置信的影响力和影响力 全球巡演。与“音乐特征和歌曲分析”选项卡一样，此选项卡在后台使用 BigQuery 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.kaggle.com/datasets/tymonbot/taylor-swift-eras-toure&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Kaggle 数据集&lt;/a&gt;。它的一些亮点包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;地理地图面板（如上所示），按纬度和经度绘制每个旅游站点，并附有出席人数。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;按出席人数排列的顶级城市排名。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;每场演出的开场表演列表。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;饼图和表格详细说明了惊喜表现。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tab-4-the-life-of-a-showgirl-&#34;&gt;标签 4：歌舞女郎的生活 ✨&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由于泰勒的新专辑激发了这个项目的灵感，&lt;a href=&#34;https://swifties.grafana.net/public-dashboards/6eac2dfe57674a7280eaa78dfb9d9f5f&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;第四个也是最后一个选项卡&lt;/a&gt;当然致力于 &lt;em&gt;歌舞女郎的生活&lt;/em&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/e40b9ced61/life-of-a-showgirl-tab.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/e40b9ced61/life-of-a-showgirl-tab.png&#34;alt=&#34;Taylor Swift 仪表板的第四个选项卡，显示与 The Life of Showgirl 专辑相关的数据，包括曲目时长分析条形图和内容咨询细分。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x995/e40b9ced61/life-of-a-showgirl-tab.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Taylor Swift 仪表板的第四个选项卡，显示与《The Life of Showgirl》专辑相关的数据，包括曲目时长分析条形图和内容咨询细分。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此选项卡提供了专辑的直观概述，包括曲目列表和持续时间分析、制作团队的统计数据以及特殊功能，例如 Sabrina Carpenter 合作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bonus-a-grafana-assistant-easter-egg&#34;&gt;奖励：Grafana 助手“复活节彩蛋”&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Swiftie 诗句中，“复活节彩蛋”指的是泰勒在她的作品中植入的隐藏线索或细节，暗示着大事（比如新专辑）即将到来。当然，我们新仪表板背后的 Grafana Labs 策划者创造了他们自己的小复活节彩蛋。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;克拉ss=&#34;灯箱链接&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1716x1766/300e583a8b/shake-it-off-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1716x1766/300e583a8b/shake-it-off-gif.gif&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Assistant 中植入的“复活节彩蛋”gif，使 UI 震动。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1716x1766/300e583a8b/shake-it-off-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana Assistant 中植入的“复活节彩蛋”gif 动图，让 UI 震动。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您在 Grafana Cloud 中打开 Grafana Assistant 时，您可以在聊天框中输入某首歌曲的名称（见上文），UI 会给您带来令人愉悦的小震动&lt;em&gt;摇...摇...摇&lt;/em&gt;。 （还没有 Grafana Cloud 帐户？您可以&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即注册一个免费帐户&lt;/a&gt;并开始使用 Google 助理进行探索。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;build-the-dashboards-of-your-wildest-dreams&#34;&gt;构建您最狂野梦想的仪表板&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;致所有 Swifties，祝《The Life of a Showgirl》发行日快乐。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们希望您能探索这个新的仪表板来跟踪泰勒的职业里程碑、音乐演变等等。如果您还没有尝试过 Grafana Assistant。新的人工智能代理可以让您更轻松、更快速地在 Grafana Cloud 中构建仪表板 - 无论您是监控系统正常运行时间还是世界上最大的流行歌星。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>