<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</title>
    <link>/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</description>
    <item>
      <title>【ObservabilityCON on the Road: New cities announced for 2025】ObservabilityCON 路上：宣布 2025 年新城市</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/09/observabilitycon-on-the-road-new-cities-announced-for-2025/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Last September, observability enthusiasts and experts came together in New York City for &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;, our flagship open source observability conference that showcases the latest updates to the Grafana LGTM Stack (&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; for logs, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; for visualization, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/tempo/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt; for traces, and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt; for metrics) as well as deep-dive demos, workshops, and user success stories.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But for those of you who couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it to New York, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck: We&amp;rsquo;re bringing all the goodness of ObservabilityCON to a city near you with &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON on the Road&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After seeing the overwhelming excitement for these local events at the end of last year, we&amp;rsquo;re extending ObservabilityCON on the Road to the following locations:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bay Area on Feb. 25 (&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/2025/san-francisco-bay-area/&#34;&gt;Register now&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tokyo on Feb. 25, presented with Japanese translation (&lt;a href=&#34;/ja/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/2025/tokyo/&#34;&gt;Register now&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chicago on March 11 (&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/2025/chicago/&#34;&gt;Register now&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sydney on March 25 (&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/2025/sydney/&#34;&gt;Register now&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;btn-row &#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn--primary &#34; href=&#34;https://grafana.com/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Register for ObservabilityCON on the Road&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-to-expect-at-observability-on-the-road&#34;&gt;What to expect at Observability on the Road&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of the things &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/02/09/inside-observabilitycon-i-picked-up-so-much-practical-information/&#34;&gt;the community loves most about ObservabilityCON&lt;/a&gt; — Technical deep dives! Live demos! Ask the Experts booth! — will be included in these special one-day events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Along with presenting the original technical sessions from ObservabilityCON, Grafana Labs experts will share the stage in each city with local observability pros who will walk through their success stories and the lessons they learned along the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Registration is now open for ObservabilityCON on the Road in all four locations. We look forward to seeing you at one of these events!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;去年 9 月，可观测性爱好者和专家齐聚纽约，参加我们的旗舰开源可观测性会议 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;展示了 Grafana LGTM Stack 的最新更新 (&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; for日志，&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; 用于可视化，&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/tempo/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body -txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt; 用于跟踪，&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt; 用于指标）以及深入研究演示、研讨会和用户成功案例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是对于那些无法前往纽约的人来说，您很幸运：我们通过 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon-on 将 ObservabilityCON 的所有优点带到您附近的城市-the-road/&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 路上&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在去年年底看到这些当地活动的巨大兴奋之后，我们将 ObservabilityCON on the Road 扩展到以下地点：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;湾区 2 月 25 日（&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/2025/san-francisco-bay-area/&#34;&gt;立即报名&lt;/a&gt;）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2 月 25 日东京，提供日语翻译（&lt;a href=&#34;/ja/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/2025/tokyo/&#34;&gt;立即注册&lt;/a&gt;）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 月 11 日芝加哥（&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/2025/chicago/&#34;&gt;立即注册&lt;/a&gt;）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3 月 25 日悉尼（&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/2025/sydney/&#34;&gt;立即注册&lt;/a&gt;）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;btn-row &#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn--primary &#34; href=&#34;https://grafana.com/events/observabilitycon-on-the-road/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt &#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;注册 ObservabilityCON on the Road&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-to-expect-at-observability-on-the-road&#34;&gt;Observability on the Road 的期望&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/02/09/inside-observabilitycon-i-picked-up-so-much-practical-information/&#34;&gt;社区最喜欢 ObservabilityCON 的所有内容&lt;/a &gt; — 技术深入探讨！现场演示！请咨询专家展位！ — 将包含在这些特殊的一日活动中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了介绍 ObservabilityCON 的原创技术会议外，Grafana Labs 专家还将在每个城市与当地可观测性专业人士分享舞台，他们将讲述他们的成功故事以及一路上学到的经验教训。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ObservabilityCON on the Road 的注册现已在所有四个地点开放。我们期待在其中一场活动中见到您！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Add observability to cart: How online retailer ASOS reduces MTTR with Grafana Cloud】添加可观察性到购物车：在线零售商 ASOS 如何利用 Grafana Cloud 降低 MTTR</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/12/30/add-observability-to-cart-how-online-retailer-asos-reduces-mttr-with-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Like the fit your friend got on ASOS? There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance Grafana Cloud had something to do with that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each year, more than 20 million customers come to the UK-based online retailer to fill their digital carts, and they expect a seamless online experience as they shop and check out. ASOS can consistently provide that with the help of Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“There are alerts set up for many of our customer-facing journeys,” said Dylan Morley, Lead Principal Engineer at ASOS. &amp;ldquo;We know pretty instantly as soon as something starts going wrong.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;t4a9q4OLXfo&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/t4a9q4OLXfo?autoplay=1&amp;amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That was not always the case. About 10 years ago, &amp;ldquo;observability didn&amp;rsquo;t really exist as a concept. Data was spread out. It was difficult to find what you needed,&amp;rdquo; says Morley. Without a centralized data store, &amp;ldquo;when there was an incident, you had to go and find all of the information you wanted.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To alleviate that stress, ASOS began to use Grafana OSS in 2017, in large part due to Grafana Labs&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;big tent&amp;rdquo; philosophy, which allows organizations to choose their own tools and bring together all of their disparate data into one dynamic dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a growing catalog of &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/all-plugins/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;100+ plugins for Grafana&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/data-configuration/integrations/integration-reference/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;65+ Grafana Cloud integrations&lt;/a&gt; for monitoring third-party tools, &amp;ldquo;the data source model that Grafana gives us means that we can quickly plot any data from any source that we want alongside existing telemetry data that we might already have,&amp;rdquo; says Morley. &amp;ldquo;It gives us this holistic view to understand our systems from a user perspective.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Given the immediate benefits of Grafana, ASOS’ adoption of the open source tool grew quickly. By 2022, the team moved to the fully hosted Grafana Cloud platform to avoid updating and maintaining Grafana so they can focus on scaling their observability strategy and investing in other Grafana Cloud tools, such as &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/slo/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana SLO&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Monitoring&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Access to &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Enterprise plugins&lt;/a&gt; was another key benefit of moving to Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“When we were running Grafana ourselves, we needed to query New Relic and ServiceNow, so we built some in-house versions of plugins — but all that came with the overhead of maintenance,” Morley said. “One of the benefits of the Enterprise plugins was that we could deprecate [our existing plugins], just take advantage of the Grafana Cloud offering, and have less code that we need to own and maintain.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now when an issue occurs, &amp;ldquo;all the monitoring in one place helps,&amp;rdquo; says Fahri Ulucay, Site Reliability Engineer at ASOS. &amp;ldquo;We have high-level dashboards. If we see something fluctuating there, we can all go into Grafana, zoom in, look into details and that helps to identify [the issue] quicker and then resolve it quicker as well.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;When something shows red on our SLOs or our error budgets, we know that that&amp;rsquo;s a real problem … We are much more confident that the metrics that we are using accurately represent and describe the systems that ASOS relies on.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— Adam Watson, Lead Site Reliability Engineer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sounds too good to be true? There are about 800 other ASOS engineers using Grafana who would back this up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We have quite a few tools actually in SRE that we try and get people to use in the platforms, but I have never seen people have a problem with Grafana,&amp;rdquo; says Adam Watson, Lead Site Reliability Engineer. &amp;ldquo;I have to say one of the nice things about Grafana is, it&amp;rsquo;s just never been a blocker.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a result, &amp;ldquo;we are more prepared and more confident,&amp;rdquo; continues Watson. &amp;ldquo;We understand not only what metrics matter most to us but we understand how they sit in the holistic picture of the systems and the services that we support.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;To learn more about ASOS&amp;rsquo; observability stack and how Grafana Cloud has reduced MTTR and their overall costs, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;/success/asos/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ASOS success story&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;喜欢您朋友在 ASOS 上的表现吗？ Grafana Cloud 很可能与此有关。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每年，超过 2000 万客户来到这家英国在线零售商填写他们的数字购物车，他们希望在购物和结账时获得无缝的在线体验。 ASOS 可以在 Grafana Cloud 的帮助下始终如一地提供这一服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们为许多面向客户的旅程设置了警报，”ASOS 首席首席工程师 Dylan Morley 说道。 “一旦出现问题，我们就会立即知道。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“t4a9q4OLXfo”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/t4a9q4OLXfo?autoplay=1&amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;情况并非总是如此。大约 10 年前，“可观察性并不是一个真正存在的概念。数据被分散开来。很难找到你需要的东西，”莫利说。如果没有集中式数据存储，“当发生事件时，您必须去查找所需的所有信息。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了缓解这种压力，ASOS 于 2017 年开始使用 Grafana OSS，这在很大程度上归功于 Grafana Labs 的“大帐篷”理念，该理念允许组织选择自己的工具并将所有不同的数据整合到一个动态中仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/all-plugins/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;100 多个 Grafana 插件&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/ grafana-cloud/data-configuration/integrations/integration-reference/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;65+ Grafana Cloud 集成&lt;/a&gt;，用于监控第三方工具，“数据源模型Grafana 为我们提供了一种方法，让我们可以快速绘制我们想要的任何来源的任何数据以及我们可能已经拥有的现有遥测数据。”Morley 说道。 “它为我们提供了从用户角度理解我们系统的整体视图。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;鉴于 Grafana 带来的直接好处，ASOS 对开源工具的采用迅速增长。到 2022 年，该团队迁移到完全托管的 Grafana Cloud 平台，以避免更新和维护 Grafana，这样他们就可以专注于扩展其可观测性策略并投资其他 Grafana Cloud 工具，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/slo/ ?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana SLO&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/kubernetes/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Kubernetes监控&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;访问 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Enterprise 插件&lt;/a&gt;是迁移到 Grafana Cloud 的另一个主要好处。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“当我们自己运行 Grafana 时，我们需要查询 New Relic 和 ServiceNow，因此我们构建了一些内部版本的插件 - 但所有这些都伴随着维护开销，”Morley 说。 “企业插件的好处之一是我们可以弃用[我们现有的插件]，只需利用 Grafana云服务，我们需要拥有和维护的代码更少。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，当出现问题时，“在一个地方进行所有监控都会有所帮助”，ASOS 站点可靠性工程师 Fahri Ulucay 说道。 “我们有高级仪表板。如果我们看到那里有一些波动，我们都可以进入 Grafana，放大，查看细节，这有助于更快地识别[问题]，然后也更快地解决它。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“当我们的 SLO 或错误预算上出现红色时，我们就知道这是一个真正的问题……我们更有信心，我们使用的指标能够准确地表示和描述 ASOS 所依赖的系统。 ”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— Adam Watson，首席站点可靠性工程师&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;听起来好得令人难以置信？还有大约 800 名其他使用 Grafana 的 ASOS 工程师会支持这一点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们实际上在 SRE 中拥有相当多的工具，我们尝试让人们在平台中使用它们，但我从未见过人们对 Grafana 存在问题，”首席站点可靠性工程师 Adam Watson 说道。 “我不得不说 Grafana 的优点之一是，它从来都不是一个障碍。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，“我们准备得更充分，也更有信心，”沃森继续说道。 “我们不仅了解哪些指标对我们最重要，而且了解它们在我们支持的系统和服务的整体情况中的地位。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;要详细了解 ASOS 的可观测性堆栈以及 Grafana Cloud 如何降低 MTTR 及其总体成本，请查看 &lt;a href=&#34;/success/asos/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ASOS成功故事&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana SLO: Easily predict the likelihood that you&#39;ll hit your target】Grafana SLO：轻松预测实现目标的可能性</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/14/grafana-slo-easily-predict-the-likelihood-that-youll-hit-your-target/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Service-level objectives (SLOs) can be a great way to ensure you&amp;rsquo;re hitting your goals, but many software teams struggle to set realistic targets when they first set up the service-level indicators (SLIs) that underpin those efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes management has a decree that all services will operate with “three 9s” of availability; other times engineers pick a number out of thin air. But you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be selecting arbitrary figures or suggesting unrealistic expectations based on what others are doing. The whole point is to converge on a set of targets that serve as a quantifiable representation of reliable services and satisfied customers—customers who aren’t churning and leaving your service for your competitors&#39;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The classic guidance is to pick something and then iterate, but we think we (and you!) can do better. By leaning on the Grafana Machine Learning team&amp;rsquo;s statistical analysis experience and by assessing and iterating on your historical data, we can now give you a distilled view in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/slo/&#34;&gt;Grafana SLO&lt;/a&gt;—our application that makes it easy to create, manage, and scale SLOs, SLO dashboards, and error budget alerts in Grafana Cloud—that helps identify the risk associated with a given target.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-we-solve-the-guessing-game&#34;&gt;How we solve the guessing game&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With some experience with statistics and a set of historical data, we can produce a distilled view of the risk associated with a given target.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your boss may want you to achieve three 9s, but it’s hard to assess the probability that you’d hit that target or what the impact of an SLA breach might be—financial or otherwise. To quantify that risk, the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/slo/create/#statistical-predictions-beta&#34;&gt;statistical predictions&lt;/a&gt; feature (currently in beta) in Grafana SLO takess 90 days of historical data—queried from the metrics you specify when creating the SLO—and then we run some simulations on that data to produce a histogram of which simulations achieved what performance over a given month.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; We went with 90 days because it offers a nice balance of providing enough data to run simulations on and learn from while still being able to respond fairly quickly. While more data would be better, it would also slow down the predictions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We calculate the risk of breaching your error budget by taking the result of the simulation and fitting it to a cumulative distribution function. To begin with we are using a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Weibull_distribution&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Weibull Distribution&lt;/a&gt; that fits our data fairly well and is traditionally used in failure analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By fitting a distribution, we can use the cumulative distribution function to easily calculate the probability of meeting a target and display a meaningful visualization to the user. As this feature matures we will continue to iterate on the models used to provide the most accurate predictions possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-check-your-chances-of-meeting-your-objective&#34;&gt;How to check your chances of meeting your objective&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get started, simply go to Grafana SLO and click on &lt;strong&gt;Manage SLOs&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Edit SLO&lt;/strong&gt;. Next, go to &lt;strong&gt;Set target and error budget&lt;/strong&gt;, where you&amp;rsquo;ll see a graph that allows you to &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/slo/create/#statistical-predictions-beta&#34;&gt;drag the vertical line along the x-axis&lt;/a&gt; with your cursor or click to drop the cursor on a given point along the x-axis. As you move your cursor, the text above the graph will update to show the probability of meeting that target.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From this view, you can eyeball where your desired performance might lie on the histogram and get a feel for whether your historical data supports your target. But the real goal is to empower service owners to make better decisions with the data—and we believe that quantifying the risk associated with a given target is a powerful way to think about it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/slo-prediction/prediction.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/slo-prediction/prediction.gif&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;600&#34;height=&#34;404&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/slo-prediction/prediction.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;600&#34;height=&#34;404&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you’re operating as a startup and rapidly trying to enter an emerging market, you might be OK with a 50% chance of missing a target service level. But as your product matures, you might assume a more risk-averse target and only accept a 5% chance of breaching an SLO each month.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you have certain high value customers who require a more reliable service. Being able to assess the risk associated with a given service level objective allows you to make more informed business decisions in your SLA contracts, or to determine when special customers need to be split out of multi-tenant infrastructure to be able to provide a guaranteed level or service.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-slos&#34;&gt;How to get the most out of your SLOs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SLOs can be incredibly powerful, but they&amp;rsquo;re still a relatively new endeavor for most teams. Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve shown you how to use this feature, let&amp;rsquo;s briefly discuss some additional best practices to keep in mind as you build out your goals and how Grafana SLO can help you get there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Empowering your teams with the knowledge and confidence to believe they can actually achieve their targets is a noble endeavor, but it isn’t the end goal if it doesn’t align with your customer’s expectations. Customer satisfaction is the real target of any SLO—you want a proxy measurement that correlates with customer satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ML can help you pick realistic targets on Day One, but you still need to iterate and bring user surveys and information from your customer support teams into the mix. It’s a chicken-and-egg kind of problem; most customers can’t tell you how many 9s they’ll be satisfied with, and most greenfield products can’t guarantee a minimum level of service. We can help you pick a realistic target, based on historical data, but you still have to iterate with your users and validate that your targets yield satisfied customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your achievable target isn’t good enough and your customers are leaving for other offerings in the market, then you should raise your target and prioritize stability work to keep them from churning. If your target is too high, you might be spending too much time on reliability and you’re missing the opportunity to operate at a higher velocity with continuous deployment pipelines and canary deployment models. High velocity teams make for satisfied engineers and that impacts your bottom line, too. It’s all about having the data to balance the tradeoffs for your business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another hidden pitfall of high reliability systems is that most customers will begin to assume that the performance they are getting is the standard, even if it’s better than what they’ve actually been promised. There are &lt;a href=&#34;https://sre.google/sre-book/service-level-objectives/#xref_risk-management_global-chubby-planned-outage&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;published studies from Google&lt;/a&gt; about the benefits of intentionally degrading your service level to ensure that your customers don’t come to expect near-perfect performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You won’t often hear praise from customers for above-satisfied performance of your service, but you’ll hear the bad. If customer support escalations aren&amp;rsquo;t clearly reflected by error budget burn in your existing SLOs, you need to review whether you&amp;rsquo;re measuring the right things. If you’ve been over-delivering, you run the risk of angering your users with an outage, even if you’re within your error budget. You might schedule some end-of–month downtime before your users grow too accustomed to your too-high availability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SLOs should impact software planning and inform future priorities. But you need to make sure they represent your customers&amp;rsquo; needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-could-come-next-for-grafana-slo&#34;&gt;What could come next for Grafana SLO&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re excited about this new functionality, but we think this can be taken further to help users select an SLO target that produces an acceptable volume of alerts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When using &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/slo/best-practices/#multidimensional-sli&#34;&gt;multidimensional SLIs&lt;/a&gt; (i.e., SLIs that “group by” cluster, for example), the alerts fire for individual dimensions, not for the combined SLO as is used for the simulation and target selection. Our current simulations don’t take into account realities where one cluster may be consistently underperforming others, but this is something we&amp;rsquo;d like to look into in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s not all! Accurately modeling the risk of breaching an SLO allows us to rethink how we use SLOs. For example, after an incident it is common to want to know if you are now at risk of exhausting your error budget or not. Using this simulation technique we can quantitatively answer this question and allow you to quickly pivot to prioritizing more reliability work if necessary, or perhaps delay risky features until the next period. There are also use cases for improving how we alert on SLOs to reduce noise and only alert when there is significant risk of error budget exhaustion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;服务级别目标 (SLO) 是确保实现目标的好方法，但许多软件团队在首次设置支撑这些工作的服务级别指标 (SLI) 时很难设定切合实际的目标.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有时，管理层会颁布一项法令，要求所有服务都以“三个 9”的可用性运行；有时工程师会凭空挑选一个数字。但你不应该根据其他人的行为来选择任意的数字或提出不切实际的期望。重点是集中在一组目标上，这些目标可以量化地代表可靠的服务和满意的客户——这些客户不会流失并离开你的服务而转向竞争对手。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;经典的指导是选择一些东西然后迭代，但我们认为我们（和你！）可以做得更好。凭借 Grafana 机器学习团队的统计分析经验以及对您的历史数据进行评估和迭代，我们现在可以在 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/slo/&#34;&gt;Grafana SLO&lt;/a&gt; 中为您提供精炼视图- 我们的应用程序可以轻松地在 Grafana Cloud 中创建、管理和扩展 SLO、SLO 仪表板和错误预算警报 - 有助于识别与给定目标相关的风险。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-we-solve-the-guessing-game&#34;&gt;我们如何解决猜谜游戏&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;凭借一些统计经验和一组历史数据，我们可以生成与给定目标相关的风险的精炼视图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您的老板可能希望您实现三个 9，但很难评估您实现该目标的可能性或违反 SLA 可能产生的影响（财务或其他方面）。为了量化该风险，Grafana 中的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/slo/create/#statistical-predictions-beta&#34;&gt;统计预测&lt;/a&gt;功能（目前处于测试阶段） SLO 需要 90 天的历史数据（根据您在创建 SLO 时指定的指标进行查询），然后我们对该数据运行一些模拟，以生成一个直方图，显示哪些模拟在给定的范围内实现了哪些性能月。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;我们选择了 90 天，因为它提供了一个很好的平衡，既提供足够的数据来运行模拟并从中学习，同时仍然能够相当快速地做出响应。虽然数据越多越好，但也会减慢预测速度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们通过模拟结果并将其拟合到累积分布函数来计算超出错误预算的风险。首先，我们使用非常适合我们数据的&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Weibull_distribution&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;威布尔分布&lt;/a&gt;传统上用于故障分析。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过拟合分布，我们可以使用累积分布函数轻松计算满足目标的概率并向用户显示有意义的可视化。作为该功能成熟后，我们将继续迭代用于提供最准确预测的模型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-check-your-chances-of-meeting-your-objective&#34;&gt;如何检查实现目标的机会&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要开始使用，只需转到 Grafana SLO 并点击&lt;strong&gt;管理 SLO&lt;/strong&gt; &gt; &lt;strong&gt;编辑 SLO&lt;/strong&gt;。接下来，转到&lt;strong&gt;设置目标和错误预算&lt;/strong&gt;，您将在其中看到一个图表，可让您&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/slo/create/ #statistical-predictions-beta&#34;&gt;用光标沿 x 轴拖动垂直线&lt;/a&gt;，或单击将光标放在 x 轴上的给定点上。当您移动光标时，图表上方的文本将会更新，以显示达到该目标的概率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从此视图中，您可以观察您想要的性能可能位于直方图上的位置，并了解您的历史数据是否支持您的目标。但真正的目标是让服务所有者能够利用数据做出更好的决策，而且我们相信量化与给定目标相关的风险是一种强有力的思考方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：600px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/slo-prediction/prediction.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/slo-prediction/prediction.gif”alt =“”宽度=“600”高度=“404”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/slo-prediction/prediction.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=“”宽度=“600”高度=“404”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您作为一家初创公司运营并迅速尝试进入新兴市场时，即使有 50% 的机会无法达到目标服务水平，您也可以接受。但随着您的产品成熟，您可能会假设一个更加规避风险的目标，并且每月仅接受 5% 的违反 SLO 的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;也许您有某些需要更可靠服务的高价值客户。能够评估与给定服务级别目标相关的风险，使您能够在 SLA 合同中做出更明智的业务决策，或者确定何时需要将特殊客户从多租户基础架构中分离出来，以便能够提供有保证的级别或服务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-get-the-most-out-of-your-slos&#34;&gt;如何充分利用 SLO&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SLO 的功能非常强大，但对于大多数团队来说，它们仍然是一项相对较新的尝试。现在我们已经向您展示了如何使用此功能，让我们简要讨论一下在您制定目标时需要记住的一些其他最佳实践，以及 Grafana SLO 如何帮助您实现目标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为您的团队提供知识和信心，让他们相信他们能够真正实现目标是一项崇高的努力，但如果它与客户的期望不符，那么它就不是最终目标。库斯托用户满意度是任何 SLO 的真正目标 - 您需要一个与客户满意度相关的代理衡量标准。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;机器学习可以帮助您在第一天选择现实的目标，但您仍然需要迭代并将用户调查和客户支持团队的信息纳入其中。这是一个先有鸡还是先有蛋的问题。大多数客户无法告诉您他们会对多少个 9 感到满意，而且大多数新产品也无法保证最低水平的服务。我们可以帮助您根据历史数据选择一个现实的目标，但您仍然需要与您的用户进行迭代并验证您的目标是否能带来满意的客户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的可实现目标不够好，并且您的客户正在转向市场上的其他产品，那么您应该提高目标并优先考虑稳定性工作，以防止他们流失。如果您的目标太高，您可能会在可靠性上花费太多时间，并且错过通过持续部署管道和金丝雀部署模型以更高速度运行的机会。高速度的团队会让工程师满意，这也会影响您的利润。这一切都是为了利用数据来平衡您的业务的权衡。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;高可靠性系统的另一个隐藏陷阱是，大多数客户会开始认为他们获得的性能是标准的，即使它比他们实际承诺的要好。有&lt;a href=&#34;https://sre.google/sre-book/service-level-objectives/#xref_risk-management_global-chubby-planned-outage&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;已发表的研究Google&lt;/a&gt;介绍了故意降低服务级别以确保您的客户不会期望近乎完美的性能的好处。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您不会经常听到客户对您的服务表现感到满意，但您会听到不好的声音。如果现有 SLO 中的错误预算消耗没有清楚地反映客户支持升级，那么您需要检查您是否在衡量正确的事情。如果您过度交付，即使在错误预算之内，您也会面临因中断而激怒用户的风险。您可以在用户太习惯您过高的可用性之前安排一些月末停机时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SLO 应影响软件规划并为未来的优先事项提供信息。但您需要确保它们代表客户的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-c​​ould-come-next-for-grafana-slo&#34;&gt;Grafana SLO 接下来会发生什么&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们对这项新功能感到很兴奋，但我们认为可以进一步帮助用户选择产生可接受数量的警报的 SLO 目标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/slo/best-practices/#multiDimension-sli&#34;&gt;多维 SLI&lt;/a&gt; 时（即“分组依据”的 SLI）例如，集群），警报会针对个人的一毛钱而触发nsions，不适用于用于模拟和目标选择的组合 SLO。我们当前的模拟没有考虑到一个集群可能始终表现不佳的现实，但这是我们未来想要研究的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这还不是全部！准确地对违反 SLO 的风险进行建模使我们能够重新思考如何使用 SLO。例如，发生事件后，通常想知道您现在是否面临耗尽错误预算的风险。使用这种模拟技术，我们可以定量地回答这个问题，并允许您在必要时快速转向优先考虑更多的可靠性工作，或者可能将有风险的功能推迟到下一个时期。还有一些用例可以改进我们对 SLO 的警报方式，以减少噪音，并且仅在存在错误预算耗尽的重大风险时发出警报。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to send OTLP or Prometheus metrics and logs to Grafana Cloud with Grafana Alloy】如何使用 Grafana Alloy 将 OTLP 或 Prometheus 指标和日志发送到 Grafana Cloud</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/03/how-to-send-otlp-or-prometheus-metrics-and-logs-to-grafana-cloud-with-grafana-alloy/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We introduced &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/alloy-opentelemetry-collector/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt; last year in an effort to create the best possible open source &amp;ldquo;big tent&amp;rdquo; telemetry collector. A continuation of our work on Grafana Agent Flow, we designed Alloy to simplify observability at scale and to easily integrate with the OpenTelemetry and Prometheus ecosystems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ve seen lots of interest since Alloy was &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/alloy-opentelemetry-collector/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;announced at GrafanaCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;, and industry observers are &lt;a href=&#34;https://observability-360.com/article/ViewArticle?id=o11ys-observability-awards-2024&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;taking notice, too&lt;/a&gt;. That&amp;rsquo;s because Alloy is an OTLP-compatible collector with built-in Prometheus optimizations and enterprise-grade features for collecting signals across your metrics, logs, traces, and profiles—making it ideal for all your cloud native infrastructure and application observability demands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alloy can also process and transform your data before sending it to OTel-compabile databases or collectors, including Grafana Cloud. You can even use Alloy to write alerting rules.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If this all sounds great but you aren&amp;rsquo;t sure where to start, keep reading for handy tips and demos from our Grafana Labs experts about how to send and receive telemetry with Alloy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-receive-otlp-metrics-and-send-them-to-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;How to receive OTLP metrics and send them to Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seeing as how Alloy is a distribution of the OpenTelemetry Collector, it only makes sense to start with OTLP (OpenTelemetry protocol) metrics. More specifically, let&amp;rsquo;s look at how to use Alloy to receive metrics from an application instrumented with OTel and then send that data to &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To do so, you&amp;rsquo;ll use four OpenTelemetry components:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;otelcol.receiver.otlp&lt;/code&gt;, which receives metrics in OTLP format via HTTP and forwards them&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;otelcol.processor.attributes&lt;/code&gt;, which transforms the attributes associated with a metric&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;otelcol.exporter.otlphttp&lt;/code&gt;, which sends the metrics to Grafana Cloud using credentials&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;otelcol.auth.basic&lt;/code&gt; for exposing those credentials&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll also enable Alloy&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/alloy/latest/troubleshoot/debug/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;live debugging&lt;/a&gt; feature, which will help build the transformations we want for the attributes processor and to make sure we&amp;rsquo;re comfortable with those attributes before we begin sending the metrics to Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you have that set up, you&amp;rsquo;ll use the &lt;code&gt;run&lt;/code&gt; command, and you&amp;rsquo;ll then be able to see the four connected components in the Alloy UI. If you click on the &lt;code&gt;otelcol.processor.attributes&lt;/code&gt; component, you can go into live debugging to see which metrics are passing through the component and identify any necessary changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From there, you can go to your Grafana Cloud instance and look for the specific OTLP metric you&amp;rsquo;ve set Alloy to collect. If you run a query on that metric, it should appear in your graph in just a few seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more details on how to set up this type of OTLP metrics pipeline, check out the full Ask the Experts demo from William Dumont, a software engineer on the Alloy squad, below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;IRqQEzc0kvA&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IRqQEzc0kvA?autoplay=1&amp;amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; As we alluded to earlier, if you have experience with Grafana Agent Flow, you&amp;rsquo;ll be right at home with Alloy, as it uses the same components, code, and concepts. However, Grafana Agent and Grafana Agent Operator have been depreciated. They are currently in Long-Term Support (LTS) and are expected to reach End-of-Life (EOL) on Nov. 1, 2025. For more information on how to transition to Alloy, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-agent-to-grafana-alloy-opentelemetry-collector-faq/&#34;&gt;Agent to Alloy FAQ blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-send-prometheus-metrics-to-grafana-cloud-using-alloy&#34;&gt;How to send Prometheus metrics to Grafana Cloud using Alloy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we already mentioned, while Alloy is a distribution of the OpenTelmetry Collector, it&amp;rsquo;s also designed to work seamlessly with Prometheus, as well. This is essential functionality, as 85% of OpenTelemetry users also use Prometheus in production, according to our second annual &lt;a href=&#34;/observability-survey/2024/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#oss-is-the-de-facto-approach-to-observability&#34;&gt;Observability Survey&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate how to use Alloy to send Prometheus metrics to Grafana Cloud, let&amp;rsquo;s imagine you have an application exposing metrics in a Docker container. For this, we&amp;rsquo;ll need three components:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;prometheus.scrape&lt;/code&gt;, which collects metrics from our target every three seconds&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;prometheus.relabel&lt;/code&gt;, which is used to edit labels attached to the metrics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;prometheus.remote_write&lt;/code&gt;, which sends the metrics to Grafana Cloud using basic authentication to pass the necessary credentials.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Again, we&amp;rsquo;ll use live debugging—this time to assist in building the rules for &lt;code&gt;prometheus.relabel&lt;/code&gt;. Before running the config, we&amp;rsquo;ll use a little trick and break the pipeline so we can shape the labels before they&amp;rsquo;re stored in our database. To do so, use the &lt;code&gt;run&lt;/code&gt; command, bypass the path for the config file, and set the stability level to &lt;code&gt;experimental&lt;/code&gt;. From there you check your &lt;code&gt;prometheus.remote_write&lt;/code&gt; component via live debugging and add any desired rules to filter out any unwanted data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just like our last example, once you&amp;rsquo;ve set up your pipeline, you can go to Grafana Cloud, where you should be able to find your metric and quickly run a query on it. For more details, check out William&amp;rsquo;s second Ask the Expert video below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;_MbB8IVKMfw&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_MbB8IVKMfw?autoplay=1&amp;amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-send-grafana-alloy-logs-to-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;How to send Grafana Alloy logs to Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve walked through sending OpenTelemetry and Prometheus metrics to Grafana Cloud, let&amp;rsquo;s look at the next most popular telemetry type: logs. In this example, we&amp;rsquo;ll send the data to Grafana Cloud Logs, which is powered by Grafana Loki.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To do so, we&amp;rsquo;ll need three components:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;logging&lt;/code&gt;, and in our example we&amp;rsquo;ll use &lt;code&gt;debug&lt;/code&gt; level to get the most information possible, as well as &lt;code&gt;logfmt&lt;/code&gt; for the format, though you can also use JSON. The other important argument here is &lt;code&gt;write_to&lt;/code&gt;, which tells the logging framework where to send those logs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.process&lt;/code&gt;, which is a pipeline unto itself. You can add any number of stages here, but for our purposes we&amp;rsquo;ll just add the service name, and we&amp;rsquo;ll use &lt;code&gt;alloy&lt;/code&gt; so we can identify it on the frontend&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.write&lt;/code&gt;, is what actually sends the data from Alloy to Grafana Cloud, or any Loki-compatible endpoint.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you have that set up to suit your needs, go back to the Alloy UI to see all your components running. Then, go to Grafana Cloud and look for the Alloy label filter. If you run a query on that label filter, you should see logs coming though and you can manipulate your data as needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To find out more, check out this Ask the Expert video below from Matthew Durham, a senior software developer on the Alloy squad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;nUwHzT1sprU&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nUwHzT1sprU?autoplay=1&amp;amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more-about-alloyonline-or-in-person&#34;&gt;Learn more about Alloy—online or in person&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for more information to help you get started with Grafana Alloy, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/alloy/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; for all sorts of helpful resources, and read &lt;a href=&#34;/tags/grafana-alloy/&#34;&gt;some of our Grafana Alloy-related blogs&lt;/a&gt; that run through specific Alloy use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also watch our &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/introducing-otel-collector-distribution-grafana-alloy/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2024&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/opentelemetry-grafana-alloy-beyla-demo-of-instrumentation-ingestion/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt; talks that featured the collector. And if you plan on attending either &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025 in Seattle&lt;/a&gt; this May, or ObservabilityCON 2025 later this year, remember that we&amp;rsquo;ll have Ask the Expert booths fully staffed to help answer all your toughest questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们去年推出了&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/alloy-opentelemetry-collector/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt;，致力于打造最好的开源“大帐篷” ”遥测收集器。作为 Grafana Agent Flow 工作的延续，我们设计了 Alloy 来大规模简化可观测性，并轻松与 OpenTelemetry 和 Prometheus 生态系统集成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自 Alloy &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/alloy-opentelemetry-collector/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;在 GrafanaCON 2024 上发布&lt;/a&gt;以来，我们已经看到了很多人的兴趣，行业观察家也表示&lt;a href=&#34;https://observability-360.com/article/ViewArticle?id=o11ys-observability-awards-2024&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;也注意到了&lt;/a&gt;。这是因为 Alloy 是一款兼容 OTLP 的收集器，具有内置的 Prometheus 优化和企业级功能，用于收集指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件中的信号，使其成为满足所有云原生基础设施和应用程序可观测性需求的理想选择。 p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alloy 还可以在将数据发送到 OTel 兼容数据库或收集器（包括 Grafana Cloud）之前处理和转换您的数据。您甚至可以使用 Alloy 编写警报规则。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果这一切听起来不错，但您不确定从哪里开始，请继续阅读我们的 Grafana Labs 专家提供的有关如何使用 Alloy 发送和接收遥测数据的实用提示和演示。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-receive-otlp-metrics-and-send-them-to-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;如何接收 OTLP 指标并将其发送到 Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;鉴于 Alloy 是 OpenTelemetry Collector 的一个发行版，只有从 OTLP（OpenTelemetry 协议）指标开始才有意义。更具体地说，让我们看看如何使用 Alloy 从使用 OTel 检测的应用程序接收指标，然后将该数据发送到 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a &gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为此，您将使用四个 OpenTelemetry 组件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;otelcol.receiver.otlp&lt;/code&gt;，它通过 HTTP 接收 OTLP 格式的指标并转发它们&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;otelcol.processor.attributes&lt;/code&gt;，用于转换与指标关联的属性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;otelcol.exporter.otlphttp&lt;/code&gt;，它使用凭据将指标发送到 Grafana Cloud&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;otelcol.auth.basic&lt;/code&gt; 用于公开这些凭据&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还将启用 Alloy 的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/alloy/latest/troubleshoot/debug/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;实时调试&lt;/a&gt;功能，这将有助于构建我们的转换需要属性处理器，并确保在开始将指标发送到 Grafana Cloud 之前我们对这些属性感到满意。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成设置后，您将使用 &lt;code&gt;run&lt;/code&gt; 命令，然后您将能够在 Alloy UI 中看到四个连接的组件。如果点击&lt;code&gt;otelcol.processor.attributes&lt;/code&gt;组件，就可以进入live 调试以查看哪些指标正在通过组件并确定任何必要的更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从那里，您可以转到 Grafana Cloud 实例并查找您设置 Alloy 收集的特定 OTLP 指标。如果您对该指标运行查询，它应该会在几秒钟内出现在您的图表中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关如何设置此类 OTLP 指标管道的更多详细信息，请查看下面由 Alloy 团队的软件工程师 William Dumont 提供的完整“专家咨询”演示。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“IRqQEzc0kvA”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/IRqQEzc0kvA?autoplay=1&amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;正如我们之前提到的，如果您有使用 Grafana Agent Flow 的经验，您就会熟悉 Alloy，因为它使用相同的组件、代码和概念。但是，Grafana Agent 和 Grafana Agent Operator 已折旧。它们目前处于长期支持 (LTS) 状态，预计将于 2025 年 11 月 1 日达到生命周期终止 (EOL)。有关如何过渡到 Alloy 的更多信息，请查看我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/ blog/2024/04/09/grafana-agent-to-grafana-alloy-opentelemetry-collector-faq/&#34;&gt;Agent to Alloy 常见问题博文&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-send-prometheus-metrics-to-grafana-cloud-using-alloy&#34;&gt;如何使用 Alloy 将 Prometheus 指标发送到 Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正如我们已经提到的，虽然 Alloy 是 OpenTelmetry Collector 的发行版，但它也被设计为与 Prometheus 无缝协作。这是一项基本功能，因为根据我们的第二份年度报告，85% 的 OpenTelemetry 用户也在生产中使用 Prometheus &lt;a href=&#34;/observability-survey/2024/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt#oss-is-the-de -facto-approach-to-observability&#34;&gt;可观察性调查&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了说明如何使用 Alloy 将 Prometheus 指标发送到 Grafana Cloud，我们假设您有一个在 Docker 容器中公开指标的应用程序。为此，我们需要三个组件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;prometheus.scrape&lt;/code&gt;，每三秒从我们的目标收集一次指标&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;prometheus.relabel&lt;/code&gt;，用于编辑附加到指标的标签。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;prometheus.remote_write&lt;/code&gt;，它使用基本身份验证来传递必要的凭据，将指标发送到 Grafana Cloud。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将再次使用实时调试，这一次是为了帮助构建 &lt;code&gt;prometheus.relabel&lt;/code&gt; 的规则。在运行配置之前，我们将使用一些小技巧并打破管道，以便我们可以在将标签存储到数据库之前对其进行整形。为此，请使用 &lt;code&gt;run&lt;/code&gt; 命令，绕过配置文件的路径，并将稳定性级别设置为&lt;code&gt;实验&lt;/code&gt;。从那里，您可以通过实时调试检查您的 &lt;code&gt;prometheus.remote_write&lt;/code&gt; 组件，并添加任何所需的规则来过滤掉任何不需要的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;就像我们的上一个示例一样，设置管道后，您可以转到 Grafana Cloud，您应该能够在其中找到您的指标并快速对其运行查询。有关更多详细信息，请观看下面 William 的第二个“询问专家”视频。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“_MbB8IVKMfw”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/_MbB8IVKMfw?autoplay=1&amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-send-grafana-alloy-logs-to-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;如何将 Grafana Alloy 日志发送到 Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在我们已经完成了将 OpenTelemetry 和 Prometheus 指标发送到 Grafana Cloud 的过程，让我们看看下一个最流行的遥测类型：日志。在此示例中，我们将数据发送到由 Grafana Loki 提供支持的 Grafana Cloud Logs。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为此，我们需要三个组件：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;logging&lt;/code&gt;，在我们的示例中，我们将使用 &lt;code&gt;debug&lt;/code&gt; 级别来获取尽可能多的信息，以及 &lt;code&gt;logfmt&lt;/code&gt; 格式，不过您也可以使用 JSON。这里的另一个重要参数是 write_to，它告诉日志框架将这些日志发送到哪里&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.process&lt;/code&gt;，它本身就是一个管道。您可以在此处添加任意数量的阶段，但出于我们的目的，我们将仅添加服务名称，并且我们将使用&lt;code&gt;alloy&lt;/code&gt;，以便我们可以在前端识别它&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.write&lt;/code&gt;，实际上是将数据从 Alloy 发送到 Grafana Cloud 或任何与 Loki 兼容的端点。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;完成满足您需求的设置后，请返回 Alloy UI 以查看所有组件的运行情况。然后，转到 Grafana Cloud 并查找 Alloy 标签过滤器。如果您对该标签过滤器运行查询，您应该会看到日志，并且您可以根据需要操作数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解更多信息，请观看下面由 Alloy 团队的高级软件开发人员 Matthew Durham 制作的“询问专家”视频。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“nUwHzT1sprU”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nUwHzT1sprU?autoplay=1&amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more-about-alloyonline-or-in-person&#34;&gt;在线或亲自了解有关 Alloy 的更多信息&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您正在寻找更多信息来帮助您开始使用 Grafana Alloy，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/alloy/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;获取各种有用的资源，并阅读&lt;a href=&#34;/tags/grafana-alloy/&#34;&gt;我们的一些与 Grafana Alloy 相关的博客&lt;/a&gt;，其中介绍了特定 Alloy 用例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您还可以观看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/introducing-otel-collector-distribution-grafana-alloy/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;一个href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/opentelemetry-grafana-alloy-beyla-demo-of-instrumentation-ingestion/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt; 以收藏家为主角的演讲。如果您计划参加&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; &gt;今年 5 月在西雅图举行的 GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/a&gt;，或今年晚些时候举行的 ObservabilityCON 2025，请记住，我们将配备配备齐全的“专家咨询”摊位来帮助解答所有问题你最棘手的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OpenTelemetry and Grafana Labs: what’s new and what’s next in 2025】OpenTelemetry 和 Grafana Labs：2025 年的新增功能和下一步发展</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/07/opentelemetry-and-grafana-labs-whats-new-and-whats-next-in-2025/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As the new year rolls in, it’s a great time to reflect and think big. What were some of your notable achievements in 2024, and what are your goals for 2025? We often do this in our personal lives — but why not apply this same line of thinking to observability, as well?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Observability continues to be a hot topic, and OpenTelemetry, in particular, continues to gain some serious momentum. One of the fastest growing open source projects in the cloud native arena, OpenTelemetry saw a 45% YoY increase in code commits on GitHub in 2024, along with a 100% increase in search volume on Google, according to a&lt;a href=&#34;/opentelemetry-report/&#34;&gt; recent OpenTelemetry report&lt;/a&gt;. The open source project was also a popular topic at major industry events, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://monitorama.com/2024/pdx.html#schedule&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Monitorama&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://promcon.io/2024-berlin/schedule/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;PromCon&lt;/a&gt;, KubeCon &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;North America&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccnceu2024.sched.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Europe&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs remains fully committed to OpenTelemetry, with several Grafanistas — myself included — actively maintaining and contributing to the project. In the spirit of the new year, let’s take a look back at some of the major ways the OpenTelemetry project evolved last year, and provide a peek at what’s to come in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;recent-opentelemetry-project-milestones&#34;&gt;Recent OpenTelemetry project milestones&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;support-for-profiling&#34;&gt;Support for profiling&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2023, OpenTelemetry achieved stability for &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2023/11/07/opentelemetry-at-kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2023-update/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;logs, metrics, and traces&lt;/a&gt; and, in 2024, the OTel community made another major announcement: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/03/19/opentelemetry-announces-support-for-profiling/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;support for profiling&lt;/a&gt;. OpenTelemetry’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/oteps/blob/main/text/profiles/0239-profiles-data-model.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;profiling signal&lt;/a&gt; enables users to easily jump from resource telemetry data to a corresponding profile so they can correlate, for example, a spike in CPU usage to the specific code components consuming that resource.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/oteps/blob/main/text/profiles/0239-profiles-data-model.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;profiles data model&lt;/a&gt; is currently stable and is being used to lay the foundation for production-ready implementations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-spring-boot-starter-reaches-stability&#34;&gt;The Spring Boot starter reaches stability&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Spring Boot starter, which is a powerful tool that simplifies the process of instrumenting Spring Boot applications with OpenTelemetry, is also now &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/blog/2024/spring-starter-stable/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;stable&lt;/a&gt;, making it easier for users to observe their Sprint Boot applications. The main features of the Sprint Boot stable release include out-of-the-box instrumentation, declarative SDK autoconfiguration setup, and programmatic SDK autoconfiguration setup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;updates-to-semantic-conventions&#34;&gt;Updates to Semantic Conventions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A number of new &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/specs/semconv/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Semantic Conventions&lt;/a&gt; groups emerged in 2024, including those for Databases, Messaging, RPC, System, AI/LLM and Contributor Experience — so we can expect advancements in those areas.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Databases, Semantic Conventions are currently being stabilized, and implementations have been created in a few SDKs, including JavaScript SDK with Postgres and .NET SDK with MySQL.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By the way, if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in any of these areas, please feel free to reach out to the Semantic Conventions groups directly. You can learn more about how to get involved on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/community&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;datadog-receiver-updates&#34;&gt;Datadog receiver updates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last June, we released &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/06/18/translate-datadog-metrics-into-otlp-with-the-opentelemetry-collector-and-grafana-alloy/&#34;&gt;new open source code for the OpenTelemetry Datadog receiver&lt;/a&gt; that allows users to translate Datadog metric formats into native OpenTelemetry protocol (OTLP) format. These metrics can then be sent to any OpenTelemetry-compatible metrics system, whether it’s Prometheus, Grafana Mimir, or another backend database.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have made this code available and marked it as experimental in&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/alloy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt; Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt;, our distribution of the OpenTelemetry Collector that uniquely provides native pipelines for both&lt;a href=&#34;/opentelemetry-report/&#34;&gt; OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; and Prometheus formats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-notable-updates-and-improvements&#34;&gt;Other notable updates and improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re starting the new year off with more new capabilities in OpenTelemetry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s now possible to &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/blog/2024/collecting-otel-compliant-java-logs-from-files/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;collect OTel-compliant Java logs directly from files&lt;/a&gt;, which is helpful in scenarios where logs need to be output to files or stdout due to organizational or reliability requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OTel community announced several other improvements and new features, including:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Resource detectors for &lt;code&gt;host.id&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;service.instance.id&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;service.name&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;service.version&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The addition of &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-php-contrib/pull/228&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;auto-instrumentation for openai-php&lt;/a&gt; to help understand the interaction with OpenAI compatible services&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The addition of metrics for Node.js runtime.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, localization teams have been translating the &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry website&lt;/a&gt; into Chinese, French, Japanese, Portuguese, and Spanish, making its content more broadly accessible to non-English speakers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And last, but certainly not least, in 2024 OpenTelemetry &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/pull/1271&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;applied&lt;/a&gt; to become a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Graduated CNCF project&lt;/a&gt; — a move that emphasizes how much the open source project has matured over the years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;opentelemetry-at-grafana-labs&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry at Grafana Labs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&#34;/observability-survey/2024/&#34;&gt;the results of our second annual Observability Survey&lt;/a&gt;, the vast majority of respondents are adopting multiple observability solutions, with 89% investing in Prometheus and 85% in OpenTelemetry — and 40% in both. Grafana Labs is one of the only companies serving as a leading contributor to both OpenTelemetry and Prometheus, and its engineers have played a pivotal role in the advancement and adoption of these projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We continue to focus on building compatibility with both Prometheus and OpenTelemetry into our products and open source projects. Here’s a look at some of the ways we did this with OTel in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;opentelemetry--ebpf&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry + eBPF&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/beyla-ebpf/&#34;&gt;Grafana Beyla&lt;/a&gt;, we added generic trace context propagation support for HTTP, so that our eBPF-based auto-instrumentation can work with OTel-instrumented services. We’ve also added support for detecting OTel instrumentation within services to avoid double accounting of telemetry data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;opentelemetry-collector--grafana-alloy&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector + Grafana Alloy&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Alloy now supports numerous OpenTelemetry Collector components, such as the Datadog receiver, the interval processor, and the syslog exporter. These components integrate with new Alloy features, such as &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/alloy/latest/troubleshoot/debug/#live-debugging-page&#34;&gt;live debugging&lt;/a&gt; and remote sourcing of configurations with &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/alloy/latest/get-started/modules/&#34;&gt;modules&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;opentelemetry--application-observability&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry + application observability&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/application-observability/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Application Observability&lt;/a&gt;, an out-of-the box solution to monitor applications and minimize MTTR (mean time to resolution), natively supports both Prometheus and OpenTelemetry. In 2024, we continued to add new features to Application Observability to help you quickly and easily visualize your data and accelerate root cause analysis. To learn more about these updates, please check out this &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/06/13/improved-anomaly-detection-and-faster-root-cause-analysis-the-latest-features-in-grafana-cloud-application-observability/&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1024px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/app-observability-updates/application-observability-updates-incontext-nav.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/app-observability-updates/application-observability-updates-incontext-nav.gif&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;1024&#34;height=&#34;541&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/app-observability-updates/application-observability-updates-incontext-nav.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;1024&#34;height=&#34;541&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-in-store-for-2025&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s in store for 2025&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The year has barely started and the OpenTelemetry community is already thinking of all the new things we want to build!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We hope that with our &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/community/issues/2406&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;donation of Beyla eBPF auto-instrumentation tooling&lt;/a&gt; to the OpenTelemetry project we can leverage the same technology as the OTel profiler to build easy trace-to-profile correlation — more to come there. We also hope to expand the number of supported protocols by our eBPF instrumentation and provide better language-level support for certain programming languages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year we&amp;rsquo;re also expecting OpenTelemetry Collector to be marked as stable, with its v1 release. This will increase overall adoption of the collector, as well as signal that the community can provide long-term support and not introduce backwards-incompatible changes on minor versions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, in 2025, Grafana Labs will continue to focus on driving collaboration and innovation within the broader OpenTelemetry community. Stay tuned for more!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着新年的到来，这是反思和思考的好时机。 2024 年您取得了哪些显着成就？2025 年您的目标是什么？我们在个人生活中经常这样做——但为什么不将同样的思路也应用到可观察性上呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可观测性仍然是一个热门话题，尤其是 OpenTelemetry，继续获得一些强劲的势头。据 a&lt;a href=&#34;/ opentelemetry-report/&#34;&gt;最近的 OpenTelemetry 报告&lt;/a&gt;。该开源项目也是重大行业活动中的热门话题，包括 &lt;a href=&#34;https://monitorama.com/2024/pdx.html#schedule&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Monitorama&lt; /a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://promcon.io/2024-berlin/schedule/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;PromCon&lt;/a&gt;、KubeCon &lt;a href=&#34;https://kccncna2024.sched.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;北美&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34; https://kccnceu2024.sched.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;欧洲&lt;/a&gt;，以及&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs 仍然完全致力于 OpenTelemetry，包括我在内的几位 Grafanista 积极维护该项目并为该项目做出贡献。本着新年的精神，让我们回顾一下 OpenTelemetry 项目去年发展的一些主要方式，并展望 2025 年的发展。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;recent-opentelemetry-project-milestones&#34;&gt;近期 OpenTelemetry 项目里程碑&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;support-for-profiling&#34;&gt;支持分析&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2023 年，OpenTelemetry 实现了&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2023/11/07/opentelemetry-at-kubecon-cloudnativecon-north-america-2023-update/&#34; 的稳定性target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;日志、指标和跟踪&lt;/a&gt;以及 2024 年的 OTel 社区发布了另一项重大公告：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/blog/2024/03/19/opentelemetry-announces-support-for-profiling/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; &gt;支持分析&lt;/a&gt;。 OpenTelemetry 的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/oteps/blob/main/text/profiles/0239-profiles-data-model.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;分析信号&lt;/a&gt;使用户能够轻松地从资源遥测数据跳转到相应的配置文件，以便他们可以将 CPU 使用率峰值与消耗该资源的特定代码组件相关联。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;新的&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/oteps/blob/main/text/profiles/0239-profiles-data-model.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34; noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;配置文件数据模型&lt;/a&gt;目前稳定，用于为生产就绪实施奠定基础。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-spring-boot-starter-reaches-stability&#34;&gt;Spring Boot 启动器达到稳定&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;春天的嘘声t starter 是一个强大的工具，可以简化使用 OpenTelemetry 检测 Spring Boot 应用程序的过程，现在也 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/blog/2024/spring-starter-stable/&#34; target=&#34; _blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;稳定&lt;/a&gt;，让用户更容易观察他们的 Sprint Boot 应用程序。 Sprint Boot 稳定版本的主要功能包括开箱即用的检测、声明式 SDK 自动配置设置和编程式 SDK 自动配置设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;updates-to-semantic-conventions&#34;&gt;语义约定更新&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2024 年出现了许多新的&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/specs/semconv/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;语义约定&lt;/a&gt;群组，包括数据库、消息传递、RPC、系统、AI/LLM 和贡献者体验 - 因此我们可以期待这些领域的进步。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;说到数据库，语义约定目前正在稳定，并且已经在一些 SDK 中创建了实现，包括带有 Postgres 的 JavaScript SDK 和带有 MySQL 的 .NET SDK。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;顺便说一句，如果您对这些领域中的任何一个感兴趣，请随时直接与语义约定小组联系。您可以详细了解如何参与 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/community&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p &gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;datadog-receiver-updates&#34;&gt;Datadog 接收器更新&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;去年 6 月，我们发布了&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/06/18/translate-datadog-metrics-into-otlp-with-the-opentelemetry-collector-and-grafana-alloy/&#34;&gt;新开放OpenTelemetry Datadog 接收器的源代码&lt;/a&gt;，允许用户将 Datadog 指标格式转换为本机 OpenTelemetry 协议 (OTLP) 格式。然后，这些指标可以发送到任何与 OpenTelemetry 兼容的指标系统，无论是 Prometheus、Grafana Mimir 还是其他后端数据库。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已提供此代码，并将其标记为 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/alloy&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt; Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt; 中的实验性代码，我们的 OpenTelemetry Collector 发行版，它独特地为 &lt;a href=&#34;/opentelemetry-report/&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; 和 Prometheus 格式提供本机管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-notable-updates-and-improvements&#34;&gt;其他值得注意的更新和改进&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将以 OpenTelemetry 的更多新功能开启新的一年。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在可以 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/blog/2024/collecting-otel-company-java-logs-from-files/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; &gt;直接从文件中收集符合OTel标准的Java日志&lt;/a&gt;，这对于由于组织或可靠性要求而需要将日志输出到文件或stdout的场景很有帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OTel 社区宣布了其他几项改进和新功能，包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;host.id&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;service.instance.id&lt;/code&gt;、&lt;code&gt;s 的资源检测器服务.名称&lt;/code&gt;，&lt;code&gt;服务.版本&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;添加了&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-php-contrib/pull/228&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;openai 自动检测-php&lt;/a&gt; 帮助理解与 OpenAI 兼容服务的交互&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;添加了 Node.js 运行时的指标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同时，本地化团队已将 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry 网站&lt;/a&gt;翻译成中文、法文、日文、葡萄牙语和西班牙语，使非英语国家更容易理解其内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，但同样重要的是，2024 年 OpenTelemetry &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cncf/toc/pull/1271&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;应用&lt;/ a&gt; 成为&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cncf.io/projects/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;毕业 CNCF 项目&lt;/a&gt; — 这一举动强调了开源项目多年来已经成熟了多少。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;opentelemetry-at-grafana-labs&#34;&gt;Grafana 实验室的 OpenTelemetry&lt;/h2​​&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据&lt;a href=&#34;/observability-survey/2024/&#34;&gt;我们第二次年度可观测性调查的结果&lt;/a&gt;，绝大多数受访者正在采用多种可观测性解决方案，其中 89% 投资于 Prometheus 和OpenTelemetry 占 85%，两者均为 40%。 Grafana Labs 是少数同时为 OpenTelemetry 和 Prometheus 提供主要贡献者的公司之一，其工程师在这些项目的推进和采用中发挥了关键作用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们继续致力于在我们的产品和开源项目中构建与 Prometheus 和 OpenTelemetry 的兼容性。以下是我们在 2024 年与 OTel 合作实现这一目标的一些方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;opentelemetry--ebpf&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry + eBPF&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/beyla-ebpf/&#34;&gt;Grafana Beyla&lt;/a&gt; 中，我们添加了对 HTTP 的通用跟踪上下文传播支持，以便我们基于 eBPF 的自动检测可以与 OTel 检测一起使用服务。我们还添加了对检测服务内 OTel 仪器的支持，以避免遥测数据的重复计算。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;opentelemetry-collector--grafana-alloy&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry 收集器 + Grafana 合金&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Alloy 现在支持众多 OpenTelemetry Collector 组件，例如 Datadog 接收器、间隔处理器和 syslog 导出器。这些组件与新的 Alloy 功能集成，例如&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/alloy/latest/troubleshoot/debug/#live-debugging-page&#34;&gt;实时调试&lt;/a&gt;以及使用 &lt;a href= 远程获取配置“/docs/alloy/latest/get-started/modules/&#34;&gt;模块&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;opentelemetry--application-observability&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry + 应用程序可观察性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/application-observability/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Application Observability&lt;/a&gt;，一种开箱即用的解决方案，用于监控应用程序并最大限度地减少 MTTR（平均解决时间）两者都支持普罗米修斯和 OpenTelemetry。 2024 年，我们继续为应用程序可观测性添加新功能，帮助您快速轻松地可视化数据并加速根本原因分析。要了解有关这些更新的更多信息，请查看此 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/06/13/improved-anomaly-detection-and-faster-root-cause-analysis-the-latest-features-in-grafana -cloud-application-observability/&#34;&gt;博客文章&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1024px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/app-observability-updates/application-observability-updates-incontext-nav.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/app-observability-updates/application-observability-updates-incontext-nav.gif”alt =“”宽度=“1024”高度=“541”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/app-observability-updates/application-observability-updates-incontext-nav.gif”&#xA;alt=“”宽度=“1024”高度=“541”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-in-store-for-2025&#34;&gt;2025 年即将推出的产品&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;新的一年刚刚开始，OpenTelemetry 社区已经在考虑我们想要构建的所有新事物！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们希望通过&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/community/issues/2406&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;捐赠 Beyla eBPF 自动仪器工具&lt;/a&gt;到 OpenTelemetry 项目，我们可以利用与 OTel 分析器相同的技术来构建简单的跟踪到配置文件关联 - 未来还会有更多。我们还希望扩大 eBPF 工具支持的协议数量，并为某些编程语言提供更好的语言级支持。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年，我们还预计 OpenTelemetry Collector 将在其 v1 版本中被标记为稳定。这将提高收集器的整体采用率，并表明社区可以提供长期支持，并且不会在次要版本上引入向后不兼容的更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同时，到 2025 年，Grafana Labs 将继续专注于推动更广泛的 OpenTelemetry 社区内的协作和创新。请继续关注更多内容！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Metrics, logs, and literature: Inside The National Library of the Netherlands’ observability stack】指标、日志和文献：荷兰国家图书馆可观测性堆栈内部</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/06/metrics-logs-and-literature-inside-the-national-library-of-the-netherlands-observability-stack/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Even in the digital age, you can’t deny the power of a good book. And at The National Library of the Netherlands, ensuring seamless access to those books is a top priority.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Literature adds value to humanity,” said Gerard van Engelen, platform engineer for The National Library of the Netherlands, during &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/data-management-and-monitoring-at-national-library-of-the-netherlands/&#34;&gt;a talk at GrafanaCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;. “We connect people around the world, but mainly in the Netherlands, by making Dutch literature available in a digital and physical way.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Physically, the library houses a lot of books — so many, in fact, that the collection could span an impressive 120 kilometers if laid out back to back. But it also stores a lot of data to help eager readers digitally access those books and other literary resources via their website.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We store 3.5 petabytes of digital literature, and it&amp;rsquo;s growing at 300-400 terabytes a year,” van Engelen explained. “We have literature dating back 406 years, and we make it available 24/7 on our site.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To deliver on that goal — and ensure seamless and reliable access to their digital assets — the team turned to Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to tell your own story at GrafanaCON, our largest community conference of the year? We’re &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;looking for speakers to share their real-world experiences&lt;/a&gt; with Grafana, custom-built plugins, cool dashboards, and more. This is a community-driven conference focused on your favorite visualization tool, its big tent of data source plugins, and the surrounding open source ecosystem — Prometheus, Loki, OpenTelemetry, Mimir, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;authoring-an-observability-strategy&#34;&gt;Authoring an observability strategy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The National Library of the Netherlands wanted to formalize their observability strategy for a few critical reasons. For starters, they prioritize the user experience, and wanted deeper insights into application performance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I think we all write software to solve a problem. And if the problem is not solved, the software is not working,” van Engelen said. “But if you don&amp;rsquo;t know that your software isn’t working, how can you act upon it?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;tICGNIIW-n8&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/tICGNIIW-n8?autoplay=1&amp;amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, as a government organization, they have strict requirements around log retention times. They wanted a platform that could provide centralized log storage, with clear and defined policies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, the team wanted the ability to make decisions based on real-time data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“In the case of the Dutch library, we are expanding our storage a lot,” van Engelen said. “We want to be able to plan for that upfront, and observability can help us with that.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-the-grafana-stack-for-library-stacks&#34;&gt;Why the Grafana stack for library stacks&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The National Library of the Netherlands had previous experience with Splunk, but ultimately chose to implement Grafana to drive their observability strategy. Ease of use, according to van Engelen, was a big reason why, especially because the engineering team wanted to empower developers to build their own dashboards for data visualization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Once you get your infrastructure rolled out, the developer experience with Grafana is pretty easy, and I think most people that use Grafana already know this,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second factor in choosing Grafana over Splunk was cost. “It meant a cost reduction of nearly 80,000 Euros a year, which is a nice one, in terms of OpEx,” van Engelen said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Native Prometheus support was also a major factor in the decision to go with Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“In the end, we looked at all these attributes and came up with Grafana as being number one for us,” van Engelen told attendees.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;empowering-developers-and-reducing-mttr&#34;&gt;Empowering developers and reducing MTTR&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The National Library of the Netherlands deployed two Grafana servers on bare-metal VMs with a PostgreSQL database, as well as &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt; for metrics and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; for logs, both running in &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/references/architecture/deployment-modes/#monolithic-mode&#34;&gt;monolithic mode&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for displaying log data at The National Library of the Netherlands.&#34;width=&#34;1999&#34;height=&#34;1086&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for displaying log data at The National Library of the Netherlands.&#34;width=&#34;1999&#34;height=&#34;1086&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For all applications that run on VMs in their landscape, they installed &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/agent/latest/&#34;&gt;Grafana Agent&lt;/a&gt;, which scrapes the logs and then the Prometheus endpoints, and then sends those logs and metrics to Loki and Mimir. &lt;em&gt;(Note: At GrafanaCON 2024, we &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-alloy-opentelemetry-collector-with-prometheus-pipelines/&#34;&gt;introduced Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt;, our new open source telemetry collector that is 100% OTLP compatible and offers native pipelines for OpenTelemetry and Prometheus telemetry formats, supporting metrics, logs, traces, and profiles. Alloy uses the same components, code, and concepts that were first introduced in Grafana Agent Flow. Grafana Agent is now deprecated and is in Long-Term Support. To learn more, please refer to this &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-agent-to-grafana-alloy-opentelemetry-collector-faq/&#34;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team also created their own &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Ansible collection&lt;/a&gt; to further simplify the developer experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We templated this all out, and actually, the only thing that developers need to do when defining their infrastructure as code is to define a variable with an app name and a port number, and then they&amp;rsquo;re good to go,” van Engelen said. “Everything else is rolled out automatically.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By visualizing application performance data in Grafana, the team is able to achieve what any librarian hopes for: a quiet environment where teams can debug issues and identify root causes faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for application performance metrics at The National Library of the Netherlands.&#34;width=&#34;1999&#34;height=&#34;1087&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for application performance metrics at The National Library of the Netherlands.&#34;width=&#34;1999&#34;height=&#34;1087&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We can use these dashboards to really drill down into issues relatively quickly with a minimal amount of configuration,” van Engelen said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;What’s next&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The National Library of the Netherlands has big plans to expand their use of the Grafana stack for their library stacks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, for example, they’re going to implement &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/&#34;&gt;Grafana Alerting&lt;/a&gt; to address performance issues more proactively, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/&#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt; for distributed tracing, and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/faro/&#34;&gt;Grafana Faro&lt;/a&gt; for real user monitoring and frontend app observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Ths is is just the tip of the iceberg for us,” van Engelen said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;即使在数字时代，你也不能否认一本好书的力量。在荷兰国家图书馆，确保无缝访问这些图书是首要任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“文学为人类增添了价值，”荷兰国家图书馆平台工程师 Gerard van Engelen 在&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/data-management-and-monitoring-at-national -library-of-the-netherlands/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2024 上的演讲&lt;/a&gt;。 “我们通过以数字和物理方式提供荷兰文学，将世界各地的人们联系在一起，但主要是荷兰的人们。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从物理上看，图书馆藏有大量书籍，事实上，如果背靠背排列，藏书的长度可能会长达 120 公里。但它还存储了大量数据，以帮助热切的读者通过其网站以数字方式访问这些书籍和其他文学资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们存储了 3.5 PB 的数字文献，并且每年以 300-400 TB 的速度增长，”van Engelen 解释道。 “我们拥有 406 年前的文献，并且我们的网站上全天候 (24/7) 提供这些文献。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了实现这一目标，并确保无缝、可靠地访问其数字资产，团队转向了 Grafana。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想在我们年度最大的社区会议 GrafanaCON 上讲述您自己的故事吗？我们正在&lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;寻找演讲者与 Grafana 分享他们的真实经验&lt;/a&gt;，定制插件、炫酷的仪表板等等。这是一个社区驱动的会议，重点讨论您最喜欢的可视化工具、其庞大的数据源插件以及周围的开源生态系统 - Prometheus、Loki、OpenTelemetry、Mimir 等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;authoring-an-observability-strategy&#34;&gt;编写可观察性策略&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;出于一些关键原因，荷兰国家图书馆希望正式制定其可观测性策略。首先，他们优先考虑用户体验，并希望更深入地了解应用程序性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我认为我们编写软件都是为了解决问题。如果问题没有解决，软件就无法工作，”van Engelen 说。 “但是，如果您不知道您的软件无法运行，您该如何采取行动呢？”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“tICGNIIW-n8”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/tICGNIIW-n8?autoplay=1&amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;其次，作为政府组织，他们对日志保留时间有严格的要求。他们想要一个能够提供集中日志存储并具有明确定义的策略的平台。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，团队希望能够根据实时数据做出决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“就荷兰图书馆而言，我们正在大量扩大我们的存储空间，”范恩格伦说。 “我们希望能够为预先做好准备，可观察性可以帮助我们做到这一点。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-the-grafana-stack-for-library-stacks&#34;&gt;为什么将 Grafana 堆栈用于库堆栈&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;荷兰国家图书馆之前曾使用过 Splunk，但最终选择实施 Grafana 来推动其可观测性策略。 van Engelen 认为，易用性是一个重要原因，特别是因为工程团队希望让开发人员能够构建自己的数据可视化仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“一旦推出基础设施，Grafana 的开发人员体验就非常简单，我认为大多数使用 Grafana 的人已经知道这一点，”他说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;选择 Grafana 而不是 Splunk 的第二个因素是成本。 “这意味着每年可以降低近 80,000 欧元的成本，就运营支出而言，这是一个不错的结果，”van Engelen 说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;原生 Prometheus 支持也是决定使用 Grafana 的一个主要因素。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“最后，我们考虑了所有这些属性，并认为 Grafana 是我们的第一选择，”van Engelen 告诉与会者。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;empowering-developers-and-reducing-mttr&#34;&gt;为开发者赋能并缩短 MTTR&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;荷兰国家图书馆在带有 PostgreSQL 数据库的裸机虚拟机上部署了两台 Grafana 服务器，以及用于指标和 &lt;a href 的 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt; =&#34;/oss/loki/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; 用于日志，两者都在 &lt;a 中运行href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/references/architecture/deployment-modes/#monolithic-mode&#34;&gt;整体模式&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1999px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard。 w=320 320w, /media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=750 750瓦， /media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=1040 1040瓦， /media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png?w=1920 1920瓦”&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;用于显示荷兰国家图书馆日志数据的 Grafana 仪表板。&#34;width=&#34;1999&#34;height=&#34;1086&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_logs-dashboard.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;用于显示荷兰国家图书馆日志数据的 Grafana 仪表板。&#34;width=&#34;1999&#34;高度=&#34;1086&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于在其环境中的虚拟机上运行的所有应用程序，他们安装了 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/agent/latest/&#34;&gt;Grafana Agent&lt;/a&gt;，该代理会抓取日志，然后抓取 Prometheus 端点，然后发送将这些日志和指标发送给 Loki 和 Mimir。 &lt;em&gt;（注：在 GrafanaCON 2024 上，我们&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-alloy-opentelemetry-collector-with-prometheus-pipelines/&#34;&gt;推出了 Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt;，我们的新的开源遥测收集器，100% OTLP 兼容，并为 OpenTelemetry 和 Prometheus 遥测格式提供本机管道，支持指标、日志、 Alloy 使用 Grafana Agent Flow 中首次引入的相同组件、代码和概念，现已弃用并提供长期支持。要了解更多信息，请参阅此 &lt;a href=&#34;。 /blog/2024/04/09/grafana-agent-to-grafana-alloy-opentelemetry-collector-faq/&#34;&gt;博客文章&lt;/a&gt;。）&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;团队还创建了自己的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Ansible 集合&lt;/a&gt;进一步简化开发者体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们将这一切都模板化了，实际上，开发人员在将基础设施定义为代码时需要做的唯一一件事就是定义一个带有应用程序名称和端口号的变量，然后就可以开始了， ”范恩格伦说道。 “其他一切都会自动推出。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过在 Grafana 中可视化应用程序性能数据，团队能够实现任何图书馆员所希望的：一个安静的环境，团队可以在其中更快地调试问题并确定根本原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1999px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/national-library-of-netherlands/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard. w=320 320w, /media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=750 750瓦， /media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=1040 1040瓦， /media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/荷兰国家图书馆/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png?w=1920 1920瓦”&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;荷兰国家图书馆应用程序性能指标的 Grafana 仪表板。&#34;width=&#34;1999&#34;height=&#34;1087&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/national-libra荷兰/dutch-library_metrics-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;荷兰国家图书馆应用程序性能指标的 Grafana 仪表板。&#34;width=&#34;1999&#34;height=&#34;1087&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们可以使用这些仪表板，以最少的配置相对快速地真正深入研究问题，”van Engelen 说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;下一步是什么&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;荷兰国家图书馆制定了扩大 Grafana 堆栈在图书馆书库中的使用范围的宏伟计划。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，展望未来，他们将实施 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/&#34;&gt;Grafana Alerting&lt;/a&gt; 来更主动地解决性能问题，&lt;a href=&#34;/ oss/tempo/&#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt; 用于分布式跟踪，&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/faro/&#34;&gt;Grafana Faro&lt;/a&gt; 用于真实用户监控和前端应用程序可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“这对我们来说只是冰山一角，”van Engelen 说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GrafanaCON 2025: Apply to speak at our biggest community event!】GrafanaCON 2025：申请在我们最大的社区活动中发言！</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/08/grafanacon-2025-apply-to-speak-at-our-biggest-community-event/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON&lt;/a&gt; is our biggest community conference of the year, and the GrafanaCON organizers have been hard at work shaping our annual event. We’re excited to see you all in person in Seattle on May 6-8, but what we would &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; love to see is many of you on the GrafanaCON stage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The open source community is at the heart of this event, so it&amp;rsquo;s only fitting that we’re dedicating a large part of the GrafanaCON agenda to spotlight talks from the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in presenting your Grafana dashboard or walking through a demo, please apply to speak at GrafanaCON via our &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/cfp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CFP process&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;btn-row &#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn--primary &#34; href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/cfp&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Apply to speak at GrafanaCON&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-speakers-can-expect-at-grafanacon-2025&#34;&gt;What speakers can expect at GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, our annual conference will be bigger and better than ever, with a unique conference space, hands-on workshops, live demos, and, of course, community-led sessions focused on your favorite visualization tool, our big tent data sources, and the surrounding open source ecosystem — Prometheus, Loki, OpenTelemetry, Mimir, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for speakers to share their real-world experiences with Grafana, from quirky and unexpected use cases to cool dashboards to custom-built plugins and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All talks will be given in-person in Seattle, and speakers will have support from the Grafana Labs team to fine-tune presentations and prepare to share their use case with hundreds of eager observability peers. Speakers also receive free entry to the three-day event, an invitation to a super fun VIP gathering, and GrafanaCON event swag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-should-apply&#34;&gt;Who should apply&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for open source contributors and hands-on practitioners to share their stories with the broader community. We’re open to a wide range of topics aimed at everyone from dashboard beginners to seasoned observability experts and we welcome speakers from all backgrounds and industries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to be an expert to give a great talk. If you have a project to share, you are qualified to speak alongside other Grafana enthusiasts. What we love to see most is a proposal that reflects your excitement for a topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Take it from one of the GrafanaCON co-chairs: “I am most excited about people getting a chance to present something they&amp;rsquo;re passionate about, but they&amp;rsquo;re not necessarily classed as professionals in,&amp;quot; said Mihaela Maior, Director of Engineering at Grafana Labs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-topics-to-submit-for-grafanacon&#34;&gt;What topics to submit for GrafanaCON&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feeling ready to present? Fantastic! There are two types of proposals we’re looking for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lightning talks (10 minutes):&lt;/strong&gt; A high-impact presentation on a powerful idea or challenging project.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use case stories (25 minutes):&lt;/strong&gt; A deep dive into a complex topic, focusing on actionable insights for the audience. A Q&amp;amp;A session will take place after the presentation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you need some inspiration, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/12/09/grafana-community-dashboards-memorable-use-cases-of-2024/&#34;&gt;list of memorable Grafana dashboards of 2024&lt;/a&gt; to find some of the wide-ranging projects that popped up last year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of our favorite dashboards presented at last year&amp;rsquo;s GrafanaCON was used to monitor and analyze bird songs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;mInRa1salmY&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mInRa1salmY?autoplay=1&amp;amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs Software Engineers Ivana Huckova and Sven Großmann used an inexpensive microphone, a Raspberry Pi 4, plus open source tools like BirdNET (an AI-powered bird sound recognition framework), &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/prometheus/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; to monitor and analyze bird tweets and chirps. They also set up alerts so they would know when a favorite species was detected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another superstar Grafana dashboard from GrafanaCON 2024 addressed a simple problem: &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/31/monitoring-your-morning-commute-with-grafana-the-story-of-a-golden-grot-awards-winner/&#34;&gt;monitoring your morning commute&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 960px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/golden-grot/2024/dashboards/screenshot-goldengrot-ruben-fernandez.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/golden-grot/2024/dashboards/screenshot-goldengrot-ruben-fernandez.gif&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard showing the morning commute to Atlanta&#34;width=&#34;960&#34;height=&#34;460&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/golden-grot/2024/dashboards/screenshot-goldengrot-ruben-fernandez.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard showing the morning commute to Atlanta&#34;width=&#34;960&#34;height=&#34;460&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ruben Fernandez, an SRE based in Atlanta, won the Golden Grot award in the personal dashboard category for &lt;a href=&#34;https://cuponesruben.grafana.net/public-dashboards/bc2d84c6d80e4acf9e826a32c4620351?orgId=1&amp;amp;refresh=5s&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;his Grafana dashboard&lt;/a&gt; that helps him navigate his daily trip to the office, including when to leave and which mode of transportation to take.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He used APIs and GTFS real-time feeds to pull in data from &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.weather.gov/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;weather.gov&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.itsmarta.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Metropolitan Atlanta Transit Authority&lt;/a&gt;, as well as drive-time and traffic information from Google Maps and Bing Maps. He also used a Prometheus instrumentation library for Python to combine metrics and send them to &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7jFJyiG2svY&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CFP judges look for more&lt;/a&gt; than just quirky Grafana dashboards. That amazing dashboard you hacked together for your job could be a winner, too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I get most excited when different projects interact with each other. So when multiple projects can naturally form a bond and get better together,&amp;quot; said Carl Bergquist, Grafana Labs Principal Engineer and a GrafanaCON co-chair. &amp;ldquo;Whenever silos of knowledge interact with each other and form a better view of something, that makes me happy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Above all, it&amp;rsquo;s the love of open source and the creative ways OSS is used in our daily lives that will always stand out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I really like the funky [use cases]. When someone comes in to show us monitoring the humidity around their plants or doing something interesting with their sourdough starters, that’s very special,&amp;quot; said Mihaela. &amp;ldquo;It’s such a unique way to use the tools that are typically classed as professional.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tips-for-first-time-speakers&#34;&gt;Tips for first-time speakers&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;People who are new to public speaking are more than welcome at GrafanaCON! We encourage submissions from new speakers and those from underrepresented groups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Talks from creators and experts are great, but talks from people who’re just learning a technology are also valuable,” writes software engineer Holly Cummins, in one of our favorite blogs about public speaking, &lt;a href=&#34;https://hollycummins.com/so-you-want-to-speak-at-conferences/?&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;So You Want to Speak at Conferences?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are new to conference speaking and (understandably) nervous to speak in front of hundreds of people, there are ways to get started. Start with a project demo in front of friendly colleagues, or present your work to another team in your company. (Holly Cummins calls this a &lt;a href=&#34;https://hollycummins.com/so-you-want-to-speak-at-conferences/?&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Speaker Ladder&lt;/a&gt;, an approachable method to get started with conference speaking.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your talk is accepted, prepare your content long in advance, and seek the help of colleagues and event organizers. For GrafanaCON, our teams will be supporting you throughout the conference experience. Confidence comes from being well prepared, knowing your content is in tip-top shape and having positive feedback from the organizers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-you-waiting-for&#34;&gt;What are you waiting for?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now is as good a time as any to submit your CFP application, which will close on Jan. 30.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our panel of CFP reviewers wear many hats in the event planning process (and they have new features to ship!). While the GrafanaCON CFP team members love this job, be kind and consider how they will receive your submission.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t wait until the last day to apply,&amp;rdquo; said Mihaela. &amp;ldquo;It makes our jobs harder as judges!”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The best first step is to simply get started: You can &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/cfp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;draft your proposal&lt;/a&gt; and return to it when you’re ready to complete and submit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We look forward to learning more about all the creative ways the community has solved problems or sparked new hobbies with Grafana and all the open source tools in our ecosystem. And we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to celebrate your incredible stories together at GrafanaCON this year.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON&lt;/a&gt; 是我们今年最大的社区会议，GrafanaCON 组织者一直在努力塑造我们的年度活动。我们很高兴于 5 月 6 日至 8 日在西雅图见到你们，但我们&lt;em&gt;真正&lt;/em&gt;希望看到你们中的许多人出现在 GrafanaCON 舞台上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开源社区是本次活动的核心，因此我们将 GrafanaCON 议程的大部分内容用于重点关注社区的讨论，这是再合适不过的了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您有兴趣展示 Grafana 仪表板或进行演示，请通过我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/cfp&#34; target=&#34;_blank 申请在 GrafanaCON 上发言&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CFP 流程&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;btn-row &#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn--primary &#34; href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/cfp&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;申请在 GrafanaCON 上发言&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-speakers-can-expect-at-grafanacon-2025&#34;&gt;演讲者在 GrafanaCON 2025 上可以期待什么&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年，我们的年度会议将比以往任何时候都规模更大、更好，拥有独特的会议空间、实践研讨会、现场演示，当然还有社区主导的会议，重点关注您最喜欢的可视化工具——我们的大帐篷数据源以及周围的开源生态系统 - Prometheus、Loki、OpenTelemetry、Mimir 等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在寻找演讲者来分享他们使用 Grafana 的真实体验，从古怪和意想不到的用例到炫酷的仪表板再到定制的插件等等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所有演讲都将在西雅图现场进行，演讲者将得到 Grafana Labs 团队的支持，以微调演示文稿并准备与数百名热切的可观察性同行分享他们的用例。演讲者还可免费参加为期三天的活动、超级有趣的 VIP 聚会邀请函以及 GrafanaCON 活动赠品。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-should-apply&#34;&gt;谁应该申请&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们正在寻找开源贡献者和实践者与更广泛的社区分享他们的故事。我们对面向所有人的广泛主题持开放态度，从仪表板初学者到经验丰富的可观测性专家，我们欢迎来自各个背景和行业的演讲者。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您不必成为专家才能发表精彩的演讲。如果您有一个项目要分享，您就有资格与其他 Grafana 爱好者一起发言。我们最喜欢看到的是反映您对某个主题的兴奋的提案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;摘自 GrafanaCON 联合主席之一的话：“我最兴奋的是人们有机会展示他们热衷的东西，但他们不一定被归类为专业人士，”总监 Mihaela Maior 说道Grafana 实验室工程博士。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-topics-to-submit-for-grafanacon&#34;&gt;要向 GrafanaCON 提交哪些主题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;准备好展示了吗？极好的！我们正在寻找两种类型的提案：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;闪电演讲（10 分钟）：&lt;/strong&gt;关于强有力的想法或具有挑战性的项目的高影响力演讲。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;用例故事（25 分钟）：&lt;/strong&gt;深入探讨复杂的主题，重点关注为受众提供可行的见解。演示结束后将进行问答环节。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您需要一些灵感，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/12/09/grafana-community-dashboards-memorable-use-cases-of-2024/&#34;&gt;令人难忘的 Grafana 仪表板列表2024&lt;/a&gt; 寻找去年出现的一些广泛项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;去年 GrafanaCON 上展示的我们最喜欢的仪表板之一用于监控和分析鸟鸣。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“mInRa1salmY”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mInRa1salmY?autoplay=1&amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs 软件工程师 Ivana Huckova 和 Sven Großmann 使用了便宜的麦克风、Raspberry Pi 4，以及 BirdNET（人工智能驱动的鸟声识别框架）、&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/prometheus/? pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;普罗米修斯&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; 用于监控和分析鸟类推文和鸣叫声。他们还设置了警报，以便在检测到最喜欢的物种时知道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GrafanaCON 2024 的另一个超级明星 Grafana 仪表板解决了一个简单的问题：&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/31/monitoring-your-morning-commute-with-grafana-the-story-of-a-golden -grot-awards-winner/&#34;&gt;监控您早上的通勤&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：960px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/golden-grot/2024/dashboards/screenshot-goldengrot-ruben-fernandez.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/golden-grot/2024/dashboards/screenshot-goldengrot-ruben-fernandez.gif&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板显示早上通勤到亚特兰大&#34;width=&#34;960&#34;height=&#34;460&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/golden-grot/2024/dashboards/screenshot-goldengrot-ruben-fernandez.gif”&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板显示早上前往亚特兰大的通勤路线&#34;width=&#34;960&#34;height=&#34;460&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ruben Fernandez 是一位位于亚特兰大的 SRE，凭借 &lt;a href=&#34;https://cuponesruben.grafana.net/public-dashboards/bc2d84c6d80e4acf9e826a32c4620351?orgId=1&amp;refresh=5s&#34; 赢得了个人仪表板类别的 Golden Grot 奖target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;这个Grafana 仪表板&lt;/a&gt;帮助他导航每天去办公室的行程，包括何时离开以及采取哪种交通方式。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他使用 API 和 GTFS 实时源从 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.weather.gov/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt; 提取数据Weather.gov&lt;/a&gt; 和&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.itsmarta.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;亚特兰大大都会交通局&lt;/a&gt;，以及drive -来自 Google 地图和 Bing 地图的时间和交通信息。他还使用了适用于 Python 的 Prometheus 检测库来组合指标并将其发送到 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7jFJyiG2svY&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CFP 评委寻找的不仅仅是古怪的 Grafana&lt;/a&gt;仪表板。您为工作而拼凑而成的令人惊叹的仪表板也可能成为赢家。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“当不同的项目相互交互时，我感到最兴奋。因此，当多个项目能够自然地形成联系并共同进步时，”Grafana Labs 首席工程师兼 GrafanaCON 联合主席 Carl Bergquist 说道。“每当知识孤岛相互影响并形成对某件事更好的看法时，我就会快乐。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最重要的是，对开源的热爱以及 OSS 在我们日常生活中使用的创造性方式将永远脱颖而出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我真的很喜欢时髦的[用例]。当有人进来向我们展示监测他们的植物周围的湿度或用他们的酵母发酵剂做一些有趣的事情时，这是非常特别的，”米哈埃拉说。“这是使用通常被归类为专业工具的独特方式。”&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tips-for-first-time-speakers&#34;&gt;给初次演讲者的提示&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GrafanaCON 非常欢迎刚开始公开演讲的人！我们鼓励新演讲者和代表性不足的群体提交意见。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“来自创作者和专家的演讲很棒，但来自刚学习技术的人的演讲也很有价值，”软件工程师 Holly Cummins 在我们最喜欢的公开演讲博客之一中写道，&lt;a href=&#34;https ://hollycummins.com/so-you-want-to-speak-at-conferences/？” target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;您想在会议上发言吗？&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您是会议演讲新手，并且（可以理解）在数百人面前演讲感到紧张，可以通过以下方法开始。从在友好的同事面前进行项目演示开始，或者向公司的其他团队展示您的工作。 （Holly Cummins 将此称为&lt;a href=&#34;https://hollycummins.com/so-you-want-to-speak-at-conferences/?&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;扬声器阶梯&lt; /a&gt;，一种开始会议演讲的平易近人的方法。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您的演讲被接受，请提前准备好内容，并寻求同事和活动组织者的帮助。对于 GrafanaCON，我们的团队将在整个会议体验中为您提供支持。信心来自于充分的准备、知道您的内容处于最佳状态以及组织者的积极反馈。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-you-waiting-for&#34;&gt;你在做什么你在等什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在正是提交 CFP 申请的最佳时机，申请将于 1 月 30 日截止。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的 CFP 审核小组在活动策划过程中身兼数职（他们有新功能要发布！）。虽然 GrafanaCON CFP 团队成员热爱这份工作，但请善待并考虑他们将如何收到您的提交内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“不要等到最后一天才申请，”米哈埃拉说。 “这让我们作为法官的工作变得更加困难！”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最好的第一步就是开始：您可以&lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/cfp&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;起草您的提案&lt; /a&gt; 并在准备好完成并提交时返回。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们期待更多地了解社区使用 Grafana 以及我们生态系统中的所有开源工具解决问题或激发新爱好的所有创造性方式。我们迫不及待地想在今年的 GrafanaCON 上共同庆祝你们的精彩故事。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How CERN uses Grafana and Mimir to monitor the world&#39;s largest computer grid】CERN 如何使用 Grafana 和 Mimir 监控世界上最大的计算机网格</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/02/how-cern-uses-grafana-and-mimir-to-monitor-the-worlds-largest-computer-grid/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The European Organization for Nuclear Research (CERN) is famous for operating &lt;a href=&#34;https://home.web.cern.ch/science/accelerators/large-hadron-collider&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;the world&amp;rsquo;s largest particle accelerator&lt;/a&gt;, but did you know that CERN is also at the heart of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest computing grid? And with such unprecedented computing demands comes some serious observability needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CERN operates two data centers at its facility near Ganeva, Switzerland, which includes 11,000 servers, 470,000 cores, and 380 PB of archived data. But CERN also wants to make that data available for scientists around the world to analyze, which is why they coordinate the Worldwide Large Hadron Collider Computing Grid (WLCG). The WLCG extends to 170 institutes and universities across 42 countries, bringing the combined infrastructure to 1.4 million computing cores and 1.5 exabytes of available storage, generating 2 million tasks per day at a global transfer rate of 260 GB/s.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, it&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt; of data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Of course, such infrastructure requires monitoring, and this is where the monitoring service itself comes into place with our main mandate to monitor the data center, WLGC, but also our services that are running in our IT department,&amp;rdquo; said Nikolay Tsvetkov, Staff Computing Engineer at CERN.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CERN uses Grafana and Grafana Mimir as part of a scalable, fault-tolerant stack that makes sure the 12,000 physicists who rely on the WLCG have access to the data they need.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Grafana is crucial for the monitoring service at CERN, providing us with many, many useful dashboards, but also with alerting functionality,&amp;rdquo; Tsvetkov said, noting that the recent addition of Grafana Mimir &amp;ldquo;provides the missing bit&amp;rdquo; in their Prometheus architecture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tsvetkov works on the IT Monitoring and Data Streaming services at CERN and also serves as the service manager for their monitoring visualization tools. He &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/cern-monitors-largest-computing-grid-with-grafana-and-mimir/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;shared his experience at GrafanaCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;, highlighting how Grafana and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt; help CERN and the WLCG operate at a truly massive scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to tell your story at GrafanaCON, our largest community conference of the year? We’re &lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;looking for speakers to share their real-world experiences&lt;/a&gt; with Grafana, custom-built plugins, cool dashboards, and more. This is a community-driven conference focused on your favorite visualization tool, its big tent of data source plugins, and the surrounding open source ecosystem — Prometheus, Loki, OpenTelemetry, Mimir, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-cern-uses-grafana-to-visualize-its-data&#34;&gt;How CERN uses Grafana to visualize its data&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tsvetkov&amp;rsquo;s team monitors roughly 15,000 hosts and receives around 85,000 documents every second, which translates to 3.3 TB of data stored every day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Having such a wide range of services to monitor, of course provides some challenges for us,&amp;rdquo; Tsvetkov said. &amp;ldquo;The first one is that we get data from heterogeneous data sources. We need to actually unify the way we get this data so we can cope with this.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;UDMoWQxW3iA&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UDMoWQxW3iA?autoplay=1&amp;amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2016, CERN adopted Grafana as its primary monitoring interface to address that issue. Today with more than 5,000 Grafana users across 70 organizations creating more than 2,700 dashboards and 680 alert rules, it&amp;rsquo;s safe to say, &amp;ldquo;our users, they love it,&amp;rdquo; said Tsvetkov. &amp;ldquo;Of course, they&amp;rsquo;re creating a lot of dashboards, but we found that Grafana is quite useful as a unified data source.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s because Grafana provides a proxy, so some of CERN&amp;rsquo;s systems are accessing data from Grafana data sources through the Grafana APIs. &amp;ldquo;It actually hides the complexity of the different databases that are behind the data sources,&amp;rdquo; Tsvetkov said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1516px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for ETF tests&#34;width=&#34;1516&#34;height=&#34;774&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for ETF tests&#34;width=&#34;1516&#34;height=&#34;774&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Their Grafana deployment is split between a public instance that&amp;rsquo;s available to anyone (hosted on two VMs behind load balancers in different availability zones), and private instances that sit behind CERN&amp;rsquo;s SSO (multi-organization, with six servers behind a DNS load balancer and VMs in three availability zones.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Managing all those dashboards can present some operational challenges, so they rely on the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/organization-management/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;organizations&lt;/a&gt; feature in Grafana. Public organizations need to be available to all Grafana users, so Tsvetkov&amp;rsquo;s team runs some scripts to synchronize them regularly. The private organizations are mainly used by service managers, so those managers are given the flexibility to decide who should have access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1536px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for monitoring CERN&amp;#39;s OpenStack environment&#34;width=&#34;1536&#34;height=&#34;784&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for monitoring CERN&amp;#39;s OpenStack environment&#34;width=&#34;1536&#34;height=&#34;784&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even managing plugins became easier: While physicists often created custom plugins for Grafana, in recent years, this hasn&amp;rsquo;t been an issue. &amp;ldquo;Grafana has became a more and more complete product, and we are getting anything that we need almost out of the box,&amp;rdquo; Tsvetkov said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-mimir-the-missing-piece&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir: the missing piece&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, the team was aware of a lack of support in their stack for users who wanted to integrate long-term storage for Prometheus metrics. They began working on a solution in 2020 using InfluxDB as a backend, but it was clear that it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t scale well in the future, Tsvetkov said. They ultimately turned their attention to Mimir, our horizontally scalable, highly available, multi-tenant TSDB for long-term storage, and began testing how it would suit their use case.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With 80 million active series, they found Mimir could scale to meet their needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Also, we liked the fact that you can scale at a different component, either at the ingestion site or the query site,&amp;rdquo; Tsvetkov said. &amp;ldquo;Mimir also provides a lot of flexibility, with multi-tenancy and getting data from, from different users, so this would also allow us to integrate all the data into a single storage.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They began a pilot service in 2023 running on their Kubernetes deployment, which had 49 nodes, including 46 worker nodes that provide more than 1.2 TB of memory and 730 CPU cores, as well as different node groups to address the different hardware requirements. They also used Amazon S3 as their object storage, with 40-day default retention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1388px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Kubernetes monitoring with a Grafana dashboard&#34;width=&#34;1388&#34;height=&#34;590&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Kubernetes monitoring with a Grafana dashboard&#34;width=&#34;1388&#34;height=&#34;590&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Mimir, they were running 29 tenants, producing 30 millions of active series. By their calculations, those tenants could have accommodated 150 million active series and processed around 2,000 queries per second.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a result, &amp;ldquo;now Mimir is well integrated within the pipeline,&amp;rdquo; Tsvetkov said.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1370px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for CERN&amp;#39;s distributors&#34;width=&#34;1370&#34;height=&#34;768&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for CERN&amp;#39;s distributors&#34;width=&#34;1370&#34;height=&#34;768&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Going forward, more open source tools are under consideration for CERN, including Open Telemetry and Grafana Tempo for tracing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But no matter how big the computing grid becomes, the foundation for their infrastructure is firmly rooted in Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It has been with us since the beginning of the architecture,&amp;rdquo; Tsvetkov said, &amp;ldquo;and we have always been very happy using Grafana.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;欧洲核研究组织 (CERN) 因运营 &lt;a href=&#34;https://home.web.cern.ch/science/accelerators/large-hadron-collider&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel= 而闻名“noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;世界上最大的粒子加速器&lt;/a&gt;，但您是否知道 CERN 也是世界上最大的计算网格的核心？伴随着这种前所未有的计算需求，随之而来的是一些严重的可观测性需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CERN 在瑞士加内瓦附近的设施中运营着两个数据中心，其中包括 11,000 台服务器、470,000 个核心和 380 PB 的存档数据。但欧洲核子研究中心也希望将这些数据提供给世界各地的科学家进行分析，这就是他们协调全球大型强子对撞机计算网格（WLCG）的原因。 WLCG 扩展到 42 个国家/地区的 170 个研究所和大学，使综合基础设施拥有 140 万个计算核心和 1.5 艾字节可用存储，每天以 260 GB/s 的全球传输速率生成 200 万个任务。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;换句话说，这是&lt;em&gt;大量&lt;/em&gt;数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“当然，这样的基础设施需要监控，这就是监控服务本身发挥作用的地方，我们的主要任务是监控数据中心、WLGC，以及我们 IT 部门运行的服务，”Nikolay 说道Tsvetkov，CERN 计算工程师。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;CERN 使用 Grafana 和 Grafana Mimir 作为可扩展、容错堆栈的一部分，确保依赖 WLCG 的 12,000 名物理学家能够访问他们所需的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Grafana 对于 CERN 的监控服务至关重要，它为我们提供了很多很多有用的仪表板，而且还具有警报功能，”Tsvetkov 说，并指出最近添加的 Grafana Mimir “提供了 Prometheus 中缺失的部分”架构。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tsvetkov 在 CERN 从事 IT 监控和数据流服务工作，并担任其监控可视化工具的服务经理。他&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/cern-monitors-largest-computing-grid-with-grafana-and-mimir/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;分享了他在 GrafanaCON 2024 上的经验&lt;/a &gt;，重点介绍 Grafana 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt;帮助 CERN 和 WLCG 真正大规模运作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想在我们年度最大的社区会议 GrafanaCON 上讲述您的故事吗？我们正在&lt;a href=&#34;https://pretalx.com/grafanacon-2025/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;寻找演讲者与 Grafana 分享他们的真实经验&lt;/a&gt;，定制插件、炫酷的仪表板等等。这是一个社区驱动的会议，重点讨论您最喜欢的可视化工具、其庞大的数据源插件以及周围的开源生态系统 - Prometheus、Loki、OpenTelemetry、Mimir 等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-cern-uses-grafana-to-visualize-its-data&#34;&gt;CERN 如何使用 Grafana 进行可视化整理其数据&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tsvetkov 的团队监控大约 15,000 台主机，每秒接收大约 85,000 个文档，这意味着每天存储 3.3 TB 的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“要监控如此广泛的服务，当然给我们带来了一些挑战，”Tsvetkov 说。 “第一个是我们从异构数据源获取数据。我们实际上需要统一获取这些数据的方式，以便我们能够应对这一问题。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“UDMoWQxW3iA”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/UDMoWQxW3iA?autoplay=1&amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2016 年，CERN 采用 Grafana 作为其主要监控界面来解决该问题。如今，70 个组织的 5,000 多名 Grafana 用户创建了 2,700 多个仪表板和 680 条警报规则，可以肯定地说，“我们的用户喜欢它，”Tsvetkov 说。 “当然，他们正在创建很多仪表板，但我们发现 Grafana 作为统一数据源非常有用。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是因为 Grafana 提供了代理，因此 CERN 的一些系统正在通过 Grafana API 访问来自 Grafana 数据源的数据。 “它实际上隐藏了数据源背后不同数据库的复杂性，”Tsvetkov 说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1516px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png？w = 320 320w，/媒体/博客/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/cern -gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;用于 ETF 测试的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;width=&#34;1516&#34;height=&#34;774&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-etf-tests.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;用于 ETF 测试的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;width=&#34;1516&#34;height=&#34;774&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他们的 Grafana 部署分为可供任何人使用的公共实例（托管在不同可用区域的负载均衡器后面的两个虚拟机上）和位于 CERN SSO 后面的私有实例（多组织，在 DNS 负载后面有六台服务器）平衡器和虚拟机位于三个可用区。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;管理所有这些仪表板可能会带来一些运营挑战，因此它们依赖于&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/organization-management/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;组织&lt;/a &gt; Grafana 中的功能。公共组织需要o 可供所有 Grafana 用户使用，因此 Tsvetkov 的团队运行一些脚本来定期同步它们。私有组织主要由服务经理使用，因此这些经理可以灵活地决定谁应该有权访问。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1536px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png？w = 320 320w，/媒体/博客/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/cern -gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;用于监控 CERN OpenStack 环境的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;width=&#34;1536&#34;height=&#34;784&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-openstack-services.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;用于监控 CERN OpenStack 环境的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;width=&#34;1536&#34;height=&#34;784&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;甚至管理插件也变得更加容易：虽然物理学家经常为 Grafana 创建自定义插件，但近年来，这已经不再是问题。 “Grafana 已经成为一个越来越完整的产品，我们几乎可以开箱即用地获得我们需要的任何东西，”Tsvetkov 说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-mimir-the-missing-piece&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir：缺失的部分&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从一开始，团队就意识到他们的堆栈中缺乏对想要集成 Prometheus 指标长期存储的用户的支持。 Tsvetkov 表示，他们于 2020 年开始研究使用 InfluxDB 作为后端的解决方案，但很明显，该解决方案未来无法很好地扩展。他们最终将注意力转向 Mimir，这是我们用于长期存储的水平可扩展、高可用性、多租户 TSDB，并开始测试它如何适合他们的用例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;凭借 8000 万个活跃系列，他们发现 Mimir 可以扩展以满足他们的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“此外，我们还喜欢这样一个事实：您可以在不同的组件上进行扩展，无论是在摄取站点还是在查询站点，”Tsvetkov 说。 “Mimir 还提供了很大的灵活性，支持多租户并从不同用户获取数据，因此这也使我们能够将所有数据集成到单个存储中。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他们于 2023 年开始在 Kubernetes 部署上运行试点服务，该部署有 49 个节点，其中包括 46 个工作节点，提供超过 1.2 TB 的内存和 730 个 CPU 核心，以及不同的节点组来满足不同的硬件要求。他们还使用 Amazon S3 作为对象存储，默认保留期为 40 天。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1388px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png？w = 320 320w，/media/blog/ cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png？w=900 900w，/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png？w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/cern-gcon /cern-cluster.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;使用 Grafana 仪表板进行 Kubernetes 监控&#34;width=&#34;1388&#34;height=&#34;590&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-cluster.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;使用 Grafana 仪表板进行 Kubernetes 监控&#34;width=&#34;1388&#34;height=&#34;590&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Mimir，他们运营着 29 个租户，生产了 3000 万个活跃剧集。根据他们的计算，这些租户可以容纳 1.5 亿个活跃系列，每秒处理大约 2,000 个查询。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，“现在 Mimir 已经很好地集成到了管道中，”Tsvetkov 说。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1370px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png？w = 320 320w，/media/blog/ cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern -distributor.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;CERN 分销商的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;width=&#34;1370&#34;height=&#34;768&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/cern-gcon/cern-distributor.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;CERN 分销商的 Grafana 仪表板&#34;width=&#34;1370&#34;height=&#34;768&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;展望未来，CERN 正在考虑更多开源工具，包括用于跟踪的 Open Telemetry 和 Grafana Tempo。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但无论计算网格变得有多大，其基础设施的基础都牢牢植根于 Grafana。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“从架构一开始，它就一直伴随着我们，”Tsvetkov 说，“我们一直非常高兴使用 Grafana。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;是最简单的这是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What is Adaptive Telemetry, and how can it reduce MTTR, noise, and cost?】什么是自适应遥测？它如何降低 MTTR、噪音和成本？</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/14/what-is-adaptive-telemetry-and-how-can-it-reduce-mttr-noise-and-cost/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As your applications scale, so too does the flood of logs, metrics, profiles, and traces—along with the costs to store and manage them. Collecting everything might feel like the safest bet, but it often leaves you buried in noise and struggling to find the signals that matter, all while costs spiral out of control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, there&amp;rsquo;s a better way with Adaptive Telemetry, a range of features in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; that optimizes which signals get stored and ensures you only keep the most valuable telemetry. Through classification and prioritization, Adaptive Telemetry (which includes &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/reduce-costs/metrics-costs/control-metrics-usage-via-adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/reduce-costs/logs-costs/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Logs&lt;/a&gt;) helps you lower costs without sacrificing the insights you need to keep your systems running smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog, we’ll look closer at how Adaptive Telemetry works, share real-world examples of how organizations are utilizing it today, and show how you can use it to help achieve cost-efficient, effective observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;class=&#34;youtube-lazyload responsive-video&#34;&#xA;data-embed=&#34;Dz5XLSPTpWA&#34;&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Dz5XLSPTpWA?autoplay=1&amp;amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;data-title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem-with-the-collect-everything-mindset&#34;&gt;The problem with the &amp;lsquo;collect everything&amp;rsquo; mindset&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we dig deeper into Adaptive Telemetry, let&amp;rsquo;s first look at the problem we&amp;rsquo;re trying to solve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Telemetry is essential for understanding system performance. But when you collect everything indiscriminately, problems emerge. Instead of clarity, you get chaos. Instead of insights, you get overwhelmed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This “collect everything” approach often does more harm than good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You drown in data.&lt;/strong&gt; Unfiltered telemetry creates data overload. Your team spends hours wading through endless metrics, struggling to identify what actually matters. Instead of driving informed decisions, the data paralyzes progress.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Costs surge.&lt;/strong&gt; Storing and processing excessive telemetry isn’t free. It drains budgets, inflates operational costs, and steals resources from critical projects. Worse, the expense often outweighs the value the data provides.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Signals get buried in noise.&lt;/strong&gt; Collecting everything makes it harder to pinpoint what’s relevant. High-value metrics get lost in the shuffle, and your team’s focus is diluted. Instead of empowering decisions, the data becomes a distraction.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This approach is unsustainable, especially as you scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-adaptive-telemetry-works&#34;&gt;How Adaptive Telemetry works&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Telemetry fundamentally changes how you manage observability data, automating classification and optimization so you can regain control and focus on telemetry that actually delivers value. It also gives you the flexibility you need for your team and system, whether you want to be more hands off or completely in control.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how it works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;classification-based-on-use&#34;&gt;Classification based on use&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Telemetry classifies incoming data based on how it’s used. Is it powering an alert? Displayed on a dashboard? Queried ad hoc? Not all of that data is valuable, so signals that support critical operations are prioritized, while those with limited utility are identified as low value. This precision allows your team to focus on actionable data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;automated-optimization&#34;&gt;Automated optimization&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once classified, low-value data is automatically aggregated, sampled, dropped, or reduced.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This process keeps your observability efficient, aligning costs with actual value. The system’s feedback loop continuously learns from your usage patterns, adjusting its behavior to adapt to changing needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As your environment evolves, Adaptive Telemetry evolves with it—without manual intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;flexibility-for-your-needs&#34;&gt;Flexibility for your needs&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every organization has unique requirements, and Adaptive Telemetry is built accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to ensure specific signals are always preserved? Use Exemptions to override recommendations and retain critical data. Prefer a more hands-on approach? Review and approve optimization suggestions before they’re applied.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-the-most-from-your-logs-and-metrics&#34;&gt;Get the most from your logs and metrics&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Telemetry currently includes two forms: Adaptive Metrics and Adaptive Logs. They operate slightly differently, but the net benefit is still the same: delivering just the telemetry you need and removing the unneeded clutter and associated costs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;adaptive-metrics&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Metrics was our first foray into this space. &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/05/09/adaptive-metrics-grafana-cloud-announcement/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Introduced in 2023&lt;/a&gt;, it aggregates unused and partially used metrics into lower cardinality versions of themselves to reduce costs. To date, Adaptive Metrics has delivered a &lt;strong&gt;35% reduction in metrics costs on average for more than 1,500 organizations.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1200px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;1200&#34;height=&#34;443&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;1200&#34;height=&#34;443&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see from the workflow above, Adaptive Metrics analyzes how metrics are used—across dashboards, alerts, and queries—and classifies them to optimize data retention, ensuring you store only what matters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;adaptive-logs&#34;&gt;Adaptive Logs&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/24/introducing-adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Introduced at ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;, Adaptive Logs uses AI/ML techniques to analyze observability data at a scale that wouldn’t be feasible with manual processes. It identifies commonly ingested log patterns and creates a set of customized recommendations for dropping unused telemetry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The mechanics of Adaptive Logs and Adaptive Metrics are fairly similar. They both analyze usage and create recommendations that translate to reduced ingestion and cost savings. However, Adaptive Logs differs slightly in that it groups logs into patterns responsible for high log volumes. It also drops a percentage of logs, rather than aggregating them like Adaptive Metrics does.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1200px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;1200&#34;height=&#34;628&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;1200&#34;height=&#34;628&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each of the lines in the chart above represents a hypothetical pattern generated by Adaptive Logs. In the middle example, you can see the logs are queried frequently, so the recommendation is to keep them all. For patterns that are queried infrequently or not at all, Adaptive Logs recommends dropping a certain percentage of those logs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;worried-about-losing-data-weve-got-you-covered&#34;&gt;Worried about losing data? We&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s only natural to worry about losing critical telemetry data, especially when your systems depend on accurate and reliable observability during incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine this: it’s 3 a.m. and your systems are in chaos. Alerts are firing, dashboards are blank, and your team is scrambling to understand what’s happening. But you can’t find the signal you need because it was lost in a cost-cutting effort to unilaterally aggregate low-value data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In those critical moments, every byte of telemetry matters—and losing the wrong data could cost your business downtime, trust, and revenue. Thankfully, this nightmare scenario doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to happen—this is exactly why &lt;strong&gt;Exemptions&lt;/strong&gt; exist in Adaptive Telemetry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/22/how-to-aggregate-metrics-but-retain-critical-data-introducing-exemptions-in-adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Exemptions&lt;/a&gt; let you identify and preserve the signals you can’t afford to lose—whether it’s specific metrics tied to SLAs or critical labels needed for detailed investigations. You have full control to ensure that, even as you optimize costs, your most important data is always available when you need it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 3356px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Exemptions.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Exemptions.gif&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;3356&#34;height=&#34;1824&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Exemptions.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;width=&#34;3356&#34;height=&#34;1824&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Exemptions, you don’t have to choose between saving money and safeguarding your telemetry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether it’s protecting vital metrics or retaining key labels, Exemptions give you the confidence to trust your observability—even in the most critical scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;adaptive-telemetry-user-stories&#34;&gt;Adaptive Telemetry user stories&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Telemetry is already delivering results for organizations that manage high telemetry volumes and &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/02/15/what-are-cardinality-spikes-and-why-do-they-matter/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;high-cardinality environments&lt;/a&gt;. Here are some key outcomes achieved by engineering teams using this powerful feature.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lower costs, uncompromised coverage.&lt;/strong&gt; At TeleTracking, an integrated healthcare operations platform provider, engineers overcame some initial fears about critical data loss and the company was able to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZGquwsXt1C0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;reduce its observability costs by 50% without losing visibility&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scaling observability without scaling costs.&lt;/strong&gt; Identity security provider SailPoint &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VkrQQFPQu2g&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;reduced its metrics volume by 33%&lt;/a&gt; and used the savings to expand its observability stack. SailPoint reinvested in Grafana Cloud, adopting tools like &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/frontend-observability-for-real-user-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Frontend Observability&lt;/a&gt; to enhance monitoring capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empowering teams to focus on what matters.&lt;/strong&gt; Dell Technologies, which faced overwhelming alert fatigue and excessive data from their legacy observability tools, used Adaptive Telemetry to &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wz2a4hxt2c4&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;eliminate unused metrics, reduce noise, and improve productivity&lt;/a&gt; so their engineers could make quicker, smarter decisions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These real-world outcomes showcase how Adaptive Telemetry helps organizations optimize costs, scale observability, and empower their teams. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re aiming to reduce expenses, improve team efficiency, or enhance system insights, Adaptive Telemetry delivers value that scales with your needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-future-of-observability-is-adaptive&#34;&gt;The future of observability Is Adaptive&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adaptive Telemetry is just getting started.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While it already helps you manage metrics and logs effectively, the future holds even more. Soon, Adaptive Telemetry will extend to traces and profiles, giving you the tools to ensure that every piece of telemetry you store is worth the investment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This evolution reflects our mission to help you maximize the value of your observability data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ready to take control of your telemetry? Start using Adaptive Telemetry in Grafana Cloud today and see the difference for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;随着应用程序的扩展，日志、指标、配置文件和跟踪的洪流也会随之增加，以及存储和管理它们的成本。收集所有东西可能感觉是最安全的选择，但它常常会让你陷入噪音之中，努力寻找重要的信号，而成本却急剧失控。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;值得庆幸的是，自适应遥测有一种更好的方法，&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 中的一系列功能可以优化存储的信号并确保您只保留最有价值的遥测数据。通过分类和优先级排序，自适应遥测（其中包括 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/reduce-costs/metrics-costs/control-metrics-usage-via-adaptive-metrics/ ?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/reduce-costs/logs-costs/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应日志&lt;/a&gt;）可帮助您降低成本，而不牺牲保持系统平稳运行所需的洞察力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本博客中，我们将仔细研究自适应遥测的工作原理，分享当今组织如何利用它的真实示例，并展示如何使用它来帮助实现经济高效、有效的可观测性。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&#xA;类 =“youtube-lazyload 响应视频”&#xA;数据嵌入=“Dz5XLSPTpWA”&#xA;data-url=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Dz5XLSPTpWA?autoplay=1&amp;rel=0&#34;&#xA;数据标题=“YouTube 视频”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;play-button&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem-with-the-collect-everything-mindset&#34;&gt;“收集一切”心态的问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在深入研究自适应遥测之前，让我们首先看看我们要解决的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;遥测对于了解系统性能至关重要。但当你不加区别地收集一切时，问题就出现了。你得到的不是清晰，而是混乱。您不但没有获得洞察力，反而不知所措。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种“收集一切”的方法往往弊大于利。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;您淹没在数据中。&lt;/strong&gt;未经过滤的遥测会造成数据过载。您的团队花费数小时研究无尽的指标，努力找出真正重要的内容。数据不但不能推动明智的决策，反而会阻碍进展。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;成本激增。&lt;/strong&gt;存储和处理过多的遥测数据并不是免费的。它耗尽了预算，增加了运营成本，并从关键项目中窃取了资源。更糟糕的是，费用常常超过数据提供的价值。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;信号被淹没在噪音中。&lt;/strong&gt;收集所有内容会使确定相关内容变得更加困难。高价值指标在混乱中丢失，团队的注意力也被稀释。数据不但没有赋予决策权力，反而成为一种干扰。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种方法是不可持续的，尤其是在规模扩大时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-adaptive-telemetry-works&#34;&gt;自适应遥测的工作原理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个自适应遥测从根本上改变了您管理可观测性数据的方式，自动分类和优化，以便您可以重新获得控制权并专注于真正提供价值的遥测。它还为您提供了团队和系统所需的灵活性，无论您想要更多地放手还是完全控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是它的工作原理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;classification-based-on-use&#34;&gt;根据用途分类&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应遥测根据传入数据的使用方式对其进行分类。它是否为警报供电？显示在仪表板上？临时询问？并非所有数据都有价值，因此支持关键操作的信号会被优先考虑，而那些实用性有限的信号则被识别为低价值。这种精确度使您的团队能够专注于可操作的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;automated-optimization&#34;&gt;自动优化&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;分类后，低价值数据会自动聚合、采样、丢弃或减少。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此流程可确保您的可观察性高效，使成本与实际价值保持一致。系统的反馈循环不断地从您的使用模式中学习，调整其行为以适应不断变化的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着环境的发展，自适应遥测也会随之发展，无需手动干预。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;flexibility-for-your-needs&#34;&gt;灵活满足您的需求&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个组织都有独特的要求，自适应遥测是相应构建的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想要确保始终保留特定信号？使用豁免来覆盖建议并保留关键数据。更喜欢更实际的方法？在应用优化建议之前先审核并批准它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-the-most-from-your-logs-and-metrics&#34;&gt;充分利用您的日志和指标&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应遥测目前包括两种形式：自适应指标和自适应日志。它们的运作方式略有不同，但净收益仍然相同：仅提供您需要的遥测数据并消除不必要的混乱和相关成本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;adaptive-metrics&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应指标是我们首次涉足这一领域。 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/05/09/adaptive-metrics-grafana-cloud-announcement/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;于 2023 年推出&lt;/a&gt;，它将未使用和部分使用的指标聚合到降低自身基数版本以降低成本。迄今为止，Adaptive Metrics 已为超过 1,500 个组织实现了&lt;strong&gt;指标成本平均降低 35%。&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1200px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive -telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=900 900w，/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=1040 1040瓦， /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=1240 1240w，/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png?w=1920 1920瓦”&#xA;数据大小=“自动” alt =“”宽度=“1200”高度=“443”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics-architecture.png”&#xA;alt=“”宽度=“1200”高度=“443”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;正如您从上面的工作流程中看到的，自适应指标会分析指标在仪表板、警报和查询中的使用方式，并对它们进行分类以优化数据保留，确保您只存储重要的内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;adaptive-logs&#34;&gt;自适应日志&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/24/introducing-adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;在 ObservabilityCON 2024 上推出&lt;/a&gt;，自适应日志使用 AI/ML 技术以手动流程无法实现的规模来分析可观测性数据。它可以识别常见的日志模式，并创建一组自定义建议来删除未使用的遥测数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应日志和自适应指标的机制非常相似。他们分析使用情况并提出建议，从而减少摄入并节省成本。但是，自适应日志略有不同，它将日志分组为负责高日志量的模式。它还会删除一定比例的日志，而不是像自适应指标那样聚合它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1200px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png”data-srcset =“/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png” png?w=320 320w，/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=550 550w，/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=750 750w，/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w =900 900w， /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=1040 1040w，/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=1240 1240瓦， /media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;数据大小=“自动” alt =“”宽度=“1200”高度=“628”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Adaptive-logs-diagram.png”&#xA;alt=“”宽度=“1200”高度=“628”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ea上图中的 ch 线代表自适应日志生成的假设模式。在中间的示例中，您可以看到日志被频繁查询，因此建议全部保留。对于不经常查询或根本不查询的模式，自适应日志建议删除一定比例的日志。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;worried-about-losing-data-weve-got-you-covered&#34;&gt;担心丢失数据？我们为您服务&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;担心丢失关键遥测数据是很自然的，尤其是当您的系统依赖于事件期间准确可靠的可观测性时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想象一下：现在是凌晨 3 点，您的系统一片混乱。警报不断响起，仪表板一片空白，您的团队正忙着了解正在发生的事情。但您找不到所需的信号，因为它在单方面聚合低价值数据的成本削减工作中丢失了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这些关键时刻，遥测的每个字节都很重要，丢失错误的数据可能会导致您的企业停工、失去信任和收入。值得庆幸的是，这种噩梦般的场景不必发生——这正是自适应遥测中存在&lt;strong&gt;豁免&lt;/strong&gt;的原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/22/how-to-aggregate-metrics-but-retain-ritic-data-introducing-exemptions-in-adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body- txt&#34;&gt;豁免&lt;/a&gt;可让您识别并保留不能丢失的信号，无论是与 SLA 相关的特定指标还是详细调查所需的关键标签。您可以完全控制，以确保即使在优化成本时，最重要的数据在您需要时始终可用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：3356px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Exemptions.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Exemptions.gif”alt =“”宽度=“3356”高度=“1824”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/blog/what-is-adaptive-telemetry/Exemptions.gif”&#xA;alt=“”宽度=“3356”高度=“1824”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有了豁免，您就不必在省钱和保护遥测数据之间做出选择。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论是保护重要指标还是保留关键标签，豁免都让您有信心相信自己的可观察性 - 即使在最关键的情况下也是如此。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;adaptive-telemetry-user-stories&#34;&gt;自适应遥测用户故事&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应遥测已经为管理大量遥测数据的组织提供了结果，&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/02/15/what-are-cardinality-spikes-and-why-do-they-matter/? pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;高基数环境&lt;/a&gt;。以下是工程团队使用这一强大功能所取得的一些关键成果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;更低的成本，不受影响的覆盖范围。&lt;/strong&gt;在集成医疗保健运营平台提供商 TeleTracking，工程师克服了一些最初对关键数据丢失的担忧，该公司能够&lt;a href=&#34;https://www .youtube.com/watch?v=ZGquwsXt1C0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;将其可观察性成本降低 50% 而不会造成损失可见性&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;无需扩展成本即可扩展可观察性。&lt;/strong&gt;身份安全提供商 SailPoint &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VkrQQFPQu2g&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;将其指标量减少了 33%&lt;/a&gt;，并利用节省的资金扩展了其可观察性堆栈。 SailPoint 对 Grafana Cloud 进行了再投资，采用&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/frontend-observability-for-real-user-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;前端可观察性&lt;/a&gt;等工具来增强监控能力。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;让团队能够专注于重要的事情。&lt;/strong&gt;Dell Technologies 面临着巨大的警报疲劳和来自旧版可观测工具的过多数据，因此使用自适应遥测来&lt;a href=&#34;https://www. youtube.com/watch?v=Wz2a4hxt2c4&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;消除未使用的指标、减少噪音并提高工作效率&lt;/a&gt;，以便工程师能够更快、更智能地开发决定。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些现实世界的结果展示了自适应遥测如何帮助组织优化成本、扩展可观测性并增强团队能力。无论您的目标是减少开支、提高团队效率还是增强系统洞察力，自适应遥测都能提供根据您的需求扩展的价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-future-of-observability-is-adaptive&#34;&gt;可观测性的未来是自适应的&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;自适应遥测才刚刚开始。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然它已经可以帮助您有效地管理指标和日志，但未来还有更多。很快，自适应遥测将扩展到跟踪和配置文件，为您提供工具以确保您存储的每一项遥测数据都值得投资。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这一演变体现了我们的使命：帮助您最大限度地发挥可观测性数据的价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;准备好控制您的遥测了吗？立即开始在 Grafana Cloud 中使用自适应遥测，亲自看看有何不同。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【3D printing and observability: How Prusa Research monitors its huge printer farm with Grafana】3D 打印和可观察性：Prusa Research 如何使用 Grafana 监控其庞大的打印机农场</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/01/10/3d-printing-and-observability-how-prusa-research-monitors-its-huge-printer-farm-with-grafana/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been to a &lt;a href=&#34;/events/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs event&lt;/a&gt;, you may have seen one of the company&amp;rsquo;s two 3D printers on site churning out Grafana coins and other novelties.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2020/09/24/how-im-using-grafana-and-prometheus-to-monitor-my-3d-printing/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafanistas&lt;/a&gt; have their own &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/02/15/breathing-easy-with-grafana-dashboards-and-3d-printing/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;3D printers at home&lt;/a&gt;, too, and using them to make and build things is such a popular hobby that one of the company&amp;rsquo;s most popular and busy non-work Slack channels is devoted to 3D printing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Among the enthusiasts is Tom Wilkie, Grafana Labs CTO and co-host of &amp;ldquo;Grafana&amp;rsquo;s Big Tent.&amp;rdquo; In the Season 2 finale of the podcast, he and co-host Mat Ryer, Grafana Labs Engineering Director, chat about the intersection of observability and 3D printing. Their guests are 3D printing hobbyist and Grafana Labs Director of Community Richard &amp;ldquo;RichiH&amp;rdquo; Hartmann, and Pavel Strobl, a DevOps engineer at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.prusa3d.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Prusa Research&lt;/a&gt;. Pavel&amp;rsquo;s company not only makes many of the printers that are popular among Grafanistas, but it also uses &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; internally for web development and observability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can read some of the show’s highlights below, but listen to the full episode to hear more about the history of Prusa Research (and its similarities with Grafana Labs), and to find out who is printing wind tunnels, plant pots, and . . . teeth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;180&#34; frameborder=&#34;no&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; seamless=&#34;&#34; src=&#34;https://share.transistor.fm/e/16368400&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: The following are highlights from episode 10, season 2 of “Grafana’s Big Tent” podcast. The transcript below has been edited for length and clarity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-intersection-of-interests&#34;&gt;An intersection of interests&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom Wilkie:&lt;/strong&gt; This is an observability podcast. So why are we doing an episode on 3D printing?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richard &amp;ldquo;RichiH&amp;rdquo; Hartman:&lt;/strong&gt; Several reasons. We have a lot of engineers [at Grafana Labs], and most of them are software engineers. If you work on software all day, every day, you don&amp;rsquo;t really see any results. But still, we like tinkering, so we have a large maker community. It&amp;rsquo;s roughly split between woodworking, 3D printing, and electronics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Using the technology you work on to understand the real world and derive more information from what&amp;rsquo;s actually happening with things you can touch — that&amp;rsquo;s super-interesting and an intersection of interests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-prusa-research-and-grafana-connections&#34;&gt;The Prusa Research and Grafana connections&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Pavel, you&amp;rsquo;re using Grafana all over the place at Prusa Research, aren&amp;rsquo;t you?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel Strobl:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah. The DevOps department is mostly used for web development. We are observing web services that are running at our Kubernetes cluster, etc. — pretty usual stuff — but we also use Grafana for our development department that is developing 3D printers. Their use is different because they have to develop the printer, so they have different kinds of data than we do and use different technologies. Even though I&amp;rsquo;m not in charge of this department&amp;rsquo;s observability, I know a lot of stuff about it, and it&amp;rsquo;s even accessible at our GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; So what kind of things are the people designing these 3D printers using Grafana for?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; Basically, when you are optimizing the printer, you have to test it, and you can see metrics from the load cell. For example, the probing of the heatbed — you can see the value of the filament sensor, which is analog. You see that the values change when you are printing PLA, or PETG, or flexible filaments. You can get this data and analyze it and implement stack filament detection. There&amp;rsquo;s also all the other data that&amp;rsquo;s interesting for the users — for example, current voltage, so you can calculate power consumption.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; I really appreciate the open source nature of Prusa Research and their things. During the pandemic, it was impossible to get hold of Prusa Minis because they were sold out, so I ended up making my own. I downloaded all your designs and 3D-printed them. One of the things I really like about Prusa Research, and one of the reasons why I have your printers, is because I know I can hack on them and modify them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richi:&lt;/strong&gt; The vast majority of everything which Prusa ever produced was enabled by 3D printing. And when you visit [their campus in Prague], there are hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of 3D printers running 24/7, just churning out parts for new 3D printers — which is part of why they are so reliable, because they use them for their own production. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a product they shove out the door and it&amp;rsquo;s your problem now. They actually run long-term. Tom and I saw printers which had been running for 400 days, with basically no maintenance, and an empty error log.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Another thing that I think Grafana Labs and Prusa Research have in common is that we use a lot of our own tooling at Grafana Labs, and our staging cluster is our main operations cluster. We use our own &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; products — [powered by] &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; — to monitor our Grafana Cloud SaaS, and that&amp;rsquo;s what drives the reliability. Because ideally, if there is a problem with any of our software, we&amp;rsquo;re the ones to discover it first in our ops cluster, and so we&amp;rsquo;re constantly pushing out changes, and testing them, and using them in anger, and then only then giving them to customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2020/07/28/how-were-using-dogfooding-to-serve-up-better-alerting-for-grafana-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;dogfooding&lt;/a&gt; is something that I think really drives a quality product, and I think it&amp;rsquo;s fantastic how Prusa Research does that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat:&lt;/strong&gt; Print your own dogfood.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, you can say that our print farm is like our staging cluster, because we are running over 700 printers, I think. Most of them are MK4s. Then a few XLs for the details that are printable only on XL. Thanks to the 3D printing farm, we actually increased the reliability of our printers, and we found a few issues before the printers were released.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The input shaper was tested at the farm as well. The farm is a crucial part of the company. Without the farm, we cannot produce any printer. Having a test environment like this is actually useful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;monitoring-life-at-the-farm&#34;&gt;Monitoring life at the farm&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat:&lt;/strong&gt; The print farm sounds amazing — 700 printers. That really makes it clear why Grafana is going to help there with observability. What did you do before you had Grafana? How did you manage something like that?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; Before we had Grafana, as far as I know, we had nothing — at least for the 3D printing part of the company. Because when MK3 was in development, there was a need for monitoring the printers. You had to go and print, take the prints out, etc., and notice that there&amp;rsquo;s some issue with the printer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Datadog was used for web development, but I joined Prusa Research when Grafana was embraced, thankfully, and we have been using Grafana since then. For DevOps, we are cutting edge and running on 10.4.1, and we are preparing to migrate to &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/download/11.0.0?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt-btn&#34;&gt;version 11&lt;/a&gt;. For the development part, it&amp;rsquo;s a little bit older.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; You&amp;rsquo;re going to really like &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-11-release-all-the-new-features/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;11&lt;/a&gt;. The new &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/explore-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Explore Metrics&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/simplified-exploration/logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Explore Logs&lt;/a&gt; experiences in there are game-changing, in my opinion. It makes it so much easier for more people in an organization to access their &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/prometheus/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; metrics and their &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; logs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But you&amp;rsquo;re not using Prometheus for a lot of things, are you? You use something else.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; In DevOps we use Prometheus, but for the printers, InfluxDB is used. The main reason why is because of a need for nanosecond precision. That&amp;rsquo;s not possible with Prometheus. When you are developing a printer, you really have to know when something occurred, and nanosecond precision is a must.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Richi, why don&amp;rsquo;t we have nanosecond precision in Prometheus?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richi:&lt;/strong&gt; Because it&amp;rsquo;s always an engineering trade-off — how much precision versus how much data usage. For most computer things, microseconds are more than enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s why we use them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my somewhat strong opinion, for everything where you actually need the super-high precision, you tend to not have super-long running things. Pretty much all the established industries use metrics with whatever precision for long-running stuff. And when you have your microburst on the network, or you have your jitter on the power supply or whatever, you use logs or events with super-high precision for a very short time, and only the really important stuff gets emitted. But I don&amp;rsquo;t think the firmware of Prusa is there yet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; You can actually get metrics into Prometheus from the printers thanks to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pstrobl96/prusa_exporter&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Prusa Exporter&lt;/a&gt;, which I wrote. What the printer sends is almost the line protocol for Influx, but it&amp;rsquo;s not the line protocol, because in the line protocol you have timestamps. There is no timestamp because the printer doesn&amp;rsquo;t have enough memory to send timestamps, so it sends delta, and it sends for how long it&amp;rsquo;s running.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Richi takes a 3D printer to almost every Grafana Labs event and shows that work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richi:&lt;/strong&gt; We print swag, but the main thing is we can display all the data the printers are emitting in Grafana, and this gives you a little bit more of a tangible thing. We can put up all the demos and all the recorded videos and everything we want, but to really drive home the point of the versatility of the whole platform, we — or myself — came up with the idea of showing something people can actually touch, as opposed to just yet another Kubernetes cluster where you can&amp;rsquo;t really see what&amp;rsquo;s happening.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So you see something in the real world, you can touch and even get the product, and you can see how it&amp;rsquo;s made on the Grafana dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;powerful-visuals&#34;&gt;Powerful visuals&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Pavel, now that you&amp;rsquo;re gathering all this data, what is the most interesting thing you&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that you previously didn&amp;rsquo;t know?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; I cannot speak for the whole company, but for me it&amp;rsquo;s how a printer works with power supply and how effective it is while it&amp;rsquo;s printing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For 3D printers, it was probably the use of load cell data. Basically, if you have any 3D object in reality, you can use the load cell sensor on the nozzle to probe the model or anything you have on the printer to get the shape of the model in 3D space. It&amp;rsquo;s not easy, obviously. You have to calculate a lot, and get the data from the printer, but you can actually get a 3D model from the load cell sensor. It&amp;rsquo;s like a 3D scanner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a load cell sensor, it&amp;rsquo;s interesting that you can actually print on any surface you want, and we recently did this video about printing on different surfaces. There was a PlayStation 4 used as a printing sheet, or you can print on T-shirts. It works pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-move-to-mimir&#34;&gt;A move to Mimir&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Pavel, when we were chatting before the podcast, you said that you&amp;rsquo;re thinking of adopting Mimir for your metrics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, exactly. We are using Prometheus as our backend, but for federation, we have multiple instances. We use Thanos at this moment, and we are experimenting with Mimir because we are going to move our DevOps cluster to a different region. This is a really good opportunity to migrate the data because mostly we are going to scrap it. Using Grafana Mimir for my purposes — for Prusa Exporter — it works pretty well exporting data for everything I want. For me, it&amp;rsquo;s more scalable. And this is the future of the DevOps department for now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; This is the Big Tent podcast, so we embrace all of the metrics backends — that&amp;rsquo;s totally cool. But why are you moving off of &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/set-up/migrate/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Thanos to Mimir&lt;/a&gt;? What&amp;rsquo;s motivating that move?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; For us, it&amp;rsquo;s slow queries. We have over two years of data, and if you query over 14 days, it takes a lot of time to get the data from Thanos. That&amp;rsquo;s basically the main reason. The store gateway is starting too slowly, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; I wrote the early versions of Mimir when it was called Cortex. One of the things we designed it to do is lots of parallel queries, and really be able to scale in that dimension. We did it for fun, and at the time, it might not have been the thing people actually needed. Most people needed what you&amp;rsquo;ve just described, which is querying over months or years of data. The thing I&amp;rsquo;m most excited about is we&amp;rsquo;ve finally found a use case for being able to handle high concurrent query load, and it&amp;rsquo;s this new Explore Metrics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Explore Metrics, when you click on a metric, it&amp;rsquo;s gonna go off and do a query for every single label behind that metric to see which labels have outliers, and what the distributions are. Clicking on a metric issues, like, 15 queries instantaneously, and it puts a lot of load on the Mimir cluster, but it&amp;rsquo;s something Mimir handles very well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s really interesting, because we&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of users tell that story where, &amp;ldquo;Oh, I&amp;rsquo;m moving off of Thanos, because I started using the Explore Metrics and it was killing my cluster. And so I&amp;rsquo;m starting to move to Mimir, or to Grafana Cloud.&amp;rdquo; We run &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Metrics&lt;/a&gt; with many, many replicas of the querier to deal with this exact use case. It kind of was a solution in search of a problem for a while, but we&amp;rsquo;ve found one, finally.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat:&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;rsquo;s another version of dogfooding, really. We basically &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/20/ddos-protection-observability-automation-and-curiosity/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;DDoS&lt;/a&gt; ourselves, and then we have to make sure that works and keeps working. It&amp;rsquo;s quite fun.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; I remember when the Explore Metrics team was like, &amp;ldquo;Oh, we&amp;rsquo;ve got to be careful with how many queries we issue to the metrics back,&amp;rdquo; and I&amp;rsquo;m like, &amp;ldquo;No, no, no. You&amp;rsquo;re just giving the metrics team a challenge — giving them something to work on.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat:&lt;/strong&gt; And we&amp;rsquo;ve done that for &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/24/queryless-metrics-logs-traces-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;logs, profiles, and traces&lt;/a&gt;, of course, as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;top-3d-printing-projects&#34;&gt;Top 3D printing projects&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat:&lt;/strong&gt; What is the best thing you have 3D-printed?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;rsquo;re all holding up a little &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.printables.com/model/655662-grafana-grot-mascot&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;3D-printed Grot&lt;/a&gt;, the Grafana Labs mascot that&amp;rsquo;s a little like a juvenile dinosaur. I found someone who would turn our art department&amp;rsquo;s 2D images into a 3D STL. I posted it up on Printables, and Pavel downloaded it and colorized it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richi:&lt;/strong&gt; Honestly, mine is probably the first thing which I printed, which is a lamp holder. I whipped it up with no skills within, like, half an hour. It&amp;rsquo;s still going strong, years later, and it still holds up the lamp.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel:&lt;/strong&gt; Atlantis, the city from Stargate Atlantis, was one of my first prints and I still have it somewhere. It&amp;rsquo;s silver PLA. That&amp;rsquo;s probably the best print I ever did.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; You can download your GitHub timeline — the green dots — as an STL to print, where each one&amp;rsquo;s like a different height. Mat, I&amp;rsquo;ll print yours for you and send it over.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh, let me do some coding first. I could probably do it at the moment with a 2D printer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s just a blank sheet of paper for Mat.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat:&lt;/strong&gt; I&amp;rsquo;m genuinely considering getting a 3D printer now, just for that!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Grafana’s Big Tent” podcast wants to hear from you. If you have a great story to share, want to join the conversation, or have any feedback, please contact the Big Tent team at &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/23/grafanas-big-tent-podcast-season-2-is-here/bigtent@grafana.com&#34;&gt;bigtent@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;. You can also catch up on the first and second season of “Grafana’s Big Tent” on &lt;a href=&#34;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/grafanas-big-tent/id1616725129&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/show/3beQvS8to0rYs1gxOnPrfD?si=bf046f54fe214615&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;如果您曾经参加过 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs 活动&lt;/a&gt;，您可能在现场看到过该公司的两台 3D 打印机之一大量生产 Grafana 硬币和其他新奇物品。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;许多&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2020/09/24/how-im-using-grafana-and-prometheus-to-monitor-my-3d-printing/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt; Grafanistas&lt;/a&gt; 有他们自己的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/02/15/breathing-easy-with-grafana-dashboards-and-3d-printing/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;家用 3D 打印机&lt;/a&gt;，以及使用它们来制造和建造东西是一种非常流行的爱好，以至于该公司最受欢迎和最繁忙的非工作 Slack 频道之一专门致力于 3D 打印。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs 首席技术官兼“Grafana’s Big Tent”的联合主持人 Tom Wilkie 就是其中的狂热者。在播客的第二季结局中，他和 Grafana 实验室工程总监 Mat Ryer 共同主持，讨论了可观测性和 3D 打印的交叉点。他们的嘉宾是 3D 打印爱好者和 Grafana Labs 社区总监 Richard “RichiH” Hartmann，以及 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.prusa3d.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34; 的 DevOps 工程师 Pavel Strobl noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Prusa 研究&lt;/a&gt;。 Pavel 的公司不仅生产许多在 Grafanista 中流行的打印机，而且还在内部使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; 进行 Web 开发和可观察性。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以阅读下面的一些节目亮点，但也可以收听整集，了解更多有关 Prusa Research 的历史（及其与 Grafana Labs 的相似之处）的信息，并了解谁在打印风洞、花盆、和 。 。 。牙齿。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“100％”height =“180”frameborder =“否”滚动=“否”无缝=“”src =“https://share.transistor.fm/e/16368400”&gt; &lt;/ iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：以下是“Grafana’s Big Tent”播客第二季第 10 集的精彩片段。为了长度和清晰度，下面的文字记录已经过编辑。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-intersection-of-interests&#34;&gt;兴趣的交集&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom Wilkie：&lt;/strong&gt;这是一个可观察性播客。那么我们为什么要制作一集关于 3D 打印的节目呢？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;理查德“RichiH”Hartman：&lt;/strong&gt;有几个原因。我们[Grafana Labs]有很多工程师，其中大多数是软件工程师。如果你每天都在软件上工作，你不会真正看到任何结果。但我们仍然喜欢修补，所以我们有一个庞大的创客社区。它大致分为木工、3D 打印和电子产品。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用您正在研究的技术来了解现实世界，并从您可以触摸的事物实际发生的情况中获取更多信息 - 这是非常有趣的，也是兴趣的交集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-prusa-research-and-grafana-connections&#34;&gt;Prusa Research 和 Grafana 的联系&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;Pavel，你到处都在使用 Grafana在 Prusa Research，不是吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;帕维尔·斯特罗布尔：&lt;/strong&gt;是的。 DevOps 部门主要用于 Web 开发。我们正在观察在 Kubernetes 集群等上运行的 Web 服务（这是很常见的事情），但我们也将 Grafana 用于开发 3D 打印机的开发部门。他们的用途不同，因为他们必须开发打印机，因此他们拥有与我们不同类型的数据并使用不同的技术。尽管我不负责这个部门的可观察性，但我知道很多关于它的东西，甚至可以在我们的 GitHub 上访问它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;那么人们使用 Grafana 设计这些 3D 打印机的目的是什么？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel：&lt;/strong&gt;基本上，当您优化打印机时，您必须对其进行测试，并且您可以从称重传感器中看到指标。例如，加热床的探测 - 您可以看到灯丝传感器的值，它是模拟的。当您打印 PLA、PETG 或柔性耗材时，您会发现这些值会发生变化。您可以获得这些数据并对其进行分析并实施堆栈灯丝检测。还有用户感兴趣的所有其他数据 - 例如当前电压，以便您可以计算功耗。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;我真的很欣赏 Prusa Research 及其产品的开源性质。在大流行期间，不可能买到 Prusa Mini，因为它们已经卖完了，所以我最终自己做了。我下载了您的所有设计并进行了 3D 打印。我真正喜欢 Prusa Research 的原因之一，也是我拥有你们打印机的原因之一，是因为我知道我可以破解它们并修改它们。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richi：&lt;/strong&gt;Prusa 生产的绝大多数产品都是通过 3D 打印实现的。当您参观 [他们在布拉格的园区] 时，您会发现成百上千台 3D 打印机 24/7 不间断地运行，只是为新的 3D 打印机生产零件——这就是它们如此可靠的部分原因，因为它们将它们用于他们自己生产。这不仅仅是他们推出的产品，现在也是您的问题。他们实际上是长期运行的。我和 Tom 看到打印机已经运行了 400 天，基本没有维护，错误日志为空。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;我认为 Grafana Labs 和 Prusa Research 的另一个共同点是，我们在 Grafana Labs 使用了很多我们自己的工具，而我们的临时集群是我们的主要运营集群。我们使用自己的 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 产品 — [技术支持]&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt =body-txt&#34;&gt;米米尔&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;洛基&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; — 至监控我们的 Grafana Cloud SaaS，这就是驱动力e 可靠性。因为理想情况下，如果我们的任何软件出现问题，我们是最先在操作集群中发现它的人，因此我们不断推出更改，测试它们，并愤怒地使用它们，然后然后才将它们提供给客户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2020/07/28/how-were-using-dogfooding-to-serve-up-better-alerting-for-grafana-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt &#34;&gt;我认为内部测试&lt;/a&gt;确实能够推动优质产品的发展，而且我认为 Prusa Research 的做法非常棒。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat：&lt;/strong&gt;打印您自己的狗粮。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel：&lt;/strong&gt;是的，你可以说我们的打印农场就像我们的临时集群，因为我认为我们运行着 700 多台打印机。其中大部分是MK4。然后是一些 XL 的细节，这些细节只能在 XL 上打印。感谢 3D 打印农场，我们实际上提高了打印机的可靠性，并且在打印机发布之前我们发现了一些问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;输入整形器也在农场进行了测试。农场是公司的重要组成部分。没有农场，我们就无法生产任何打印机。拥有这样的测试环境实际上很有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;monitoring-life-at-the-farm&#34;&gt;监控农场的生活&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat：&lt;/strong&gt; 打印农场听起来棒极了——有 700 台打印机。这确实清楚地表明了为什么 Grafana 将在可观察性方面提供帮助。在使用 Grafana 之前您做了什么？你是如何处理这样的事情的？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel：&lt;/strong&gt;在我们拥有 Grafana 之前，据我所知，我们什么都没有——至少对于公司的 3D 打印部分来说是这样。因为MK3开发的时候，有监控打印机的需求。您必须去打印、取出打印件等，然后注意到打印机出现了一些问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Datadog 用于 Web 开发，但谢天谢地，当 Grafana 被拥抱时，我加入了 Prusa Research，从那时起我们就一直在使用 Grafana。对于 DevOps，我们处于领先地位并在 10.4.1 上运行，我们正准备迁移到&lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/download/11.0.0?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt-btn&#34;&gt;版本 11&lt;/一个&gt;。对于开发部分来说，它有点旧。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;您会非常喜欢&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-11-release-all-the-new-features/?pg=博客&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;11&lt;/a&gt;。新的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/explore-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;探索指标&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore在我看来，/simplified-exploration/logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;探索日志&lt;/a&gt; 体验改变了游戏规则。它使组织中的更多人可以更轻松地访问他们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/prometheus/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Prometheus&lt;/a&gt; 指标及其 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss /loki/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; 日志。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是您并没有使用 Prometheus 来做很多事情，是吗？你用别的东西。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel：&lt;/strong&gt;在 DevOps 中，我们使用 Prometheus，但对于打印机，使用 InfluxDB。主要原因是需要纳秒精度。对于普罗米修斯来说这是不可能的。当您开发打印机时，您确实必须知道什么时候发生了事情，而纳秒精度是必须的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;Richi，为什么我们在 Prometheus 中没有纳秒精度？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richi：&lt;/strong&gt;因为这始终是一个工程权衡——多少精度与多少数据使用量。对于大多数计算机事物来说，微秒就足够了，这就是我们使用它们的原因。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我看来，对于真正需要超高精度的所有东西，你往往不会有超长时间运行的东西。几乎所有成熟的行业都对长期运行的东西使用任何精度的指标。当网络上出现微突发，或者电源出现抖动或其他任何情况时，您会在很短的时间内使用超高精度的日志或事件，并且只有真正重要的内容才会被发射。但我认为 Prusa 的固件还没有。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel：&lt;/strong&gt;由于 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/pstrobl96/prusa_exporter&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener，您实际上可以从打印机将指标获取到 Prometheus 中noreferrer&#34;&gt;Prusa Exporter&lt;/a&gt;，我写的。打印机发送的几乎是 Influx 的线路协议，但它不是线路协议，因为在线路协议中你有时间戳。没有时间戳，因为打印机没有足够的内存来发送时间戳，因此它发送增量，并发送它运行的时间。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;Richi 几乎在每次 Grafana Labs 活动中都会携带 3D 打印机并展示其工作原理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richi：&lt;/strong&gt;我们打印赃物，但最重要的是我们可以在 Grafana 中显示打印机发出的所有数据，这为您提供了更多有形的东西。我们可以发布所有演示、所有录制的视频以及我们想要的一切，但为了真正让人们了解整个平台的多功能性，我们（或我自己）提出了展示人们可以实际触摸的东西的想法，与另一个 Kubernetes 集群相反，您无法真正看到正在发生的事情。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，您可以在现实世界中看到一些东西，您可以触摸甚至获得该产品，并且您可以在 Grafana 仪表板上看到它是如何制作的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;powerful-visuals&#34;&gt;强大的视觉效果&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆：&lt;/strong&gt;帕维尔，现在您正在收集所有这些数据，您发现的最有趣的事情是什么？您以前不知道？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel：&lt;/strong&gt;我不能代表整个公司，但对我来说，这就是打印机在电源下的工作方式以及打印时的效率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于 3D 打印机来说，这可能是e 使用称重传感器数据。基本上，如果现实中有任何 3D 物体，您可以使用喷嘴上的称重传感器来探测模型或打印机上的任何物体，以获得 3D 空间中模型的形状。显然，这并不容易。您必须进行大量计算，并从打印机获取数据，但实际上您可以从称重传感器获取 3D 模型。它就像 3D 扫描仪。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为称重传感器，有趣的是您实际上可以在任何您想要的表面上进行打印，我们最近制作了有关在不同表面上进行打印的视频。有一个PlayStation 4用作打印纸，或者你可以打印在T恤上。效果非常好。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-move-to-mimir&#34;&gt;搬到米米尔&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;Pavel，当我们在播客之前聊天时，你说你正在考虑采用 Mimir 作为你的指标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;帕维尔：&lt;/strong&gt;是的，完全正确。我们使用 Prometheus 作为后端，但对于联合，我们有多个实例。我们目前使用 Thanos，并且正在试验 Mimir，因为我们要将 DevOps 集群移动到不同的区域。这是一个迁移数据的好机会，因为大多数情况下我们都会废弃它。使用 Grafana Mimir 来实现我的目的（Prusa Exporter），它可以很好地导出我想要的所有数据。对我来说，它更具可扩展性。这就是 DevOps 部门目前的未来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;这是 Big Tent 播客，因此我们采用所有指标后端 - 这非常酷。但你为什么要离开&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/set-up/migrate/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Thanos to Mimir&lt;/a&gt;？是什么促使这一举动？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pavel：&lt;/strong&gt;对于我们来说，查询速度很慢。我们有两年多的数据，如果查询超过14天，从Thanos获取数据需要花费很多时间。这基本上就是主要原因。商店网关启动太慢等&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;我编写了 Mimir 的早期版本，当时它被称为 Cortex。我们设计它的目的之一是进行大量并行查询，并且真正能够在该维度上进行扩展。我们这样做是为了好玩，在当时，这可能不是人们真正需要的东西。大多数人需要您刚才描述的功能，即查询数月或数年的数据。最让我兴奋的是我们终于找到了一个能够处理高并发查询负载的用例，这就是这个新的探索指标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在“探索指标”中，当您单击某个指标时，它会开始查询该指标后面的每个标签，以查看哪些标签有异常值以及分布是什么。点击某个指标会出现瞬时 15 个查询等问题，这会给 Mimir 集群带来很大的负载，但 Mimir 处理得很好。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这真的很有趣，因为我们有很多用户讲述这样的故事：“哦，我要离开 Thanos，因为我开始使用 Explore Metrics，但它正在杀死我的集群。所以我开始转向 Mimir 或 Grafana Cloud。”我们使用许多查询器副本运行 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Metrics&lt;/a&gt; 来处理这个确切的用例。这有点像是一段时间寻找问题的解决方案，但我们终于找到了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat：&lt;/strong&gt;这确实是dogfooding的另一个版本。我们基本上是自己&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/20/ddos-protection-observability-automation-and-curiosity/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;DDoS&lt;/a&gt;，然后我们必须确保其有效并持续有效。挺好玩的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt; 我记得当探索指标团队说时，“哦，我们必须小心我们向指标发出的查询数量，”我想， “不，不，不。你只是给指标团队一个挑战——给他们一些工作要做。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat：&lt;/strong&gt;我们已经为 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/24/queryless-metrics-logs-traces-profiles/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body- 做到了这一点txt&#34;&gt;日志、配置文件和痕迹&lt;/a&gt;，当然，也是如此。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;top-3d-printing-projects&#34;&gt;顶级 3D 打印项目&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat：&lt;/strong&gt;您 3D 打印的最好的东西是什么？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;我们都有点犹豫&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.printables.com/model/655662-grafana-grot-mascot&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;3D 打印的 Grot&lt;/a&gt;，Grafana 实验室的吉祥物，有点像幼年恐龙。我找到了一个可以将我们艺术部门的 2D 图像转换为 3D STL 的人。我将其发布在 Printables 上，Pavel 下载了它并对其进行了着色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Richi：&lt;/strong&gt;老实说，我打印的第一个东西可能是我的，它是一个灯座。我毫无技巧地在半小时之内就完成了它。几年后它仍然很强大，并且仍然支撑着灯。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;帕维尔：&lt;/strong&gt;亚特兰蒂斯，《星际之门》中的亚特兰蒂斯城市，是我的第一张印刷品之一，我仍然在某处保存着它。这是银色的PLA。这可能是我做过的最好的印刷品。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom：&lt;/strong&gt;您可以将 GitHub 时间线（绿点）下载为 STL 进行打印，其中每个时间线的高度都不同。 Mat，我会为您打印并发送给您。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat：&lt;/strong&gt;哦，让我先写一些代码。我现在可能可以使用 2D 打印机来完成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆：&lt;/strong&gt;是的，这对 Mat 来说只是一张白纸。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat：&lt;/strong&gt;我现在真的正在考虑购买一台 3D 打印机，就是为了这个！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Grafana 的大帐篷”播客希望收到您的来信。如果您有精彩的故事要分享，想加入对话站，或有任何反馈，请联系 Big Tent 团队：&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/23/grafanas-big-tent-podcast-season-2-is-here/bigtent@grafana.com&#34; &gt;bigtent@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;。您还可以在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/grafanas-big-tent/id1616725129&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; 上观看《Grafana&#39;s Big Tent》第一季和第二季rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Apple 播客&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/show/3beQvS8to0rYs1gxOnP​​rfD?si=bf046f54fe214615&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>