<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</title>
    <link>/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How to use AI to analyze and visualize CAN data with Grafana Assistant】如何通过 Grafana Assistant 使用 AI 分析和可视化 CAN 数据</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/12/12/how-to-use-ai-to-analyze-and-visualize-can-data-with-grafana-assistant/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;A version of this post originally appeared on the&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/grafana-assistant-can-bus-data-ai-llm-dashboards&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CSS Electronics blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Martin Falch, co-owner and head of sales and marketing at CSS Electronics, is an expert on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/can-bus-simple-intro-tutorial&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CAN bus data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Martin works closely with end users, typically OEM engineers, across diverse industries, including automotive, maritime, and industrial. He is passionate about data visualization and AI—and he&amp;rsquo;s been working extensively with Grafana Assistant.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At CSS Electronics, we build pro specs and simple-to-use &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/can-bus-hardware-products&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CAN bus data loggers&lt;/a&gt; including optional WiFi/LTE/GPS. In short, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/can-bus-simple-intro-tutorial&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CAN bus&lt;/a&gt; is a protocol used for communicating sensor data within vehicles and machinery, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/j1939-data-logger-wifi-telematics-fleet-management&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;trucks&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/obd2-data-logger-sd-memory-convert&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;cars&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/marine-telematics-boat-data&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;ships&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/canopen-data-logger&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;robots&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our end users include engineers at automotive and industrial manufacturers (OEMs) who need to monitor assets in the field for R&amp;amp;D, diagnostics, or &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/predictive-maintenance-can-bus-iot&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;predictive maintenance&lt;/a&gt;. A large share of our users also visualize their data via Grafana dashboards using Amazon Athena or Google BigQuery data sources (see our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/13/how-to-visualize-vehicle-can-bus-data-with-the-amazon-athena-data-source-for-grafana/&#34;&gt;previous blog post&lt;/a&gt; for details).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog, we show how &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; can be used to easily unleash the power of AI for data analysis and dashboard visualization—directly within Grafana!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-use-grafana-assistant-for-can-data-analyses&#34;&gt;Why use Grafana Assistant for CAN data analyses?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our users face a challenge: They can collect tons of CAN/LIN data using the CANedge, but they have to then explore or visualize data across several devices, thousands of log files, and months (or even years) of data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of our users are engineers, but they&amp;rsquo;re not data scientists. And even if they are, statistical data analysis/visualization can be extremely time consuming.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-not-use-chatgpt&#34;&gt;Why not use ChatGPT?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One solution to this challenge is to use ChatGPT to help analyze the data, which we wrote about in a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/chatgpt-can-bus-data-time-series-code-interpreter&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;2023 article&lt;/a&gt;. However, ChatGPT has some practical limitations:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Limited to manually uploading small files (e.g. 100 MB CSV)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Analysis results are not easy to share&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Outputs are &amp;ldquo;static&amp;rdquo; (e.g., Python-generated plots)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;key-features-of-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;Key features of Grafana Assistant &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x600/75de30d1ec/can-data-architecture.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x600/75de30d1ec/can-data-architecture.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Architectural diagram showing data going from heavy machinery to Google Cloud to Grafana Cloud and back&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In practice, our end users typically upload gigabytes (or terabytes) of data to their own AWS, Google Cloud, or Microsoft Azure cloud servers using our devices. Here, the data is auto-processed into Parquet data lakes, which can be queried via &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/18/visualize-google-cloud-bigquery-data-in-grafana-the-latest-updates-key-features-and-more/&#34;&gt;Grafana’s Athena/BigQuery data sources&lt;/a&gt;. In other words, the complete data lake is easily accessible within Grafana. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the new assistant, Grafana Cloud now enables seamless LLM access to existing data sources that are already in place. This introduces multiple powerful features:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zero set up:&lt;/strong&gt; If you have already deployed a Grafana integration, you can start prompting your data immediately—no set up required.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Analyze terabytes of data:&lt;/strong&gt; Unlike ChatGPT, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to limit your analysis to 100 MB of data. The assistant can query your entire data lake out-the-box.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data exploration:&lt;/strong&gt; Simply chat your way to powerful data insights and through complex diagnostic analyses—no query language or coding knowledge required.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dashboard creation:&lt;/strong&gt; The assistant can create fully customized Grafana dashboards in seconds based on high level prompts, drastically reducing time spent.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Retain and share insights:&lt;/strong&gt; Any data insights can be easily summarized into Grafana dashboards, enabling you to navigate the data temporally and share it with your team.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s basically Cursor/Windsurf for your dashboards and data lake.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-start-analyzing-can-data-with-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;How to start analyzing CAN data with Grafana Assistant &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1023/88223b6f97/can-timeseries.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1023/88223b6f97/can-timeseries.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard showing CAN timeseries data&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you have already connected your data source in Grafana Cloud, no further set up is necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To start chatting with the assistant, you can open the chat window via the left-menu Assistant tab. Alternatively, you can open the chat panel within a dashboard via the sparkle icon in the upper right corner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, to get the best experience, we recommend following these steps:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use a dashboard template:&lt;/strong&gt; At CSS we provide various dashboard templates customized for our end users, which include relevant &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/visualizations/dashboards/variables/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana variable&lt;/a&gt; dropdowns. Using templates as the basis for LLM-based dashboard development is highly recommended as it allows dashboard users to subsequently interact with the generated dashboards (e.g. switching between different devices)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Select data source as context:&lt;/strong&gt; Make sure to select the relevant data source in the Grafana Assistant chat window to explicitly tell it what data to work with.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use a system prompt:&lt;/strong&gt; In our documentation we provide a &amp;ldquo;system prompt&amp;rdquo; that our users can add as a &amp;ldquo;rule&amp;rdquo; within the Grafana Assistant settings. This provides context about the data lake structure, query syntax and more—and significantly improves the results. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;example-use-cases&#34;&gt;Example use cases&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To showcase how Grafana Assistant can help with data analyses, we&amp;rsquo;ll use our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/ev-data-pack-electric-vehicles&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;public data pack&lt;/a&gt;, which consists of 1GB of data from a Kia EV6 electric vehicle. Below we highlight example use cases for the LLM:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;example-1-see-what-data-is-available&#34;&gt;Example 1: See what data is available&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, we use the LLM to get an overview of our data lake.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a useful starting point for exploring a CAN bus data lake as you do not necessarily have a clear overview of what devices, CAN messages, and CAN signals are available. Further, constructing the SQL queries to extract this information is quite complex.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;Prompt:&#xA;My data source contains data from a Kia EV6 electric car, recorded with a CANedge CAN bus data logger with device ID 2A896980. The data includes battery data from the EV and GPS/IMU data from a sensor module. I want to know the following:&#xA;1: What tables and columns are available for this device?&#xA;2: What time period does the data span?&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant starts analyzing the data via multiple queries, summarizing the results in a tabular form, and in the chat. Notice how the LLM iterates through multiple queries to understand the data structure. You can of course inspect what queries are used to generate each result, ensuring full transparency. The summary provides us with a good starting point for further investigation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/742056367?transparent=0&#34; title=&#34;vimeo video&#34; webkitallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; mozallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;div &gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;example-2-explore-data-ad-hoc&#34;&gt;Example 2: Explore data ad hoc&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In many cases you&amp;rsquo;ll want to explore the data directly in the chat window prior to creating actual panels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here, Grafana Assistant runs the relevant queries and produces the output in-chat as text or as plots. We can also prompt the LLM to create a panel that displays speed over time within our dashboard, which Grafana does successfully as shown below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;Prompt:&#xA;What is the average speed from the CAN2_GnssSpeed message in July 2023? It&amp;#39;s in m/s. Please create a panel in this dashboard to visualize the average speed over time&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/742056367?transparent=0&#34; title=&#34;vimeo video&#34; webkitallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; mozallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;div &gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;example-3-create-dashboard-via-a-high-level-prompt&#34;&gt;Example 3: Create dashboard via a high-level prompt&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An obvious use case for Grafana Assistant is to create a new dashboard from scratch. In this example we try a minimal-effort prompt—leaving a lot up to the imagination of the LLM.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The result is a functional 12-panel dashboard where all SQL queries are as expected (i.e., as per our system prompt guidance). Notice in particular that the LLM proactively identifies available (and relevant) messages/signals. Pretty cool! It&amp;rsquo;s worth reflecting on how commoditized LLMs + tools have already become. If this was 2022 we&amp;rsquo;d have been blown away.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the dashboard we get is highly inconsistent between re-runs of the same prompt. This is of course to be expected given the open-ended nature of our request. In our view, there&amp;rsquo;s not much practical value to providing prompts that are this high level if the goal is to create real Grafana dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;Prompt:&#xA;My data source contains data from a Kia EV6 electric car, recorded with a CANedge CAN bus data logger with device ID 2A896980. The data includes battery data from the EV and GPS/IMU data from a sensor module.&#xA;Update my dashboard to include panels showing my Kia EV6 battery data and GPS/IMU data.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/742056367?transparent=0&#34; title=&#34;vimeo video&#34; webkitallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; mozallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;div &gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;example-4-create-a-dashboard-via-a-detailed-prompt&#34;&gt;Example 4: Create a dashboard via a detailed prompt&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead of using a fairly vague prompt, a much better approach is of course to provide highly detailed guidance, similar to what you would provide a human assistant if they were to design your dashboard. You can find the full detailed prompt &lt;a href=&#34;https://canlogger1000.csselectronics.com/files/guides/grafana-assistant-intro/grafana-assistant-detailed-dashboard-prompt.txt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see, the result looks as intended. And more importantly, when we run this 10x (in new conversations each time), we get a 90%+ consistent dashboard each time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You might argue that writing a prompt like this is also time consuming, but in our experience it is still five to 10 times faster than if we were to construct this dashboard from scratch. For example, notice that many of our message/signal names are approximate, leaving Grafana Assistant to figure out what the exact table and column names are. Further, some of the panels involve semi-complex queries (e.g., the consumed State of Charge and the delta distance traveled), which would require significant SQL expertise to create.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, the prompt specifies no SQL syntax, which is important as 99%+ of our end users have zero SQL experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out the generated dashboard in our &lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.csselectronics.stellarhosted.com/d/grafana-assistant-ev6-bigquery/grafana-assistant-ev6-bigquery?orgId=1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;public playground&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/742056367?transparent=0&#34; title=&#34;vimeo video&#34; webkitallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; mozallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;div &gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-summary-thoughts&#34;&gt;Our summary thoughts&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We spent 20+ hours with Grafana Assistant. Here are our overarching thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1: Excellent concept.&lt;/strong&gt; For users that have already hooked up Grafana to their data, it is extremely simple to start working with the data through the LLM. This ease-of-access is a critical advantage—and the Grafana Assistant UI is great.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2: A drunk genius.&lt;/strong&gt; Grafana Assistant can give you that &amp;ldquo;magical experience&amp;rdquo; where you sit back and watch it produce an entire Grafana dashboard in one shot according to your specifications. However, in some cases it will produce invalid queries, get stuck or hallucinate—just like all LLMs. Make sure to always review the output.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3: Visualization vs. analysis.&lt;/strong&gt; The LLM is able to modify dashboards and execute SQL queries, making it an excellent tool for data visualization and light exploration. However, it is not able to run scripts (in contrast to ChatGPT, for example), making it less suitable for highly complex, multi-step data analysis—at least for now. Such functionality could be a powerful future mode/variation of the assistant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4: Huge potential.&lt;/strong&gt; While the current version has limitations in terms of performance and data source support, we are confident that Grafana Assistant will become an extremely handy tool for data visualization and exploration. In just our one month of testing, Grafana added a ton of improvements to the LLM, so we are excited to see how this tool develops!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more and see additional showcases, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.csselectronics.com/pages/grafana-assistant-can-bus-data-ai-llm-dashboards&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;full Grafana Assistant article&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;本文的一个版本最初出现在&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/grafana-assistant-can-bus-data-ai-llm-dashboards&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CSS Electronics 博客&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CSS Electronics 共同所有人兼销售和营销主管 Martin Falch 是&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/can-bus-simple-intro-tutorial&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CAN 总线数据&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;方面的专家。 &lt;em&gt;Martin 与汽车、海事和工业等不同行业的最终用户（通常是 OEM 工程师）密切合作。他对数据可视化和人工智能充满热情，并且一直与 Grafana Assistant 进行广泛的合作。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 CSS Electronics，我们打造专业规格和简单易用的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/can-bus-hardware-products&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CAN 总线数据记录器&lt;/a&gt;，包括可选的 WiFi/LTE/GPS。简而言之，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/can-bus-simple-intro-tutorial&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CAN 总线&lt;/a&gt;是一种用于在车辆和机械内传输传感器数据的协议，包括&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/j1939-data-logger-wifi-telematics-fleet-management&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;卡车&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/obd2-data-logger-sd-memory-convert&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;汽车&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/marine-telematics-boat-data&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;船舶&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/canopen-data-logger&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;机器人&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的最终用户包括汽车和工业制造商 (OEM) 的工程师，他们需要监控现场资产以进行研发、诊断或&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/predictive-maintenance-can-bus-iot&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;预测性维护&lt;/a&gt;。我们的很大一部分用户还使用 Amazon Athena 或 Google BigQuery 数据源通过 Grafana 仪表板可视化他们的数据（有关详细信息，请参阅我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/13/how-to-visualize-vehicle-can-bus-data-with-the-amazon-athena-data-source-for-grafana/&#34;&gt;之前的博文&lt;/a&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在本博客中，我们将展示如何使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; 直接在 Grafana 中轻松释放 AI 的力量，进行数据分析和仪表板可视化！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-use-grafana-assistant-for-can-data-analysiss&#34;&gt;为什么使用 Grafana Assistant 进行 CAN 数据分析？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的用户面临着挑战：他们可以使用 CANedge 收集大量 CAN/LIN 数据，但随后必须跨多个设备、数千个日志文件和数月（甚至数年）的数据探索或可视化数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;大多数人用户是工程师，但他们不是数据科学家。即使是这样，统计数据分析/可视化也可能非常耗时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-not-use-chatgpt&#34;&gt;为什么不使用 ChatGPT？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;应对这一挑战的一个解决方案是使用 ChatGPT 来帮助分析数据，我们在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/chatgpt-can-bus-data-time-series-code-interpreter&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;2023 年文章&lt;/a&gt;中对此进行了介绍。然而，ChatGPT 有一些实际限制：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仅限手动上传小文件（例如 100 MB CSV）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;分析结果不容易分享&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;输出是“静态的”（例如，Python 生成的图）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;key-features-of-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;Grafana 助手的主要功能&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x600/75de30d1ec/can-data-architecture.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x600/75de30d1ec/can-data-architecture.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;显示数据从重型机械到 Google Cloud 到 Grafana Cloud 并返回的架构图&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;实际上，我们的最终用户通常使用我们的设备将千兆字节（或太字节）的数据上传到他们自己的 AWS、Google Cloud 或 Microsoft Azure 云服务器。在这里，数据会自动处理到 Parquet 数据湖中，可以通过 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/18/visualize-google-cloud-bigquery-data-in-grafana-the-latest-updates-key-features-and-more/&#34;&gt;Grafana 的 Athena/BigQuery 数据源&lt;/a&gt;查询。换句话说，可以在 Grafana 中轻松访问完整的数据湖。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借助新的助手，Grafana Cloud 现在可以实现对现有数据源的无缝 LLM 访问。这引入了多个强大的功能：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;零设置&lt;/strong&gt;：如果您已经部署了 Grafana 集成，则可以立即开始提示您的数据 - 无需设置。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;分析 TB 级数据&lt;/strong&gt;：与 ChatGPT 不同，您不必将分析限制为 100 MB 数据。该助手可以开箱即用地查询整个数据湖。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;数据探索&lt;/strong&gt;：只需通过聊天即可获得强大的数据见解并通过复杂的诊断分析 - 无需查询语言或编码知识。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;仪表板创建&lt;/strong&gt;：助手可以根据高级提示在几秒钟内创建完全自定义的 Grafana 仪表板，从而大大减少花费的时间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;保留和分享见解：&lt;/strong&gt;任何数据见解都可以轻松汇总到 Grafana 仪表板中，使您能够临时导航数据并与您共享r 团队。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它基本上是用于仪表板和数据湖的 Cursor/Windsurf。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-start-analyzing-can-data-with-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;如何开始使用 Grafana Assistant 分析 CAN 数据&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1023/88223b6f97/can-timeseries.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1023/88223b6f97/can-timeseries.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板显示 CAN 时间序列数据&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您已在 Grafana Cloud 中连接数据源，则无需进一步设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要开始与助手聊天，您可以通过左侧菜单“助手”选项卡打开聊天窗口。或者，您可以通过右上角的闪光图标打开仪表板内的聊天面板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，为了获得最佳体验，我们建议执行以下步骤：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用仪表板模板&lt;/strong&gt;：CSS 提供了为最终用户定制的各种仪表板模板，其中包括相关的 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/visualizations/dashboards/variables/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana 变量&lt;/a&gt;下拉列表。强烈建议使用模板作为基于 LLM 的仪表板开发的基础，因为它允许仪表板用户随后与生成的仪表板进行交互（例如在不同设备之间切换）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;选择数据源作为上下文&lt;/strong&gt;：确保在 Grafana Assistant 聊天窗口中选择相关数据源，以明确告诉它要使用哪些数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;使用系统提示&lt;/strong&gt;：在我们的文档中，我们提供了一个“系统提示”，用户可以将其添加为 Grafana Assistant 设置中的“规则”。这提供了有关数据湖结构、查询语法等的上下文，并显着改善了结果。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;example-use-cases&#34;&gt;示例用例&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了展示 Grafana Assistant 如何帮助进行数据分析，我们将使用&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/ev-data-pack-electric-vehicles&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;公共数据包&lt;/a&gt;，其中包含来自 Kia EV6 电动汽车的 1GB 数据。下面我们重点介绍法学硕士的示例用例：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;example-1-see-what-data-is-available&#34;&gt;示例 1：查看可用数据&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，我们使用法学硕士来了解我们的数据湖的概述。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是探索 CAN 总线数据湖的一个有用的起点，因为您不一定清楚了解可用的设备、CAN 消息和 CAN 信号。此外，构建 SQL 查询来提取此信息非常复杂。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-片段代码-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;提示：&#xA;我的数据源包含来自起亚 EV6 电动汽车的数据，使用设备 ID 为 2A896980 的 CANedge CAN 总线数据记录器记录。这些数据包括来自 EV 的电池数据和来自传感器模块的 GPS/IMU 数据。我想了解以下内容：&#xA;1：该设备有哪些表和列可用？&#xA;2：数据跨越什么时间段？&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 开始通过多个查询分析数据，并在聊天中以表格形式总结结果。请注意 LLM 如何迭代多个查询来理解数据结构。您当然可以检查用于生成每个结果的查询，确保完全透明。该摘要为我们进一步调查提供了良好的起点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/742056367?transparent=0&#34; title=&#34;vimeo 视频&#34; webkitallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; mozallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;example-2-explore-data-ad-hoc&#34;&gt;示例 2：临时探索数据&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在许多情况下，您需要在创建实际面板之前直接在聊天窗口中探索数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这里，Grafana Assistant 运行相关查询并以文本或绘图的形式在聊天中生成输出。我们还可以提示法学硕士创建一个面板，在我们的仪表板中显示随时间变化的速度，Grafana 成功做到了这一点，如下所示。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;提示：&#xA;2023 年 7 月 CAN2_GnssSpeed 消息的平均速度是多少？单位是米/秒。请在此仪表板中创建一个面板，以可视化一段时间内的平均速度&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/742056367?transparent=0&#34; title=&#34;vimeo 视频&#34; webkitallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; mozallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;example-3-create-dashboard-via-a-high-level-prompt&#34;&gt;示例 3：通过高级提示创建仪表板&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant 的一个明显用例是从头开始创建新的仪表板。在这个例子中，我们尝试了一个最省力的提示——给法学硕士留下了很多想象空间。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;结果是一个功能性的 12 面板仪表板，其中所有 SQL 查询都符合预期（即按照我们的系统提示指导）。请特别注意，法学硕士会主动识别可用的（和相关的）消息/信号。很酷！值得反思的是法学硕士+工具已经变得如何商品化。如果这是 2022 年，我们一定会大吃一惊。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，我们得到的仪表板在同一提示的重新运行之间高度不一致。鉴于我们请求的开放性，这当然是可以预料的。我们认为，如果目标是创建真正的 Grafana 仪表板，那么提供如此高级别的提示并没有太大的实际价值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;提示：&#xA;我的数据源包含来自起亚 EV6 电动汽车的数据，使用设备 ID 为 2A896980 的 CANedge CAN 总线数据记录器记录。这些数据包括来自 EV 的电池数据和来自传感器模块的 GPS/IMU 数据。&#xA;更新我的仪表板，添加显示我的 Kia EV6 电池数据和 GPS/IMU 数据的面板。&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/742056367?transparent=0&#34; title=&#34;vimeo 视频&#34; webkitallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; mozallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;example-4-create-a-dashboard-via-a-detailed-prompt&#34;&gt;示例 4：通过详细提示创建仪表板&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更好的方法当然是提供非常详细的指导，而不是使用相当模糊的提示，类似于如果他们要设计仪表板，您将向人类助理提供指导。您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;https://canlogger1000.css electronics.com/files/guides/grafana-assistant-intro/grafana-assistant-detailed-dashboard-prompt.txt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;此处&lt;/a&gt;找到完整的详细提示。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如您所见，结果看起来符合预期。更重要的是，当我们运行这 10 次（每次都在新对话中）时，我们每次都会获得 90% 以上的一致仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可能会说编写这样的提示也很耗时，但根据我们的经验，它仍然比我们从头开始构建此仪表板快 5 到 10 倍。例如，请注意，我们的许多消息/信号名称都是近似的，让 Grafana Assistant 找出确切的表和列名称。此外，一些面板涉及半复杂的查询（例如，消耗的充电状态和行驶的增量距离），这需要大量的 SQL 专业知识来创建。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最重要的是，提示指定没有SQL syntax，这很重要，因为我们 99% 以上的最终用户的 SQL 经验为零。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们的&lt;a href=&#34;https://grafana.css electronics.stellarhosted.com/d/grafana-assistant-ev6-bigquery/grafana-assistant-ev6-bigquery?orgId=1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;公共游乐场&lt;/a&gt;中查看生成的仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://player.vimeo.com/video/742056367?transparent=0&#34; title=&#34;vimeo 视频&#34; webkitallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34; mozallowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;our-summary-thoughts&#34;&gt;我们的总结想法&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们与 Grafana Assistant 一起度过了 20 多个小时。这是我们的总体想法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1：优秀的概念。&lt;/strong&gt;对于已经将 Grafana 连接到其数据的用户来说，通过法学硕士开始使用数据非常简单。这种易于访问性是一个关键优势，而且 Grafana Assistant UI 非常棒。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2：醉酒的天才。&lt;/strong&gt;Grafana Assistant 可以为您提供“神奇的体验”，让您坐下来看着它根据您的规格一次性生成整个 Grafana 仪表板。然而，在某些情况下，它会产生无效的查询、卡住或产生幻觉——就像所有法学硕士一样。确保始终检查输出。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3：可视化与分析。&lt;/strong&gt;法学硕士能够修改仪表板并执行 SQL 查询，使其成为数据可视化和轻度探索的出色工具。然而，它无法运行脚本（例如，与 ChatGPT 相比），这使得它不太适合高度复杂的多步骤数据分析——至少目前是这样。此类功能可能是助手未来的强大模式/变体。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4：潜力巨大。&lt;/strong&gt;虽然当前版本在性能和数据源支持方面存在局限性，但我们相信 Grafana Assistant 将成为极其方便的数据可视化和探索工具。在短短一个月的测试中，Grafana 对 LLM 进行了大量改进，因此我们很高兴看到这个工具的发展！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解更多信息并查看其他展示，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.css electronics.com/pages/grafana-assistant-can-bus-data-ai-llm-dashboards&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;完整的 Grafana Assistant 文章&lt;/a&gt;！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【‘Grafana’s Big Tent’ podcast: Welcome to season 3!】“Grafana 的大帐篷”播客：欢迎来到第三季！</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/12/11/grafanas-big-tent-podcast-welcome-to-season-3/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Sometimes the simplest questions spark the most entertaining rabbit holes. Questions like: “Can you monitor a candle without starting a fire?” or “Should your robot boat have redundancy, or just a twin?” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we’re excited to kick off season 3 of “Grafana’s Big Tent” — the &lt;a href=&#34;https://devopsdozen.com/devops-dozen-2022-community-award-winners/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;award-winning&lt;/a&gt; podcast about the people, community, tools, and tech shaping observability — to answer these pressing questions (and more). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We launched &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/04/04/welcome-to-grafanas-big-tent-a-podcast-about-people-community-tech-and-tools-around-observability/&#34;&gt;“Grafana’s Big Tent” in 2022&lt;/a&gt; to spark fun, open conversations across the observability community. The show embodies and celebrates our “big tent” philosophy — the belief that you should be able to access your data anywhere, and use the observability tools and strategies that work best for you. Most importantly, the podcast has resonated with the open source community, with more than 30,000 downloads across 120+ countries. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the first episode of season 3, you’ll hear a live recording from &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafanacon-2025-announcements/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; in Seattle, featuring hosts Mat Ryer, Principal Software Engineer at Grafana Labs, and Tom Wilkie, Grafana Labs CTO. The topic? Homelabs gone wild, adventures in tinkering, and IoT wins and fails. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our hosts are joined by Ivana Huckova, Staff Software Engineer at Grafana Labs; Andrew McCalip, Head of Research and Development at Varda Space Industries (and builder of an &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2025/monitor-project-bob-droneship-with-grafana-and-tailscale/&#34;&gt;autonomous drone-ship&lt;/a&gt;); and Brad Fitzpatrick, Chief Engineer at Tailscale, creator of LiveJournal, and former member of the Go team. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The group discuss everything from a self-righting boat to dog happiness monitoring (version 2 pending) and a “magic wand” wishlist for Grafana. Oh, and we learn why switching between pounds and kilos mid-sentence is a dangerous maritime practice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can watch the full episode in the YouTube video below, or listen on &lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/show/3beQvS8to0rYs1gxOnPrfD&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/grafanas-big-tent/id1616725129&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/p22K_Q0SAlo&#39; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: The following are highlights from episode 1, season 3 of “Grafana’s Big Tent” podcast. The transcript below has been edited for length and clarity.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-tinkers-from-zx-spectrums-to-5000-lb-garage-surprises&#34;&gt;First tinkers: from ZX Spectrums to 5,000-lb garage surprises&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat Ryer:&lt;/strong&gt; My dad was into computers really early, so we had a ZX Spectrum at home. That’s where I learned BASIC first. I loved it — you could make things happen in this little universe. I’ve been hooked ever since. I kind of miss when tech used to be rubbish; now everything’s shiny and just works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brad Fitzpatrick:&lt;/strong&gt; We had a bootleg Apple II my dad made from stolen parts and a stolen ROM. He taught me to program when I was like five or six, and I kind of haven’t stopped since.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew McCalip:&lt;/strong&gt;  I sort of shocked my parents when I was 14 — I brought home this old CNC machine, a 5,000-pound monstrosity, and parked it in the garage. That was the start of my hardware career… and there’s basically always been a CNC around since.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ivana Huckova:&lt;/strong&gt; I joined Grafana as a frontend engineer, so naturally my onboarding project was a little IoT monitoring solution. My manager Dan mailed me an ESP32 board in an envelope, with all the sensors. That really sparked everything — since then I’ve built monitoring for my sourdough starter, my avocado plant, my standing desk, and I once tried to build a dog happiness monitoring solution. That one failed, so it’s on the list for version two.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;useful-3d-printing-beyond-trinkets&#34;&gt;Useful 3D printing: beyond trinkets&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom Wilkie:&lt;/strong&gt; I saw on your profile you’ve got a 3D printer. What have you actually been using it for?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brad:&lt;/strong&gt; My kids wanted one for Christmas, then lost interest after about a day… so now I have a 3D printer. At this point, half our house is plastic. I’ve printed baby-proofing corner guards, a Wi-Fi mount. We had this bathtub with a tiny one-inch gap at the back where everything fell and you couldn’t reach it, so I printed a shelf that clicks together and fills it. Now nothing falls down there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; You’re the first person I’ve asked who didn’t just say ‘I printed parts for more printers.’&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brad:&lt;/strong&gt; Oh no, I love CAD. Making useful stuff is the fun part.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom (to Andrew):&lt;/strong&gt; But you’ve got a &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; 3D printer… or rather a CNC, right?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew:&lt;/strong&gt; Yeah, a 17,000-pound Haas CNC. You can actually pay people to move something that big on 18-wheelers. I think of it as a metal compiler — metal goes in, parts come out. It’s super-satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;iot-wins-and-one-smoky-fail&#34;&gt;IoT wins (and one smoky fail)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ivana&lt;/strong&gt;: With my plant monitoring, I learned more than from any blog post — how much water they need, how much sun, what the light looks like over the day. I was terrible at taking care of plants, but after wiring all this up I actually became good at it. One of my biggest failed projects was candle monitoring. I wanted to watch the PM particles when you blow a candle out, and I also wanted to know if I’d left a candle burning after leaving the apartment. The idea was that if it was still on, I could remotely shut it down. So I built a system where a wooden lid would drop on the candle. During testing, the lid… caught fire. I did at least learn that you shouldn’t mess with fire when you’re outside your apartment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom&lt;/strong&gt;: My laser cutter is in the garage for exactly that reason — not in my office. Also, it smells terrible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ivana&lt;/strong&gt;: And as for dog happiness v1 — my dog is very hairy. Double-coated, very long hair. I tried using a heart rate monitor on him, but if you just strap a sensor onto a lot of fur, it’s not very reliable. I also put a little camera on him, and every time his heart rate went up, it took a photo. The results were mostly hair, feet, and pavement. So I need a better heart rate sensor, or a different camera placement. I’m not abandoning the idea — version 2 is definitely on the list for a future Grafana hackathon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom&lt;/strong&gt;: I have five 3D printers in my office. I dread monitoring the air in there. I am made of microplastics now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-ocean-robot-ballast-barnacles-and-redundancy&#34;&gt;The ocean robot: ballast, barnacles, and “redundancy”&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; I want to ask about your ocean-going drone ship. How are you going to handle terrible weather? What happens when it inevitably capsizes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew:&lt;/strong&gt; Good question. If you’re not careful, things in the ocean don’t stay upright. So we gave the boat a really deep keel with a big lead ballast. If it flips over, the idea is it self-rights. We actually wrote a whole Python script to model the hydrodynamics and buoyancy, then tested it in water a few times — it works great.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brad:&lt;/strong&gt; Did you model the keel breaking?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew:&lt;/strong&gt; We have two models: the strong keel and the fast keel. Priority one, since we’re mechanical people more than software people, was ‘Make sure it doesn’t flip over.’ Priority two was ‘turn it off and back on again.’&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you have a secondary backup control system?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew:&lt;/strong&gt; No. No backup. There was a big philosophical debate about redundancy. Is anything truly redundant? In the end we decided the easiest redundancy is: make a second boat. So we test, test, test, and when we’re happy, we ship it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; And when it fails in the ocean, how do you get to it to reboot it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew:&lt;/strong&gt; We don’t. We’ll tell Twitter, ‘It was last seen at this latitude/longitude. If anybody finds it, please tow it back to Los Angeles.’ It’ll just be out there floating around.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; Does it have a name? And why is it not Boaty McBoatface?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Andrew:&lt;/strong&gt; Boaty McBoatface was a strong contender, but it’s kind of taken. It’s called Bob, after the Bobiverse books — sci-fi about a sentient spacecraft that makes copies of itself and explores the universe. It’s poetic, and also a pun.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;parting-words&#34;&gt;Parting words&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It wouldn’t be Big Tent without a nod to history.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brad:&lt;/strong&gt; LiveJournal was like Twitter in 1998. The first client was a Windows app with a single input bar across the bottom of your screen. You typed, hit Enter, and it posted. No paragraphs — hitting Enter just posted it. Somehow it ended up with millions of users. In the opening scene of that Facebook movie, the actor playing Zuckerberg is actually on LiveJournal. That’s my little movie cameo, via software.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom:&lt;/strong&gt; I don’t think anything I’ve written has ever been in a movie.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat:&lt;/strong&gt; What a flex.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Grafana’s Big Tent” podcast wants to hear from you. If you have a great story to share, want to join the conversation, or have any feedback, please contact the Big Tent team at&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bigtent@grafana.com&#34;&gt;bigtent@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;有时，最简单的问题会引发最有趣的兔子洞。诸如此类的问题：“你能在不生火的情况下监控蜡烛吗？”或者“你的机器人船应该有冗余，还是只有双胞胎？” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们很高兴推出“Grafana 的大帐篷”第 3 季 - &lt;a href=&#34;https://devopsdozen.com/devops-dozen-2022-community-award-winners/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;屡获殊荣的&lt;/a&gt;播客，内容涉及塑造可观察性的人员、社区、工具和技术 - 来回答这些紧迫的问题（以及更多）。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们于 2022 年推出了&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/04/04/welcome-to-grafanas-big-tent-a-podcast-about-people-community-tech-and-tools-around-observability/&#34;&gt;“Grafana 的大帐篷”&lt;/a&gt;，以在可观察性社区中激发有趣、开放的对话。该节目体现并颂扬了我们的“大帐篷”理念，即您应该能够在任何地方访问数据，并使用最适合您的可观察性工具和策略。最重要的是，该播客引起了开源社区的共鸣，在 120 多个国家/地区的下载量超过 30,000 次。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在第三季的第一集中，您将听到西雅图 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafanacon-2025-announcements/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; 的现场录音，由 Grafana Labs 首席软件工程师 Mat Ryer 和 Grafana Labs 首席技术官 Tom Wilkie 主持。主题？疯狂的家庭实验室、修补的冒险以及物联网的成功和失败。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs 的软件工程师 Ivana Huckova 也加入了我们的主持人行列； Andrew McCalip，Varda Space Industries 研发主管（也是&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2025/monitor-project-bob-droneship-with-grafana-and-tailscale/&#34;&gt;自主无人机船&lt;/a&gt;的建造者）； Brad Fitzpatrick，Tailscale 的首席工程师，LiveJournal 的创建者，Go 团队的前成员。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;小组讨论了从自动扶正船到狗幸福监测（版本 2 待定）以及 Grafana 的“魔杖”愿望清单等各种内容。哦，我们还了解到为什么在句子中切换磅和公斤是一种危险的海上做法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在下面的 YouTube 视频中观看完整剧集，或在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://open.spotify.com/show/3beQvS8to0rYs1gxOnPrfD&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; 或 &lt;a href=&#34;https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/grafanas-big-tent/id1616725129&#34; 上收听target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Apple 播客&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“560”height =“315”src =&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/p22K_Q0SAlo&#39;title =“YouTube视频播放器”frameborder =“0”allow =“加速计;自动播放;剪贴板写入;加密媒体;陀螺仪;画中画;网络共享”referrerpolicy =“strict-origin-when-cross-origin”allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：以下是“Grafana’s Big Tent”播客第三季第一集的精彩片段。下面的文字记录已经过长度和清晰度的编辑ty.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-tinkers-from-zx-spectrums-to-5000-lb-garage-surprises&#34;&gt;第一批修补匠：从 ZX Spectrums 到 5,000 磅车库惊喜&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mat Ryer：&lt;/strong&gt;我爸爸很早就迷上了电脑，所以我们家里有一台 ZX Spectrum。那是我首先学习 BASIC 的地方。我喜欢它——你可以在这个小宇宙中让事情发生。从那时起我就迷上了。我有点怀念科技曾经是垃圾的时候；现在一切都闪闪发亮并且可以正常工作了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brad Fitzpatrick：&lt;/strong&gt;我们有一台我父亲用偷来的零件和偷来的 ROM 制作的盗版 Apple II。当我五六岁时，他教我编程，从那以后我就没有停止过。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安德鲁·麦卡利普&lt;/strong&gt;：我 14 岁时让我的父母感到震惊 - 我把这台旧数控机床（一个重 5,000 磅的庞然大物）带回家，然后把它停在车库里。那是我硬件职业生涯的开始……从那时起，数控机床就一直存在。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ivana Huckova：&lt;/strong&gt;我作为前端工程师加入 Grafana，所以我的入职项目自然是一个小型物联网监控解决方案。我的经理 Dan 给我邮寄了一个装在信封里的 ESP32 板，其中包含所有传感器。这确实激发了一切——从那时起，我就为我的酵母发酵剂、我的鳄梨植物、我的站立式办公桌建立了监控，我曾经尝试建立一个狗的幸福监控解决方案。那个失败了，所以它出现在第二版的列表中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;useful-3d-printing-beyond-trinkets&#34;&gt;有用的 3D 打印：超越小饰品&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom Wilkie：&lt;/strong&gt;我在您的个人资料上看到您有一台 3D 打印机。您实际上用它来做什么？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;布拉德：&lt;/strong&gt;我的孩子们想要一个作为圣诞节礼物，但大约一天后就失去了兴趣……所以现在我有了一台 3D 打印机。现在，我们的房子有一半是塑料的。我打印了婴儿防护护角、Wi-Fi 支架。我们的浴缸后面有一个一英寸的小缝隙，所有东西都会掉下来，你够不到它，所以我打印了一个架子，可以卡扣在一起并填满它。现在那里没有东西掉下来。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆：&lt;/strong&gt;你是我问过的第一个不只是说“我为更多打印机打印零件”的人。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brad：&lt;/strong&gt;哦不，我喜欢 CAD。制作有用的东西是有趣的部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆（对安德鲁）：&lt;/strong&gt;但是你有一台&lt;em&gt;真正的&lt;/em&gt; 3D 打印机……或者更确切地说是 CNC，对吧？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安德鲁：&lt;/strong&gt;是的，一台 17,000 磅的 Haas CNC。事实上，你可以付钱让人用 18 轮车搬运这么大的东西。我认为它是一个金属编译器——金属进去，零件出来。真是太满足了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;iot-wins-and-one-smoky-fail&#34;&gt;IoT 获胜（而 smoky 失败）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ivana&lt;/strong&gt;：通过我的植物监测，我比从任何博客文章中了解到的更多 - 他们需要多少水，多少阳光，一天中的光线是什么样的。我不擅长照顾植物，但在将所有这些连接起来之后，我实际上变得很擅长。一我最大的失败项目之一是蜡烛监控。我想观察吹灭蜡烛时的颗粒物颗粒，我还想知道离开公寓后我是否留下了燃烧的蜡烛。我的想法是，如果它仍然打开，我可以远程关闭它。所以我建立了一个系统，将木盖放在蜡烛上。在测试过程中，盖子……着火了。我至少了解到，当你在公寓外面时，不应该乱火。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆&lt;/strong&gt;：正是出于这个原因，我的激光切割机放在车库里，而不是放在我的办公室里。而且，味道很难闻。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ivana&lt;/strong&gt;：至于狗的幸福感 v1——我的狗毛茸茸的。双层涂层，头发很长。我尝试在他身上使用心率监测器，但如果你只是将传感器绑在很多皮毛上，那就不太可靠。我还在他身上放了一个小相机，每当他的心率上升时，就拍一张照片。结果主要是头发、脚和路面。所以我需要一个更好的心率传感器，或者不同的摄像头位置。我不会放弃这个想法——版本 2 肯定会出现在未来 Grafana 黑客马拉松的名单上。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tom&lt;/strong&gt;：我的办公室里有五台 3D 打印机。我害怕监测那里的空气。我现在是由微塑料制成的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-ocean-robot-ballast-barnacles-and-redundancy&#34;&gt;海洋机器人：压舱物、藤壶和“冗余”&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆：&lt;/strong&gt;我想问一下你们的远洋无人机船的情况。你将如何应对恶劣的天气？当它不可避免地倾覆时会发生什么？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安德鲁：&lt;/strong&gt;好问题。如果你不小心，海洋里的东西就不会保持直立。所以我们给船设计了一个非常深的龙骨和一个大的铅压载物。如果它翻转了，这个想法就是它的自我权利。实际上，我们编写了一个完整的 Python 脚本来模拟流体动力学和浮力，然后在水中测试了几次 - 效果很好。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;布拉德：&lt;/strong&gt;你模拟了龙骨断裂吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安德鲁：&lt;/strong&gt;我们有两种型号：强龙骨和快速龙骨。因为我们是机械人而不是软件人，所以第一要务是“确保它不会翻转”。第二要务是“将其关闭并重新打开。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆：&lt;/strong&gt;您有辅助备用控制系统吗？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安德鲁：&lt;/strong&gt;不。没有备份。关于冗余存在着一场大的哲学辩论。真的有什么是多余的吗？最后我们决定最简单的冗余是：建造第二艘船。所以我们测试、测试、测试，当我们满意时，我们就会发货。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆：&lt;/strong&gt;当它在海洋中出现故障时，您如何才能重新启动它？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安德鲁：&lt;/strong&gt;我们不知道。我们会告诉 Twitter，‘最后一次看到它是在这个纬度/经度。如果有人发现它，请把它拖回洛杉矶。’它就会在那里漂浮。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆：&lt;/strong&gt;它有名字吗？为什么不是 Boaty McBoatface？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安德鲁：&lt;/strong&gt;Boaty McBoatface 是一个强有力的竞争者，但它有点被抢走了。它被称为鲍勃（Bob），源自《Bobiverse》系列书籍——一部关于一艘有感知能力的航天器可以自我复制并探索宇宙的科幻小说。这是诗意的，也是双关语。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;parting-words&#34;&gt;分手词&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果没有向历史致敬，就不会是大帐篷。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brad：&lt;/strong&gt;LiveJournal 就像 1998 年的 Twitter。第一个客户端是一个 Windows 应用程序，屏幕底部有一个输入栏。你输入，按 Enter 键，然后它就发布了。没有段落 - 按 Enter 键即可发布。不知何故，它最终拥有了数百万用户。在 Facebook 电影的开场场景中，扮演扎克伯格的演员实际上是在 LiveJournal 上。这是我通过软件在电影中客串的小片段。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;汤姆：&lt;/strong&gt;我认为我写的任何东西都没有出现在电影中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;垫子：&lt;/strong&gt;多么灵活。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Grafana 的大帐篷”播客希望收到您的来信。如果您有精彩的故事要分享、想要加入对话或有任何反馈，请联系 Big Tent 团队：&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bigtent@grafana.com&#34;&gt;bigtent@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana Labs: Top 10 moments of 2025】Grafana 实验室：2025 年十大时刻</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/12/11/grafana-labs-top-10-moments-of-2025/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;For Grafana Labs, 2025 was a year defined by innovation, growth, and the power of our community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We celebrated the release of Grafana 12 at our 10th annual GrafanaCON event, and marked major milestones across open source projects, including Mimir, k6, Beyla, Faro, and Alloy. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was also a year of taking bold steps forward in how teams interact with their systems and data. With the launch of our actually useful AI-powered agent Grafana Assistant, our end-to-end Adaptive Telemetry suite, and Grafana Cloud Knowledge Graph, we continued on our mission to make observability smarter, easier, and more accessible to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just as importantly, 2025 was a year of strengthening the bonds across our global community. We expanded our presence in Japan and shared insights from more than 1,200 practitioners from around the world in our third annual Observability Survey. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“It’s really satisfying for me to sit back and realize that we’ve become a force in open source observability, but we’ve done it as part of this wider community and wider ecosystem,” said Raj Dutt, CEO and co-founder of Grafana Labs, at GrafanaCON this year. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a look at some of the top moments that defined 2025 at Grafana Labs. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-actually-useful-ai-with-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;1. Actually useful AI with Grafana Assistant &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;rsquo;t mention AI, are you even a tech company? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Grafana Labs, though, AI is much more than the latest observability trend. It’s become essential to how organizations keep their systems running, and we want it to &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/&#34;&gt;play a pivotal role&lt;/a&gt; in simplifying the observability experience for every user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; — our AI-powered agent in Grafana Cloud — deeply reflects this belief. What started as an internal hackathon project at the beginning of the year quickly evolved into a generally available feature that lets you query, build, and troubleshoot faster using natural language. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve seen teams use it for &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-for-grafana-onboarding-get-your-teams-started-quicker-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;simplified onboarding&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/09/11/debug-query-and-build-faster-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;faster debugging&lt;/a&gt;, and easier dashboard building for every use case. (The color-coded &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/03/taylor-swift-grafanas-version-how-to-track-and-visualize-data-related-to-pop-s-biggest-superstar/&#34;&gt;Taylor Swift eras dashboard&lt;/a&gt;? Assistant helped build that.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddddc/assistant-ga-ui.gif/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddddc/assistant-ga-ui.gif/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A GIF showing Grafana Assistant responding to a request for help writing a LogQL query.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The best part? We’re just getting started. We’ve also &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/#get-more-from-assistant-with-our-latest-improvements&#34;&gt;rolled out Assistant Investigations&lt;/a&gt; (in public preview), an AI-powered feature that extends Grafana Assistant to accelerate multi-step incident investigations.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Assistant docs&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-grafana-12-release-and-more-oss-milestones&#34;&gt;2. Grafana 12 release and more OSS milestones&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even as the observability market moves at warp speed, one thing remains constant for us: open source software will always be part of our DNA. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We really believe, and continue to believe, that open source is going to win, and is ultimately the best way to develop software,” Raj told attendees at GrafanaCON 2025, where we &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafana-12-release-all-the-new-features/&#34;&gt;launched Grafana 12&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The latest major release introduced powerful observability as code features, such as &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/git-sync-grafana-12/&#34;&gt;Git Sync&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/dynamic-dashboards-grafana-12/&#34;&gt;dynamic dashboards&lt;/a&gt;. There were also some fun data visualization updates (who doesn’t love a new &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafana-12-release-all-the-new-features/#new-themes-in-grafana-dashboards&#34;&gt;dashboard theme&lt;/a&gt;?!) and an expansion of our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/visualizations/simplified-exploration/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Drilldown suite of applications&lt;/a&gt; for queryless, point-and-click data exploration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mHSzaVYBh38&#39; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many of our other open source projects hit major milestones this year — milestones we couldn’t have reached without the support of our OSS community. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/03/grafana-mimir-3-0-release-all-the-latest-updates/&#34;&gt;Mimir 3.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: This major release delivers dramatic improvements in reliability, performance, and cost efficiency, marking a new era for the open source, horizontally scalable, multi-tenant time series database (TSDB).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafana-k6-1.0-release/&#34;&gt;k6 1.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;:  k6 1.0 rolled out with TypeScript support, revamped test insights, and clear support and versioning guarantees to power the next decade of performance and reliability testing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/10/grafana-beyla-2.0-distributed-traces-scalable-kubernetes-deployments-and-more/&#34;&gt;Beyla 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: The latest major release of our vendor-agnostic, open source eBPF zero-code instrumentation tool introduced performance and functional improvements — like support for new protocols and distributed tracing — along with deeper alignment with the OpenTelemetry project (spoiler alert: more on that below). &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-11-21-faro-web-sdk-v20-is-now-ga/&#34;&gt;Faro 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Released in November, v2.0 of the Faro Web SDK introduces improvements to Web Vitals, simplifies configuration, cleans up deprecated internals, and more to provide a more streamlined and performant user experience. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/08/alloy-one-year/&#34;&gt;One-year anniversary for Alloy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: In May, we celebrated one year of Grafana Alloy, our open source OpenTelemetry collector with built-in Prometheus pipelines and support for metrics, logs, traces, and profiles. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can read more about OSS updates on &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/&#34;&gt;our blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation-beyla-donated-to-the-otel-project&#34;&gt;3. OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation: Beyla donated to the OTel project&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the years, we’ve prioritized contributing to the OpenTelemetry project and building compatibility with OpenTelemetry into our products and open source projects. &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/beyla-ebpf/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Beyla&lt;/a&gt; is a leading example of both of those efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year, with the support from both Grafanistas and the open source community, we officially &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation-beyla-donation/&#34;&gt;donated Beyla to OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt;, under the new project name &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation&lt;/a&gt; (commonly referred to as OBI). It was a special moment for us, and one that marked a significant milestone in the evolution of zero-code eBPF instrumentation within the open source community at large.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/dc515f1400/beyla-demo.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/dc515f1400/beyla-demo.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard in a Beyla demo, showing RED (rate, error, and duration) metrics, as well as service graph metrics, generated for the OpenTelemetry Demo Checkout service directly from Beyla&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As part of the donation, we announced that Beyla will continue to exist as Grafana Labs’ distribution of the upstream OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation. In August, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/04/building-on-the-foundation-of-opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation-what-s-new-in-grafana-beyla-2-5/&#34;&gt;we rolled out Beyla 2.5&lt;/a&gt;, the first Beyla release where we directly vendored most of the code from the upstream repository. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, we’re excited to continue collaborating and driving further innovation around zero-effort instrumentation within the OTel community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation, visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/zero-code/obi/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry docs&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-first-ever-science-fair-at-grafanacon&#34;&gt;4. First-ever &amp;ldquo;Science Fair&amp;rdquo; at GrafanaCON &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There were no exploding volcanoes, but there were 3D printers and plenty of IoT devices. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our 10th annual &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafanacon-2025-announcements/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON&lt;/a&gt; featured our inaugural Science Fair, a series of interactive booths—complete with tri-fold poster boards—where attendees could check out and play with projects demonstrating all the different things you can monitor with Grafana. Highlights included the team from PRUSA monitoring a 3D printer (mini Grots for everyone!); a desktop wind tunnel built for model race cars created by Grafana Labs CTO Tom Wilkie; and the hackathon booth, where attendees could get hands-on with popular projects from &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/03/01/grafana-labs-hackathon-projects-where-are-they-now/&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs hackathons&lt;/a&gt;, like Dash Dash Revolution and &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/03/31/can-grafana-run-doom/&#34;&gt;Doomfana&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1333/6fb8b42b1c/3d-printed-grots.jpg/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1333/6fb8b42b1c/3d-printed-grots.jpg/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A photo of 3D printed Grots.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the Science Fair, GrafanaCON 2025 featured more than 32 live sessions, our Ask the Experts booth, hands-on labs, a welcome reception, and more fun, community-driven activities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to get in on the action next year? Be sure to sign up to get notified when discount tickets are available and get an early heads-up about all the topics we&amp;rsquo;ll be highlighting at &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2026&lt;/a&gt;, which will take place April 20-22 in Barcelona. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-named-a-leader-in-the-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-observability-platforms-again&#34;&gt;5. Named a Leader in the Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Observability Platforms (again!) &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs is proud to be recognized as &lt;a href=&#34;/resources/grafana-observability-platforms-gartner-magic-quadrant-2025/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;a Leader in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Observability Platforms&lt;/a&gt; for the second year in a row.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year’s report placed Grafana Labs furthest to the right of the Magic Quadrant for “Completeness of Vision,” which we believe reflects our deep commitment to building a full-stack open observability platform that gives users flexibility, control, and the tools to own their observability strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1808x1999/08e0a53d18/gartner-magic-quadrant-2025.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1808x1999/08e0a53d18/gartner-magic-quadrant-2025.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Observability Platforms.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This was one of several recognitions in 2025 that demonstrated how our company and community is playing a vital role in shaping the future of observability. We were also honored to be included in:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forbes.com/cloud100&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Forbes Cloud 100 list&lt;/a&gt;, which recognizes the top private cloud companies in the world; Grafana Labs ranked number 13. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Silicon Valley Defense Group’s NATSEC100, which &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.natsec100.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;ranked Grafana Labs 26th&lt;/a&gt; out of “the top 100 venture-backed, dual-use and defense technology companies driving forward U.S. national security.”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crn.com/news/software/2025/the-coolest-dataops-and-data-observability-companies-of-the-2025-big-data-100?page=7&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Coolest DataOps and Data Observability Companies of the 2025 Big Data 100&lt;/a&gt;, produced by CRN.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redpoint.com/infrared/100/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;InfraRed 100&lt;/a&gt;, an unranked list that honors transformative companies in cloud infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While we’re proud of these accolades, we’ll always consider our users’ success to be the ultimate validation of our products. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“We&amp;rsquo;re so privileged to be at the center of this really dynamic and vibrant ecosystem and community,” Raj said at &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/agenda/2025/keynote/&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;6-the-end-to-end-adaptive-telemetry-suite&#34;&gt;6. The end-to-end Adaptive Telemetry suite&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More observability data doesn’t always bring more clarity — in fact, it often just creates more noise and costs. That’s why we built Adaptive Telemetry, a set of features in Grafana Cloud that optimizes observability data by ensuring only the most valuable telemetry is stored and surfaced. It uses intelligent classification and prioritization techniques to analyze how telemetry is used and then automatically recommends actions like aggregating, sampling, dropping, or reducing low-value data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our Adaptive Telemetry suite started with &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Metrics&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Adaptive Logs&lt;/a&gt;, and this year expanded to include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/#adaptive-traces-retain-only-your-most-valuable-traces&#34;&gt;Adaptive Traces (generally available)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Automatically identifies and retains your most valuable traces using tail sampling to deliver critical performance insights. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/#adaptive-profiles-the-power-of-continuous-profiling-without-runaway-costs&#34;&gt;Adaptive Profiles (private preview)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Dynamically adjusts data collection based on workload behavior, enabling continuous profiling at scale without high costs. &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeIFky5ut3g3tvhIOApTqV1yyuZ6i0Cv_Vg2G0wTbS6r98elQ/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt; to join our private preview.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x876/4ad7118eeb/adaptive-telemetry-suite-timeline.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x876/4ad7118eeb/adaptive-telemetry-suite-timeline.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;An image showing a timeline of product releases for the Adaptive Telemetry suite.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Before Adaptive Traces, we had two bad options: send everything and blow our budget, or send so little we couldn’t get meaningful insight,” said Geoff Schultz, Manager, Infrastructure Engineering at Auditboard. “Now tracing is actually usable. We can dial sampling up or down as needed, keep costs in check, and still give teams the visibility they need.” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this end-to-end Adaptive Telemetry suite, you can extend the benefits of the adaptive model across all core pillars of your observability strategy, ensuring every piece of telemetry you store is truly worth the investment. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Check out &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/&#34;&gt;our documentation&lt;/a&gt; to learn more about Adaptive Telemetry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;7-introducing-grafana-labs-japan&#34;&gt;7. Introducing Grafana Labs Japan&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether it’s attending community meetups, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-the-community-behind-the-code/&#34;&gt;developing Grafana data sources&lt;/a&gt;, or even monitoring the country&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/01/how-japans-space-agency-used-grafana-to-monitor-its-first-moon-landing-in-real-time/&#34;&gt;first moon landing&lt;/a&gt;, our users and partners in Japan have been an active and integral part of the broader Grafana community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s why we were excited to announce &lt;a href=&#34;/about/press/2025/11/12/grafana-labs-establishes-japan-subsidiary-to-accelerate-local-market-expansion/&#34;&gt;the establishment of Grafana Labs Japan&lt;/a&gt;, a new subsidiary in Tokyo, this year. With this investment, we strengthen our ability to deliver localized support, foster closer collaboration with Japanese enterprises and partners, and accelerate digital transformation initiatives across the region.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1086x724/29cade6881/grafana-labs-japan-opening-event.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1086x724/29cade6881/grafana-labs-japan-opening-event.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A photo of Grafana Labs employees at the Grafana Labs Japan opening event.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“At Grafana Labs, open is not just our strategy; it’s our differentiator. With our open and flexible observability platform, we help organizations see and understand anything from anywhere — turning signals into smarter, faster action. We are excited to extend this vision to more organizations in Japan,&amp;quot; said Raj.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;8-extending-the-grafana-cloud-stack&#34;&gt;8. Extending the Grafana Cloud stack&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are consistently shipping new features for &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; in an effort to make our hosted open observability platform more efficient, intelligent, and easier to use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to Grafana Assistant and the end-to-end Adaptive Telemetry suite, here are some other ways we’ve evolved Grafana Cloud in 2025 to enable more powerful, full-stack observability strategies. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/observabilitycon-2025-announcements/#full-stack-observability-powered-by-the-knowledge-graph&#34;&gt;Knowledge graph&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: By combining telemetry from across your system’s apps, databases, and infrastructure into a single intelligent map, the knowledge graph helps you reduce MTTR and find root causes faster. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/fedramp-federal-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: FedRAMP High authorized and DoD IL5 compliant, Grafana Federal Cloud offers organizations secure and reliable cloud-based monitoring for their infrastructure, applications, and services, ensuring data protection and compliance with stringent security standards.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/12/01/improve-service-reliability-and-ops-culture-with-grafana-cloud-service-center/&#34;&gt;Service Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: This unified hub in Grafana Cloud offers a service-first view of system health to help you improve service reliability and operational culture. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/13/understand-diagnose-and-optimize-sql-queries-introducing-grafana-cloud-database-observability/&#34;&gt;Database Observability&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: By tracking every query across your databases and easily correlating queries with app and infrastructure signals, this solution (shown below) makes database troubleshooting faster and easier. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instrumentation Hub&lt;/strong&gt;: This point-and-click experience allows you to automatically discover instrumentation gaps and deploy observability coverage at scale.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/c4e0215688/database-observability-dashboard.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/c4e0215688/database-observability-dashboard.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Database Observability dashboard.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can read more about these and other new features in our &lt;a href=&#34;/tags/grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud blog posts&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;9-the-third-annual-observability-survey&#34;&gt;9. The third annual Observability Survey &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Across companies of all shapes and sizes, observability practices are maturing and getting attention at the highest levels. At the same time, cost and complexity continue to hinder efforts as teams look to emerging tools to help simplify their processes in hopes of better outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These were some of the key findings from the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/03/25/observability-survey-takeaways/&#34;&gt;third annual Observability Survey&lt;/a&gt; brought to you by Grafana Labs. In total, we collected 1,255 responses online and at industry events around the world (that&amp;rsquo;s 4x more than last year!), making it the largest community-driven survey on the state of observability. We also produced versions of the survey for &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/12/observability-trends-in-brazil-insights-from-our-localized-survey/&#34;&gt;Brazil&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/13/japan-observability-survey-25/&#34;&gt;Japan&lt;/a&gt; to better understand how organizations there are adopting observability, and to share that information with the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wTEuti1Ica4&#39; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The survey helps us better understand the state of observability, but we also see it as an asset for our community and the broader industry. The &lt;a href=&#34;/observability-survey/2025/&#34;&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; is free (no email required!), and this past year we added an &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/d/feg4yc4qw3wn4b/third-annual-observability-survey?orgId=1&amp;amp;from=2025-03-13T02:49:20.476Z&amp;amp;to=2025-03-14T02:49:20.476Z&amp;amp;timezone=utc&amp;amp;var-region=$__all&amp;amp;var-role=$__all&amp;amp;var-size=$__all&amp;amp;var-industry=$__all&amp;amp;var-filters=%60Region%60%20in%20%28%27Europe%27,%27Asia%27,%27North%20America%27,%27Africa%27,%27South%20America%27,%27Oceania%27,%27Middle%20East%27%29%20AND%20%60Role%60%20IN%20%28%27Platform%20team%27,%27SRE%27,%27CTO%27,%27Engineering%20manager%27,%27Developer%27,%27Director%20of%20engineering%27,%27Other%27%29%20AND%20%60Size_of_organization%60%20IN%20%28%2710%20or%20fewer%20employees%27,%2711%20-%20100%20employees%27,%27101%20-%20500%20employees%27,%27501%20-%201,000%20employees%27,%271,001%20-%202,500%20employees%27,%272,501%20-%205,000%20employees%27,%275,001%2B%20employees%27%29%20AND%20%60Industry%60%20IN%20%28%27Telecommunications%27,%27Healthcare%27,%27IoT%27,%27Financial%20services%27,%27Education%27,%27Government%27,%27Applied%20Sciences%27,%27Software%20%26%20Technology%27,%27Media%20%26%20Entertainment%27,%27Travel%20%26%20Transportation%27,%27Retail%2FE-commerce%27,%27Energy%20%26%20Utilities%27,%27Automotive%20%26%20Manufacturing%27,%27Other%27%29&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;interactive Grafana dashboard&lt;/a&gt; where you can dig into the numbers, too. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Didn’t get to participate in the survey last year? No worries — we are still collecting &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/01/take-grafana-labs-4th-annual-observability-survey/&#34;&gt;responses for next year&amp;rsquo;s survey&lt;/a&gt;. It only takes a few minutes, all responses will be kept anonymous, and you could win some swag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;10-raising-the-bar-on-growth&#34;&gt;10. Raising the bar on growth &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In September, Grafana Labs &lt;a href=&#34;/about/press/2025/09/30/grafana-labs-surpasses-400m-arr-and-7000-customers-gains-new-investors-to-accelerate-global-expansion/&#34;&gt;completed a secondary transaction&lt;/a&gt; led by Ontario Teachers’ Pension Plan, with participation from Sapphire Ventures and Tiger Global. Existing investors Lightspeed Venture Partners, GIC, Coatue, Sequoia Capital, CapitalG, and Lead Edge Capital also took part. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was one of several moments that underscored our growing momentum in the observability market. We also surpassed $400 million in annual recurring revenue and grew to more than 7,000 global customers. Today, some of the world’s most recognized companies — from Anthropic and NVIDIA to Salesforce and Microsoft — rely on Grafana Labs to power their observability strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“This is really an incredible accomplishment,” Raj said on stage at ObservabilityCON. “We really appreciate you helping us get to that number.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And that’s a wrap! Of course, we couldn’t have hit any of these milestones without our incredible open source community. Thank you for continuing to support and inspire us, and we can’t wait for a new year filled with fresh ideas, shared wins, and even deeper connections.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gartner®, Magic Quadrant™ for Observability Platforms, By Gregg Siegfried, Matt Crossley, Padraig Byrne, Andre Bridges, Martin Caren, 7 July 2025&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;GARTNER is a registered trademark and service mark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates in the U.S. and internationally, MAGIC QUADRANT is a registered trademark of Gartner, Inc. and/or its affiliates and is used herein with permission. All rights reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gartner does not endorse any vendor, product or service depicted in its research publications and does not advise technology users to select only those vendors with the highest ratings or other designation. Gartner research publications consist of the opinions of Gartner’s Research &amp;amp; Advisory organization and should not be construed as statements of fact. Gartner disclaims all warranties, expressed or implied, with respect to this research, including any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This graphic was published by Gartner, Inc. as part of a larger research document and should be evaluated in the context of the entire document. The Gartner document is available upon request from Grafana Labs.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;对于 Grafana Labs 来说，2025 年是创新、增长和社区力量的一年。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们在第十届年度 GrafanaCON 活动上庆祝了 Grafana 12 的发布，并标志着 Mimir、k6、Beyla、Faro 和 Alloy 等开源项目的重要里程碑。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这也是在团队如何与其系统和数据交互方面采取大胆举措的一年。随着我们实用的人工智能代理 Grafana Assistant、端到端自适应遥测套件和 Grafana Cloud 知识图的推出，我们继续履行我们的使命，让每个人都能更智能、更轻松、更容易地获得可观测性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同样重要的是，2025 年是加强我们全球社区联系的一年。我们扩大了在日本的业务，并在第三次年度可观测性调查中分享了来自世界各地 1,200 多名从业者的见解。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;Grafana Labs 首席执行官兼联合创始人 Raj Dutt 在今年的 GrafanaCON 上表示：“坐下来意识到我们已经成为开源可观察性的一支力量，这对我来说真的很令人满意，但我们已经将其作为这个更广泛的社区和更广泛的生态系统的一部分。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是 Grafana Labs 定义 2025 年的一些重要时刻。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-actually-useful-ai-with-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;1.通过 Grafana Assistant 实现真正有用的人工智能&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不提人工智能，你还是科技公司吗？ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不过，在 Grafana Labs，人工智能不仅仅是最新的可观察性趋势。它对于组织如何保持系统运行至关重要，我们希望它&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/&#34;&gt;在简化每个用户的可观察性体验方面发挥关键作用&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt;——我们在 Grafana Cloud 中的人工智能代理——深刻地体现了这一信念。今年年初最初是一个内部黑客马拉松项目，但很快就发展成为一项普遍可用的功能，让您可以使用自然语言更快地查询、构建和排除故障。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经看到团队使用它来&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-for-grafana-onboarding-get-your-teams-started-quicker-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;简化入职流程&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/09/11/debug-query-and-build-faster-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;更快的调试&lt;/a&gt;，并为每个用例更轻松地构建仪表板。 （颜色编码的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/03/taylor-swift-grafanas-version-how-to-track-and-visualize-data-lated-to-pop-s-biggest-superstar/&#34;&gt;Taylor Swift时代仪表板&lt;/a&gt;？Google Assistant帮助构建了它。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddddc/assistant-ga-ui.gif/m/&#34;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/d0ce1ddddc/assistant-ga-ui.gif/m/&#34;alt=&#34;GIF 显示 Grafana Assistant 响应编写 LogQL 查询的帮助请求。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最好的部分？我们才刚刚开始。我们还&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/#get-more-from-assistant-with-our-latest-improvements&#34;&gt;推出了助理调查&lt;/a&gt;（公开预览版），这是一项人工智能支持的功能，可扩展 Grafana Assistant 以加速多步骤事件调查。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如需了解更多信息，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;助理文档&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-grafana-12-release-and-more-oss-milestones&#34;&gt;2. Grafana 12 发布和更多 OSS 里程碑&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使可观测性市场飞速发展，有一件事对我们来说仍然不变：开源软件将永远是我们 DNA 的一部分。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们确实相信，并且仍然相信，开源将会获胜，并且最终是开发软件的最佳方式，”Raj 在 GrafanaCON 2025 上告诉与会者，我们在会上&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafana-12-release-all-the-new-features/&#34;&gt;推出了 Grafana 12&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最新的主要版本引入了强大的可观察性作为代码功能，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/git-sync-grafana-12/&#34;&gt;Git Sync&lt;/a&gt; 和&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/dynamic-dashboards-grafana-12/&#34;&gt;动态仪表板&lt;/a&gt;。还有一些有趣的数据可视化更新（谁不喜欢新的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafana-12-release-all-the-new-features/#new-themes-in-grafana-dashboards&#34;&gt;仪表板主题&lt;/a&gt;？！）以及我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/visualizations/simplified-exploration/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Drilldown 应用程序套件&lt;/a&gt;，用于无查询、点击式数据探索。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“560”height =“315”src =&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/mHSzaVYBh38&#39;title =“YouTube视频播放器”frameborder =“0”allow =“加速计;自动播放;剪贴板写入;加密媒体;陀螺仪;画中画;网络共享”referrerpolicy =“strict-origin-when-cross-origin”allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的许多其他开源项目今年都达到了重大里程碑——如果没有 OSS 社区的支持，我们就不可能达到这些里程碑。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/03/grafana-mimir-3-0-release-all-the-latest-updates/&#34;&gt;Mimir 3.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：这一主要版本在可靠性、性能和成本效率方面带来了显着改进，标志着开源、水平可扩展、多租户时间序列数据库 (TSDB) 进入了新时代。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafana-k6-1.0-release/&#34;&gt;k6 1.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：k6 1.0 推出了 TypeScript 支持、改进的测试见解以及明确的支持和版本控制保证为未来十年的性能和可靠性测试提供动力。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/10/grafana-beyla-2.0-distributed-traces-scalable-kubernetes-deployments-and-more/&#34;&gt;Beyla 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：我们与供应商无关的开源 eBPF 零代码检测工具的最新主要版本引入了性能和功能改进（例如对新协议和分布式跟踪的支持）以及更深入的功能与 OpenTelemetry 项目保持一致（剧透警告：更多内容见下文）。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-11-21-faro-web-sdk-v20-is-now-ga/&#34;&gt;Faro 2.0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：Faro Web SDK v2.0 于 11 月发布，引入了对 Web Vitals 的改进、简化了配置、清理了已弃用的内部结构等，以提供更加简化和高性能的用户体验。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/08/alloy-one-year/&#34;&gt;Alloy 一周年&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：5 月份，我们庆祝了 Grafana Alloy 一周年，这是我们的开源 OpenTelemetry 收集器，具有内置 Prometheus 管道并支持指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/&#34;&gt;我们的博客&lt;/a&gt;上了解有关 OSS 更新的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation-beyla-donated-to-the-otel-project&#34;&gt;3. OpenTelemetry eBPF 仪器：Beyla 捐赠给 OTel 项目&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多年来，我们优先考虑为 OpenTelemetry 项目做出贡献，并将与 OpenTelemetry 的兼容性构建到我们的产品和开源项目中。 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/beyla-ebpf/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Beyla&lt;/a&gt; 是这两项努力的典范。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年，在 Grafanista 和开源社区的支持下，我们正式&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation-beyla-donation/&#34;&gt;将 Beyla 捐赠给 OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt;，并以新项目名称&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/open-telemetry/opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation&lt;/a&gt;（通常称为 OBI）。这对我们来说是一个特殊的时刻，标志着整个开源社区中零代码 eBPF 工具发展的一个重要里程碑。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/dc515f1400/beyla-demo.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/dc515f1400/beyla-demo.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Beyla 演示中 Grafana 仪表板的屏幕截图，显示直接从 Beyla 为 OpenTelemetry Demo Checkout 服务生成的 RED（速率、错误和持续时间）指标以及服务图指标&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为捐赠的一部分，我们宣布 Beyla 将继续作为 Grafana Labs 分发上游 OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation。 8 月，&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/04/building-on-the-foundation-of-opentelemetry-ebpf-instrumentation-what-s-new-in-grafana-beyla-2-5/&#34;&gt;我们推出了 Beyla 2.5&lt;/a&gt;，这是第一个 Beyla 版本，我们直接从上游存储库提供了大部分代码。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;展望未来，我们很高兴能够继续在 OTel 社区内围绕零工作量仪器进行合作并推动进一步创新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关 OpenTelemetry eBPF Instrumentation 的更多信息，请访问 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/zero-code/obi/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry 文档&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-first-ever-science-fair-at-grafanacon&#34;&gt;4. GrafanaCON 举办首届“科学博览会”&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;没有火山喷发，但有 3D 打印机和大量物联网设备。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的第十届年度&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/grafanacon-2025-announcements/&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON&lt;/a&gt;以我们的首届科学博览会为特色，这是一系列互动展位（配有三折海报板），与会者可以在其中查看和玩项目，展示您可以使用 Grafana 监控的所有不同事物。亮点包括 PRUSA 团队监控 3D 打印机（适合所有​​人的迷你 Grots！）；由 Grafana Labs 首席技术官 Tom Wilkie 创建的为模型赛车打造的桌面风洞；以及黑客马拉松展位，与会者可以在这里亲身体验 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/03/01/grafana-labs-hackathon-projects-where-are-they-now/&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs 黑客马拉松&lt;/a&gt;中的热门项目，例如 Dash Dash Revolution 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/03/31/can-grafana-run-doom/&#34;&gt;Doomfana&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1333/6fb8b42b1c/3d-printed-grots.jpg/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1333/6fb8b42b1c/3d-printed-grots.jpg/m/&#34;alt=&#34;3D 打印 Grots 的照片。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了科学博览会之外，GrafanaCON 2025 还举办了超过 32 场现场会议、专家咨询展位、动手实验室、欢迎招待会以及更多有趣的社区驱动的活动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想参与明年的活动吗？请务必注册以便在有折扣门票时收到通知，并尽早了解我们将在 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;GrafanaCON 2026&lt;/a&gt;（将于 4 月 20 日至 22 日在巴塞罗那举行）上重点介绍的所有主题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-named-a-leader-in-the-gartner-magic-quadrant-for-observability-platforms-again&#34;&gt;5.再次被评为 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Observability Platform 的领导者！&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs 很荣幸被认可为 &lt;a href=&#34;/resources/grafana-observability-platforms-gartner-magic-quadrant-2025/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;连续第二年成为 2025 年 Gartner® 可观测性平台魔力象限™ 的领导者&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年的报告将 Grafana Labs 置于“愿景完整性”魔力象限右侧最远的位置，我们相信这反映了我们对构建全栈开放可观测性平台的坚定承诺，为用户提供灵活性、控制力和拥有其可观测性策略的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1808x1999/08e0a53d18/gartner-magic-quadrant-2025.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1808x1999/08e0a53d18/gartner-magic-quadrant-2025.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;2025 年 Gartner 可观测性平台魔力象限的屏幕截图。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是 2025 年获得的多项认可之一，展示了我们的公司和社区如何在塑造可观测性的未来方面发挥着至关重要的作用。我们还很荣幸被纳入：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.forbes.com/cloud100&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;福布斯云 100 强榜单&lt;/a&gt;，表彰全球顶级私有云公司； Grafana Labs 排名第 13。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;硅谷国防集团的 NATSEC100，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.natsec100.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;将 Grafana Labs 在“推动美国国家安全的 100 家风投支持的军民两用和国防技术公司”中排名第 26 位&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crn.com/news/software/2025/the-coolest-dataops-and-data-observability-companies-of-the-2025-big-data-100?page=7&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;2025 年大数据 100 强中最酷的数据运营和数据可观测性公司&lt;/a&gt;，由 CRN 制作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.redpoint.com/infrared/100/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;InfraRed 100&lt;/a&gt;，这是一份未排名的榜单，旨在表彰云基础设施领域的变革型公司。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然我们为这些荣誉感到自豪，但我们始终将用户的成功视为对我们产品的最终验证。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“我们非常荣幸能够成为这个真正充满活力和活力的生态系统和社区的中心，”Raj 在 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/agenda/2025/keynote/&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2025&lt;/a&gt; 上说道。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;6-the-end-to-end-adaptive-telemetry-suite&#34;&gt;6.端到端自适应遥测套件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更多的可观测性数据并不总是带来更多的清晰度 - 事实上，它通常只会产生更多的噪音和成本。这就是我们构建自适应遥测的原因，这是 Grafana Cloud 中的一组功能，可通过 e 优化可观测性数据确保仅存储和显示最有价值的遥测数据。它使用智能分类和优先级技术来分析遥测的使用方式，然后自动建议聚合、采样、删除或减少低价值数据等操作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的自适应遥测套件始于&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-metrics/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应指标&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/adaptive-telemetry/adaptive-logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;自适应日志&lt;/a&gt;，今年扩展到包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/#adaptive-traces-retain-only-your-most-valuable-traces&#34;&gt;自适应跟踪（普遍可用）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：使用尾部采样自动识别和保留最有价值的跟踪，以提供关键的性能洞察。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/adaptive-telemetry-suite-in-grafana-cloud/#adaptive-profiles-the-power-of-continuous-profiling-without-runaway-costs&#34;&gt;自适应配置文件（私人预览版）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：根据工作负载行为动态调整数据收集，无需高成本即可大规模连续分析。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeIFky5ut3g3tvhIOApTqV1yyuZ6i0Cv_Vg2G0wTbS6r98elQ/viewform&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;在此注册&lt;/a&gt;以加入我们的私人预览版。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x876/4ad7118eeb/adaptive-telemetry-suite-timeline.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x876/4ad7118eeb/adaptive-telemetry-suite-timeline.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;显示自适应遥测套件产品发布时间表的图像。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“在自适应跟踪之前，我们有两个糟糕的选择：发送所有内容并超出我们的预算，或者发送太少，我们无法获得有意义的见解，”Auditboard 基础设施工程经理 Geoff Schultz 说道。 “现在跟踪实际上是可用的。我们可以根据需要增加或减少采样，控制成本，并仍然为团队提供他们所需的可见性。” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;借助此端到端自适应遥测套件，您可以将自适应模型的优势扩展到可观测性策略的所有核心支柱，确保您存储的每一项遥测数据都真正值得投资。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;查看&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/adaptive-telemetry/&#34;&gt;我们的文档&lt;/a&gt;，了解有关自适应遥测的更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;7-introducing-grafana-labs-japan&#34;&gt;7.介绍 Grafana Labs Japan&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论是参加社区聚会，&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-the-community-behind-the-code/&#34;&gt;开发 Grafana 数据源&lt;/a&gt;，甚至监控该国的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/08/01/how-japans-space-agency-used-grafana-to-monitor-its-first-moon-landing-in-real-time/&#34;&gt;首次登月&lt;/a&gt;，我们的用户和日本的合作伙伴一直是更广泛的 Grafana 社区的积极组成部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;因此，我们很高兴地宣布今年在东京成立新子公司 Grafana Labs Japan&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;/about/press/2025/11/12/grafana-labs-builtes-japan-subsidiary-to-accelerate-local-market-expansion/&#34;&gt;。通过这项投资，我们增强了提供本地化支持的能力，促进与日本企业和合作伙伴更密切的合作，并加速整个地区的数字化转型计划。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1086x724/29cade6881/grafana-labs-japan-opening-event.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1086x724/29cade6881/grafana-labs-japan-opening-event.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Labs 员工在 Grafana Labs Japan 开幕活动上的照片。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“在 Grafana Labs，开放不仅是我们的战略，也是我们的战略。这是我们的与众不同之处。借助我们开放、灵活的可观测平台，我们可以帮助组织随时随地查看和理解任何事物，将信号转化为更智能、更快速的行动。我们很高兴能够将这一愿景扩展到日本的更多组织。”Raj 说道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;8-extending-the-grafana-cloud-stack&#34;&gt;8.扩展 Grafana 云堆栈&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们不断为 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 提供新功能，努力使我们托管的开放式可观测平台更加高效、智能且易于使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了 Grafana Assistant 和端到端自适应遥测套件之外，我们还通过以下一些方式在 2025 年发展 Grafana Cloud，以实现更强大的全栈可观测性策略。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/observabilitycon-2025-announcements/#full-stack-observability-powered-by-the-knowledge-graph&#34;&gt;知识图&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：通过将系统应用、数据库和基础设施的遥测数据合并到单个智能地图中，知识图可以帮助您缩短 MTTR 并更快地找到根本原因。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/fedramp-federal-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Federal Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：Grafana Federal Cloud 获得 FedRAMP 高授权且符合 DoD IL5 标准，为组织提供安全可靠的基于云的基础设施、应用程序和服务监控，确保数据保护和遵守严格的安全标准。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/12/01/improve-service-reliability-and-ops-culture-with-grafana-cloud-service-center/&#34;&gt;服务中心&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：Grafana Cloud 中的这个统一中心提供服务优先的系统运行状况视图，帮助您提高服务可靠性和运营文化。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/13/understand-diagnose-and-optimize-sql-queries-introducing-grafana-cloud-database-observability/&#34;&gt;数据库可观察性&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;：通过跟踪数据库中的每个查询并轻松将查询与应用和基础架构信号关联起来，此解决方案（如下所示）使数据库故障排除变得更快、更轻松。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;仪表中心&lt;/strong&gt;：这种点击式体验可让您自动发现仪表差距并大规模部署可观测性覆盖范围。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/c4e0215688/database-observability-dashboard.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1144/c4e0215688/database-observability-dashboard.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;数据库可观测性仪表板的屏幕截图。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/tags/grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud 博客文章&lt;/a&gt;中了解有关这些功能和其他新功能的更多信息。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;9-the-third-annual-observability-survey&#34;&gt;9.第三次年度可观测性调查&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在各种类型和规模的公司中，可观察性实践正在日趋成熟并受到最高层的关注。与此同时，成本和复杂性继续阻碍着团队的努力，因为团队寻求新兴工具来帮助简化流程，以期获得更好的结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些是 Grafana Labs 为您带来的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/03/25/observability-survey-takeaways/&#34;&gt;第三次年度可观测性调查&lt;/a&gt;的一些主要发现。我们总共在网上和世界各地的行业活动中收集了 1,255 份回复（比去年多了 4 倍！），这使其成为最大的社区驱动的可观察性状态调查。我们还制作了&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/12/observability-trends-in-brazil-insights-from-our-localized-survey/&#34;&gt;巴西&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/13/japan-observability-survey-25/&#34;&gt;日本&lt;/a&gt;的调查版本，以更好地了解那里的组织如何采用可观察性，并分享与社区的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“560”height =“315”src =&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wTEuti1Ica4&#39;title =“YouTube视频播放器”frameborder =“0”允许=“加速计;自动播放;剪贴板写入;加密媒体;陀螺仪;画中画;网络共享”referrerpolicy =“strict-origin-when-cross-origi”n&#34; 允许全屏&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这项调查帮助我们更好地了解可观察性的状况，但我们也将其视为我们社区和更广泛行业的资产。 &lt;a href=&#34;/observability-survey/2025/&#34;&gt;报告&lt;/a&gt;是免费的（无需电子邮件！），去年我们添加了&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/d/feg4yc4qw3wn4b/third-annual-observability-survey?orgId=1&amp;from=2025-03-13T02:49:20.476Z&amp;to=2025-03-14T02:49:20.476Z&amp;tim ezone=utc&amp;var-region=$__all&amp;var-role=$__all&amp;var-size=$__all&amp;var-industry=$__all&amp;var-filters=%60Region%60%20in%20%28%27Europe%27,%27Asia%27,%27North%20A美洲%27,%27非洲%27,%27南部%20美洲%27,%27大洋洲%27,%27中部%20东部%27%29%20AND%20%60角色%60%20IN%20%28%27平台%20团队%27,%27SRE%27,%27CTO%2 7、%27工程%20经理%27、%27开发人员%27、%27总监%20of%20工程%27、%27其他%27%29%20AND%20%60Size_of_organization%60%20IN%20%28%2710%20或%2 0少%20员工%27,%2711%20-%20100%20员工%27,%27101%20-%20500%20emp员工%27,%27501%20-%201,000%20员工%27,%271,001%20-%202,500%20员工%27,%272,501%20-%205,000%20员工%27,%275,001%2B%20员工%27%29%20AND%20%60行业%60%20IN%20%28%27电信%27,%27医疗%27,%27IoT% 27,%27金融%20服务%27,%27教育%27,%27政府%27,%27应用%20科学%27,%27软件%20%26%20技术%27,%27媒体%20%26%20娱乐t%27,%27旅游%20%26%20交通%27,%27零售%2FE-商业%27,%27能源%20%26%20公用事业%27,%27汽车%20%26%20制造业%27,%27其他%27%29&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;交互式 Grafana 仪表板&lt;/a&gt;，您也可以在其中深入研究数字。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;去年没有参加调查吗？不用担心 - 我们仍在收集&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/01/take-grafana-labs-4th-annual-observability-survey/&#34;&gt;明年调查的回复&lt;/a&gt;。只需几分钟，所有回复都将保持匿名，您还可以赢得一些奖品。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;10-raise-the-bar-on-growth&#34;&gt;10.提高增长标准&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;9 月，Grafana Labs &lt;a href=&#34;/about/press/2025/09/30/grafana-labs-surpasses-400m-arr-and-7000-customers-gains-new-investors-to-accelerate-global-expansion/&#34;&gt;完成了一项二级交易&lt;/a&gt;，由安大略省教师养老金计划牵头，Sapphire Ventures 和 Tiger Global 参与其中。现有投资者 Lightspeed Venture Partners、GIC、Coatue、红杉资本、CapitalG 和 Lead Edge Capital 也参与其中。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是凸显我们在可观测性市场不断增长势头的几个时刻之一。我们的年度经常性收入也超过了 4 亿美元，全球客户数量已超过 7,000 家。如今，一些世界上最知名的公司（从 Anthropic 和 NVIDIA 到 Salesforce 和 Microsoft）都依靠 Grafana Labs 来支持他们的可观察性策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“这确实是一项令人难以置信的成就，”Raj 在 ObservabilityCON 的舞台上说道。 “我们非常感谢您的帮助让我们达到这个数字。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这就结束了！当然，如果没有我们令人难以置信的开源社区，我们不可能实现这些里程碑。感谢您继续支持和激励我们，我们迫不及待地等待充满新想法、共同胜利和更深入联系的新一年。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gartner®，可观测性平台魔力象限™，作者：Gregg Siegfried、Matt Crossley、Padraig Byrne、Andre Bridges、Martin Caren，2025 年 7 月 7 日&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;GARTNER 是 Gartner, Inc. 和/或其附属公司在美国和国际上的注册商标和服务标志，MAGIC QUADRANT 是 Gartner, Inc. 和/或其附属公司的注册商标，经许可在本文中使用。保留所有权利。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gartner 不认可其研究出版物中描述的任何供应商、产品或服务，也不建议技术用户仅选择那些具有最高评级或其他称号的供应商。 Gartner 研究出版物包含 Gartner 研究与咨询组织的意见，不应被视为事实陈述。 Gartner 不承担与本研究相关的所有明示或暗示的保证，包括对适销性或特定用途适用性的任何保证。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;该图由 Gartner, Inc. 作为较大研究文件的一部分发布，应在整个文件的背景下进行评估。 Gartner 文档可向 Grafana Labs 索取。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Removal of Drilldown Investigations in Grafana: What you need to know】删除 Grafana 中的深入调查：您需要了解的内容</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/12/04/removal-of-drilldown-investigations-in-grafana-what-you-need-to-know/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Back in May, we introduced the &lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-05-04-introducing-investigations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;public preview of Grafana Drilldown Investigations&lt;/a&gt;, a new feature intended to help Grafana OSS and Grafana Cloud users accelerate their incident response.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, as we head into the new year, we&amp;rsquo;ve made the difficult decision to deprecate this feature from OSS and deprovision it from Grafana Cloud. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To be clear, your &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/visualizations/simplified-exploration/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Drilldown apps&lt;/a&gt; (logs, metrics, traces, profiles) will not be affected, and neither will the classic Explore. Also, Drilldown Investigations should not be confused with &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/introduction/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant Investigations&lt;/a&gt;, which remains available to all Grafana Cloud users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Though this feature never became generally available, we want to be transparent about the decision. Below you’ll find the timeline, what changes, and strategies on how to preserve notes and links you’ve saved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Drilldown Investigations set out to give you one place to collect and correlate key findings from different signals—metrics, logs, traces, and profiles—so you could move faster during an incident or a tricky performance dive. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sounds great, right? In practice, however, adoption was low compared to our core Drilldown apps and dashboards, and the extra side panel/UI surface area added complexity without enough day‑to‑day payoff for most teams. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rather than take Investigations to GA, we’re making the hard call to deprecate it and re‑invest that energy where you spend the majority of your time: Drilldown apps, dashboards, and guided pivots between signals. (If you’re new to Drilldown and how it differs from classic Explore, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/20/grafana-drilldown-apps-the-improved-queryless-experience-formerly-known-as-the-explore-apps/&#34;&gt;here’s the background&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;whats-not-changing&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s not changing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metrics Drilldown, Logs Drilldown, Traces Drilldown, and Profiles Drilldown remain.&lt;/strong&gt; These are the queryless, point‑and‑click experiences many of you rely on daily. They’re still the fastest way to move from “something looks off” to the relevant service, pod, span, or profile.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Classic Explore remains.&lt;/strong&gt; If you prefer to type queries, that workflow isn’t going anywhere.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;whats-changing-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s changing (Grafana Cloud)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Drilldown Investigations app (the sidebar experience that lets you collect items across Drilldown apps, add notes/markdown, and view a timeline or time‑range comparisons) will be removed from Grafana Cloud. Existing “investigations” artifacts (your notes and item lists) will not be available after removal.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;whats-changing-grafana-oss&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s changing (Grafana OSS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Drilldown Investigations app plugin will be marked as deprecated in the Plugin Catalog and eventually removed, unavailable for future installation in OSS Grafana.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;when-it&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When it&amp;rsquo;s changing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week of January 5:&lt;/strong&gt; Removal and decommissioning of Grafana Drilldown Investigations app&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week of January 5:&lt;/strong&gt; Removal of Grafana Drilldown Investigations documentation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-should-do-now-migration-options&#34;&gt;What you should do now (migration options)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using the Drilldown Investigations app, you have several options going forward. And if you have any additional questions, please reach out to your Grafana Cloud account manager. If you&amp;rsquo;re using this feature in OSS, reach out in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana community Slack&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;convert-an-investigation-into-a-dashboard&#34;&gt;Convert an investigation into a dashboard&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If an investigation captured the right panels and comments, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/visualizations/simplified-exploration/investigations/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;create a dashboard from the investigation&lt;/a&gt; to preserve its structure in a standard dashboard. This is the best one‑click way to keep a living artifact your team can iterate on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;copy-notes-and-links-you-want-to-keep&#34;&gt;Copy notes and links you want to keep&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Investigations were mostly pointers and markdown used to add context around your telemetry data. If you have stored any important information in a Grafana Drilldown Investigation, copy any commentary you care about into runbooks, tickets, or dashboards before the removal date. (Your underlying telemetry remains unchanged.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;use-assistant-investigations-part-of-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;Use Assistant Investigations, part of Grafana Assistant&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/introduction/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant Investigations&lt;/a&gt; is not a replacement for Drilldown Investigations; it&amp;rsquo;s a completely new feature that supports running investigations. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This feature allows you to investigate incidents autonomously and asynchronously. And thanks to a tight integration with Grafana Assistant, our AI-powered chat bot, you can also take a number of follow-up actions (build a dashboard, create queries, create an alert, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;早在 5 月份，我们就推出了&lt;a href=&#34;/whats-new/2025-05-04-introducing-investigations/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Drilldown Investigations 公开预览版&lt;/a&gt;，这是一项旨在帮助 Grafana OSS 和 Grafana Cloud 用户加快事件响应速度的新功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，当我们进入新的一年时，我们做出了一个艰难的决定：从 OSS 弃用此功能，并从 Grafana Cloud 取消配置它。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需要明确的是，您的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/visualizations/simplified-exploration/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;深入分析应用&lt;/a&gt;（日志、指标、跟踪、配置文件）不会受到影响，经典的“探索”也不会受到影响。此外，不应将 Drilldown Investigations 与 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/introduction/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant Investigations&lt;/a&gt; 混淆，后者仍然可供所有 Grafana Cloud 用户使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然此功能从未普遍可用，但我们希望对这一决定保持透明。您将在下面找到时间线、更改内容以及如何保留已保存的注释和链接的策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;背景&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;深入调查旨在为您提供一个地方来收集和关联来自不同信号（指标、日志、跟踪和配置文件）的关键发现，以便您可以在事件或棘手的性能下降期间更快地采取行动。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;听起来不错，对吧？然而，在实践中，与我们的核心 Drilldown 应用程序和仪表板相比，采用率较低，而且额外的侧面板/UI 表面积增加了复杂性，而对大多数团队来说没有足够的日常回报。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们并没有将调查带到 GA 上，而是艰难地呼吁弃用它，并将精力重新投入到您花费大部分时间的地方：深入应用、仪表板和信号之间的引导枢轴。 （如果您不熟悉 Drilldown 以及它与经典 Explore 的区别，&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/20/grafana-drilldown-apps-the-improved-queryless-experience-known-as-the-explore-apps/&#34;&gt;这里是背景知识&lt;/a&gt;。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;whats-not-having&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;什么没有改变&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;指标钻取、日志钻取、跟踪钻取和配置文件钻取仍然存在。&lt;/strong&gt;这些是许多人每天依赖的无查询、点击式体验。它们仍然是从“看起来不太对劲”转向相关服务、pod、跨度或配置文件的最快方式。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;经典探索仍然存在。&lt;/strong&gt;如果您更喜欢输入查询，那么该工作流程将不会有任何变化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;whats-having-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;变化 (Grafana Cloud)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drilldown Investigations 应用（侧边栏体验可让您跨 Drilldown 应用收集项目、添加注释/Markdown 以及查看时间线或时间范围比较）将从 Grafana Cloud 中删除。现有的“调查”工件（您的笔记和项目列表）在删除后将不可用。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;whats-having-grafana-oss&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;变化内容 (Grafana OSS)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drilldown Investigations 应用插件将在插件目录中被标记为已弃用，并最终被删除，以后无法在 OSS Grafana 中安装。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;when-it&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;变化时&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1 月 5 日当周&lt;/strong&gt;：删除并停用 Grafana Drilldown 调查应用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1 月 5 日当周&lt;/strong&gt;：删除 Grafana 深入调查文档&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-should-do-now-migration-options&#34;&gt;您现在应该做什么（迁移选项）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您当前正在使用“深入调查”应用，那么您以后有多种选择。如果您还有任何其他问题，请联系您的 Grafana Cloud 客户经理。如果您在 OSS 中使用此功能，请访问 &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana 社区 Slack&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;convert-an-investigation-into-a-dashboard&#34;&gt;将调查转换为仪表板&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果调查捕获了正确的面板和评论，请&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/visualizations/simplified-exploration/investigations/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;根据调查创建仪表板&lt;/a&gt;以在标准仪表板中保留其结构。这是保持团队可以迭代的活工件的最佳一键式方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;copy-notes-and-links-you-want-to-keep&#34;&gt;复制您要保留的笔记和链接&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;调查主要是用于在遥测数据周围添加上下文的指针和降价。如果您在 Grafana 深入调查中存储了任何重要信息，请在删除日期之前将您关心的任何评论复制到操作手册、票证或仪表板中。 （您的基础遥测保持不变。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;use-assistant-investigations-part-of-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;使用 Assistant Investigations，Grafana Assistant 的一部分&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/assistant/introduction/investigations/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana 助理调查&lt;/a&gt; 不能替代深入调查；这是一个支持运行调查的全新功能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此功能允许您自主且异步地调查事件。由于与我们的人工智能聊天机器人 Grafana Assistant 的紧密集成，您还可以执行许多后续操作（构建仪表板、创建查询、创建警报等）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Send OpenTelemetry traces and logs from Cloudflare Workers to Grafana Cloud】将 OpenTelemetry 跟踪和日志从 Cloudflare Workers 发送到 Grafana Cloud</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/12/04/send-opentelemetry-traces-and-logs-from-cloudflare-workers-to-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: This blog was co-authored by Nevika Shah, a senior product manager at Cloudflare.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://workers.cloudflare.com/product/workers-ai?gclsrc=aw.ds&amp;amp;&amp;amp;utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;amp;utm_campaign=20580233211&amp;amp;utm_term=_go_cmp-20580233211_adg-181172125365_ad-765256143338_dsa-2446653702475_dev-c_ext-_prd-_sig-CjwKCAiAlrXJBhBAEiwA-5pgwmTZCcxaXTXcoSytbMN3_oym4BKM5tO6KVxKrIdWS8Sx-9BG89MOYxoC5_kQAvD_BwE&amp;amp;utm_content=765256143338&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=20580233211&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAADnzVeSrSlN2TnL1qpVncmnPxkXEn&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAiAlrXJBhBAEiwA-5pgwmTZCcxaXTXcoSytbMN3_oym4BKM5tO6KVxKrIdWS8Sx-9BG89MOYxoC5_kQAvD_BwE&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Cloudflare Workers&lt;/a&gt; is a developer platform for deploying serverless functions, frontends, containers, and databases to a global network, spanning 330+ cities around the world. However, as your application scales, it becomes crucial to have the right observability tools to investigate issues, monitor performance, and get alerts when issues arise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last month, Cloudflare Workers announced support for &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-tracing-now-in-open-beta/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;exporting OpenTelemetry logs and traces&lt;/a&gt;, letting you send this data directly to &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;. By adopting the &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Protocol&lt;/a&gt; (OTLP) as the transport layer and exposing an easy configuration workflow in both platforms, you can stream traces and logs from your Workers application directly to your Grafana Cloud stack. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-cloudflare-workers/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Cloudflare Workers integration for Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; offers pre-built dashboards, allowing you to quickly visualize and get value from your data. This includes the ability to drill down into traces and logs based on attributes like request location and duration. By sending data to Grafana Cloud, you can use: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt;, powered by &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/tempo/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt;, which provides distributed tracing capabilities to follow a request through your Worker&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/logs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Logs&lt;/a&gt;, powered by &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt;, which stores logs so you can search them centrally&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;traces-logs-and-dashboards-out-of-the-box&#34;&gt;Traces, logs, and dashboards out of the box&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Exporting data from your Workers application uses a push‑based pipeline that forwards telemetry directly to Grafana Cloud using Cloudflare’s built-in Workers Observability feature called &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/exporting-opentelemetry-data/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Destinations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Just add your OpenTelemetry endpoint and start sending — no agent installation and no sidecar management. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once configured, you can automatically investigate:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traces:&lt;/strong&gt; OpenTelemetry spans are automatically instrumented within the Workers runtime. Spans like subrequests to APIs and calls to &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/traces/spans-and-attributes/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Worker bindings&lt;/a&gt; like &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/r2/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;R2 Object Storage&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/kv/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Workers Key-Value Store&lt;/a&gt; are automatically emitted and ingested by Tempo. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Logs&lt;/strong&gt;: Logs emitted by your Workers are forwarded to Loki and indexed for search and alerting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pre‑built dashboards&lt;/strong&gt;: Grafana Cloud provides ready‑made panels tailored to Cloudflare Workers telemetry, letting you see request volumes, latency distributions, error rates, and geographical patterns without building dashboards from scratch.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multiple Workers can send data to the same Grafana Cloud stack, and the pipeline scales automatically; there is no infrastructure to provision or maintain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;practical-scenarios&#34;&gt;Practical scenarios&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s look at a few scenarios where this data is used to diagnose and manage application health: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debugging performance in specific regions:&lt;/strong&gt; If users in Europe report slowness, filter the dashboard to those colos and examine latency distributions. You can use Tempo to follow slow traces step by step, and Loki to see whether errors or long‑running operations correlate. Because telemetry is global, you can compare the European pattern to other continents to isolate the issue.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Capacity and traffic planning:&lt;/strong&gt; By watching request volume trends across continents and time zones, you can anticipate growth and adjust caching or compute limits accordingly. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security and anomaly detection:&lt;/strong&gt; Sudden spikes from unusual HTTP methods or from unexpected countries may indicate abuse. The integration’s real‑time metrics and logs help you identify these anomalies quickly and initiate mitigations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User experience optimization:&lt;/strong&gt; Client analytics reveal which browsers, OSes, or devices dominate your traffic. If you see poor performance for a particular browser version, you can reproduce and fix it. Language and locale information can inform localization decisions or A/B testing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-set-up&#34;&gt;Get set up &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At a high level, the integration consists of two pieces: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/exporting-opentelemetry-data/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Destination&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; set-up in your Cloudflare dashboard that points at your Grafana Cloud OTLP endpoint&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A small snippet of configuration for your Worker, telling Cloudflare to send traces and logs to Grafana Cloud&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;configure-otlp-destinations&#34;&gt;Configure OTLP destinations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create a Grafana Cloud access policy token&lt;/strong&gt; in your Grafana portal. When you add a new OTLP connection, Grafana will display an OTLP endpoint (such as &lt;code&gt;https://otlp-gateway-prod-us-east-2.grafana.net/otlp&lt;/code&gt;) and a header name/value pair for authentication. The header name is &lt;code&gt;Authorization&lt;/code&gt;, and the value is a Base64‑encoded token beginning with &lt;code&gt;Basic …&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add destinations in Cloudflare Workers Observability.&lt;/strong&gt; In your Cloudflare dashboard, go to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://dash.cloudflare.com/?to=/:account/workers-and-pages/observability/destinations&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Workers Observability page&lt;/a&gt; and add two destinations: one for traces and one for logs. For each, provide the Grafana OTLP endpoint with the appropriate suffix (&lt;code&gt;/v1/traces&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;/v1/logs&lt;/code&gt;), and supply the &lt;code&gt;Authorization&lt;/code&gt; header and its value from the previous step.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1170x1158/6e1084c117/cloudflare-destinations-ui.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1170x1158/6e1084c117/cloudflare-destinations-ui.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the &amp;#39;Add New Destination&amp;#39; UI with Traces selected as the destination type.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;enable-observability-on-your-worker&#34;&gt;Enable observability on your Worker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, configure your Worker to emit telemetry. You can do this by &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/exporting-opentelemetry-data/#enabling-opentelemetry-export-for-your-worker&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;editing your Wrangler configuration file&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;[observability.traces]&#xA;enabled = true&#xA;destinations = [&amp;#34;grafana-traces&amp;#34;]&#xA;[observability.logs]&#xA;enabled = true&#xA;destinations = [&amp;#34;grafana-logs&amp;#34;]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The destination names must match the names you configured in the Cloudflare dashboard. After deployment, data will begin sending to Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;inside-the-pre-built-dashboards&#34;&gt;Inside the pre-built dashboards&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e8c91f0194/cloudflare-workers-panel-1.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e8c91f0194/cloudflare-workers-panel-1.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana Cloud dashboard for Cloudflare Workers, showing metrics including total numbers of events, request rate, and unique countries.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once telemetry reaches Grafana, the pre‑built dashboard surfaces a rich set of insights:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;request-patterns-and-performance&#34;&gt;Request patterns and performance&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud charts total request counts, requests per second, and unique requests (based on Ray IDs) so you can spot spikes or drops in traffic. Time‑series panels compare latency metrics across methods and endpoints and show the distribution of HTTP methods (GET, POST, etc.), while bar charts visualize the most frequently accessed URL paths. You can click into an error trace and immediately view the associated log messages. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;geographic-distribution&#34;&gt;Geographic distribution&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge‑native applications serve users all over the world, so geography matters. The dashboard includes a geomap heatmap that highlights countries by request volume. You can drill down to see which Cloudflare data centers handle the most traffic and analyze patterns by continent, time zone, region, or even by autonomous system number (ASN). These views help identify high‑latency regions or unusual traffic sources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;client-environment&#34;&gt;Client environment&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understanding the devices and software hitting your Worker can help prioritize testing and optimization. The integration enriches logs with user‑agent details, letting you break down requests by browser family (Chrome, Firefox, Safari, Edge), operating system (Windows, macOS, Linux, iOS, Android), rendering engine, and even user‑preferred language. You can compare performance across these dimensions to detect regressions or device‑specific issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;execution-context-and-protocols&#34;&gt;Execution context and protocols&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The dashboards also show which handlers were invoked on your Worker, such as HTTP requests, cron events, and queue consumers. Combined with latency graphs, these metrics make it easier to investigate Worker latency by handler type. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;log-trends-and-errors&#34;&gt;Log trends and errors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/441022f192/cloudflare-workers-panel-2.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/441022f192/cloudflare-workers-panel-2.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud logs panel for Cloudflare Workers showing a table of trace IDs and start times, and a selected trace detail panel with span timeline.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Loki indexes all logs from your Worker and surfaces severity trends in the dashboard. Bar charts split counts of info, warning, and error messages over time. Anomalies (e.g., a sudden increase in error logs from a specific region) can trigger alerts, and because each log entry includes a trace ID, you can jump from a log line directly to the related trace in Tempo.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;want-to-learn-more&#34;&gt;Want to learn more? &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To dive deeper into the tools and standards behind this integration, you can explore the following resources:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloudflare Workers integration documentation:&lt;/strong&gt; Find &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-cloudflare-workers/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;detailed instructions&lt;/a&gt; for installing and configuring the integration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloudflare’s export guide:&lt;/strong&gt; Get &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/exporting-opentelemetry-data/grafana-cloud/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;step‑by‑step guidance&lt;/a&gt; for exporting telemetry to Grafana Cloud and other OTLP destinations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry specification:&lt;/strong&gt; Learn how OTLP standardizes telemetry across vendors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tempo and Loki:&lt;/strong&gt; Explore how Grafana’s &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/tempo/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;tracing&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;logging&lt;/a&gt; backends work.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：本博客由 Cloudflare 高级产品经理 Nevika Shah 共同撰写。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;一href=&#34;https://workers.cloudflare.com/product/workers-ai?gclsrc=aw.ds&amp;&amp;utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;utm_campaign=20580233211&amp;utm _term=_go_cmp-20580233211_adg-181172125365_ad-765256143338_dsa-2446653702475_dev-c_ext-_prd-_sig-CjwKCAiAlrXJBhBAEiwA-5pgwmTZCcxaXT XcoSytbMN3_oym4BKM5tO6KVxKrIdWS8Sx-9BG89MOYxoC5_kQAvD_BwE&amp;utm_content=765256143338&amp;gad_source=1&amp;gad_campaignid=20580233211&amp;gbraid=0 AAAAADnzVeSrSlN2TnL1qpVncmnPxkXEn&amp;gclid=CjwKCAiAlrXJBhBAEiwA-5pgwmTZCcxaXTXcoSytbMN3_oym4BKM5tO6KVxKrIdWS8Sx-9BG89MOYxoC5_kQAvD_BwE&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Cloudflare Workers&lt;/a&gt; 是一个开发者平台，用于将无服务器功能、前端、容器和数据库部署到覆盖全球 330 多个城市的全球网络。然而，随着应用程序的扩展，拥有正确的可观察性工具来调查问题、监控性能并在问题出现时获取警报变得至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上个月，Cloudflare Workers 宣布支持&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.cloudflare.com/workers-tracing-now-in-open-beta/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;导出 OpenTelemetry 日志和跟踪&lt;/a&gt;，让您可以将此数据直接发送到 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;。通过采用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Protocol&lt;/a&gt; (OTLP) 作为传输层并在两个平台中公开简单的配置工作流程，您可以将跟踪和日志从 Workers 应用程序直接流式传输到 Grafana Cloud 堆栈。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;全新的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/integrations/integration-reference/integration-cloudflare-workers/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud 的 Cloudflare Workers 集成&lt;/a&gt;提供预构建的仪表板，让您能够快速可视化数据并从数据中获取价值。这包括基于请求位置和持续时间等属性深入查看跟踪和日志的能力。通过将数据发送到 Grafana Cloud，您可以使用：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt;，由 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/tempo/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt; 提供支持，提供分布式跟踪功能，可通过您的工作器跟踪请求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/logs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Logs&lt;/a&gt;，由 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; 提供支持，它存储日志，以便您可以集中搜索&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;traces-logs-and-dashboards-out-of-the-box&#34;&gt;开箱即用的跟踪、日志和仪表板&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从 Workers 应用程序导出数据使用基于推送的管道，该管道使用 Cloudflare 的内置 Workers Obser 将遥测数据直接转发到 Grafana Cloud称为&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/exporting-opentelemetry-data/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;目的地&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;的可用性功能。只需添加您的 OpenTelemetry 端点并开始发送 - 无需安装代理，也无需 sidecar 管理。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;配置完成后，您可以自动调查：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;跟踪&lt;/strong&gt;：OpenTelemetry 跨度会在 Workers 运行时中自动检测。跨越对 API 的子请求以及对 &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/traces/spans-and-attributes/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Worker 绑定&lt;/a&gt; 的调用，例如 &lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/r2/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;R2 对象存储&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/kv/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Workers键值存储&lt;/a&gt;由Tempo自动发出和摄取。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;日志&lt;/strong&gt;：您的工作人员发出的日志将转发到 Loki 并编入索引以供搜索和警报。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;预构建的仪表板&lt;/strong&gt;：Grafana Cloud 提供针对 Cloudflare Workers 遥测量身定制的现成面板，让您可以查看请求量、延迟分布、错误率和地理模式，而无需从头开始构建仪表板。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多个Worker可以将数据发送到同一个Grafana Cloud堆栈，管道自动扩展；没有需要配置或维护的基础设施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;practical-scenarios&#34;&gt;实际场景&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们看一下使用这些数据来诊断和管理应用程序运行状况的一些场景：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;调试特定区域的性能&lt;/strong&gt;：如果欧洲用户报告速度缓慢，请在仪表板中筛选这些区域并检查延迟分布。您可以使用 Tempo 逐步跟踪慢速跟踪，并使用 Loki 来查看错误或长时间运行的操作是否相关。由于遥测是全球性的，因此您可以将欧洲模式与其他大陆进行比较来隔离问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;容量和流量规划&lt;/strong&gt;：通过观察各大洲和时区的请求量趋势，您可以预测增长情况并相应调整缓存或计算限制。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;安全和异常检测&lt;/strong&gt;：来自异常 HTTP 方法或来自意外国家/地区的突然峰值可能表明滥用。该集成的实时指标和日志可帮助您快速识别这些异常情况并启动缓解措施。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;用户体验优化&lt;/strong&gt;：客户端分析揭示哪些浏览器、操作系统或设备主导您的流量。如果您发现特定浏览器版本的性能不佳，您可以重现并修复它。语言和区域设置信息可以为本地化决策或 A/B 测试提供信息。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-set-up&#34;&gt;开始设置&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从较高的层面来看，集成由两部分组成：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/exporting-opentelemetry-data/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;目标&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Cloudflare 控制面板中指向 Grafana Cloud OTLP 端点的设置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Worker 的一小段配置，告诉 Cloudflare 将跟踪和日志发送到 Grafana Cloud&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;configure-otlp-destinations&#34;&gt;配置 OTLP 目标&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在 Grafana 门户中创建 Grafana Cloud 访问策略令牌&lt;/strong&gt;。当您添加新的 OTLP 连接时，Grafana 将显示 OTLP 端点（例如 https://otlp-gateway-prod-us-east-2.grafana.net/otlp&lt;/code&gt;）和用于身份验证的标头名称/值对。标头名称为 &lt;code&gt;Authorization&lt;/code&gt;，值是以 &lt;code&gt;Basic ...&lt;/code&gt; 开头的 Base64 编码令牌&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;在 Cloudflare Workers Observability 中添加目标。&lt;/strong&gt;在 Cloudflare 控制面板中，转到 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dash.cloudflare.com/?to=/:account/workers-and-pages/observability/destinations&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Workers Observability 页面&lt;/a&gt;并添加两个目标：一个用于跟踪，一个用于日志。对于每个端点，为 Grafana OTLP 端点提供适当的后缀（&lt;code&gt;/v1/traces&lt;/code&gt; 或 &lt;code&gt;/v1/logs&lt;/code&gt;），并提供上一步中的 &lt;code&gt;Authorization&lt;/code&gt; 标头及其值。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1170x1158/6e1084c117/cloudflare-destinations-ui.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1170x1158/6e1084c117/cloudflare-destinations-ui.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;“添加新目标”UI 的屏幕截图，其中选择跟踪作为目标类型。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;enable-observability-on-your-worker&#34;&gt;启用您的工作人员的可观察性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，配置您的 Worker 以发出遥测数据。您可以通过&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/exporting-opentelemetry-data/#enabling-opentelemetry-export-for-your-worker&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;编辑 Wrangler 配置文件&lt;/a&gt;来完成此操作： &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;[observability.traces]&#xA;启用=真&#xA;目的地= [“grafana-traces”]&#xA;[观察性ity.logs]&#xA;启用=真&#xA;目的地 = [&#34;grafana-logs&#34;]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;目标名称必须与您在 Cloudflare 仪表板中配置的名称匹配。部署后，数据将开始发送到 Grafana Cloud。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;inside-the-pre-built-dashboards&#34;&gt;预构建仪表板内部&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e8c91f0194/cloudflare-workers-panel-1.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/e8c91f0194/cloudflare-workers-panel-1.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Cloudflare Workers 的 Grafana Cloud 仪表板的屏幕截图，显示包括事件总数、请求率和唯一国家/地区在内的指标。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦遥测数据到达 Grafana，预构建的仪表板就会显示一组丰富的见解：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;request-patterns-and-performance&#34;&gt;请求模式和性能&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 绘制总请求计数、每秒请求数和唯一请求（基于 Ray ID）的图表，以便您可以发现流量的峰值或下降。时间序列面板比较不同方法和端点的延迟指标，并显示 HTTP 方法（GET、POST 等）的分布，而条形图则可视化最常访问的 URL 路径。您可以单击错误跟踪并立即查看关联的日志消息。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;geographic-distribution&#34;&gt;地理分布&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;边缘原生应用程序为世界各地的用户提供服务，因此地理位置很重要。仪表板包括一个地理地图热图，按请求量突出显示国家/地区。您可以深入了解哪些 Cloudflare 数据中心处理的流量最多，并按大陆、时区、地区甚至自治系统编号 (ASN) 分析模式。这些视图有助于识别高延迟区域或异常流量源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;client-environment&#34;&gt;客户端环境&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解工作人员使用的设备和软件有助于确定测试和优化的优先顺序。该集成通过用户代理详细信息丰富了日志，让您可以按浏览器系列（Chrome、Firefox、Safari、Edge）、操作系统（Windows、macOS、Linux、iOS、Android）、渲染引擎，甚至用户首选语言来细分请求。您可以比较这些维度的性能，以检测回归或设备特定的问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;execution-context-and-protocols&#34;&gt;执行上下文和协议&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仪表板还显示在您的 Worker 上调用了哪些处理程序，例如 HTTP 请求、cron 事件和队列使用者。与延迟图相结合，这些指标可以更轻松地按处理程序类型调查 Worker 延迟。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;log-trends-and-errors&#34;&gt;记录趋势和错误&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p“&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/441022f192/cloudflare-workers-panel-2.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1920x1080/441022f192/cloudflare-workers-panel-2.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Cloudflare Workers 的 Grafana Cloud 日志面板，显示跟踪 ID 和开始时间表，以及带有跨度时间线的选定跟踪详细信息面板。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Loki 对您的工作人员的所有日志进行索引，并在仪表板中显示严重性趋势。条形图按时间划分信息、警告和错误消息的计数。异常情况（例如，特定区域的错误日志突然增加）可能会触发警报，并且由于每个日志条目都包含跟踪 ID，因此您可以从日志行直接跳转到 Tempo 中的相关跟踪。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;want-to-learn-more&#34;&gt;想要了解更多信息吗？ &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要深入了解此集成背后的工具和标准，您可以探索以下资源：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloudflare Workers 集成文档&lt;/strong&gt;：查找&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/integrations/integration-reference/integration-cloudflare-workers/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;有关安装和配置集成的详细说明&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cloudflare 的导出指南&lt;/strong&gt;：获取&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.cloudflare.com/workers/observability/exporting-opentelemetry-data/grafana-cloud/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;分步指南&lt;/a&gt;，将遥测数据导出到 Grafana Cloud 和其他 OTLP 目标&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OpenTelemetry 规范&lt;/strong&gt;：了解 OTLP 如何标准化跨供应商的遥测&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tempo 和 Loki&lt;/strong&gt;：探索 Grafana 的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/tempo/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;跟踪&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;日志记录&lt;/a&gt;后端如何工作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What&#39;s new in the Grafana Image Renderer: higher-quality results, security enhancements, and more】Grafana 图像渲染器的新增功能：更高质量的结果、安全性增强等等</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/12/03/whats-new-in-the-grafana-image-renderer-higher-quality-results-security-enhancements-and-more/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Whether it’s for an email or that upcoming presentation, many Grafana users like to share their favorite dashboards or panels outside of Grafana itself. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-image-renderer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Image Renderer&lt;/a&gt; is a backend service for Grafana that helps you do just that by rendering panels and dashboards as images, such as PNGs and PDFs, via a headless browser. It’s commonly used to support Grafana features like exporting dashboards, generating images for alert notifications, and creating PDF reports.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, we started working towards improving the Grafana Image Renderer, with the overall goal of enhancing the service’s performance, reliability, and security. Recently, these efforts resulted in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-image-renderer/releases&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;v5.0 release&lt;/a&gt;, which involved a whole rewrite of the service and included significant security improvements for our &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-the-grafana-image-renderer&#34;&gt;What is the Grafana Image Renderer?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a backend service for Grafana OSS, Grafana Enterprise, and Grafana Cloud, the Grafana Image Renderer enables various use cases related to generating and sharing images from Grafana. These include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Exporting dashboards and panels as PDFs and PNG images&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Including images in alert notifications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sharing rendered images via direct links &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Generating images for PDF exports and scheduled reports (available in Grafana Cloud and Grafana Enterprise)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a long time, you could choose between installing the Image Renderer as a plugin for Grafana, or deploying it as a service. The plugin was deprecated in September 2025, and the Image Renderer now exists only as a service that you can deploy separately alongside Grafana; it is not bundled with Grafana out of the box. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;recent-updates-to-the-grafana-image-renderer&#34;&gt;Recent updates to the Grafana Image Renderer&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;heuristics-for-higher-quality-results&#34;&gt;Heuristics for higher-quality results&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve used the Grafana Image Renderer — or a feature that it enables, like Grafana reporting and images in alert notifications — you have possibly experienced the service returning a partially blank result. This could have been an entire blank page or a panel that wasn’t fully loaded, or, in some cases, a result that featured your login screen rather than your dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address this, the service now uses more heuristics to determine when the rendered website has finished loading. It does this by tracking the number of Grafana queries, network requests, and whether the website keeps changing visually. This leads to higher-quality results in reports and similar. The details include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The service will wait for all ongoing network requests to finish, as this is generally an indicator that all API requests and data source queries are complete.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The service will wait for Grafana to mark all data source queries as complete. Note: this capability requires the &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/scenes/&#34;&gt;Grafana Scenes framework&lt;/a&gt; to be enabled.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The service will wait for the website to complete its rendering process. For example, if there are changes to text or other components, it will wait until everything stabilizes fully. In the configuration options, we call this “DOM hashcode stabilization.”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1420x722/5a73285cee/grafana-image-renderer-screenshot.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1420x722/5a73285cee/grafana-image-renderer-screenshot.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard that&amp;#39;s displaying metrics for the Grafana Image Renderer service, including browser render action durations and active browsers per cluster.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;security-improvements-in-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;Security improvements in Grafana Cloud&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the v5.0 release, we took the opportunity to tear down the old implementation and rebuild it to be faster and hardened.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Grafana Image Renderer relies on Chromium, the upstream open source project behind Chrome, Brave, and Edge. Earlier this year, we reviewed the vulnerabilities that had occurred in the Image Renderer and found they came from one source: Chromium. When a new memory bug was fixed in Chromium every few months, we would rush to fix it in our service as well. While this approach generally worked, we knew we needed a better, more stable plan. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To break this cycle of constantly patching vulnerabilities, we shifted gears and implemented a significantly enhanced sandbox for Chromium. While Chromium includes its own sandbox out of the box, it didn’t provide the level of isolation required for Grafana Cloud, so we built our own. It works by placing the Chromium browser inside a custom-built, highly restrictive sandbox, powered by &lt;a href=&#34;https://man7.org/linux/man-pages/man7/namespaces.7.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Linux’s namespace feature&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This new sandbox environment strengthens operational security by offering complete isolation from other services, eliminating the possibility of persistent files and terminating all processes once they are complete. If you’re interested in learning more about this, we recommend reading about &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/nsjail&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;nsjail&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/containers/bubblewrap&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;bubblewrap&lt;/a&gt;, which are solutions for similar problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As of writing, we’ve since seen 23 CVEs reported for Chromium, but our team did not have to rush to release a fix; our implementation was not impacted because of the way it’s now built.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-noteworthy-updates&#34;&gt;Other noteworthy updates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the above changes related to heuristics and security, we’ve made the following updates to the Grafana Image Renderer:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The service has been migrated to Go, meaning less memory usage at idle, and enabling us to implement lower-level security improvements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The service will adjust its rate-limit according to your available memory, meaning it will not take a new request if it can’t handle the load.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;There are now significant acceptance tests to the service: no changes can be implemented if they break the service or its interaction with Grafana.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The service now has &lt;em&gt;a lot&lt;/em&gt; of configuration options. You can now tweak every timeout and wait duration, disable heuristics, set various security features like mTLS for tracing, and much more. If you can’t find an option for something you need for your use case, please open an issue on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-image-renderer/issues/new/choose&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;our issue tracker&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;self-managed-environments&#34;&gt;Self-managed environments&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Like always, if you are a Grafana Cloud user, you have already received all these updates, and don’t need to do anything at all. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you run the Grafana Image Renderer on premises, you will need to do a couple things to take advantage of these updates:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you use the Grafana Image Renderer as a plugin, you need to migrate to the service deployment instead. &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/image-rendering/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#installation&#34;&gt;Our installation guide&lt;/a&gt; has details on how to do this.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The entire configuration scheme has changed, so if you use &lt;code&gt;:latest&lt;/code&gt; tags, please switch to pinned tags. We have kept the environment variable &lt;code&gt;AUTH_TOKEN&lt;/code&gt; to keep &lt;code&gt;:latest&lt;/code&gt; users functional until the configuration is changed to the new options.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;wrapping-up&#34;&gt;Wrapping up&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the v5.0 release of the Grafana Image Renderer delivers a more reliable and secure image rendering service. We can’t wait to hear what you think.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you run into issues, please refer to &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/image-rendering/troubleshooting/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#troubleshooting&#34;&gt;our troubleshooting guide&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-image-renderer/issues/new/choose&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;open an issue&lt;/a&gt; and we’d be happy to help.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;无论是电子邮件还是即将举行的演示文稿，许多 Grafana 用户都喜欢在 Grafana 之外分享他们最喜欢的仪表板或面板。 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-image-renderer&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana 图像渲染器&lt;/a&gt; 是 Grafana 的一项后端服务，可通过无头浏览器将面板和仪表板渲染为图像（例如 PNG 和 PDF）来帮助您实现这一目标。它通常用于支持 Grafana 功能，例如导出仪表板、生成警报通知图像以及创建 PDF 报告。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年早些时候，我们开始致力于改进 Grafana 图像渲染器，总体目标是增强服务的性能、可靠性和安全性。最近，这些努力促成了 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-image-renderer/releases&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;v5.0 版本&lt;/a&gt;，其中涉及对服务的整体重写，并为我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 用户提供了重大的安全改进。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-the-grafana-image-renderer&#34;&gt;什么是 Grafana 图像渲染器？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为 Grafana OSS、Grafana Enterprise 和 Grafana Cloud 的后端服务，Grafana Image Renderer 支持与从 Grafana 生成和共享图像相关的各种用例。其中包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将仪表板和面板导出为 PDF 和 PNG 图像&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在提醒通知中包含图像&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;通过直接链接共享渲染图像&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;生成用于 PDF 导出和计划报告的图像（在 Grafana Cloud 和 Grafana Enterprise 中提供）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;长期以来，您可以选择将图像渲染器安装为 Grafana 的插件，或将其部署为服务。该插件已于 2025 年 9 月被弃用，图像渲染器现在仅作为一项服务存在，您可以与 Grafana 一起单独部署；它没有与 Grafana 开箱即用捆绑在一起。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;recent-updates-to-the-grafana-image-renderer&#34;&gt;Grafana 图像渲染器的最新更新&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;heuristics-for-higher-quality-results&#34;&gt;启发式以获得更高质量的结果&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您使用过 Grafana 图像渲染器 - 或者它启用的功能，例如 Grafana 报告和警报通知中的图像 - 您可能会遇到该服务返回部分空白结果的情况。这可能是整个空白页面或未完全加载的面板，或者在某些情况下，结果是您的登录屏幕而不是仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了解决这个问题，该服务现在使用更多启发式方法来确定呈现的网站何时完成加载。它通过跟踪 Grafana 查询、网络请求的数量以及网站是否在视觉上不断变化来实现这一点。这会带来更高质量的报告和类似结果。详细信息包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;该服务将等待所有正在进行的事情g 网络请求完成，因为这通常表明所有 API 请求和数据源查询都已完成。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;该服务将等待 Grafana 将所有数据源查询标记为完成。注意：此功能需要启用 &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/scenes/&#34;&gt;Grafana Scenes 框架&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;该服务将等待网站完成其渲染过程。例如，如果文本或其他组件发生变化，它将等到一切完全稳定。在配置选项中，我们称之为“DOM 哈希码稳定”。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1420x722/5a73285cee/grafana-image-renderer-screenshot.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1420x722/5a73285cee/grafana-image-renderer-screenshot.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板的屏幕截图，显示 Grafana 图像渲染器服务的指标，包括浏览器渲染操作持续时间和每个集群的活动浏览器。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;security-improvements-in-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud 的安全性改进&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 v5.0 版本中，我们借此机会拆除了旧的实现并重建它，使其速度更快、更坚固。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana 图像渲染器依赖于 Chromium，它是 Chrome、Brave 和 Edge 背后的上游开源项目。今年早些时候，我们审查了图像渲染器中发生的漏洞，发现它们来自一个来源：Chromium。当 Chromium 每隔几个月修复一个新的内存错误时，我们也会急于在我们的服务中修复它。虽然这种方法通常有效，但我们知道我们需要一个更好、更稳定的计划。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了打破不断修补漏洞的循环，我们改变了方向，为 Chromium 实施了一个显着增强的沙箱。虽然 Chromium 包含自己的开箱即用的沙箱，但它没有提供 Grafana Cloud 所需的隔离级别，因此我们构建了自己的沙箱。它的工作原理是将 Chromium 浏览器放置在一个定制的、高度限制的沙箱中，该沙箱由 &lt;a href=&#34;https://man7.org/linux/man-pages/man7/namespaces.7.html&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Linux 的命名空间功能&lt;/a&gt;提供支持。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种新的沙箱环境通过提供与其他服务的完全隔离、消除持久文件的可能性以及一旦完成就终止所有进程来增强操作安全性。如果您有兴趣了解更多相关信息，我们建议您阅读 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/nsjail&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;nsjail&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/containers/bubblewrap&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;bubbblewrap&lt;/a&gt;，这是类似问题的解决方案。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;截至撰写本文时，我们已经看到 Chromium 报告了 23 个 CVE，但我们的团队不必急于发布修复程序；我们的实现并未因为现在的构建方式而受到影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-noteworthy-updates&#34;&gt;其他值得注意的更新&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了上述与启发式和安全性相关的更改之外，我们还对 Grafana 图像渲染器进行了以下更新：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;该服务已迁移到 Go，这意味着空闲时的内存使用量更少，并使我们能够实现较低级别的安全改进。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;该服务将根据您的可用内存调整其速率限制，这意味着如果无法处理负载，它将不会接受新请求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;目前对该服务进行了重要的验收测试：如果这些测试破坏了服务或其与 Grafana 的交互，则无法实施任何更改。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;该服务现在有&lt;em&gt;很多&lt;/em&gt;配置选项。现在，您可以调整每个超时和等待持续时间、禁用启发式方法、设置各种安全功能（例如用于跟踪的 mTLS）等等。如果您找不到适合您的用例所需的选项，请在&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-image-renderer/issues/new/choose&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;我们的问题跟踪器&lt;/a&gt;上提出问题。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;self-management-environments&#34;&gt;自我管理环境&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;与往常一样，如果您是 Grafana Cloud 用户，您已经收到了所有这些更新，并且根本不需要执行任何操作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您在本地运行 Grafana 图像渲染器，则需要执行一些操作才能利用这些更新：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;如果您使用 Grafana Image Renderer 作为插件，则需要迁移到服务部署。 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/image-rendering/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt/#installation&#34;&gt;我们的安装指南&lt;/a&gt;详细介绍了如何执行此操作。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;整个配置方案已更改，因此如果您使用 &lt;code&gt;:latest&lt;/code&gt; 标签，请切换到固定标签。我们保留了环境变量 &lt;code&gt;AUTH_TOKEN&lt;/code&gt; 以使 &lt;code&gt;:latest&lt;/code&gt; 用户保持功能，直到配置更改为新选项。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;wrapping-up&#34;&gt;总结&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;总体而言，Grafana Image Renderer v5.0 版本提供了更可靠、更安全的图像渲染服务。我们迫不及待想听听您的想法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您遇到问题，请参阅&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/image-rendering/troubleshooting/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt/#troubleshooting&#34;&gt;我们的故障排除指南&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-image-renderer/issues/new/choose&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;提出问题&lt;/a&gt;，我们很乐意提供帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用 Metr 的最简单方法ICS、日志、跟踪、仪表板等。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Contextual, in-product guidance for every Grafana user: A closer look at Interactive Learning】为每个 Grafana 用户提供上下文相关的产品内指导：深入了解交互式学习</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/12/02/contextual-in-product-guidance-for-every-grafana-user-a-closer-look-at-interactive-learning/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;As developer advocates at Grafana Labs, we’re always looking for new ways to help our users better understand and learn observability. You might remember our previous project that brought learning to life through an &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/11/20/metrics-logs-traces-and-mayhem-introducing-an-observability-adventure-game-powered-by-grafana-alloy-and-otel/&#34;&gt;adventure-style game&lt;/a&gt;, and now we’re really excited to share something else we’ve been working on: &lt;strong&gt;Interactive Learning&lt;/strong&gt;, a new way to get the technical help you need directly in Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever been deep in a dashboard or configuring a data source and hit a wall, you know how frustrating it can be to stop what you’re doing, open a browser tab, and hunt through documentation to find the answer you need. While those docs are great and go into a ton of detail, they also live outside Grafana. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Interactive Learning, we bring helpful and contextual learning resources into the Grafana platform itself, so you can find what you’re looking for quickly and easily — no context switching required.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZB_T2yQMR20&#39; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-we-built-interactive-learning&#34;&gt;Why we built Interactive Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our goal was simple: make help available where it’s needed most. Instead of sending you away from your workflow in Grafana, we wanted to bring the right information to you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That idea turned into something much bigger once we realized what was possible. Because we can render help text right inside Grafana itself, we suddenly had access to Grafana’s full runtime and Document Object Model (or DOM, which is the structure of the user interface itself). That meant help didn’t have to be static; it could be dynamic, contextual, and even &lt;strong&gt;interactive&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1093x547/8b49769f7b/interactive-learning-recommended-documenation.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1093x547/8b49769f7b/interactive-learning-recommended-documenation.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot showing the Recommended Documentation feature for Interactive Learning in Grafana.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started-with-interactive-learning&#34;&gt;Getting started with Interactive Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Interactive Learning became available in public preview in all editions of Grafana as part of the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/19/grafana-12-3-release-all-the-latest-features/&#34;&gt;Grafana 12.3 release&lt;/a&gt;. You can enable it by using the &lt;code&gt;interactiveLearning&lt;/code&gt; feature flag, or install it directly from the plugin catalog by searching for &lt;strong&gt;Interactive Learning&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You’ll then find the new Interactive Learning experience by clicking the question mark icon in the top-right corner of Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/548x73/ba66b2ddde/interactive-learning-help-icon.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/548x73/ba66b2ddde/interactive-learning-help-icon.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the Grafana UI with a red circle around the help icon, which looks like a question mark.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s the same help button that’s always been there. Before Interactive Learning, it just provided a few links to places like our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;documentation&lt;/a&gt; or the &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Community Forum&lt;/a&gt;. Now, it opens a side panel that brings you contextual help, in-product documentation, and even guided learning journeys, all without leaving Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-interactive-learning-does&#34;&gt;What Interactive Learning does&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you open the side panel, what you see depends on where you are in Grafana; the content is completely context-aware. Whether you’re viewing a dashboard, editing a data source, or creating a visualization, Grafana will surface documentation and learning material that’s relevant to what you’re doing right then and there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And this isn’t just static text. You’re seeing the full documentation rendered directly in Grafana, complete with images, videos, and step-by-step examples. No more jumping between tabs or trying to remember what you just read.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1094x717/7901c2cd88/interactive-learning-grafana-data-sources-resources.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1094x717/7901c2cd88/interactive-learning-grafana-data-sources-resources.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the Grafana UI showing documentation text and video resources for Grafana data sources.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;interactive-learning-guides&#34;&gt;Interactive learning guides&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve also introduced a new type of learning content: &lt;strong&gt;interactive learning guides&lt;/strong&gt;. These are built right into the documentation and guide you through tasks, step by step, from within the Grafana UI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each guide breaks things down into easy, specific steps, and some steps also include a &lt;strong&gt;Show Me&lt;/strong&gt; and/or a &lt;strong&gt;Do It&lt;/strong&gt; function. &lt;strong&gt;Show Me&lt;/strong&gt; highlights the relevant UI element and adds extra context.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1666x1014/8de6bda836/interactive-learning-show-me-gif.gif/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1666x1014/8de6bda836/interactive-learning-show-me-gif.gif/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A GIF demonstrating the Show Me functionality in Interactive Learning in Grafana.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Do It&lt;/strong&gt; function performs an action for you, such as clicking a button or filling out a field.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1666x1014/510fc0a73e/interactive-learning-do-it-gif.gif/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1666x1014/510fc0a73e/interactive-learning-do-it-gif.gif/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A GIF demonstrating the Do It functionality in Interactive Learning in Grafana.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also run entire interactive sections at once to watch the full flow unfold.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to see an interactive learning guide in action, try the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/d/to6j8mh/grafana-play-home?doc=bundled:prometheus-grafana-101&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Prometheus 101 tutorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, which walks you through setting up your first Prometheus data source and dashboard in Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1232x839/30d82df244/interactive-learning-prometheus-tutorial.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1232x839/30d82df244/interactive-learning-prometheus-tutorial.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the Grafana UI, featuring step 1 of the Prometheus 101 tutorial.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;smarter-context-aware-help&#34;&gt;Smarter, context-aware help&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Interactive Learning is powered by two components: a frontend plugin and a service we call the &lt;strong&gt;recommender&lt;/strong&gt;. The recommender is context-aware and will surface help and interactive learning guides with the highest likelihood of relevance to you and what you’re working on in Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, Interactive Learning runs entirely in &lt;strong&gt;offline mode&lt;/strong&gt;, which means it still provides great, context-based help without sending any data externally. If you choose to enable the recommender service, Grafana can deliver even more tailored documentation and tutorials to match your current task, all while respecting your privacy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next-for-interactive-learning&#34;&gt;What’s next for Interactive Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is just the beginning. We’re already exploring a few exciting directions to take this feature next:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Custom interactive guides:&lt;/strong&gt; This would enable you to create your own interactive guides inside Grafana for onboarding new teammates or walking through internal workflows. If this is something you or your team would find valuable, we’d love to hear from you on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.grafana.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Community Slack&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Community Forum&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integration with Grafana Assistant:&lt;/strong&gt; We’re exploring ways to combine the capabilities of &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt;, our AI-powered agent in Grafana Cloud, with guided learning to make it even easier to explore and understand your data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/469x455/925b6ea74e/interactive-learning-assistant.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/469x455/925b6ea74e/interactive-learning-assistant.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the Grafana UI with text that says &amp;#39;Ask Assistant&amp;#39; and then outlines next steps for navigating Grafana Cloud, understanding key areas like dashboards and data sources, and finding your way around the interface.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshop mode:&lt;/strong&gt; This would serve as a live session where a presenter can guide participants through Grafana, step by step. Great for team onboarding, internal training, or community workshops.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1236x1248/c18109b987/interactive-learning-live-session-qr-code.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1236x1248/c18109b987/interactive-learning-live-session-qr-code.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the Grafana UI with a box that says &amp;#39;Live Session&amp;#39; and a QR code.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;try-interactive-learning-today&#34;&gt;Try Interactive Learning today&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A great way to get started is to &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;try the new Interactive Learning experience in Grafana Play&lt;/a&gt;, our sandbox environment for testing and learning Grafana, hosted on Grafana Cloud. Interactive Learning is enabled by default in Play, and comes with an introductory interactive learning guide that walks you through all that Play has to offer. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Or, if you’re ready to dive right in and start using this feature in your own Grafana instance, please follow the instructions in the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/12/02/contextual-in-product-guidance-for-every-grafana-user-a-closer-look-at-interactive-learning/#getting-started-with-interactive-learning&#34;&gt;Getting started with Interactive Learning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; section above.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, like Grafana itself, the Interactive Learning plugin is &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-pathfinder-app&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;open source&lt;/a&gt;. This feature has been shaped by community input from day one, and we’re happy to accept contributions, whether that’s general feedback or ideas for improvements. We can’t wait to see where Interactive Learning goes next. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;作为 Grafana Labs 的开发者倡导者，我们一直在寻找新的方法来帮助我们的用户更好地理解和学习可观察性。您可能还记得我们之前的项目，该项目通过&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/11/20/metrics-logs-traces-and-mayhem-introducing-an-observability-adventure-game-powered-by-grafana-alloy-and-otel/&#34;&gt;冒险风格游戏&lt;/a&gt;将学习带入生活，现在我们非常高兴能分享我们一直在研究的其他内容：&lt;strong&gt;交互式学习&lt;/strong&gt;，直接在 Grafana 中获取所需技术帮助的新方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您曾经深入了解仪表板或配置数据源并遇到困难，您就会知道停止正在做的事情、打开浏览器选项卡并搜索文档以找到所需的答案是多么令人沮丧。虽然这些文档很棒并且介绍了大量细节，但它们也位于 Grafana 之外。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过交互式学习，我们将有用的情境学习资源引入 Grafana 平台本身，因此您可以快速轻松地找到所需内容 - 无需上下文切换。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“560”height =“315”src =&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZB_T2yQMR20&#39;title =“YouTube视频播放器”frameborder =“0”allow =“加速计;自动播放;剪贴板写入;加密媒体;陀螺仪;画中画;网络共享”referrerpolicy =“strict-origin-when-cross-origin”allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-we-built-interactive-learning&#34;&gt;我们为什么建立交互式学习&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的目标很简单：在最需要的地方提供帮助。我们不想让您离开 Grafana 的工作流程，而是希望为您提供正确的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦我们意识到什么是可能的，这个想法就变成了更大的事情。因为我们可以在 Grafana 本身内部渲染帮助文本，所以我们突然可以访问 Grafana 的完整运行时和文档对象模型（或 DOM，这是用户界面本身的结构）。这意味着帮助不必是静态的；它可以是动态的、上下文相关的，甚至是&lt;strong&gt;交互式&lt;/strong&gt;的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1093x547/8b49769f7b/interactive-learning-recommended-documenation.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1093x547/8b49769f7b/interactive-learning-recommended-documenation.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;显示 Grafana 中交互式学习的推荐文档功能的屏幕截图。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started-with-interactive-learning&#34;&gt;交互式学习入门&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/19/grafana-12-3-release-all-the-latest-features/ 的一部分，交互式学习在所有版本的 Grafana 中提供公共预览版&#34;&gt;Grafana 12.3 版本&lt;/a&gt;。您可以使用&lt;code&gt;interactiveLearning&lt;/code&gt; 功能标志启用它，或者通过搜索&lt;strong&gt;交互式学习&lt;/strong&gt;直接从插件目录安装它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，您将通过单击 Grafana 右上角的问号图标找到新的交互式学习体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/548x73/ba66b2ddde/interactive-learning-help-icon.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/548x73/ba66b2ddde/interactive-learning-help-icon.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana UI 的屏幕截图，帮助图标周围有一个红色圆圈，看起来像一个问号。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一直存在的相同帮助按钮。在交互式学习之前，它只是提供了一些指向我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;或&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;社区论坛&lt;/a&gt;等地方的链接。现在，它会打开一个侧面板，为您提供上下文帮助、产品内文档，甚至指导学习之旅，所有这些都无需离开 Grafana。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-interactive-learning-does&#34;&gt;交互式学习的作用&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您打开侧面板时，您看到的内容取决于您在 Grafana 中的位置；内容完全是上下文感知的。无论您是查看仪表板、编辑数据源还是创建可视化，Grafana 都会显示与您当时正在做的事情相关的文档和学习材料。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这不仅仅是静态文本。您将看到直接在 Grafana 中呈现的完整文档，其中包含图像、视频和分步示例。不再需要在选项卡之间跳转或尝试记住刚刚阅读的内容。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1094x717/7901c2cd88/interactive-learning-grafana-data-sources-resources.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1094x717/7901c2cd88/interactive-learning-grafana-data-sources-resources.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana UI 的屏幕截图，显示 Grafana 数据源的文档文本和视频资源。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;interactive-learning-guides&#34;&gt;交互式学习指南&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还推出了一种新型学习内容：&lt;strong&gt;交互式学习指南&lt;/strong&gt;。这些内容直接内置于文档中，并指导您逐步完成任务，从 Grafana UI 中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;每个指南都将内容分解为简单、具体的步骤，有些步骤还包括&lt;strong&gt;演示&lt;/strong&gt;和/或&lt;strong&gt;执行&lt;/strong&gt;功能。 &lt;strong&gt;显示&lt;/strong&gt;突出显示相关的 UI 元素并添加额外的上下文。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1666x1014/8de6bda836/interactive-learning-show-me-gif.gif/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1666x1014/8de6bda836/interactive-learning-show-me-gif.gif/m/&#34;alt=&#34;GIF 演示 Grafana 交互式学习中的 Show Me 功能。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do It&lt;/strong&gt; 函数会为您执行一项操作，例如单击按钮或填写字段。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1666x1014/510fc0a73e/interactive-learning-do-it-gif.gif/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1666x1014/510fc0a73e/interactive-learning-do-it-gif.gif/m/&#34;alt=&#34;GIF 演示 Grafana 交互式学习中的 Do It 功能。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您还可以一次运行整个交互部分来观看整个流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您想查看实际的交互式学习指南，请尝试&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/d/to6j8mh/grafana-play-home?doc=bundled:prometheus-grafana-101&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Prometheus 101 教程&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;，该教程将引导您完成第一个 Prometheus 的设置Grafana 中的数据源和仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1232x839/30d82df244/interactive-learning-prometheus-tutorial.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1232x839/30d82df244/interactive-learning-prometheus-tutorial.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana UI 的屏幕截图，包含 Prometheus 101 教程的步骤 1。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;smarter-context-aware-help&#34;&gt;更智能、上下文感知的帮助&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;交互式学习由两个组件提供支持：前端插件和我们称为&lt;strong&gt;推荐器&lt;/strong&gt;的服务。推荐器具有上下文感知能力，将提供与您和您正在学习的内容最有可能相关的帮助和交互式学习指南在 Grafana 中继续工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认情况下，交互式学习完全在&lt;strong&gt;离线模式&lt;/strong&gt;下运行，这意味着它仍然可以提供出色的基于上下文的帮助，而无需向外部发送任何数据。如果您选择启用推荐服务，Grafana 可以提供更加量身定制的文档和教程来匹配您当前的任务，同时尊重您的隐私。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next-for-interactive-learning&#34;&gt;交互式学习的下一步发展&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这仅仅是开始。我们已经在探索一些令人兴奋的方向来实现此功能的下一步：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;自定义交互式指南：&lt;/strong&gt;这将使您能够在 Grafana 内创建自己的交互式指南，以帮助新团队成员入职或逐步完成内部工作流程。如果您或您的团队认为这很有价值，我们很乐意在我们的&lt;a href=&#34;https://slack.grafana.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;社区 Slack&lt;/a&gt; 或&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;社区论坛&lt;/a&gt;上听取您的意见。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;与 Grafana Assistant 集成&lt;/strong&gt;：我们正在探索如何将 Grafana Cloud 中由人工智能驱动的代理 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/10/08/grafana-assistant-ga-assistant-investigations-preview/&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant&lt;/a&gt; 的功能与引导式学习相结合，让您更轻松地探索和理解数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/469x455/925b6ea74e/interactive-learning-assistant.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/469x455/925b6ea74e/interactive-learning-assistant.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana UI 的屏幕截图，其中文字为“询问助手”，然后概述了导航 Grafana Cloud、了解仪表板和数据源等关键区域以及找到界面的后续步骤。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;研讨会模式：&lt;/strong&gt;这将作为现场会议，演示者可以逐步指导参与者使用 Grafana。非常适合团队入职、内部培训或社区研讨会。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1236x1248/c18109b987/interactive-learning-live-session-qr-code.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1236x1248/c18109b987/interactive-learning-live-session-qr-code.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana UI 的屏幕截图，其中有一个框，上面写着“实时会话”和二维码。&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;try-interactive-learning-today&#34;&gt;立即尝试交互式学习&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一个很好的入门方法是&lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;尝试 Grafana Play 中的全新交互式学习体验&lt;/a&gt;，这是我们用于测试和学习 Grafana 的沙箱环境，托管在 Grafana Cloud 上。 Play 中默认启用交互式学习，并附带介绍性交互式学习指南，引导您了解 Play 所提供的所有内容。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;或者，如果您准备好立即开始在自己的 Grafana 实例中使用此功能，请按照&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/12/02/contextual-in-product-guidance-for-every-grafana-user-a-closer-look-at-interactive-learning/#getting-started-with-interactive-learning&#34;&gt;交互式学习入门&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;中的说明进行操作上面的部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，与 Grafana 本身一样，交互式学习插件是&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-pathfinder-app&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;开源&lt;/a&gt;。此功能从第一天起就受到社区意见的影响，我们很乐意接受贡献，无论是一般反馈还是改进想法。我们迫不及待地想知道交互式学习的下一步发展。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Improve service reliability and ops culture with Grafana Cloud Service Center】使用 Grafana 云服务中心提高服务可靠性和运营文化</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/12/01/improve-service-reliability-and-ops-culture-with-grafana-cloud-service-center/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Today’s engineering organizations are built around service ownership. Service owners are accountable for keeping their services reliable, performant, and ready to scale. But no service operates in isolation; every team depends on others, and those dependencies form a complex web that can be hard to see, let alone understand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To truly deliver reliable systems, you need visibility not only into how your own service performs, but also how it affects others. A slowdown in one service can ripple across the stack, impacting customers and the engineers responsible for keeping things running. Understanding these relationships helps teams make better decisions about managing on-call rotations, tackling technical debt, and shipping new features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And there&amp;rsquo;s another pitfall that can come from this service-based approach: engineers often find themselves burning out under constant on-call pressure. Pages pile up, incidents repeat, alert storms never end, and the same people get overloaded. Engineers experience burnout when rotations aren’t balanced, services lack clear reliability goals, and teams aren’t using notification signals like SLOs to guide improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The result? Teams are reactive instead of proactive, and systems are hard to trust.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These combined pressures can have deep, negative impacts on an organization, which is why we&amp;rsquo;re excited to introduce you to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-slo-app/latest/service-center/&#34;&gt;Service Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, a new Grafana Cloud feature designed to improve service reliability and operational culture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BnHMsB20b5A&#39; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;service-center-a-new-way-to-see-and-manage-your-services&#34;&gt;Service Center: A new way to see and manage your services&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Service Center serves as a comprehensive hub for all service-related activities. It establishes a solid foundation of operational service data, empowering teams to monitor performance trends, minimize disruptive alerts, analyze past incidents for ongoing service reliability enhancements, and understand on-call page load to help prevent engineer fatigue. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this unified view, your teams can define their services with the same labels and identifiers that already exist in their systems. Once a service is defined, Grafana Cloud automatically builds a dedicated service page, filled with key information and direct links to all the relevant areas across Grafana:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLOs&lt;/strong&gt; with clear summary data to understand how reliability is trending&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alerts&lt;/strong&gt; with quick insight into current or recurring issues&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dashboards&lt;/strong&gt; that visualize performance metrics in real time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incidents&lt;/strong&gt; for context on recent or ongoing disruptions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On-call and paging information&lt;/strong&gt; to know who’s responding and how often they’ve been paged&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Teams can quickly discern whether services are performing well, identify areas requiring attention, and set priorities for investing in increased reliability over adding more features. These operational reviews translate data into actionable insights, reduce manual effort, and help consistently cultivate a stronger reliability culture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/850x791/9d1f29f6c6/service-center-ui.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/850x791/9d1f29f6c6/service-center-ui.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud Service Center UI, including panels for icnidents, SLOs, alerting, and IRM&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Service Center makes these conversations easier, more data-driven, and more impactful. It transforms what used to be scattered across dashboards and tools into a single, shared view of operational health.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And by centralizing data that used to live across different tools and dashboards, Service Center helps teams quickly answer critical questions such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How is our service performing this week?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Who owns it, and who’s on call?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What’s broken, and what’s improving?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What should we focus on next?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-behind-the-scenes-example-how-we-use-service-center&#34;&gt;A behind-the-scenes example: How we use Service Center&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate how Service Center can help in practical terms, I want to share some internal examples. Afterall, we&amp;rsquo;re big believers that operational excellence reviews are the cornerstone of keeping services performant and engineers happy, so it makes sense that the Grafana SLO team is already using Service Center as the primary source of information during our weekly reviews.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;setting-and-achieving-goals&#34;&gt;Setting and achieving goals&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re aggressive with our SLOs—never becoming complacent and always looking to work with our remaining error budget so our engineers can focus on other services, adding new features, and not treating every alert as a fire drill. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But how should you decide where to set your SLOs?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We recommend starting with a 99% service availability target as an achievable SLO and adjusting up or down based on each service’s requirements and real world performance. “Three nines” or 99.9% is an industry standard baseline for high availability services, although some service owners may wish to achieve even greater availability targets. You can also use our predictive functionality to see the probability that you&amp;rsquo;ll actually hit your SLO.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Setting lofty but achievable service targets allows our engineers to continue to improve our reliability without burning out. If you notice that you have SLOs that never burn any budget, you could be tracking the wrong indicators or your target percentage isn’t aggressive enough. The Grafana SLO team reviews our SLOs weekly, walking through each service page to view the prior week’s performance. We tune our SLOs and alerts to ensure we are continuously providing a better experience for our customers without generating too much noise. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;improving-incident-response-operations&#34;&gt;Improving incident response operations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Incidents are the next area we focus on. All Incidents tagged to our service within the service page’s timeframe are reviewed. It’s very easy after an incident is resolved to go back to your daily tasks—engineers are tired, the service is “fixed,” and budget stops burning. But often these fixes are done in haste with the intention to go back and put the real fixes in later. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Depending on the nature of the incident, better SLIs, alerts, or follow up changes may be needed. Reviewing previous incidents and ensuring their tasks are completed is a major part of the SLO team’s operational review. We want to learn from our incidents and prevent reoccurrence; scheduled fixes are always easier than 3 a.m. pages. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;preventing-burnout&#34;&gt;Preventing burnout&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our final service check is to ensure none of our engineers are getting burned out. Our service page shows how often each engineer was paged, and how many alert groups have fired during the set time period. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We review the Grafana Cloud IRM alert groups for each of our engineers. If one person is taking the brunt of on-call work, they could be suffering in silence. No one wants to call out that they&amp;rsquo;re getting too much work, especially when they designed parts of the service they’re getting paged on. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ensuring there is an even spread of work going to your engineers will help prevent burnout, increasing a team’s overall engineering culture. Service Center makes it very easy for us to gauge workload balancing and manually rotate our schedule if we’re having a tough on-call week. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-stakeholder-self-service-landing-page&#34;&gt;A stakeholder self service landing page&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Defining our services within the Service Center lets our engineers focus on building and fixing, and it provides stakeholders with direct access to the information they need. The Service Center eliminates the need for teams to compile resources for stakeholders, providing instant updates on service performance and reliability. Stakeholders can access dedicated service pages for performance insights, identify on-call personnel for immediate issues, and review cost or resource consumption dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Previously, stakeholders relied on chat channels for assistance, requiring our team to manually gather monthly/quarterly data. By defining services within the Service Center, engineers can prioritize development and issue resolution, while stakeholders gain direct access to essential information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started-with-service-center-today&#34;&gt;Get started with Service Center today&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Service Center is free for all Grafana Cloud customers. Service pages are created by users or can be pulled in via our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/service-center/services/&#34;&gt;Backstage module&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The pages utilize the &lt;code&gt;service_name&lt;/code&gt; label, so the first thing you need to do to get started is to ensure you are labeling your SLOs, alerts, and incidents with the &lt;code&gt;service_name&lt;/code&gt; label that is set in the Service Center identifier object. Dashboards are then synced via dashboard tags, and OnCall information is derived from the team that is added to the service definition during creation. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While we don&amp;rsquo;t yet have a connection to your observability services in Grafana Cloud (Application Observability, Kubernetes Monitoring, Frontend Observability, Cloud Provider Observability, and Database  Observability ), we do utilize the static metadata links for our services to add the URLs to our Kubernetes Monitoring dashboards and entity catalog pages. This makes for easy navigation to the opinionated areas for our services that Grafana Cloud provides out of the box. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about how to use Service Center, check out &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-slo-app/latest/service-center/&#34;&gt;our docs&lt;/a&gt; today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当今的工程组织是围绕服务所有权构建的。服务所有者有责任保持其服务可靠、高性能且易于扩展。但没有任何服务是孤立运行的；每个团队都依赖于其他团队，而这些依赖关系形成了一个复杂的网络，很难看到，更不用说理解了。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要真正交付可靠的系统，您不仅需要了解自己的服务如何执行，还需要了解它如何影响其他服务。一项服务的速度下降可能会波及整个堆栈，影响客户和负责保持事物运行的工程师。了解这些关系有助于团队在管理待命轮换、解决技术债务和发布新功能方面做出更好的决策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这种基于服务的方法可能存在另一个陷阱：工程师经常发现自己在持续的待命压力下精疲力竭。页面堆积，事件重复，警报风暴永远不会结束，同样的人也会超负荷。当轮换不平衡、服务缺乏明确的可靠性目标以及团队不使用 SLO 等通知信号来指导改进时，工程师就会感到精疲力竭。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结果呢？团队是被动的而不是主动的，系统很难信任。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些综合压力可能会对组织产生深远的负面影响，因此我们很高兴向您介绍&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-slo-app/latest/service-center/&#34;&gt;服务中心&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;，这是一项新的 Grafana Cloud 功能，旨在提高服务可靠性和运营文化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“560”height =“315”src =&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/BnHMsB20b5A&#39;title =“YouTube视频播放器”frameborder =“0”allow =“加速计;自动播放;剪贴板写入;加密媒体;陀螺仪;画中画;网络共享”referrerpolicy =“strict-origin-when-cross-origin”allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;service-center-a-new-way-to-see-and-manage-your-services&#34;&gt;服务中心：查看和管理服务的新方式&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;服务中心是所有服务相关活动的综合中心。它为运营服务数据奠定了坚实的基础，使团队能够监控性能趋势、最大限度地减少破坏性警报、分析过去的事件以持续增强服务可靠性，并了解待命页面负载以帮助防止工程师疲劳。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过这个统一的视图，您的团队可以使用其系统中已存在的相同标签和标识符来定义其服务。定义服务后，Grafana Cloud 会自动构建专用服务页面，其中包含关键信息以及指向 Grafana 所有相关区域的直接链接：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SLO&lt;/strong&gt;具有清晰的汇总数据，可帮助您了解可靠性趋势&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;警报&lt;/strong&gt;可快速洞察当前或重复出现的问题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;仪表板&lt;/strong&gt;，可在 r 中可视化性能指标实时&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;事件&lt;/strong&gt;了解最近或持续中断的背景&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;待命和寻呼信息&lt;/strong&gt;，了解谁在回复以及他们被寻呼的频率&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;团队可以快速辨别服务是否表现良好，确定需要关注的领域，并确定投资于提高可靠性而不是添加更多功能的优先级。这些运营审查将数据转化为可行的见解，减少人工工作，并帮助持续培养更强大的可靠性文化。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/850x791/9d1f29f6c6/service-center-ui.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/850x791/9d1f29f6c6/service-center-ui.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana 云服务中心 UI，包括 icnidents、SLO、警报和 IRM 面板&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;服务中心使这些对话变得更容易、更具数据驱动性且更具影响力。它将过去分散在仪表板和工具中的内容转变为单一、共享的运营状况视图。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过集中过去跨不同工具和仪表板的数据，服务中心可以帮助团队快速回答关键问题，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;本周我们的服务表现如何？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;谁拥有它，谁在值班？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;哪些方面有问题，哪些方面有改进？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;接下来我们应该关注什么？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-behind-the-scenes-example-how-we-use-service-center&#34;&gt;幕后示例：我们如何使用服务中心&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了说明服务中心如何在实际中提供帮助，我想分享一些内部示例。毕竟，我们坚信卓越运营审核是保持服务绩效和工程师满意的基石，因此 Grafana SLO 团队在每周审核期间使用服务中心作为主要信息来源是有道理的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;setting-and-achieving-goals&#34;&gt;设定并实现目标&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们对 SLO 非常积极，从不自满，始终致力于利用剩余的错误预算，以便我们的工程师可以专注于其他服务、添加新功能，而不是将每个警报都视为防火练习。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是您应该如何决定在何处设置 SLO？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们建议从 99% 的服务可用性目标开始作为可实现的 SLO，并根据每项服务的要求和实际性能进行上下调整。 “三个九”或 99.9% 是高可用性服务的行业标准基线，尽管一些服务所有者可能希望实现更高的可用性目标。您还可以使用我们的预测功能来查看您实际达到 SLO 的概率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;设定崇高但可实现的服务目标使我们的工程师能够继续提高我们的可靠性，而不会精疲力尽。如果您发现 SLO 从未消耗任何预算，则您可能跟踪了错误的指标，或者您的目标百分比不够激进。 Grafana SLO 团队每周审核我们的 SLO，浏览每个服务页面以查看前一周的表现。我们调整 SLO 和警报，以确保我们不断为客户提供更好的体验，而不会产生太多噪音。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;improving-incident-response-operations&#34;&gt;改进事件响应操作&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;事件是我们关注的下一个领域。在服务页面的时间范围内标记到我们的服务的所有事件都会受到审查。事件解决后，很容易返回日常任务——工程师很累，服务已“修复”，预算也不再消耗。但通常这些修复都是仓促完成的，目的是稍后返回并进行真正的修复。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;根据事件的性质，可能需要更好的 SLI、警报或后续更改。审查以前的事件并确保其任务完成是 SLO 团队运营审查的主要部分。我们希望从事件中吸取教训并防止再次发生；预定的修复总是比凌晨 3 点的页面更容易。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;preventing-burnout&#34;&gt;防止倦怠&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的最终服务检查是为了确保我们的工程师不会精疲力尽。我们的服务页面显示了每个工程师被寻呼的频率，以及在设定的时间段内触发了多少个警报组。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们会审核每位工程师的 Grafana Cloud IRM 警报组。如果一个人在值班工作中首当其冲，他们可能会默默承受痛苦。没有人愿意说他们的工作量太大了，尤其是当他们设计了他们被寻呼的部分服务时。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确保工程师均匀分配工作将有助于防止倦怠，增强团队的整体工程文化。服务中心使我们可以轻松衡量工作负载平衡，并在我们的待命周遇到困难时手动轮换我们的日程安排。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-stakeholder-self-service-landing-page&#34;&gt;利益相关者自助服务登陆页面&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在服务中心定义我们的服务可以让我们的工程师专注于构建和修复，并且让利益相关者可以直接访问他们所需的信息。服务中心消除了团队为利益相关者编译资源的需要，提供服务性能和可靠性的即时更新。利益相关者可以访问专门的服务页面以获取绩效见解、确定待命人员以解决紧急问题，并查看成本或资源消耗仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以前，利益相关者依靠聊天渠道寻求帮助，要求g 我们的团队手动收集每月/季度数据。通过在服务中心内定义服务，工程师可以优先考虑开发和问题解决，而利益相关者则可以直接访问重要信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-started-with-service-center-today&#34;&gt;立即开始使用服务中心&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana 服务中心对所有 Grafana Cloud 客户免费。服务页面由用户创建，也可以通过我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/service-center/services/&#34;&gt;后台模块&lt;/a&gt;拉入。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些页面使用 &lt;code&gt;service_name&lt;/code&gt; 标签，因此您需要做的第一件事就是确保使用在服务中心标识符对象中设置的 &lt;code&gt;service_name&lt;/code&gt; 标签来标记 SLO、警报和事件。然后，仪表板通过仪表板标签进行同步，并且 OnCall 信息源自在创建过程中添加到服务定义中的团队。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然我们尚未连接到 Grafana Cloud 中的可观测性服务（应用程序可观测性、Kubernetes 监控、前端可观测性、云提供商可观测性和数据库可观测性），但我们确实利用服务的静态元数据链接将 URL 添加到我们的 Kubernetes 监控仪表板和实体目录页面。这使得我们可以轻松导航到 Grafana Cloud 开箱即用的服务的固执己见的区域。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要详细了解如何使用服务中心，请立即查看&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-slo-app/latest/service-center/&#34;&gt;我们的文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to monitor Amazon Bedrock AgentCore AI agent infrastructure in Grafana Cloud】如何监控 Grafana Cloud 中的 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore AI 代理基础设施</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/11/28/how-to-monitor-amazon-bedrock-agentcore-ai-agent-infrastructure-in-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Modern AI agents are now highly advanced, frequently becoming essential components of engineering workflows and deployment pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, operating these systems often feels like trying to navigate a ship through a dense fog. When an agent errors, slows down, or consumes excessive resources, engineers find themselves adrift, lacking the navigational charts needed to diagnose the problem. The absence of deep insight makes debugging, performance tuning, and cost management unnecessarily difficult.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To address this, AWS&amp;rsquo; managed AI agent service, Amazon Bedrock AgentCore, emits rich telemetry data you can then use for deep observability insights.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we will explore how to leverage OpenTelemetry, Amazon CloudWatch, and Grafana Cloud to gain full, end-to-end visibility. We’ll show you how to build the dashboards you need to track essential performance and financial metrics like latency, token usage, and tool execution reliability, enabling you to confidently steer your production AI agents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This is the second part of our complete guide to observing AI agents on Amazon Bedrock AgentCore. While this post is about monitoring the infrastructure layer, the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/26/how-to-monitor-ai-agent-applications-on-amazon-bedrock-agentcore-with-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;first part&lt;/a&gt; is focused on the application layer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-amazon-bedrock-agentcore&#34;&gt;What is Amazon Bedrock AgentCore?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS Bedrock AgentCore is an AWS offering that allows developers to build and deploy generative AI agents, simplifying the creation of applications that automate complex tasks, interact with users, and reason over data. It provides a serverless runtime for these agents, integrating large language models (LLMs) with data sources and tools without requiring you to manage infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-you-should-use-grafana-cloud-to-monitor-amazon-bedrock-agentcore&#34;&gt;Why you should use Grafana Cloud to monitor Amazon Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Monitoring Amazon Bedrock AgentCore in Grafana Cloud has lots of advantages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First of all, with Grafana Cloud you gain a powerful, unified platform designed to provide comprehensive observability for your entire AWS ecosystem, from infrastructure to apps. This means you can centrally monitor your underlying AWS infrastructure—compute, storage, and networking resources—alongside the performance and operational health of all your Bedrock AgentCore agents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Crucially, Grafana Cloud eliminates data silos by enabling you to aggregate metrics from agents deployed across all your different AWS accounts and all AWS regions. This single-pane-of-glass view ensures you get a holistic understanding of your multi-account, multi-region agent deployment in one place. This unified approach simplifies complex monitoring challenges, accelerates troubleshooting, and ensures consistent operational standards across your entire AI infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;cloud-provider-observability-with-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;Cloud Provider Observability with Grafana Cloud&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another significant advantage of centralizing your monitoring data within Grafana Cloud is the immediate, out-of-the-box visibility you gain. From the moment your data starts flowing, you are equipped with pre-built, insightful views. Specifically, for monitoring your Amazon Bedrock AgentCore agents, you can leverage the robust capabilities of the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/monitor-cloud-provider/&#34;&gt;Cloud Provider Observability&lt;/a&gt;  application in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This application provides a dedicated, pre-configured dashboard and a set of alerts tailored to the metrics emitted by your AWS resources, including your Bedrock agents. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to spend valuable time building dashboards from scratch or manually configuring alert rules. Instead, you get immediate access to key performance indicators such as agent invocation rates, execution latencies, and errors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This comprehensive, ready-to-use monitoring app allows you to quickly assess the health, performance, and operational status of your generative AI agents, ensuring they are operating efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1483x325/66b47312f5/bedrock-infra-cloud-provider.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1483x325/66b47312f5/bedrock-infra-cloud-provider.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Amazon Bedrock AgentCore agents monitored in the Cloud Provider Observability app in Grafana Cloud&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The dashboard, as shown above, allows for filtering by various parameters such as data source, job, account, or region. It also provides a comprehensive summary of key metrics, including error and throttle rates, in addition to the total count of Bedrock input and output tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1461x971/c2b534f66c/bedrock-infra-throttle-error.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1461x971/c2b534f66c/bedrock-infra-throttle-error.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud UI showing panels to track different error and throttle rates&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The dashboard&amp;rsquo;s subsequent section offers a comprehensive overview of all your Bedrock AgentCore agents, detailing their duration, invocations, latency, and rates of error and throttling. You can narrow down the results in this table by job, account, region, or name using the text filter located above the table.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clicking the name of an agent will take you to a detailed view presenting key metrics specifically filtered for that agent. The image below highlights the key metrics available on the dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1480x955/77e53cc4b8/bedrock-infra-latency-duration-more.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1480x955/77e53cc4b8/bedrock-infra-latency-duration-more.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud UI including panels for latency, duration, invocations, token counts per model, CPU used, and memory used&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-get-started-or-how-to-get-your-data-in-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;How to get started (or How to get your data in Grafana Cloud)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can start monitoring your AWS Bedrock AgentCore agents in Grafana Cloud by configuring &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/monitor-cloud-provider/aws/cloudwatch-metrics/config-cw-metric-streams/&#34;&gt;CloudWatch metric streams&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;step-1-configure-metrics-streaming-in-aws&#34;&gt;Step 1: Configure Metrics streaming in AWS&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Go to Amazon Data Firehose, then on Firehose streams, and click &lt;strong&gt;Create Firehose stream&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Select &lt;strong&gt;Kinesis Data Streams&lt;/strong&gt; as source and &lt;strong&gt;HTTP Endpoint&lt;/strong&gt; as the Destination.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enter a name for the Firehose.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enter the endpoint name according to Grafana Cloud provider’ &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/monitor-cloud-provider/aws/cloudwatch-metrics/config-cw-metric-streams/#data-firehose-delivery-stream-component&#34;&gt;docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enter an access key according to Grafana Cloud provider’ &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/monitor-cloud-provider/aws/cloudwatch-metrics/config-cw-metric-streams/#data-firehose-delivery-stream-component&#34;&gt;docs&lt;/a&gt;, which is &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;prometheus id&amp;gt;:&amp;lt;auth token&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Create Firehose stream&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Then move to &lt;strong&gt;CloudWatch&lt;/strong&gt;, click Streams in the left navigation and click &lt;strong&gt;Create metric stream&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Select &lt;strong&gt;Custom setup with Firehose&lt;/strong&gt; as the Destination.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click the Amazon Data Firehose stream you just created in step 6.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Select &lt;strong&gt;All Metrics&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Select metrics&lt;/strong&gt; and add the &lt;strong&gt;AWS/Bedrock-AgentCore&lt;/strong&gt; namespace.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Create metric stream&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;step-2-configure-metrics-streaming-in-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;Step 2: Configure Metrics streaming in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can start monitoring your AWS Bedrock AgentCore agents in Grafana Cloud by configuring &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/monitor-cloud-provider/aws/cloudwatch-metrics/config-cw-metric-streams/&#34;&gt;CloudWatch metric streams.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;step-3-view-your-data&#34;&gt;Step 3: View your data&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Navigate to your Grafana Cloud stack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In the navigation, click on &lt;strong&gt;Observability&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Cloud provider &amp;gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;AWS&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You should start seeing &lt;strong&gt;AWS/Bedrock-AgentCore&lt;/strong&gt; in the &lt;strong&gt;Services&lt;/strong&gt; tab shortly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x532/e458b7a518/bedrock-infra-services-tab.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x532/e458b7a518/bedrock-infra-services-tab.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. Click on the name and view your data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s it! Once you have everything set up, your AWS telemetry will automatically get fed into your dashboards, giving you full visibility into your AI agents from one dashboard in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about how you can use Cloud Provider Observability to monitor your entire AWS environment, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/monitor-cloud-provider/&#34;&gt;Cloud Provider Observability documentation&lt;/a&gt; and read about &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/cloud-monitoring-aws/&#34;&gt;AWS Observability&lt;/a&gt; in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;现代人工智能代理现在非常先进，经常成为工程工作流程和部署管道的重要组成部分。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然而，操作这些系统通常感觉就像试图在浓雾中驾驶船只。当代理出错、速度减慢或消耗过多资源时，工程师会发现自己陷入困境，缺乏诊断问题所需的导航图。缺乏深入的洞察力会使调试、性能调整和成本管理变得不必要的困难。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了解决这个问题，AWS 的托管 AI 代理服务 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore 会发出丰富的遥测数据，然后您可以将其用于深入的可观察性见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将探讨如何利用 OpenTelemetry、Amazon CloudWatch 和 Grafana Cloud 来获得完整的端到端可见性。我们将向您展示如何构建跟踪基本性能和财务指标（例如延迟、令牌使用情况和工具执行可靠性）所需的仪表板，使您能够自信地引导生产 AI 代理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;这是我们在 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore 上观察 AI 代理的完整指南的第二部分。虽然这篇文章是关于监控基础设施层的，但&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/26/how-to-monitor-ai-agent-applications-on-amazon-bedrock-agentcore-with-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;第一部分&lt;/a&gt;重点关注应用程序层。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-amazon-bedrock-agentcore&#34;&gt;什么是 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS Bedrock AgentCore 是一项 AWS 产品，允许开发人员构建和部署生成式 AI 代理，从而简化自动执行复杂任务、与用户交互以及数据推理的应用程序的创建。它为这些代理提供无服务器运行时，将大型语言模型 (LLM) 与数据源和工具集成，而无需您管理基础设施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-you-should-use-grafana-cloud-to-monitor-amazon-bedrock-agentcore&#34;&gt;为什么您应该使用 Grafana Cloud 监控 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Grafana Cloud 中监控 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore 有很多优势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，借助 Grafana Cloud，您可以获得一个强大的统一平台，旨在为从基础设施到应用程序的整个 AWS 生态系统提供全面的可观察性。这意味着您可以集中监控底层 AWS 基础设施（计算、存储和网络资源）以及所有 Bedrock AgentCore 代理的性能和运行状况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;至关重要的是，Grafana Cloud 使您能够汇总跨所有不同 AWS 账户和所有 AWS 区域部署的代理的指标，从而消除了数据孤岛。这种单一管理平台视图可确保您在一个地方全面了解多账户、多区域代理部署。这种统一的方法简化了复杂的监控挑战，加快了故障排除速度，并确保整个系统保持一致的操作标准。电子人工智能基础设施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;cloud-provider-observability-with-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;使用 Grafana Cloud 实现云提供商可观察性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在 Grafana Cloud 中集中监控数据的另一个显着优势是您可以获得即时、开箱即用的可见性。从数据开始流动的那一刻起，您就拥有了预先构建的、富有洞察力的视图。具体来说，为了监控您的 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore 代理，您可以利用 Grafana Cloud 中的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/monitor-cloud-provider/&#34;&gt;云提供商可观察性&lt;/a&gt;应用程序的强大功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此应用程序提供了一个专用的预配置仪表板和一组针对您的 AWS 资源（包括您的 Bedrock 代理）发出的指标量身定制的警报。您不必花费宝贵的时间从头开始构建仪表板或手动配置警报规则。相反，您可以立即访问关键性能指标，例如代理调用率、执行延迟和错误。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这款全面、即用型的监控应用程序可让您快速评估生成式 AI 代理的运行状况、性能和运行状态，确保它们高效运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1483x325/66b47312f5/bedrock-infra-cloud-provider.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1483x325/66b47312f5/bedrock-infra-cloud-provider.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud 中的云提供商可观测性应用程序中监控的 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore 代理&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如上所示，仪表板允许按各种参数进行过滤，例如数据源、作业、帐户或区域。除了基岩输入和输出代币的总数之外，它还提供了关键指标的全面摘要，包括错误率和节流率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1461x971/c2b534f66c/bedrock-infra-throttle-error.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1461x971/c2b534f66c/bedrock-infra-throttle-error.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud UI 显示用于跟踪不同错误和节流率的面板&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;仪表板的后续部分提供了所有 Bedrock AgentCore 代理的全面概述，详细说明了它们的持续时间、调用、延迟以及错误率和限制。您可以按职位、帐户、地区缩小此表中的结果范围，或使用表格上方的文本过滤器命名。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;单击代理名称将进入详细视图，其中显示专门针对该代理筛选的关键指标。下图突出显示了仪表板上可用的关键指标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1480x955/77e53cc4b8/bedrock-infra-latency-duration-more.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1480x955/77e53cc4b8/bedrock-infra-latency-duration-more.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud UI，包括延迟、持续时间、调用、每个模型的令牌计数、使用的 CPU 和使用的内存面板&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-get-started-or-how-to-get-your-data-in-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;如何开始（或如何在 Grafana Cloud 中获取数据）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以通过配置 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/monitor-cloud-provider/aws/cloudwatch-metrics/config-cw-metric-streams/&#34;&gt;CloudWatch 指标流&lt;/a&gt;开始监控 Grafana Cloud 中的 AWS Bedrock AgentCore 代理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;step-1-configure-metrics-streaming-in-aws&#34;&gt;第 1 步：在 AWS 中配置指标流&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;转到 Amazon Data Firehose，然后在 Firehose 流上，点击&lt;strong&gt;创建 Firehose 流&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;选择 &lt;strong&gt;Kinesis Data Streams&lt;/strong&gt; 作为源，选择 &lt;strong&gt;HTTP 端点&lt;/strong&gt;作为目标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;输入 Firehose 的名称。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;根据 Grafana Cloud 提供商的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/monitor-cloud-provider/aws/cloudwatch-metrics/config-cw-metric-streams/#data-firehose-delivery-stream-component&#34;&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;输入端点名称。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;根据 Grafana Cloud 提供商的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/monitor-cloud-provider/aws/cloudwatch-metrics/config-cw-metric-streams/#data-firehose-delivery-stream-component&#34;&gt;文档&lt;/a&gt;输入访问密钥，即 &lt;code&gt;&lt;prometheus id&gt;:&lt;auth token&gt;&lt;/code&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;点击&lt;strong&gt;创建 Firehose 流&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;然后转到 &lt;strong&gt;CloudWatch&lt;/strong&gt;，点击左侧导航栏中的“流”，然后点击&lt;strong&gt;创建指标流&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;选择&lt;strong&gt;使用 Firehose 进行自定义设置&lt;/strong&gt;作为目标。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;点击您刚刚在第 6 步中创建的 Amazon Data Firehose 流。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;选择&lt;strong&gt;所有指标&lt;/strong&gt;或&lt;strong&gt;选择指标&lt;/strong&gt;并添加&lt;strong&gt;AWS/Bedrock-AgentCore&lt;/strong&gt;命名空间。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;点击&lt;strong&gt;创建指标流&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;step-2-configure-metrics-streaming-in-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;第 2 步：在 Grafana Cloud 中配置指标流。&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以通过配置 &lt;a href=&#34;/ 开始监控 Grafana Cloud 中的 AWS Bedrock AgentCore 代理docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/monitor-cloud-provider/aws/cloudwatch-metrics/config-cw-metric-streams/&#34;&gt;CloudWatch 指标流。&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;step-3-view-your-data&#34;&gt;第 3 步：查看您的数据&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;导航到您的 Grafana 云堆栈。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在导航中，点击&lt;strong&gt;可观察性&lt;/strong&gt; &gt; &lt;strong&gt;云提供商&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;AWS&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;您应该很快就会开始在&lt;strong&gt;服务&lt;/strong&gt;选项卡中看到&lt;strong&gt;AWS/Bedrock-AgentCore&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x532/e458b7a518/bedrock-infra-services-tab.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x532/e458b7a518/bedrock-infra-services-tab.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4.单击名称并查看您的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;就是这样！一旦您完成所有设置，您的 AWS 遥测数据将自动输入到您的仪表板中，让您可以从 Grafana Cloud 中的一个仪表板全面了解您的 AI 代理。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要详细了解如何使用云提供商可观测性来监控整个 AWS 环境，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastruct/monitor-cloud-provider/&#34;&gt;云提供商可观测性文档&lt;/a&gt;并阅读 Grafana Cloud 中的 &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/cloud-monitoring-aws/&#34;&gt;AWS 可观测性&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to monitor AI agent applications on Amazon Bedrock AgentCore with Grafana Cloud】如何使用 Grafana Cloud 监控 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore 上的 AI 代理应用程序</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/11/26/how-to-monitor-ai-agent-applications-on-amazon-bedrock-agentcore-with-grafana-cloud/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s AI agents have grown increasingly sophisticated, moving into production environments and becoming integral parts of engineering workflows. But these agents can also be black boxes for engineers, which makes observability more critical than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Without proper monitoring, you&amp;rsquo;re often left feeling like you&amp;rsquo;re flying blind as you try to debug agent failures, understand performance bottlenecks, and track costs. We want to put our users back in control, so in this tutorial you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to deploy an AI agent on Amazon Bedrock AgentCore with full observability powered by OpenTelemetry and &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More specifically, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. Deploy AI agents on AWS Bedrock AgentCore for managed, scalable production runtime&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. Instrument agents with OpenTelemetry using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openlit/openlit&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenLit&lt;/a&gt; for automatic, zero-code observability&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. Monitor agent performance in Grafana Cloud with AI Observability dashboards&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. Debug production issues using distributed tracing&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. Optimize costs by tracking token usage and model performance&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This post focuses on AI application observability. The second part of this guide will focus on &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/28/how-to-monitor-amazon-bedrock-agentcore-ai-agent-infrastructure-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;AI observability at the infrastructure layer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-is-amazon-bedrock-agentcore&#34;&gt;What is Amazon Bedrock AgentCore?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/bedrock/agentcore/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Amazon Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/a&gt; is a managed service that simplifies deploying and running AI agents in production. Think of it as a serverless runtime for your AI agents. You provide the agent code, and AWS handles the infrastructure, scaling, and execution environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Key benefits include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Managed infrastructure:&lt;/strong&gt; No need to provision servers or manage Kubernetes clusters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon Bedrock integration:&lt;/strong&gt; Native access to foundation models like Llama 3, Claude, and others&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Container-based deployment:&lt;/strong&gt; Package your agent with all dependencies using Docker&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enterprise-ready:&lt;/strong&gt; Built-in security, IAM integration, and compliance features&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AgentCore is particularly powerful for orchestration frameworks like CrewAI, LangGraph, or Strands, where coordinating multiple agents or complex workflows is necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-use-opentelemetry-for-ai-agents&#34;&gt;Why use OpenTelemetry for AI agents?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI agents can be notoriously difficult to debug. A single user query might trigger:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multiple LLM API calls&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tool invocations and external API requests&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-step reasoning chains&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Retry logic and error handling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When something goes wrong (or worse), when performance silently degrades, you need visibility into every step. To address this, we recommend using OpenTelemetry (&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OTel&lt;/a&gt;), the industry-standard observability framework, which provides unified instrumentation for distributed applications and infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For AI agents specifically, OpenTelemetry helps you answer critical questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which LLM calls are slowest?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How many tokens am I consuming per request?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Where are errors occurring in my agent workflow?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the end-to-end latency for user requests?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And while OpenTelemetry is powerful, manually instrumenting every LLM call and agent step is tedious and error-prone. This is where &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openlit/openlit&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenLit&lt;/a&gt; shines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenLit provides automatic instrumentation for AI frameworks:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Zero code changes required; wrap your Python command with &lt;code&gt;openlit-instrument&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automatically capture LLM calls (OpenAI, Anthropic, Bedrock, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support for agent frameworks (CrewAI, LangChain, LlamaIndex)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Export OpenTelemetry-compatible data to any OTLP backend&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;tutorial-deploy-and-monitor-a-crewai-agent&#34;&gt;Tutorial: deploy and monitor a CrewAI agent&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate how this works, let&amp;rsquo;s build a complete example: a research assistant agent powered by CrewAI and Meta&amp;rsquo;s Llama 3, deployed on AWS Bedrock AgentCore, with full observability in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;prerequisites&#34;&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before starting, ensure you have:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Python 3.12+** installed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;AWS CLI configured with credentials:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt; aws configure&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll need permissions for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Amazon ECR (Elastic Container Registry)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bedrock model access (specifically &lt;code&gt;meta.llama3-8b-instruct-v1:0&lt;/code&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. Grafana Cloud account (If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, you can &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;sign up for our forever-free tier&lt;/a&gt; now.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. AgentCore CLI installed:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;  python -m venv .venv &amp;amp;&amp;amp; source .venv/bin/activate&#xA;pip install bedrock-agentcore-starter-toolkit&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-1-create-a-crewai-agent&#34;&gt;Step 1: Create a CrewAI Agent&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s create an example AI Agent using CrewAI:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;import os&#xA;from bedrock_agentcore import BedrockAgentCoreApp&#xA;from crewai import Agent, Task, Crew, Process&#xA;# Initialize AgentCore runtime&#xA;app = BedrockAgentCoreApp()&#xA;# Define a simple research assistant agent&#xA;researcher = Agent(&#xA;role=&amp;#34;Research Assistant&amp;#34;,&#xA;goal=&amp;#34;Provide helpful, accurate answers, with concise summaries.&amp;#34;,&#xA;backstory=(&amp;#34;You are a knowledgeable research assistant who answers clearly &amp;#34;&#xA;&amp;#34;and cites facts when relevant.&amp;#34;),&#xA;# Use Llama 3 8B via AWS Bedrock&#xA;llm=&amp;#34;bedrock/meta.llama3-8b-instruct-v1:0&amp;#34;,&#xA;verbose=False,&#xA;max_iter=2&#xA;)&#xA;@app.entrypoint&#xA;def invoke(payload: dict):&#xA;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;AgentCore entrypoint. Expects {&amp;#39;prompt&amp;#39;: &amp;#39;&amp;#39;}&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&#xA;user_message = payload.get(&amp;#34;prompt&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;Hello!&amp;#34;)&#xA;task = Task(&#xA;description=user_message,&#xA;agent=researcher,&#xA;expected_output=&amp;#34;A helpful, well-structured response.&amp;#34;&#xA;)&#xA;crew = Crew(&#xA;agents=[researcher],&#xA;tasks=[task],&#xA;process=Process.sequential,&#xA;verbose=False,&#xA;)&#xA;result = crew.kickoff()&#xA;return {&amp;#34;result&amp;#34;: result.raw}&#xA;if __name__ == &amp;#34;__main__&amp;#34;:&#xA;app.run()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key components:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BedrockAgentCoreApp:&lt;/strong&gt; Integrates CrewAI with the Amazon Bedrock AgentCore runtime&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agent definition:&lt;/strong&gt; Single agent with a research assistant role using Llama 3&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;@app.entrypoint&lt;/code&gt;&lt;strong&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Decorator that marks the function as the agent&amp;rsquo;s entry point&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crew orchestration:&lt;/strong&gt; CrewAI manages task execution and agent coordination&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The agent accepts JSON input like &lt;code&gt;{&amp;quot;prompt&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;your question&amp;quot;}&lt;/code&gt; and returns a JSON response.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-2-configure-dependencies&#34;&gt;Step 2: Configure dependencies&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Create a requirements.txt that includes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;crewai&amp;gt;=1.0.0&#xA;openlit&amp;gt;=1.35&#xA;litellm&#xA;bedrock-agentcore&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-3-configure-agentcore-deployment&#34;&gt;Step 3: Configure AgentCore deployment&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Run the AgentCore configuration command:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;agentcore configure \&#xA;--deployment-type container \&#xA;--entrypoint crewai_agent.py \&#xA;--name crewai_agent \&#xA;--non-interactive&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This generates a &lt;code&gt;.bedrock_agentcore/crewai_agent/&lt;/code&gt; directory with:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;code&gt;Dockerfile&lt;/code&gt;: Container build configuration&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;code&gt;agent_config.json&lt;/code&gt;: Metadata for AgentCore&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-4-add-opentelemetry-configuration&#34;&gt;Step 4: Add OpenTelemetry configuration&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now comes the observability magic. Edit the generated Dockerfile at &lt;code&gt;.bedrock_agentcore/crewai_agent/Dockerfile&lt;/code&gt; and add these environment variables:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;dockerfile&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-dockerfile&#34;&gt;# Disable AWS ADOT observability to use OpenLIT exclusively&#xA;ENV DISABLE_ADOT_OBSERVABILITY=&amp;#34;true&amp;#34;&#xA;# OpenTelemetry configuration for Grafana Cloud&#xA;ENV OTEL_SERVICE_NAME=&amp;#34;my_service&amp;#34;&#xA;ENV OTEL_DEPLOYMENT_ENVIRONMENT=&amp;#34;my_environment&amp;#34;&#xA;ENV OTEL_EXPORTER_OTLP_ENDPOINT=&amp;#34;your_grafana_cloud_otlp_endpoint&amp;#34;&#xA;ENV OTEL_EXPORTER_OTLP_HEADERS=&amp;#34;Authorization=Basic%20&amp;#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important:&lt;/strong&gt; Replace the OTLP endpoint and headers with your Grafana Cloud credentials:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sign in to the Grafana Cloud portal and select your Grafana Cloud stack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Configure&lt;/strong&gt; in the OpenTelemetry section.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In the Password / API Token section, click &lt;strong&gt;Generate&lt;/strong&gt; to create a new API token&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Give the API token a name&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click on &lt;strong&gt;Create token&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Click on &lt;strong&gt;Close without copying the token&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Copy and replace the values for &lt;code&gt;OTEL_EXPORTER_OTLP_ENDPOINT&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;OTEL_EXPORTER_OTLP_HEADERS&lt;/code&gt; in the Dockerfile ENVs&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more information, refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/otlp/send-data-otlp/#manual-opentelemetry-setup-for-advanced-users&#34;&gt;guide on manually setting up OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; for Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, ensure the CMD line in the Dockerfile uses OpenLit&amp;rsquo;s instrumentation wrapper:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;dockerfile&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-dockerfile&#34;&gt;# Use OpenLit to automatically instrument the agent&#xA;CMD [&amp;#34;openlit-instrument&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;python&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;-m&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;crewai_agent&amp;#34;]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s happening here?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;openlit-instrument wraps your Python command&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;At runtime, OpenLit automatically monitors the CrewAI agent operations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Every LLM request and agent task is traced and exported to Grafana via OTLP&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-5-build-and-deploy&#34;&gt;Step 5: Build and deploy&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Build the Docker image and deploy to AgentCore:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;agentcore launch --local-build&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This command will:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1. Build the Docker image locally with all dependencies&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2. Push the image to Amazon ECR&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3. Deploy the agent to Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. Set up IAM execution roles&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. Configure the runtime environment&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The deployment process takes two to five minutes. You&amp;rsquo;ll see output like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;✓ Pushing to ECR...&#xA;✓ Deploying to AgentCore...&#xA;✓ Agent deployed successfully!&#xA;Agent ID: agt_abc123xyz&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-6-invoke-the-agent&#34;&gt;Step 6: Invoke the agent&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Test your deployed agent:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;# Simple test&#xA;agentcore invoke &amp;#39;{&amp;#34;prompt&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;hi&amp;#34;}&amp;#39;&#xA;# Research query&#xA;agentcore invoke &amp;#39;{&amp;#34;prompt&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Explain AI Observability&amp;#34;}&amp;#39;&#xA;# Complex request&#xA;agentcore invoke &amp;#39;{&amp;#34;prompt&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Compare supervised and unsupervised learning with examples&amp;#34;}&amp;#39;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Response:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;JSON&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-json&#34;&gt;{&#xA;&amp;#34;result&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Quantum computing is a revolutionary approach to computation that...&amp;#34;&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Response:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;JSON&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-json&#34;&gt;{&#xA;&amp;#34;result&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Quantum computing is a revolutionary approach to computation that...&amp;#34;&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-7-explore-grafana-cloud-ai-observability&#34;&gt;Step 7: Explore Grafana Cloud AI Observability&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you have telemetry flowing from CrewAI Agent on AgentCore to Grafana Cloud, you can use the pre-built dashboards from &lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud AI Observability&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Navigate to &lt;strong&gt;Connections&lt;/strong&gt; → search for &lt;strong&gt;AI Observability&lt;/strong&gt; and click on it → go to &lt;strong&gt;GenAI Observability&lt;/strong&gt;, scroll down, and install the dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what you can see in the dashboards:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;End-to-end latency:&lt;/strong&gt; Total time from request to response&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LLM call details:&lt;/strong&gt; Which model, how many tokens, latency, cost&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/701851b721/bedrock-app-grafana-ai.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/701851b721/bedrock-app-grafana-ai.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;The Grafana AI Observability dashboard with data on request rates, token usage, usage cost, and more&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agent workflow:&lt;/strong&gt; Task creation, execution, and response formatting&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x816/3f30723e9d/bedrock-app-consumption-vs-cost.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x816/3f30723e9d/bedrock-app-consumption-vs-cost.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud dashboard shows token consumption vs. average usage cost, as well as traces&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Error traces:&lt;/strong&gt; If something fails, you&amp;rsquo;ll see the exact step and error message&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x822/0113778bf4/bedrock-app-span-filters.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x822/0113778bf4/bedrock-app-span-filters.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;A list of error traces in Grafana Cloud&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;next-steps&#34;&gt;Next steps&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The combination of AWS Bedrock AgentCore, OpenTelemetry, and Grafana Cloud provides a production-ready stack for AI agents with enterprise-grade observability. Explore our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/ai-observability/%29/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud AI Observability documentation&lt;/a&gt; to learn more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当今的人工智能代理已经变得越来越复杂，进入生产环境并成为工程工作流程不可或缺的一部分。但这些代理也可能成为工程师的黑匣子，这使得可观察性比以往任何时候都更加重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果没有适当的监控，当您尝试调试代理故障、了解性能瓶颈和跟踪成本时，您常常会感觉自己是盲目的。我们希望让用户重新掌控一切，因此在本教程中，您将了解如何在 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore 上部署 AI 代理，并具有由 OpenTelemetry 和 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 提供支持的完整可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;更具体地说，您将学习如何：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.在 AWS Bedrock AgentCore 上部署 AI 代理，以实现托管、可扩展的生产运行时&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2.使用 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openlit/openlit&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenLit&lt;/a&gt; 实现 OpenTelemetry 的仪器代理，实现自动、零代码可观察性&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3.使用 AI Observability 仪表板监控 Grafana Cloud 中的代理性能&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4.使用分布式跟踪调试生产问题&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5.通过跟踪代币使用情况和模型性能来优化成本&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;注意：&lt;/strong&gt;这篇文章重点讨论人工智能应用程序的可观察性。本指南的第二部分将重点关注&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/11/28/how-to-monitor-amazon-bedrock-agentcore-ai-agent-infrastruct-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;基础设施层的人工智能可观测性&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-is-amazon-bedrock-agentcore&#34;&gt;什么是 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore？&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/bedrock/agentcore/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Amazon Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/a&gt; 是一项托管服务，可简化在生产中部署和运行 AI 代理的过程。将其视为人工智能代理的无服务器运行时。您提供代理代码，AWS 负责处理基础设施、扩展和执行环境。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主要优点包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;托管基础架构：&lt;/strong&gt;无需配置服务器或管理 Kubernetes 集群&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amazon Bedrock 集成：&lt;/strong&gt;本地访问 Llama 3、Claude 等基础模型&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;基于容器的部署：&lt;/strong&gt;使用 Docker 将代理与所有依赖项打包&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;企业就绪：&lt;/strong&gt;内置安全性、IAM 集成和合规性功能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AgentCore 对于 CrewAI、LangGraph 或 Strands 等编排框架特别强大，在这些框架中需要协调多个代理或复杂的工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-use-opentelemetry-for-ai-agents&#34;&gt;为什么将 OpenTelemetry 用于 AI 代理？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;众所周知，人工智能代理很难调试。单个用户查询可能会触发：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多次 LLM API 调用&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;工具调用和外部 API 请求&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多步推理链&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;雷特逻辑和错误处理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当出现问题（或更糟）时，当性能悄然下降时，您需要了解每一步。为了解决这个问题，我们建议使用 OpenTelemetry (&lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OTel&lt;/a&gt;)，这是行业标准的可观测性框架，它为分布式应用程序和基础设施提供统一的检测。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;特别是对于 AI 代理，OpenTelemetry 可帮助您回答关键问题：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;哪些 LLM 通话速度最慢？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;每个请求我消耗了多少令牌？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;我的代理工作流程中哪些地方发生了错误？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;用户请求的端到端延迟是多少？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 OpenTelemetry 功能强大，但手动检测每个 LLM 调用和代理步骤既乏味又容易出错。这就是 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/openlit/openlit&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenLit&lt;/a&gt; 的闪光点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OpenLit 为 AI 框架提供自动检测：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;需要零代码更改；使用 &lt;code&gt;openlit-instrument&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt; 包装您的 Python 命令&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自动捕获 LLM 调用（OpenAI、Anthropic、Bedrock 等）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;支持代理框架（CrewAI、LangChain、LlamaIndex）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;将兼容 OpenTelemetry 的数据导出到任何 OTLP 后端&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;tutorial-deploy-and-monitor-a-crewai-agent&#34;&gt;教程：部署和监控 CrewAI 代理&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了说明其工作原理，让我们构建一个完整的示例：由 CrewAI 和 Meta 的 Llama 3 提供支持的研究助理代理，部署在 AWS Bedrock AgentCore 上，在 Grafana Cloud 中具有完全可观察性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;precessions&#34;&gt;先决条件&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开始之前，请确保您已：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;已安装 Python 3.12+**&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用凭证配置的 AWS CLI：&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt; aws configure&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您需要以下权限：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基岩代理核心&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Amazon ECR（弹性容器注册表）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基岩模型访问（特别是 &lt;code&gt;meta.llama3-8b-instruct-v1:0&lt;/code&gt;）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4. Grafana Cloud 帐户（如果您没有帐户，您可以&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即注册我们的永久免费套餐&lt;/a&gt;。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5. AgentCore CLI 安装：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;  python -m venv .venv &amp;&amp; 源 .venv/bin/activate&#xA;pip 安装 bedrock-agentcore-starter-toolkit&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-1-create-a-crewai-agent&#34;&gt;第 1 步：创建 CrewAI 代理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们使用 CrewAI 创建一个示例 AI 代理：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;导入操作系统&#xA;从 bedrock_agentcore 导入 BedrockAgentCoreApp&#xA;从crewai导入代理、任务、人员、流程&#xA;# 初始化AgentCore运行时&#xA;应用程序 = BedrockAgentCoreApp()&#xA;# 定义一个简单的研究助理代理&#xA;研究员=特工(&#xA;角色=“研究助理”，&#xA;goal=&#34;提供有用、准确的答案，并附有简洁的摘要。&#34;,&#xA;backstory=(“你是一位知识渊博的研究助理，回答清晰”&#xA;“并在相关时引用事实。”），&#xA;# 通过 AWS Bedrock 使用 Llama 3 8B&#xA;llm=&#34;bedrock/meta.llama3-8b-instruct-v1:0&#34;,&#xA;详细=假，&#xA;最大迭代次数=2&#xA;）&#xA;@app.entrypoint&#xA;def 调用（有效负载：字典）：&#xA;&#34;&#34;&#34;AgentCore 入口点。需要 {&#39;prompt&#39;: &#39;&#39;}&#34;&#34;&#34;&#xA;user_message = Payload.get(&#34;提示&#34;, &#34;您好！&#34;)&#xA;任务 = 任务（&#xA;描述=用户消息，&#xA;代理人=研究员，&#xA;Expected_output=&#34;一个有用的、结构良好的响应。&#34;&#xA;）&#xA;船员=船员（&#xA;代理人=[研究员],&#xA;任务=[任务],&#xA;过程=过程.顺序，&#xA;详细=假，&#xA;）&#xA;结果=crew.kickoff()&#xA;返回 {“结果”：结果.raw}&#xA;如果 __name__ == &#34;__main__&#34;:&#xA;app.run()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;关键组件：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BedrockAgentCoreApp：&lt;/strong&gt;将 CrewAI 与 Amazon Bedrock AgentCore 运行时集成&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;代理定义：&lt;/strong&gt;使用 Llama 3 担任研究助理角色的单一代理&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;@app.entrypoint&lt;/code&gt;&lt;strong&gt;：&lt;/strong&gt;将函数标记为代理入口点的装饰器&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;人员编排：&lt;/strong&gt;CrewAI 管理任务执行和代理协调&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;代理接受 JSON 输入，例如 &lt;code&gt;{&#34;prompt&#34;: &#34;your Question&#34;}&lt;/code&gt; 并返回 JSON 响应。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-2-configure-dependency&#34;&gt;圣第 2 步：配置依赖项&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;创建一个requirements.txt，其中包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;crewai&gt;=1.0.0&#xA;开光&gt;=1.35&#xA;莱特尔姆&#xA;bedrock-agentcore&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-3-configure-agentcore-deployment&#34;&gt;第 3 步：配置 AgentCore 部署&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;运行AgentCore配置命令：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;agentcore 配置 \&#xA;--部署类型容器\&#xA;--入口点crewai_agent.py \&#xA;--名称crewai_agent \&#xA;--非交互式&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这会生成一个 &lt;code&gt;.bedrock_agentcore/crewai_agent/&lt;/code&gt; 目录，其中包含：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;code&gt;Dockerfile&lt;/code&gt;：容器构建配置&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;code&gt;agent_config.json&lt;/code&gt;：AgentCore 的元数据&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-4-add-opentelemetry-configuration&#34;&gt;第 4 步：添加 OpenTelemetry 配置&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在是可观察性魔法了。在 &lt;code&gt;.bedrock_agentcore/crewai_agent/Dockerfile&lt;/code&gt; 编辑生成的 Dockerfile 并添加以下环境变量：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;dockerfile&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-dockerfile&#34;&gt;# 禁用 AWS ADOT 可观察性以独占使用 OpenLIT&#xA;ENV DISABLE_ADOT_OBSERVABILITY=&#34;true&#34;&#xA;# Grafana Cloud 的 OpenTelemetry 配置&#xA;ENV OTEL_SERVICE_NAME=&#34;my_service&#34;&#xA;ENV OTEL_DEPLOYMENT_ENVIRONMENT=&#34;我的环境&#34;&#xA;ENV OTEL_EXPORTER_OTLP_ENDPOINT=&#34;your_grafana_cloud_otlp_endpoint&#34;&#xA;ENV OTEL_EXPORTER_OTLP_HEADERS=&#34;Authorization=Basic%20&#34;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;重要提示&lt;/strong&gt;：将 OTLP 端点和标头替换为您的 Grafana Cloud 凭据：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;登录o Grafana Cloud 门户并选择您的 Grafana Cloud 堆栈。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;点击 OpenTelemetry 部分中的&lt;strong&gt;配置&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在“密码/API 令牌”部分中，点击&lt;strong&gt;生成&lt;/strong&gt;以创建新的 API 令牌&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;为 API 令牌命名&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;点击&lt;strong&gt;创建令牌&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;点击&lt;strong&gt;关闭而不复制令牌&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;复制并替换 Dockerfile ENV 中 &lt;code&gt;OTEL_EXPORTER_OTLP_ENDPOINT&lt;/code&gt; 和 &lt;code&gt;OTEL_EXPORTER_OTLP_HEADERS&lt;/code&gt; 的值&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有关详细信息，请参阅我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/otlp/send-data-otlp/#manual-opentelemetry-setup-for-advanced-users&#34;&gt;有关为 Grafana Cloud 手动设置 OpenTelemetry 的指南&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，确保 Dockerfile 中的 CMD 行使用 OpenLit 的检测包装器：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;dockerfile&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-dockerfile&#34;&gt;# 使用 OpenLit 自动检测代理&#xA;CMD [“openlit-instrument”，“python”，“-m”，“crewai_agent”]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;这里发生了什么？&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;openlit-instrument 包装您的 Python 命令&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在运行时，OpenLit 会自动监控 CrewAI 代理操作&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;每个 LLM 请求和代理任务都会通过 OTLP 进行跟踪并导出到 Grafana&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-5-build-and-deploy&#34;&gt;第 5 步：构建和部署&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;构建 Docker 镜像并部署到 AgentCore：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;agentcore 启动 --local-build&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该命令将：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.在本地构建具有所有依赖项的 Docker 映像&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2.将映像推送到 Amazon ECR&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;3.将代理部署到 Bedrock AgentCore&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;4.设置 IAM 执行角色&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;5.配置运行环境&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;部署过程需要两到五分钟。您将看到如下输出：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;✓ 推送至 ECR...&#xA;✓ 部署到 AgentCore...&#xA;✓ 代理部署成功！&#xA;代理 ID：agt_abc123xyz&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-6-invoke-the-agent&#34;&gt;第 6 步：调用代理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;测试您部署的代理：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;Bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;# 简单测试&#xA;agentcore 调用 &#39;{&#34;prompt&#34;: &#34;hi&#34;}&#39;&#xA;# 研究查询&#xA;agentcore 调用 &#39;{&#34;prompt&#34;: &#34;Explain AI Observability&#34;}&#39;&#xA;# 复杂请求&#xA;agentcore invoke &#39;{&#34;prompt&#34;: &#34;将监督学习和无监督学习与示例进行比较&#34;}&#39;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;回应：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;JSON&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-json&#34;&gt;{&#xA;“结果”：“量子计算是一种革命性的计算方法……”&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;回应：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item lang-toolbar__item-active&#34;&gt;JSON&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-json&#34;&gt;{&#xA;“结果”：“量子计算是一种革命性的计算方法……”&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;step-7-explore-grafana-cloud-ai-observability&#34;&gt;第 7 步：探索 Grafana Cloud AI 可观测性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦您获得从 AgentCore 上的 CrewAI Agent 到 Grafana Cloud 的遥测数据流，您就可以使用预构建来自 &lt;strong&gt;Grafana Cloud AI Observability&lt;/strong&gt; 的仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;导航到&lt;strong&gt;连接&lt;/strong&gt;→搜索&lt;strong&gt;AI Observability&lt;/strong&gt;并单击它→转到&lt;strong&gt;GenAI Observability&lt;/strong&gt;，向下滚动并安装仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;以下是您在仪表板中可以看到的内容的详细信息：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;端到端延迟&lt;/strong&gt;：从请求到响应的总时间&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LLM 通话详细信息&lt;/strong&gt;：哪种型号、多少代币、延迟、成本&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/701851b721/bedrock-app-grafana-ai.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x869/701851b721/bedrock-app-grafana-ai.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana AI 可观测性仪表板，包含有关请求率、令牌使用情况、使用成本等数据&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;代理工作流程：&lt;/strong&gt;任务创建、执行和响应格式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x816/3f30723e9d/bedrock-app-conspiration-vs-cost.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x816/3f30723e9d/bedrock-app-conspiration-vs-cost.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud 仪表板显示代币消耗与平均使用成本以及痕迹&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;错误跟踪：&lt;/strong&gt;如果出现问题，您将看到确切的步骤和错误消息&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图包装图包装__lightbox w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&lt;一个&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x822/0113778bf4/bedrock-app-span-filters.png/m/&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x822/0113778bf4/bedrock-app-span-filters.png/m/&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud 中的错误跟踪列表&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;next-steps&#34;&gt;后续步骤&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS Bedrock AgentCore、OpenTelemetry 和 Grafana Cloud 的组合为具有企业级可观测性的 AI 代理提供了一个生产就绪堆栈。浏览我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/ai-observability/%29/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud AI 可观测性文档&lt;/a&gt;以了解更多信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板的最简单方法s，等等。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册！&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>