<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</title>
    <link>/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana Cloud updates: new visualization options, performance test analysis, Grafana Alerting improvements, and more】Grafana Cloud 更新：新的可视化选项、性能测试分析、Grafana 警报改进等</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/06/24/grafana-cloud-updates-new-visualization-options-performance-test-analysis-grafana-alerting-improvements-and-more/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We consistently roll out helpful updates and fun features in Grafana Cloud, our fully managed observability platform powered by the open source Grafana LGTM Stack (&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; for logs, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; for visualization, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt; for traces, and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt; for metrics).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In case you missed it, here’s a roundup of the latest and greatest updates for Grafana Cloud this month. You can also read about all the features we add to Grafana Cloud in our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/whats-new/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;What’s New in Grafana Cloud documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And if you’re not a Grafana Cloud user yet, &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;sign up&lt;/a&gt; for an account today! You can try any of these features (and more) for free with our generous Cloud Free plan.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-visualization-enhancements&#34;&gt;Data visualization enhancements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re always exploring new and creative ways to help you visualize and derive meaningful insights from your data. This month, we’re excited to share a few minor (but helpful) updates we’ve made to the data visualization experience in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;customize-percent-change-colors&#34;&gt;Customize percent change colors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/stat/&#34;&gt;stat visualizations&lt;/a&gt;, the standard behavior for a percent change is to display positive changes in green and negative changes in red. Depending on your use case, however, we realize you might want to customize these percent change colors. Now, you have the option to invert the percent change color, showing positive changes in red and negative changes in green. You can also choose to have the percent change color match the color of its associated value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1920px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-stat-percent-change-color-options.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-stat-percent-change-color-options.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A gif showing the percent color change. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1920&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;990&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-stat-percent-change-color-options.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A gif showing the percent color change. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1920&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;990&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;wrap-text-within-cells&#34;&gt;Wrap text within cells&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most frequent requests we’ve heard from users is to enable text wrapping within cells for the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/table/&#34;&gt;table panel&lt;/a&gt;. With the release of Grafana 11.1, we’re adding this long-requested capability!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, the column with the longest text will be selected for wrapping. Alternatively, you can manually configure wrapping using field overrides.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-text-wrapping.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-text-wrapping.gif&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;311&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-text-wrapping.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;311&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;visualize-x-and-y-values-in-the-xy-chart&#34;&gt;Visualize x and y values in the XY chart&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;XY charts — which we’re officially promoting out of public preview and into general availability — help you visualize arbitrary x and y values in a graph so you can easily show the relationship between two variables. XY charts are typically used to create scatter plots, but you can also use them to create bubble charts where field values determine the size of each bubble.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 2858px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=320 320w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=550 550w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=750 750w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=900 900w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the XY chart.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;2858&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;914&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the XY chart.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;2858&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;914&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refer to our technical documentation to learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud visualizations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;streaming-query-results-for-grafana-cloud-traces&#34;&gt;Streaming query results for Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt; users now get partial results from TraceQL queries as they come in, rather than having to wait for all results to be returned at once. This allows you to start looking at traces matched by your query immediately, speeding up your root cause analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-traces-streaming-query-results-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-traces-streaming-query-results-gif.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A gif showing the streaming query results feature.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;579&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-traces-streaming-query-results-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A gif showing the streaming query results feature.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;579&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Grafana Cloud Traces, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/traces/traces-query-editor/traceql-search/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#streaming-results&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;performance-test-analysis-with-cloud-insights-in-grafana-cloud-k6&#34;&gt;Performance test analysis with Cloud Insights in Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The real value of performance testing is not the test itself, but being able to analyze and draw conclusions from the results. This isn’t always easy, however, given today’s increasingly complex systems. When something goes wrong in a test, finding the root cause can be difficult and time-consuming.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We aim to address these challenges with Cloud Insights in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/k6//?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/a&gt;. Cloud Insights analyzes telemetry data generated during a test run, such as metrics, logs, and traces, to automatically identify issues in the system you’re testing and provide recommendations to fix them. This helps you and your team save time and identify root causes faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To use Cloud Insights, enable it in the Beta Features modal window in &lt;strong&gt;Testing &amp;amp; synthetics &amp;gt; Performance&lt;/strong&gt;. For more information, refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/k6/analyze-results/get-cloud-insights/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Cloud Insights documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-insights-grafana-k6-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-insights-grafana-k6-gif.gif&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;338&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-insights-grafana-k6-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;338&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;logs-filtering-and-pinning-in-grafana-explore&#34;&gt;Logs filtering and pinning in Grafana Explore&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Explore&lt;/a&gt; now supports logs filtering and pinning in the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#content-outline&#34;&gt;content outline&lt;/a&gt;, a side navigation bar that keeps track of the queries and visualization panels you create. All log levels are now automatically available in the content outline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Filtering logs&lt;/strong&gt;: You can now filter by log level, which is currently supported for Elasticsearch and Loki data sources. To select multiple filters, hold down the command key on Mac or the control key on Windows while clicking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pinning logs&lt;/strong&gt;: You can also pin logs to the content outline, making them easily accessible to reference during investigations. To pin a log, hover over a log in the logs panel and click on the &lt;strong&gt;Pin to content outline&lt;/strong&gt; icon in the log row menu. Clicking on a pinned log will open the log context modal, showing the log highlighted in context with other logs. From here, you can also open the log in split mode to preserve the time range in the left pane, while having the time range specific to that log in the right pane.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can read more about Grafana Explore in our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;private-source-map-uploads-in-grafana-cloud-frontend-observability&#34;&gt;Private source map uploads in Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This month, we introduced private source map uploads in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/frontend-observability-for-real-user-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability&lt;/a&gt;, our hosted service for real user monitoring (RUM) that provides actionable insights into the end user experience. With this new capability, Frontend Observability can now use source maps to convert stack traces from JavaScript browser errors back into their original representation. This way, you can see the exact line of code that caused the issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before rolling out this feature, source maps had to be publicly available on the internet in order for Grafana Cloud to fetch them. For many users, this wasn’t ideal, as it meant they needed to expose some of their IP. Now, Frontend Observability provides an option for users who want de-minified stack traces for errors while keeping their source map private.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simply include the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/sourcemap-upload-plugins/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;newly released JavaScript bundler plugins&lt;/a&gt; into your build pipeline, input some configuration context provided by the Frontend Observability plugin app, and you will be able to see full error stack traces without needing to host source maps publicly alongside the application bundle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more, refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/sourcemap-upload-plugins/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Frontend Observability documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-alerting-improvements&#34;&gt;Grafana Alerting improvements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have several updates to Grafana Alerting, including new options to manage silences and an easier way to select templates for your alert notification messages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rule-specific-silences-with-rbac&#34;&gt;Rule-specific silences with RBAC&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now choose who can create, edit, and read silences using the following permissions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users with the &lt;code&gt;alert.silences:create&lt;/code&gt; permission, scoped within a folder, are able to create silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users with the &lt;code&gt;alert.silences:read&lt;/code&gt; permission, scoped within a folder, are able to read silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders, and general silences.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users with the &lt;code&gt;alert.silences:write&lt;/code&gt; permission, scoped within a folder, are able to expire and recreate silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rule-specific-silences-with-permissions&#34;&gt;Rule-specific silences with permissions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More easily create silences directly from the &lt;strong&gt;Alert rule list&lt;/strong&gt; view or &lt;strong&gt;detail&lt;/strong&gt; page. These rule-specific silences are guaranteed to only apply to a single rule and permissions to read, create, update or delete are tied to a user’s permissions for that rule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;alerting-template-selector&#34;&gt;Alerting template selector&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now easily choose which templates you want to use in your alert notification messages by adding a template selector in the &lt;strong&gt;Contact Points&lt;/strong&gt; form. Select from existing templates or customize one for your specific needs. You can switch between the two tabs to access the list of available templates and copy them across to the customized version.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about setting up alerts in Grafana Cloud, refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-integrations-catchpoint&#34;&gt;New integrations: Catchpoint&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/catchpoint/monitor/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;easily monitor Catchpoint&lt;/a&gt;, a digital experience platform that provides real-time insights into the performance and availability of websites, applications, and infrastructure, within Grafana Cloud. The integration includes &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-catchpoint/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#alerts&#34;&gt;five useful alerts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-catchpoint/#dashboards&#34;&gt;three pre-built dashboards&lt;/a&gt; to help monitor and visualize Catchpoint metrics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, we introduced the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-catchpoint-datasource/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Catchpoint Enterprise data source plugin&lt;/a&gt;, which allows you to query and visualize &lt;code&gt;Tests&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;RUM&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;SLO&lt;/code&gt; data from within Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;We consistently roll out helpful updates and fun features in Grafana Cloud, our fully managed observability platform powered by the open source Grafana LGTM Stack (&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; for logs, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; for visualization, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt; for traces, and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt; for metrics).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In case you missed it, here’s a roundup of the latest and greatest updates for Grafana Cloud this month. You can also read about all the features we add to Grafana Cloud in our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/whats-new/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;What’s New in Grafana Cloud documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And if you’re not a Grafana Cloud user yet, &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;sign up&lt;/a&gt; for an account today! You can try any of these features (and more) for free with our generous Cloud Free plan.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;data-visualization-enhancements&#34;&gt;Data visualization enhancements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re always exploring new and creative ways to help you visualize and derive meaningful insights from your data. This month, we’re excited to share a few minor (but helpful) updates we’ve made to the data visualization experience in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;customize-percent-change-colors&#34;&gt;Customize percent change colors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/stat/&#34;&gt;stat visualizations&lt;/a&gt;, the standard behavior for a percent change is to display positive changes in green and negative changes in red. Depending on your use case, however, we realize you might want to customize these percent change colors. Now, you have the option to invert the percent change color, showing positive changes in red and negative changes in green. You can also choose to have the percent change color match the color of its associated value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1920px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-stat-percent-change-color-options.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-stat-percent-change-color-options.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A gif showing the percent color change. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1920&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;990&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-stat-percent-change-color-options.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A gif showing the percent color change. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1920&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;990&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;wrap-text-within-cells&#34;&gt;Wrap text within cells&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most frequent requests we’ve heard from users is to enable text wrapping within cells for the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/table/&#34;&gt;table panel&lt;/a&gt;. With the release of Grafana 11.1, we’re adding this long-requested capability!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, the column with the longest text will be selected for wrapping. Alternatively, you can manually configure wrapping using field overrides.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-text-wrapping.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-text-wrapping.gif&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;311&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/gif-grafana-11-1-text-wrapping.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;311&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;visualize-x-and-y-values-in-the-xy-chart&#34;&gt;Visualize x and y values in the XY chart&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;XY charts — which we’re officially promoting out of public preview and into general availability — help you visualize arbitrary x and y values in a graph so you can easily show the relationship between two variables. XY charts are typically used to create scatter plots, but you can also use them to create bubble charts where field values determine the size of each bubble.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 2858px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=320 320w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=550 550w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=750 750w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=900 900w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the XY chart.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;2858&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;914&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/docs/grafana/panels-visualizations/screenshot-xy-charts-v11.0.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of the XY chart.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;2858&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;914&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Refer to our technical documentation to learn more about &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud visualizations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;streaming-query-results-for-grafana-cloud-traces&#34;&gt;Streaming query results for Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt; users now get partial results from TraceQL queries as they come in, rather than having to wait for all results to be returned at once. This allows you to start looking at traces matched by your query immediately, speeding up your root cause analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-traces-streaming-query-results-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-traces-streaming-query-results-gif.gif&#34;alt=&#34;A gif showing the streaming query results feature.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;579&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-traces-streaming-query-results-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A gif showing the streaming query results feature.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;579&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Grafana Cloud Traces, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/traces/traces-query-editor/traceql-search/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#streaming-results&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;performance-test-analysis-with-cloud-insights-in-grafana-cloud-k6&#34;&gt;Performance test analysis with Cloud Insights in Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The real value of performance testing is not the test itself, but being able to analyze and draw conclusions from the results. This isn’t always easy, however, given today’s increasingly complex systems. When something goes wrong in a test, finding the root cause can be difficult and time-consuming.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We aim to address these challenges with Cloud Insights in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/k6//?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/a&gt;. Cloud Insights analyzes telemetry data generated during a test run, such as metrics, logs, and traces, to automatically identify issues in the system you’re testing and provide recommendations to fix them. This helps you and your team save time and identify root causes faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To use Cloud Insights, enable it in the Beta Features modal window in &lt;strong&gt;Testing &amp;amp; synthetics &amp;gt; Performance&lt;/strong&gt;. For more information, refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/k6/analyze-results/get-cloud-insights/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Cloud Insights documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 600px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-insights-grafana-k6-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-insights-grafana-k6-gif.gif&#34;alt=&#34;&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;338&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/grafana-cloud-updates-june-2024/cloud-insights-grafana-k6-gif.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;600&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;338&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;logs-filtering-and-pinning-in-grafana-explore&#34;&gt;Logs filtering and pinning in Grafana Explore&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Explore&lt;/a&gt; now supports logs filtering and pinning in the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#content-outline&#34;&gt;content outline&lt;/a&gt;, a side navigation bar that keeps track of the queries and visualization panels you create. All log levels are now automatically available in the content outline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Filtering logs&lt;/strong&gt;: You can now filter by log level, which is currently supported for Elasticsearch and Loki data sources. To select multiple filters, hold down the command key on Mac or the control key on Windows while clicking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pinning logs&lt;/strong&gt;: You can also pin logs to the content outline, making them easily accessible to reference during investigations. To pin a log, hover over a log in the logs panel and click on the &lt;strong&gt;Pin to content outline&lt;/strong&gt; icon in the log row menu. Clicking on a pinned log will open the log context modal, showing the log highlighted in context with other logs. From here, you can also open the log in split mode to preserve the time range in the left pane, while having the time range specific to that log in the right pane.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can read more about Grafana Explore in our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;private-source-map-uploads-in-grafana-cloud-frontend-observability&#34;&gt;Private source map uploads in Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This month, we introduced private source map uploads in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/frontend-observability-for-real-user-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability&lt;/a&gt;, our hosted service for real user monitoring (RUM) that provides actionable insights into the end user experience. With this new capability, Frontend Observability can now use source maps to convert stack traces from JavaScript browser errors back into their original representation. This way, you can see the exact line of code that caused the issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before rolling out this feature, source maps had to be publicly available on the internet in order for Grafana Cloud to fetch them. For many users, this wasn’t ideal, as it meant they needed to expose some of their IP. Now, Frontend Observability provides an option for users who want de-minified stack traces for errors while keeping their source map private.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Simply include the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/sourcemap-upload-plugins/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;newly released JavaScript bundler plugins&lt;/a&gt; into your build pipeline, input some configuration context provided by the Frontend Observability plugin app, and you will be able to see full error stack traces without needing to host source maps publicly alongside the application bundle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more, refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/sourcemap-upload-plugins/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Frontend Observability documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-alerting-improvements&#34;&gt;Grafana Alerting improvements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have several updates to Grafana Alerting, including new options to manage silences and an easier way to select templates for your alert notification messages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rule-specific-silences-with-rbac&#34;&gt;Rule-specific silences with RBAC&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now choose who can create, edit, and read silences using the following permissions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users with the &lt;code&gt;alert.silences:create&lt;/code&gt; permission, scoped within a folder, are able to create silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users with the &lt;code&gt;alert.silences:read&lt;/code&gt; permission, scoped within a folder, are able to read silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders, and general silences.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users with the &lt;code&gt;alert.silences:write&lt;/code&gt; permission, scoped within a folder, are able to expire and recreate silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rule-specific-silences-with-permissions&#34;&gt;Rule-specific silences with permissions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More easily create silences directly from the &lt;strong&gt;Alert rule list&lt;/strong&gt; view or &lt;strong&gt;detail&lt;/strong&gt; page. These rule-specific silences are guaranteed to only apply to a single rule and permissions to read, create, update or delete are tied to a user’s permissions for that rule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;alerting-template-selector&#34;&gt;Alerting template selector&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now easily choose which templates you want to use in your alert notification messages by adding a template selector in the &lt;strong&gt;Contact Points&lt;/strong&gt; form. Select from existing templates or customize one for your specific needs. You can switch between the two tabs to access the list of available templates and copy them across to the customized version.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about setting up alerts in Grafana Cloud, refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/alerting/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-integrations-catchpoint&#34;&gt;New integrations: Catchpoint&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now &lt;a href=&#34;/solutions/catchpoint/monitor/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;easily monitor Catchpoint&lt;/a&gt;, a digital experience platform that provides real-time insights into the performance and availability of websites, applications, and infrastructure, within Grafana Cloud. The integration includes &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-catchpoint/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#alerts&#34;&gt;five useful alerts&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-infrastructure/integrations/integration-reference/integration-catchpoint/#dashboards&#34;&gt;three pre-built dashboards&lt;/a&gt; to help monitor and visualize Catchpoint metrics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, we introduced the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/plugins/grafana-catchpoint-datasource/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Catchpoint Enterprise data source plugin&lt;/a&gt;, which allows you to query and visualize &lt;code&gt;Tests&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;RUM&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;SLO&lt;/code&gt; data from within Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How the DoD is embracing OSS and DevSecOps modernization with Grafana】国防部如何利用 Grafana 拥抱 OSS 和 DevSecOps 现代化</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/06/20/how-the-dod-is-embracing-oss-and-devsecops-modernization-with-grafana/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When it comes to observability, we believe open source will win in the end. It&amp;rsquo;s a sentiment shared by a wide spectrum of users, whether they work in &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/09/25/how-to-monitor-slos-with-grafana-grafana-loki-prometheus-and-pyrra-inside-the-daimler-truck-observability-stack/&#34;&gt;auto manufacturing&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/11/28/how-banco-itau-tracks-1.5b-daily-metrics-on-prem-and-in-aws-with-grafana-and-observability/&#34;&gt;banking&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/03/22/how-shipping/third-party-logistics-companies-reduce-mttr-and-increase-uptime-with-the-grafana-lgtm-stack/&#34;&gt;shipping&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. federal government is yet another industry to prove this, showing that even those operating under the strictest security and compliance requirements see OSS as their preferred approach. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a brief look at how the Department of Defense is prioritizing open source as part of a broader push to modernize its software development, and how Grafana can support those efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;oss-and-software-factories&#34;&gt;OSS and software factories&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The DoD has &lt;a href=&#34;https://dodcio.defense.gov/Open-Source-Software-FAQ/#q-does-the-dod-already-use-open-source-software&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;used open source extensively&lt;/a&gt; for decades, but it has increasingly become the starting point for Defense software projects as a means to reduce dependencies, avoid vendor lock-in, and deploy tooling built for cloud and microservices. In a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dodcio.defense.gov/portals/0/documents/library/softwaredev-opensource.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;2022 memo&lt;/a&gt;, DoD CIO John Sherman wrote that the department prefers &amp;ldquo;adopting existing government or OSS solutions before buying proprietary offerings,&amp;rdquo; adding that &amp;ldquo;OSS forms the bedrock of the software-defined world and is critical in delivering software faster.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And last year, the DoD publicly released a &lt;a href=&#34;https://dodcio.defense.gov/Portals/0/Documents/Library/SW-Mod-I-PlanExecutiveSummary.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;software modernization plan&lt;/a&gt; that prioritized not only speed, but better quality and protections in software development and management. A big part of that shift is the push to create an ecosystem of &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Software_factory&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;software factories&lt;/a&gt;, which create a framework of tools and processes to automate many of the underlying components used by developers. For the DoD, that means creating a continuous development pipeline anchored in DevSecOps principles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;pullquote en &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;pullquote__content&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OSS forms the bedrock of the software-defined world and is critical in delivering software faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;U.S. DoD CIO John Sherman&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A coalition of software factory providers has begun to emerge, with an emphasis on &lt;a href=&#34;https://coalition.dso.mil/about-us/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;building an open ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;. One of those providers, &lt;a href=&#34;https://p1.dso.mil/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Platform One&lt;/a&gt;, hosts CI/CD DevSecOps pipelines and offers a secure Kubernetes platform for hosting microservices. Platform One&amp;rsquo;s core offerings include Big Bang, a customizable platform designed to accelerate software development and deployment within the DoD. It provides a comprehensive suite of tools and services, including infrastructure provisioning, CI/CD pipelines, and security scanning, and it&amp;rsquo;s currently being used by DoD branches such as the Air Force, Army, and Navy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last year, Platform One &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs-bigbang.dso.mil/latest/blog/big-bang-2-0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;launched Big Bang 2.0&lt;/a&gt; to lower the barrier for entry and make the platform free and open by default. A big part of that release was the inclusion of three Grafana Labs open source projects: &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; for logs, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/grafana?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; for visualization, and &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt; for traces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Big Bang&amp;rsquo;s default stack has switched from a combination of Elasticsearch, Fluentbit, and Kibana to Promtail, Loki, and Grafana, with Platform One citing the lower resource cost for users and the lack of license requirements for core features. As part of that shift, Big Bang 2.0 also moves tracing from Jaeger to Tempo because it integrates better with its stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-dod-software-factories-can-rely-on-grafana&#34;&gt;How DoD software factories can rely on Grafana&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana is well suited for modern software development, regardless of industry. It&amp;rsquo;s a centralized observability platform that aggregates data from diverse sources, including infrastructure, applications, and network devices. This allows software factories to gain a comprehensive view of their entire ecosystem in a single pane of glass, enabling proactive detection and resolution of issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Developers can use customized, role-based dashboards to get immediate insights into key performance indicators (KPIs), such as build and deployment metrics, system uptime, and resource utilization. They can also use Grafana to improve system reliability by identifying bottlenecks and inefficiencies in their delivery processes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about how Grafana can help DoD teams deliver faster, more reliable deployments, email us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:federal@grafana.com&#34;&gt;federal@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;federal@grafana.com&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. And check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2021/09/29/the-u.s.-department-of-defense-formally-authorizes-grafana-grafana-enterprise-and-loki-for-its-100000-developers/&#34;&gt;other blog posts&lt;/a&gt; highlighting &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/02/04/a-look-at-how-the-u.s.-department-of-defense-deploys-the-grafana-stack/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;how the DoD is deploying Grafana&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当谈到可观察性时，我们相信开源最终会获胜。这是广大用户的共同看法，无论他们是否在 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/09/25/how-to-monitor-slos-with-grafana-grafana-loki-prometheus-and-pyrra 中工作-inside-the-daimler-truck-observability-stack/&#34;&gt;汽车制造&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/11/28/how-banco-itau-tracks-1.5b-daily-metrics -on-prem-and-in-aws-with-grafana-and-observability/&#34;&gt;银行业务&lt;/a&gt;，或&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/03/22/how-shipping/third-party-物流公司使用 Grafana-lgtm-stack 减少 Mttr 并增加正常运行时间/&#34;&gt;运输&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;美国联邦政府是另一个证明这一点的行业，这表明即使是那些在最严格的安全和合规要求下运营的行业也将 OSS 视为他们的首选方法。在这篇博文中，我们将简要介绍国防部如何优先考虑开源，作为更广泛推动软件开发现代化的一部分，以及 Grafana 如何支持这些努力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;oss-and-software-factories&#34;&gt;OSS 和软件工厂&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;国防部有&lt;a href=&#34;https://dodcio.defense.gov/Open-Source-Software-FAQ/#q-does-the-dod-already-use-open-source-software&#34; target= &#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;几十年来广泛使用开源&lt;/a&gt;，但它已日益成为国防软件项目的起点，作为减少依赖性、避免供应商锁定和部署内置工具的手段适用于云和微服务。在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://dodcio.defense.gov/portals/0/documents/library/softwaredev-opensource.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;2022 年备忘录&lt;/a&gt;中，国防部首席信息官 John Sherman 写道，该部门更喜欢“在购买专有产品之前采用现有的政府或 OSS 解决方案”，并补充说“OSS 构成了软件定义世界的基石，对于更快地交付软件至关重要。”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;去年，国防部公开发布了&lt;a href=&#34;https://dodcio.defense.gov/Portals/0/Documents/Library/SW-Mod-I-PlanExecutiveSummary.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;软件现代化计划&lt;/a&gt;不仅优先考虑速度，还优先考虑软件开发和管理中更好的质量和保护。这种转变的一个重要部分是推动创建一个&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Software_factory&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;软件工厂生态系统&lt;/a &gt;，它创建了一个工具和流程框架来自动化开发人员使用的许多底层组件。对于国防部来说，这意味着创建一个以 DevSecOps 原则为基础的持续开发管道。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote class=&#34;pullquote &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;pullquote__content&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OSS 构成了软件定义世界的基石，对于更快地交付软件至关重要。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;美国国防部首席信息官约翰·谢尔曼&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;软件工厂提供商联盟已经开始出现，重点是&lt;a href=&#34;https://coalition.dso.mil/about-us/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;构建开放的生态系统&lt;/a&gt;。其中一个提供商 &lt;a href=&#34;https://p1.dso.mil/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Platform One&lt;/a&gt; 托管 CI/CD DevSecOps 管道并提供安全的用于托管微服务的 Kubernetes 平台。 Platform One 的核心产品包括 Big Bang，这是一个可定制的平台，旨在加速国防部内的软件开发和部署。它提供了一整套工具和服务，包括基础设施配置、CI/CD 管道和安全扫描，目前正被空军、陆军和海军等国防部部门使用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;去年，平台一&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs-bigbang.dso.mil/latest/blog/big-bang-2-0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;推出Big Bang 2.0&lt;/a&gt;，降低准入门槛，默认平台免费开放。该版本的一个重要部分是包含了三个 Grafana Labs 开源项目：用于日志的 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt;、&lt;a href= &#34;/oss/grafana?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; 用于可视化，以及 &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/tempo/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Tempo&lt;/a&gt;寻找痕迹。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Big Bang 的默认堆栈已从 Elasticsearch、Fluentbit 和 Kibana 的组合切换为 Promtail、Loki 和 Grafana，Platform One 表示用户的资源成本较低，并且无需核心功能的许可证要求。作为这一转变的一部分，Big Bang 2.0 还将追踪从 Jaeger 转移到 Tempo，因为它与其堆栈集成得更好。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-dod-software-factories-can-rely-on-grafana&#34;&gt;国防部软件工厂如何依赖 Grafana&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana 非常适合现代软件开发，无论哪个行业。它是一个集中式可观察平台，聚合来自不同来源的数据，包括基础设施、应用程序和网络设备。这使得软件工厂能够在单一管理平台中全面了解整个生态系统，从而能够主动检测和解决问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开发人员可以使用基于角色的自定义仪表板来立即了解关键绩效指标 (KPI)，例如构建和部署指标、系统正常运行时间和资源利用率。他们还可以使用 Grafana 通过识别交付流程中的瓶颈和低效率来提高系统可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要详细了解 Grafana 如何帮助 DoD 团队提供更快、更可靠的部署，请发送电子邮件至 &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:federal@grafana.com&#34;&gt;federal@grafana.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href= “federal@grafana.com&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;。并查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2021/09/29/the-u.s.-department-of-defense-formally-authorizes-grafana-grafana-enterprise-and-loki-for-its-100000-developers/ &#34;&gt;其他博客文章&lt;/a&gt;突出显示&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/02/04/a-look-at-how-the-u.s.-department-of-defense-deploys-the-grafana-stack/ ?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;国防部如何部署 Grafana&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to customize your Loki deployment with Ansible】如何使用 Ansible 自定义 Loki 部署</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/05/how-to-customize-your-loki-deployment-with-ansible/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Michal Vaško is a DevOps engineer at cloudWerkstatt, with a passion for open source technology and a deep love for observability.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While operations or platform teams have long relied on visibility into metrics to react swiftly, the idea of doing the same thing with logs was once just a dream. Thankfully, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; has revolutionized the logging stack, giving you the same level of visibility with logs that you get with metrics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t embarked on the Loki journey yet, now is the time with the release of Loki 3.0!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are several deployment methods available for various deployment modes: Helm, Tanka, Docker or Docker Compose, local, and from source. For more details on all these methods, you can refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/setup/install/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki installation guide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All these installation methods are great, serving their purpose and providing flexibility to users so you can deploy Loki in a manner that fits your specific scenario. But let me introduce you to another approach — the Ansible Loki Role. This role supports Debian, Ubuntu, and Red Hat. Originally migrated from &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/voidquark/loki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Voidquark&amp;rsquo;s Loki repository&lt;/a&gt; to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Ansible collection&lt;/a&gt;, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be part of the ongoing maintenance and improvements to the role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Deployment of Loki is primarily focused on Kubernetes, for scalability reasons. But what if you&amp;rsquo;re not at that phase yet? Or you simply want to experiment? Or you have a small organization where deploying Loki is desired and you are already familiar with Ansible? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in the right place. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into setting up this Ansible role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-need-to-get-started&#34;&gt;What you need to get started&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ensure you have an Ansible controller deployed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Install the Ansible Grafana collection on your Ansible controller.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Familiarize yourself with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection/blob/main/roles/loki/README.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;README&lt;/a&gt; of the Ansible Loki Role.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create a simple default playbook or customize it to fit your requirements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to assume you already have Ansible set up and have read the Loki role README to become more familiar with it. &lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;Now, let&amp;rsquo;s proceed with installing the Ansible Grafana collection:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;ansible-galaxy collection install grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-use-the-default-deployment&#34;&gt;How to use the default deployment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s demonstrate an out-of-the-box deployment with the default configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, create a playbook named &lt;code&gt;function_loki-default.play&lt;/code&gt;. This playbook is straightforward and deploys Loki with default settings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;yaml&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;- name: Deploy Loki using the default configuration&#xA;hosts: loki&#xA;become: true&#xA;roles:&#xA;- role: grafana.grafana.loki&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;Next, execute this playbook to deploy Loki:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;ansible-playbook function_loki-default.play&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;The default deployment for Loki is now in place, but most people will want to tweak it for their own needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s move on to customizing it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-customize-your-deployment&#34;&gt;How to customize your deployment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What if you want to tinker a bit more? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re not limited! You can configure each component exactly as you wish. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into an example where we&amp;rsquo;ll use:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Filesystem storage&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A ruler with Alertmanager&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A simple SSH alerting rule&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A compactor with a four-week retention period&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Other custom parameters&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s create a playbook named &lt;code&gt;function_loki-customized.play&lt;/code&gt; for this customized deployment:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;yaml&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;- name: Deploy Loki using the local filesystem&#xA;hosts: loki&#xA;become: true&#xA;roles:&#xA;- role: grafana.grafana.loki&#xA;vars:&#xA;loki_querier:&#xA;max_concurrent: 16&#xA;engine:&#xA;max_look_back_period: 672h&#xA;loki_storage_config:&#xA;tsdb_shipper:&#xA;active_index_directory: &amp;#34;{{ loki_working_path }}/tsdb-index&amp;#34;&#xA;cache_location: &amp;#34;{{ loki_working_path }}/tsdb-cache&amp;#34;&#xA;filesystem:&#xA;directory: &amp;#34;{{ loki_working_path }}/chunks&amp;#34;&#xA;loki_ingester:&#xA;wal:&#xA;enabled: true&#xA;dir: &amp;#34;{{ loki_working_path }}/wal&amp;#34;&#xA;lifecycler:&#xA;address: 127.0.0.1&#xA;ring:&#xA;kvstore:&#xA;store: inmemory&#xA;replication_factor: 1&#xA;final_sleep: 0s&#xA;chunk_idle_period: 1h&#xA;max_chunk_age: 2h&#xA;chunk_target_size: 1048576&#xA;query_store_max_look_back_period: 672h&#xA;loki_limits_config:&#xA;split_queries_by_interval: 0&#xA;reject_old_samples: true&#xA;reject_old_samples_max_age: 168h&#xA;max_query_length: 0&#xA;max_query_series: 50000&#xA;retention_period: 672h&#xA;allow_structured_metadata: false&#xA;max_query_lookback: 672h&#xA;loki_compactor:&#xA;working_directory: &amp;#34;{{ loki_working_path }}/compactor&amp;#34;&#xA;compaction_interval: 10m&#xA;retention_enabled: true&#xA;retention_delete_delay: 2h&#xA;retention_delete_worker_count: 150&#xA;delete_request_store: filesystem&#xA;loki_common:&#xA;path_prefix: &amp;#34;{{ loki_working_path }}&amp;#34;&#xA;storage:&#xA;filesystem:&#xA;rules_directory: &amp;#34;{{ loki_working_path }}/rules&amp;#34;&#xA;replication_factor: 1&#xA;ring:&#xA;instance_addr: 127.0.0.1&#xA;kvstore:&#xA;store: inmemory&#xA;loki_ruler:&#xA;rule_path: &amp;#34;{{ loki_working_path }}/rules_tmp&amp;#34;&#xA;ring:&#xA;kvstore:&#xA;store: inmemory&#xA;enable_api: true&#xA;enable_alertmanager_v2: true&#xA;alertmanager_url: http://localhost:9093&#xA;loki_ruler_alerts:&#xA;- name: Logs.sshd&#xA;rules:&#xA;- alert: SshLoginFailed&#xA;expr: |&#xA;count_over_time({job=~&amp;#34;secure&amp;#34;} |=&amp;#34;sshd[&amp;#34; |~&amp;#34;: Failed|: Invalid|: Connection closed by authenticating user&amp;#34; | __error__=&amp;#34;&amp;#34; [15m]) &amp;gt; 6&#xA;for: 0m&#xA;labels:&#xA;severity: critical&#xA;annotations:&#xA;summary: &amp;#34;{% raw %}SSH authentication failure (instance {{ $labels.instance }}).{% endraw %}&amp;#34;&#xA;description: &amp;#34;{% raw %}Increase of SSH authentication failures in last 15 minutes\\n VALUE = {{ $value }}{% endraw %}&amp;#34;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that your customized Loki instance is deployed and ready to use, the next step is to send logs to Loki. There are various ways to send logs to Loki, such as using Grafana Alloy or Promtail. All methods are described in &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/send-data/&#34;&gt;this section of the documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once your logs are in Loki, you can query them using the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/query/logcli/&#34;&gt;LogCLI utility&lt;/a&gt; or Grafana. However, before you can explore logs from Grafana, you must connect the &amp;ldquo;Loki&amp;rdquo; data source in your Grafana instance. If you&amp;rsquo;re deploying Grafana via Ansible, note that the Grafana Ansible role is included in the same collection. You can configure this data source in your inventory and re-run the Grafana Ansible role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re not using the Ansible role, you can simply add the data source as described in the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/datasources/#manage-data-sources&#34;&gt;documentation on managing data sources&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the data source is set up, simply navigate to your Grafana URL, followed by &amp;ldquo;/explore,&amp;rdquo; and select the &amp;ldquo;Loki&amp;rdquo; data source to start exploring your logs. For more details on how to explore logs in Grafana, check out &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/logs-integration/&#34;&gt;this section of the documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One more thing: The role is idempotent, designed to deploy Loki with configurations aligned to your inventory. If you want to clean up and remove the entire deployment, simply use the &lt;code&gt;loki_uninstall&lt;/code&gt; tag. If no tag is specified, the role operates in deployment mode.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet &#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;ansible-playbook function_loki-customized.play -t loki_uninstall&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s next?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your Loki instance is now up and running — congrats! — and I assume your logs are being delivered to Loki.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To continue learning about Loki, try creating amazing dashboards tailored to your needs. If you need inspiration, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/dashboards/f/EVO2J4Hnz/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;NGINX logs dashboard&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;/orgs/voidquark&#34;&gt;my dashboards&lt;/a&gt; like SSH Logs, Promtail Monitoring, SUDO Logs or Nextcloud Logs, which utilize Loki as a data source. You can also explore the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/configure/&#34;&gt;Loki configuration&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection/tree/main/roles/loki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Loki role&lt;/a&gt; documentation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wish you a smooth deployment and lots of enjoyment on your Loki journey! And if managing the Loki stack seems overwhelming, consider &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;. With Grafana Cloud, you can enjoy hassle-free log management without the need to manage Loki.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Michal Vaško 是 cloudWerkstatt 的一名 DevOps 工程师，对开源技术充满热情，并且深爱可观察性。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然运营或平台团队长期以来一直依赖指标的可见性来快速做出反应，但对日志执行相同操作的想法曾经只是一个梦想。值得庆幸的是，&lt;a href=&#34;/oss/loki/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki&lt;/a&gt; 彻底改变了日志记录堆栈，为您提供与指标相同级别的日志可见性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您还没有开始 Loki 之旅，现在是 Loki 3.0 发布的时候了！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有多种部署方法可用于各种部署模式：Helm、Tanka、Docker 或 Docker Compose、本地和来自源。有关所有这些方法的更多详细信息，您可以参阅 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/setup/install/&#34;&gt;Grafana Loki 安装指南&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所有这些安装方法都很棒，能够满足其目的并为用户提供灵活性，以便您可以以适合您的特定场景的方式部署 Loki。但让我向您介绍另一种方法 - Ansible Loki 角色。此角色支持 Debian、Ubuntu 和 Red Hat。最初从 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/voidquark/loki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Voidquark 的 Loki 存储库&lt;/a&gt; 迁移到 &lt;a href=&#34;https:// github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Ansible 集合&lt;/a&gt;，我很高兴能够参与该角色的持续维护和改进。&lt; /p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;出于可扩展性的原因，Loki 的部署主要集中在 Kubernetes 上。但如果你还没有处于那个阶段怎么办？或者您只是想尝试一下？或者您有一个小型组织，需要部署 Loki 并且您已经熟悉 Ansible？好吧，您来对地方了。让我们深入了解这个 Ansible 角色的设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-need-to-get-started&#34;&gt;您需要什么才能开始&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;确保您部署了 Ansible 控制器。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;在 Ansible 控制器上安装 Ansible Grafana 集合。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;熟悉&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection/blob/main/roles/loki/README.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer &#34;&gt;Ansible Loki 角色的自述文件&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;创建一个简单的默认剧本或对其进行自定义以满足您的要求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我假设您已经设置了 Ansible 并阅读了 Loki 角色自述文件以更加熟悉它。 &lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;现在，让我们继续安装 Ansible Grafana 集合：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;ansible-galaxy 集合安装 grafana.grafana&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-use-the-default-deployment&#34;&gt;如何使用默认部署&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们演示一下使用默认配置的开箱即用部署。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;首先，创建一个名为 &lt;code&gt;function_loki-default.play&lt;/code&gt; 的 playbook。该剧本非常简单，并使用默认设置部署 Loki。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;yaml&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;- name：使用默认配置部署 Loki&#xA;主持人：洛基&#xA;成为：真实&#xA;角色：&#xA;- 角色：grafana.grafana.loki&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;接下来，执行此 playbook 来部署 Loki：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;ansible-playbook function_loki-default.play&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;Loki 的默认部署现已到位，但大多数人会根据自己的需要对其进行调整。让我们继续自定义它。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-customize-your-deployment&#34;&gt;如何自定义部署&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您想进一步修改怎么办？好吧，你不受限制！您可以完全按照您的意愿配置每个组件。让我们深入研究一个我们将使用的示例：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;文件系统存储&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;带有 Alertmanager 的标尺&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;简单的 SSH 警报规则&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;保留期为四个星期的压实机&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;其他自定义参数&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们为此自定义部署创建一个名为 &lt;code&gt;function_loki-customized.play&lt;/code&gt; 的剧本：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;yaml&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-yaml&#34;&gt;- name：使用本地文件系统部署 Loki&#xA;主持人：洛基&#xA;成为：真实&#xA;角色：&#xA;- 角色：grafana.grafana.loki&#xA;变量：&#xA;洛基查询器：&#xA;最大并发数：16&#xA;引擎：&#xA;最大回看周期：672小时&#xA;loki_存储_配置：&#xA;tsdb_shipper：&#xA;active_index_directory：“{{ loki_working_path }}/tsdb-index”&#xA;缓存位置：“{{ loki_working_path }}/tsdb-cache”&#xA;文件系统：&#xA;目录：“{{ loki_working_path }}/chunks”&#xA;洛基摄取：&#xA;沃尔：&#xA;启用：真&#xA;目录：“{{ loki_working_path }}/wal”&#xA;生命周期者：&#xA;地址：127.0.0.1&#xA;戒指：&#xA;kvstore:&#xA;存储：内存中&#xA;复制因子：1&#xA;最终睡眠：0 秒&#xA;块空闲周期：1小时&#xA;最大块年龄：2小时&#xA;块目标大小：1048576&#xA;query_store_max_look_back_period: 672h&#xA;loki_limits_config：&#xA;按间隔分割查询：0&#xA;拒绝旧样本：true&#xA;拒绝旧样本最大年龄：168小时&#xA;最大查询长度：0&#xA;最大查询系列：50000&#xA;保留期：672小时&#xA;允许结构化元数据：假&#xA;最大查询回顾：672h&#xA;洛基压缩器：&#xA;工作目录：“{{ loki_working_path }}/compactor”&#xA;压实间隔：10m&#xA;保留启用：真&#xA;保留删除延迟：2小时&#xA;保留删除工作人员计数：150&#xA;删除请求存储：文件系统&#xA;洛基常见：&#xA;路径前缀：“{{ loki_working_path }}”&#xA;贮存：&#xA;文件系统：&#xA;规则目录：“{{ loki_working_path }}/规则”&#xA;复制因子：1&#xA;戒指：&#xA;实例地址：127.0.0.1&#xA;kvstore:&#xA;存储：内存中&#xA;洛基统治者：&#xA;规则路径：“{{ loki_working_path }}/rules_tmp”&#xA;戒指：&#xA;kvstore:&#xA;存储：内存中&#xA;启用_API：真&#xA;启用警报管理器v2：真&#xA;Alertmanager_url：http://localhost:9093&#xA;loki_ruler_alerts：&#xA;- 名称：Logs.sshd&#xA;规则：&#xA;- 警报：SshLoginFailed&#xA;表达式: |&#xA;count_over_time({job=~&#34;secure&#34;} |=&#34;sshd[&#34; |~&#34;: 失败|: 无效|: 通过验证用户身份关闭连接&#34; | __error__=&#34;&#34; [15m]) &gt; 6&#xA;对于：0米&#xA;标签：&#xA;严重程度：严重&#xA;注释：&#xA;摘要：“{% raw %}SSH 身份验证失败（实例 {{ $labels.instance }}）。{% endraw %}”&#xA;描述：“{% raw %}过去 15 分钟内 SSH 身份验证失败次数增加\\n VALUE = {{ $value }}{% endraw %}”&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;现在您的自定义 Loki 实例已部署并可供使用，下一步是将日志发送到 Loki。有多种方法可以将日志发送到 Loki，例如使用 Grafana Alloy 或 Promtail。 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/send-data/&#34;&gt;文档的这一部分&lt;/a&gt;中描述了所有方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一旦您的日志位于 Loki 中，您就可以使用 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/query/logcli/&#34;&gt;LogCLI 实用程序&lt;/a&gt; 或 Grafana 查询它们。但是，在从 Grafana 探索日志之前，您必须连接 Grafana 实例中的“Loki”数据源。如果您通过 Ansible 部署 Grafana，请注意 Grafana Ansible 角色包含在同一集合中。您可以在清单中配置此数据源并重新运行 Grafana Ansible 角色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您不使用 Ansible 角色，则只需按照&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/datasources/#manage-data-sources&#34;&gt;有关管理数据的文档中所述添加数据源即可来源&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;设置数据源后，只需导航到 Grafana URL，然后选择“/explore”，然后选择“Loki”数据源即可开始探索日志。有关如何在 Grafana 中探索日志的更多详细信息，请查看&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/explore/logs-integration/&#34;&gt;文档的这一部分&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;还有一件事：该角色是幂等的，旨在使用与您的库存一致的配置来部署 Loki。如果您想清理并删除整个部署，只需使用 &lt;code&gt;loki_uninstall&lt;/code&gt; 标记即可。如果不指定标签，则角色在部署模式下运行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;lang-toolbar__item&#34;&gt;bash&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;按钮 x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;将代码复制到剪贴板&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/按钮&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__border&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;ansible-playbook function_loki-customized.play -t loki_uninstall&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-next&#34;&gt;下一步是什么？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您的 Loki 实例现已启动并运行 - 恭喜！ - 我假设你的日志正在发送给 Loki。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要继续了解 Loki，请尝试根据您的需求创建令人惊叹的仪表板。如果您需要灵感，请查看 &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/dashboards/f/EVO2J4Hnz/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;NGINX 日志仪表板&lt;/a&gt; 或&lt;a href=&#34;/orgs/voidquark&#34;&gt;我的仪表板&lt;/a&gt;，例如 SSH 日志、Promtail 监控、SUDO 日志或 Nextcloud 日志，它们利用 Loki 作为数据源。您还可以探索 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/configure/&#34;&gt;Loki 配置&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana-ansible-collection/tree /main/roles/loki&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Loki 角色&lt;/a&gt;文档。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;祝您部署顺利，Loki 之旅愉快！如果管理 Loki 堆栈似乎令人难以承受，请考虑 &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;。借助 Grafana Cloud，您可以享受无忧的日志管理，而无需管理 Loki。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【ObservabilityCON 2024: Register and reserve your spot today!】ObservabilityCON 2024：立即注册并预订席位！</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/06/26/observabilitycon-2024-register-and-reserve-your-spot-today/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Start spreading the news: registration is officially open for &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;, taking place September 24-25 in New York City!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Join us at our flagship observability event to explore all the latest updates to the Grafana LGTM Stack (&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; for logs, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; for visualization, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/tempo/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt; for traces, and &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt; for metrics), connect with industry experts, and get actionable advice to advance your organization’s observability strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;register now&lt;/a&gt; to take advantage of early bird pricing and save 50% on a standard full-price ticket. Limited tickets are available at this discounted rate — and they’re bound to sell out in a New York minute — so reserve your spot today!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;btn-row &#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn--primary &#34; href=&#34;https://grafana.com/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Register for ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;observabilitycon-2024-agenda-spotlight-hands-on-workshops&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024 agenda spotlight: Hands-on workshops&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have an informative, inspiring, and jam-packed agenda planned for ObservabilityCON 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the opening keynote, technical deep-dive sessions, and lessons learned from the community, we’re offering &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;hands-on workshops&lt;/a&gt; on September 24 to help you sharpen your technical skills, learn how to get started with OpenTelemetry, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This year’s workshop line-up includes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-observability-with-grafana-cloudhttpsgrafanacomeventsobservabilitycon2024workshopsintro-to-observability-with-grafana-cloudpgblogplcmtbody-txt&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-observability-with-grafana-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Introduction to observability with Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1200px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-observability-with-grafana-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png?w=320 320w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png?w=550 550w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png?w=750 750w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png?w=900 900w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;The session card for the Grafana Cloud workshop.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1200&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;628&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;The session card for the Grafana Cloud workshop.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1200&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;628&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn best practices to monitor modern applications and use Grafana Cloud&amp;rsquo;s observability workflows to identify issues, troubleshoot, and find root causes quickly. Through a combination of metrics, logs, traces, and black box monitoring, you&amp;rsquo;ll gain practical insights into observability techniques, and have the opportunity to observe a modern microservices application running on Kubernetes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-opentelemetryhttpsgrafanacomeventsobservabilitycon2024workshopsintro-to-opentelemetrypgblogplcmtbody-txt&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-opentelemetry/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Introduction to OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1200px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-opentelemetry/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png?w=320 320w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png?w=550 550w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png?w=750 750w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png?w=900 900w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;The session card for the OpenTelemetry workshop.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1200&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;628&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;The session card for the OpenTelemetry workshop.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1200&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;628&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Explore the fundamentals of OpenTelemetry — including signals, terms, tools, and best practices — for modern observability, and learn how to get started quickly with these open standards with Grafana Cloud. You’ll walk through powerful monitoring and troubleshooting workflows to reduce MTTR, and use OpenTelemetry signals to debug and resolve a problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-grafana-cloud-logs-powered-by-lokihttpsgrafanacomeventsobservabilitycon2024workshopsintro-to-grafana-cloud-logs-powered-by-lokipgblogplcmtbody-txt&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-grafana-cloud-logs-powered-by-loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Introduction to Grafana Cloud Logs powered by Loki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1200px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-grafana-cloud-logs-powered-by-loki/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=320 320w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=550 550w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=750 750w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=900 900w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;The session card for the Cloud Logs workshop.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1200&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;628&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;The session card for the Cloud Logs workshop.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1200&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;628&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn how to get started with Grafana Cloud Logs, a fully managed logging system powered by Grafana Loki. Guided by our expert solutions engineers, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn best practices and workflows for shipping, exploring, querying, and visualizing log data. You’ll also get to experience the power of the Explore Logs app to quickly navigate through vast amounts of log data, and learn how to uncover valuable insights from log patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: a &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;separate ticket&lt;/a&gt; is required to attend a workshop, and can only be purchased alongside a full conference ticket.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Want to learn more about the ObservabilityCON 2024 agenda overall? Stay tuned! We’ll have more details for you soon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;justify-your-trip&#34;&gt;Justify your trip&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We know your time is valuable — which is why your manager might ask what you’ll get out of ObservabilityCON 2024 before approving you to go.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’re confident you’ll walk away from the event with practical advice you can apply to your job and share with your team the very next day. In addition to advancing your technical skills, you’ll learn observability strategies that can drive real business impact, helping to increase customer satisfaction at your organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But don&amp;rsquo;t take our word for it — check out what &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/02/09/inside-observabilitycon-i-picked-up-so-much-practical-information/&#34;&gt;one engineer said about attending ObservabilityCON&lt;/a&gt;. And if you need more help justifying your trip, you can send this &lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/justify-your-attendance/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;prepared letter&lt;/a&gt;, outlining the costs and benefits of attending ObservabilityCON 2024, to your manager.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can’t wait to see you in September!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The countdown to &lt;a href=&#34;/about/events/observabilitycon/2024/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt; has officially begun! We’ll be sure to keep you posted on all the latest updates. And if you want to explore other upcoming events — both in-person and virtual — check out the &lt;a href=&#34;/events/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs events page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;开始传播消息：&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt; 正式开放报名，将于 9 月 24 日至 25 日在纽约市举行！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;加入我们的旗舰可观测性活动，探索 Grafana LGTM Stack (&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki&lt;/a&gt; for日志，&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt; 用于可视化，&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/tempo/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body -txt&#34;&gt;Tempo&lt;/a&gt; 用于跟踪，&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir&lt;/a&gt; 用于指标），与行业专家联系，以及获取可行的建议来推进组织的可观察性策略。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即注册&lt;/a&gt;，享受早鸟价，购买标准全价门票可节省 50% 的费用。门票数量有限，可按此折扣价购买 - 而且它们一定会在纽约一分钟内售完 - 所以今天就预订吧！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;btn-row &#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn--primary&#34; href=&#34;https://grafana.com/events/observabilitycon/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer &#34;&gt;注册 ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;observabilitycon-2024-agenda-spotlight-hands-on-workshops&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024 议程聚焦：实践研讨会&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们为 ObservabilityCON 2024 制定了内容丰富、鼓舞人心且内容丰富的议程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;除了开幕主题演讲、技术深入探讨会议以及从社区吸取的经验教训之外，我们还提供&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; &gt;9 月 24 日举办的实践研讨会&lt;/a&gt;可帮助您提高技术技能、学习如何开始使用 OpenTelemetry 等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今年的研讨会阵容包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-observability-with-grafana-cloudhttpsgrafanacomeventsobservabilitycon2024workshopsintro-to-observability-with-grafana-cloudpgblogplcmtbody-txt&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-observability- with-grafana-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud 的可观测性简介&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图形包装器w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1200px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-observability-with-grafana-cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png”data-srcset =“/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs。 png?w=320 320w，/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍-obs.png?w=550 550w，/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍- obs.png?w=750 750w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍-obs.png?w=900 900w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍- to-obs.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24--- obs 介绍.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud 研讨会的会话卡。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1200”&#xA;高度=“628”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-obs.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana Cloud 研讨会的会议卡。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1200”&#xA;高度=“628”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;学习监控现代应用程序的最佳实践，并使用 Grafana Cloud 的可观察性工作流程来快速识别问题、排除故障并找到根本原因。通过指标、日志、跟踪和黑盒监控的组合，您将获得对可观测性技术的实用见解，并有机会观察在 Kubernetes 上运行的现代微服务应用程序。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-opentelemetryhttpsgrafanacomeventsobservabilitycon2024workshopsintro-to-opentelemetrypgblogplcmtbody-txt&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-opentelemetry/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;简介开放遥测&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图形包装器w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1200px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-opentelemetry/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---OTel 简介.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---OTel 简介。 png?w=320 320w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍-OTel.png?w=550 550w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍- OTel.png?w=750 750w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍-OTel.png?w=900 900w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍- to-OTel.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---介绍-to-OTel.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24--- OTel 简介.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OpenTelemetry 研讨会的会议卡。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1200”&#xA;高度=“628”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src=&#34;/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24---intro-to-OTel.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;OpenTelemetry 研讨会的会议卡。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1200”&#xA;高度=“628”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;探索 OpenTelemetry 的基础知识（包括信号、术语、工具和最佳实践）以实现现代可观测性，并了解如何通过 Grafana Cloud 快速开始使用这些开放标准。您将逐步了解强大的监控和故障排除工作流程以减少 MTTR，并使用 OpenTelemetry 信号来调试和解决问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-grafana-cloud-logs-powered-by-lokihttpsgrafanacomeventsobservabilitycon2024workshopsintro-to-grafana-cloud-logs-powered-by-lokipgblogplcmtbody-txt&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/ Workshops/intro-to-grafana-cloud-logs-powered-by-loki/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;由 Loki 提供支持的 Grafana Cloud 日志简介&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;类=“图形包装器w-100p”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：1200px；”&#xA;itemprop =“关联媒体”&#xA;项目范围=“”&#xA;itemtype =“http://schema.org/ImageObject”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;一&#xA;类=“灯箱链接”&#xA;href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/intro-to-grafana-cloud-logs-powered-by-loki/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&#xA;itemprop=“内容网址”&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;类=“延迟加载”&#xA;data-src =“/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png”data-srcset =“/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png？w = 320 320w，/media/events/ obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=550 550w，/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=750 750w，/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png？ w=900 900w，/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png？w=1040 1040w，/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png？w=1240 1240w，/media/events/ obscon/注册/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Cloud Logs 研讨会的会话卡。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1200”&#xA;高度=“628”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;无脚本&gt;&#xA;&lt;图片&#xA;src =“/media/events/obscon/registration/Obscon24-intro_gcloudlogs.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Cloud Logs 研讨会的会话卡。&#34;&#xA;宽度=“1200”&#xA;高度=“628”&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/图&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解如何开始使用 Grafana Cloud Logs，这是一个由 Grafana Loki 提供支持的完全托管日志系统。在我们的专家解决方案工程师的指导下，您将学习运输、探索、查询和可视化日志数据的最佳实践和工作流程。您还将体验探索日志应用程序的强大功能，以快速浏览大量日志数据，并了解如何从日志模式中发现有价值的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：参加研讨会需要&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/workshops/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;单独的门票&lt;/a&gt;，并且只能与完整的会议门票一起购买。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;想要详细了解 ObservabilityCON 2024 的总体议程吗？敬请关注！我们很快就会为您提供更多详细信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;justify-your-trip&#34;&gt;证明你的旅行合理&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们知道您的时间很宝贵 - 这就是为什么您的经理在批准您参加之前可能会询问您将从 ObservabilityCON 2024 中获得什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们相信您在结束活动时会得到实用的建议，这些建议可以应用到您的工作中，并在第二天与您的团队分享。除了提高您的技术技能之外，您还将学习可观察性策略，这些策略可以推动真正的业务影响，帮助提高组织的客户满意度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但不要相信我们的话 - 看看&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/02/09/inside-observabilitycon-i-picked-up-so-much-practical-information/&#34;&gt;一位工程师谈到参加 ObservabilityCON&lt;/a&gt;。如果您需要更多帮助证明您的旅行合理性，您可以发送这封&lt;a href=&#34;/events/observabilitycon/2024/justify-your-attendance/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;准备好的信件&lt;/a&gt;，概述向您的经理介绍参加 ObservabilityCON 2024 的成本和收益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们迫不及待地想在九月见到您！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/about/events/observabilitycon/2024/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;ObservabilityCON 2024&lt;/a&gt; 倒计时已正式开始！我们一定会及时向您通报所有最新动态。如果您想探索其他即将举行的活动（现场活动和虚拟活动），请查看 &lt;a href=&#34;/events/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Labs 活动页面&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em &gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Industrial IoT visualization: Why United Manufacturing Hub chose Grafana to power its IIoT platform】工业物联网可视化：为什么 United Manufacturing Hub 选择 Grafana 为其 IIoT 平台提供支持</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/01/industrial-iot-visualization-why-united-manufacturing-hub-chose-grafana-to-power-its-iiot-platform/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Denis Gontcharov is a data consultant who helps aluminum smelters break down data barriers. For the past five years, he has supported the aluminum industry with IT and data services as an independent consultant. Denis also works as a Developer Advocate at the United Manufacturing Hub.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jeremy Theocharis is co-founder and CTO at United Manufacturing Hub. He is an expert in industrial IoT with over seven years of experience leading large-scale IIoT projects in various industries. With a background in mechanical engineering and business administration, he has been a programmer since he was 14 years old and has published several articles on topics such as scalable data processing in IIoT.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most IT professionals are familiar with Grafana as a visualization tool to monitor IT telemetry data, such as CPU consumption. Grafana is also, however, a powerful tool for industrial IoT (IIoT) — which is why our team at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umh.app/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;United Manufacturing Hub (UMH)&lt;/a&gt;, a startup that provides an open source industrial IoT platform for enterprise manufacturers, chose to leverage Grafana in our core product.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll explore why UMH grew frustrated with specialized industrial visualization solutions, how those solutions compare to Grafana in the IIoT space, and, lastly, how Grafana is creating a positive business impact for manufacturers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-data-visualization-from-home-automation-to-iiot&#34;&gt;Grafana data visualization: from home automation to IIoT&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana has become the de facto standard for visualization in IIoT. At major industrial fairs, such as the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hannovermesse.de/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Hannover Messe&lt;/a&gt; in Germany (one of the largest in the world), Grafana is prominently featured at many IIoT booths. Dashboards built with Grafana display data from all layers of the manufacturing enterprise: from the boardroom all the way to the shop floor. While the CEO observes their company’s high-level financial KPIs, the machine operator can keep a watchful eye on the critical parameters and real-time process values.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But how, exactly, did Grafana gain such widespread adoption in manufacturing? At UMH, we believe it’s because Grafana found its entry via the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/01/10/how-to-set-up-home-automation-a-beginners-guide-with-grafana-cloud-and-home-assistant/&#34;&gt;home automation niche&lt;/a&gt;, where it became popular for visualizing metrics from IoT sensors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hobbyists experimenting with Grafana in personal projects realized its potential at work. After all, if you can display the temperature of your living room in real time, why not the temperature of your melting furnace on the manufacturing floor? This realization is what led the team at UMH to choose Grafana for visualizing client’s sensor data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-grafana-beats-existing-industrial-technologies&#34;&gt;Why Grafana beats existing industrial technologies&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But wait — why did UMH, along with other IIoT vendors at the Hannover Messe, put our faith in Grafana? Why not simply implement any of the existing industrial products that are specifically designed for manufacturing?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The reason is simple: the existing industrial products weren’t meeting our needs. To be fair, some of these tools do have advantages over Grafana in some niche applications. Nevertheless, the market has demonstrated a clear preference for Grafana in general applications. Some of the key reasons for this are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Although the manufacturing industry, being rather traditional, is generally wary of modern open source IT tools, Grafana has a mature reputation, given that it’s been around for over a decade.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open source tools like Grafana are incredibly cost-effective, especially compared to some of the manufacturing-specific solutions, such as industrial &lt;a href=&#34;https://csrc.nist.gov/glossary/term/human_machine_interface&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Human Machine Interfaces (HMIs)&lt;/a&gt;. In essence, businesses can save a lot of money by leveraging a combination of powerful, modern IT technologies, such as Grafana and TimescaleDB (more on that below), rather than stick with more traditional manufacturing solutions and HMIs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;HMIs often have a user interface that feels limited and antiquated compared to Grafana’s sleek and visually compelling dashboards (example below).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=320 320w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=550 550w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=750 750w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=900 900w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard in the UMH platform.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1125&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*A Grafana dashboard designed by UMH community member Diederik Vermeersch, who works at Mayker in Ghent, Belgium.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard in the UMH platform.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1125&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*A Grafana dashboard designed by UMH community member Diederik Vermeersch, who works at Mayker in Ghent, Belgium.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Grafana dashboard designed by UMH community member Diederik Vermeersch, who works at Mayker in Ghent, Belgium.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another advantage of open source tools like Grafana is the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-the-community-behind-the-code/&#34;&gt;large online community&lt;/a&gt; behind them. The availability of public knowledge makes it easy for inexperienced users to find help and ramp up quickly. This means manufacturers won’t get stuck on some niche edge case. There’s also a large &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/dashboards/&#34;&gt;gallery of community dashboard templates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, open source technologies provide unhindered access to data. This may sound trivial, but it’s not uncommon for traditional historians — which are storage and visualization solutions for manufacturing data — to save their data in a proprietary file format, hampering the ability to transfer data to an external system, including those in the public cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main reason, however, that Grafana became so popular is its ease of use. Given Grafana’s single-pane-of-glass approach to data integration, visualizing data from disparate sources is very convenient: there is no need to combine the data in a backend store or some other vendor’s database — you can unify all your data wherever it lives. Once the data is made available in Grafana, it’s easy to create beautiful visualizations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Grafana is a powerful visualization solution for real-time data, it’s not possible to directly send information from Grafana back to an industrial controller (as you can with some specialized industrial solutions). This isn’t a dealbreaker, however. With the &lt;a href=&#34;https://volkovlabs.io/plugins/volkovlabs-form-panel/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Business Forms panel&lt;/a&gt; (previously called the &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/volkovlabs-form-panel/&#34;&gt;Data Manipulation panel&lt;/a&gt;) plugin for Grafana, data can be sent from the dashboard to a database. This workaround allows communication between the Grafana dashboard and the underlying process by means of the database.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-grafana-helps-power-the-umh-stack&#34;&gt;How Grafana helps power the UMH stack&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana is a core component of UMH’s open source &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umh.app/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;IT/OT Integration Platform&lt;/a&gt;. The UMH system operates by initially extracting data from various sources, such as Programmable Logic Controllers (PLCs), which is then streamlined into a central integration point known as the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.umh.app/lesson/chapter-2-the-rise-of-the-unified-namespace/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Unified Namespace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. This framework utilizes &lt;a href=&#34;https://mqtt.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MQTT&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://kafka.apache.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Kafka&lt;/a&gt; to ensure robust data handling. Within this Unified Namespace, time series data — commonly referred to in the industry as &lt;em&gt;tags&lt;/em&gt; (unique identifiers for data points) — is systematically organized and subsequently stored in the open source historian.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Together with the open source &lt;a href=&#34;https://timescale.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;TimescaleDB database&lt;/a&gt;, which is based on PostgreSQL, Grafana forms an essential part of this open source historian setup. The setup not only stores, but elegantly visualizes, time series data from manufacturing and IIoT devices. Grafana excels at making beautiful, real time visualizations of important process metrics and KPIs, such as temperature, flow rates, and overall equipment effectiveness. This way, operators can quickly inspect and diagnose the production process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The UMH platform acts as an invisible interface between Grafana and the TimescaleDB database, making it easy to retrieve the desired data. The platform exposes a “data model” to Grafana that a user can leverage to make graphs without having to write complex SQL queries. This is important in manufacturing, because operational technology (OT) workers are often not comfortable using SQL — plus, you don’t have time to write a query when a machine malfunctions!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1652px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A diagram of UMH&amp;#39;s platform architecture. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1652&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;802&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*The software architecture of the UMH stack, demonstrating the role of Grafana.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A diagram of UMH&amp;#39;s platform architecture. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1652&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;802&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*The software architecture of the UMH stack, demonstrating the role of Grafana.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The software architecture of the UMH stack, demonstrating the role of Grafana.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-umh-uses-grafana-cloud-to-monitor-internal-systems&#34;&gt;How UMH uses Grafana Cloud to monitor internal systems&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to using Grafana OSS as part of our IIoT platform, UMH has also leveraged Grafana Cloud for several years to monitor the internal services that underpin our Management Console. This Management Console enables our users to access their instances from any location, which requires a robust suite of services, including PostgreSQL, Kafka, Redis, and our front end and back end APIs. As long-time users of Grafana Cloud, we channel the logs and metrics from these services into it, setting up alerts and employing Grafana OnCall to address any issues that might affect our service availability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-learn-more&#34;&gt;How to learn more&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to learn more about UMH’s open source &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umh.app/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;IT/OT Integration Platform&lt;/a&gt;, and the role of Grafana, you can explore the &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.umh.app/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;UMH Learning Center&lt;/a&gt;. And if you’re interested in checking out a real industrial use case with Grafana, you can watch this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MTgIp-yqbEY&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;YouTube video&lt;/a&gt; from UMH, which demonstrates how to build a Grafana dashboard to visualize PackML data in under 20 minutes, simply by clicking, dragging, and dropping.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Denis Gontcharov is a data consultant who helps aluminum smelters break down data barriers. For the past five years, he has supported the aluminum industry with IT and data services as an independent consultant. Denis also works as a Developer Advocate at the United Manufacturing Hub.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jeremy Theocharis is co-founder and CTO at United Manufacturing Hub. He is an expert in industrial IoT with over seven years of experience leading large-scale IIoT projects in various industries. With a background in mechanical engineering and business administration, he has been a programmer since he was 14 years old and has published several articles on topics such as scalable data processing in IIoT.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most IT professionals are familiar with Grafana as a visualization tool to monitor IT telemetry data, such as CPU consumption. Grafana is also, however, a powerful tool for industrial IoT (IIoT) — which is why our team at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umh.app/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;United Manufacturing Hub (UMH)&lt;/a&gt;, a startup that provides an open source industrial IoT platform for enterprise manufacturers, chose to leverage Grafana in our core product.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we’ll explore why UMH grew frustrated with specialized industrial visualization solutions, how those solutions compare to Grafana in the IIoT space, and, lastly, how Grafana is creating a positive business impact for manufacturers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-data-visualization-from-home-automation-to-iiot&#34;&gt;Grafana data visualization: from home automation to IIoT&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana has become the de facto standard for visualization in IIoT. At major industrial fairs, such as the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hannovermesse.de/en/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Hannover Messe&lt;/a&gt; in Germany (one of the largest in the world), Grafana is prominently featured at many IIoT booths. Dashboards built with Grafana display data from all layers of the manufacturing enterprise: from the boardroom all the way to the shop floor. While the CEO observes their company’s high-level financial KPIs, the machine operator can keep a watchful eye on the critical parameters and real-time process values.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But how, exactly, did Grafana gain such widespread adoption in manufacturing? At UMH, we believe it’s because Grafana found its entry via the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/01/10/how-to-set-up-home-automation-a-beginners-guide-with-grafana-cloud-and-home-assistant/&#34;&gt;home automation niche&lt;/a&gt;, where it became popular for visualizing metrics from IoT sensors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hobbyists experimenting with Grafana in personal projects realized its potential at work. After all, if you can display the temperature of your living room in real time, why not the temperature of your melting furnace on the manufacturing floor? This realization is what led the team at UMH to choose Grafana for visualizing client’s sensor data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-grafana-beats-existing-industrial-technologies&#34;&gt;Why Grafana beats existing industrial technologies&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But wait — why did UMH, along with other IIoT vendors at the Hannover Messe, put our faith in Grafana? Why not simply implement any of the existing industrial products that are specifically designed for manufacturing?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The reason is simple: the existing industrial products weren’t meeting our needs. To be fair, some of these tools do have advantages over Grafana in some niche applications. Nevertheless, the market has demonstrated a clear preference for Grafana in general applications. Some of the key reasons for this are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Although the manufacturing industry, being rather traditional, is generally wary of modern open source IT tools, Grafana has a mature reputation, given that it’s been around for over a decade.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open source tools like Grafana are incredibly cost-effective, especially compared to some of the manufacturing-specific solutions, such as industrial &lt;a href=&#34;https://csrc.nist.gov/glossary/term/human_machine_interface&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Human Machine Interfaces (HMIs)&lt;/a&gt;. In essence, businesses can save a lot of money by leveraging a combination of powerful, modern IT technologies, such as Grafana and TimescaleDB (more on that below), rather than stick with more traditional manufacturing solutions and HMIs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;HMIs often have a user interface that feels limited and antiquated compared to Grafana’s sleek and visually compelling dashboards (example below).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1999px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=320 320w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=550 550w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=750 750w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=900 900w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard in the UMH platform.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1125&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*A Grafana dashboard designed by UMH community member Diederik Vermeersch, who works at Mayker in Ghent, Belgium.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-dashboard.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana dashboard in the UMH platform.&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1125&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*A Grafana dashboard designed by UMH community member Diederik Vermeersch, who works at Mayker in Ghent, Belgium.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Grafana dashboard designed by UMH community member Diederik Vermeersch, who works at Mayker in Ghent, Belgium.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another advantage of open source tools like Grafana is the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-the-community-behind-the-code/&#34;&gt;large online community&lt;/a&gt; behind them. The availability of public knowledge makes it easy for inexperienced users to find help and ramp up quickly. This means manufacturers won’t get stuck on some niche edge case. There’s also a large &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/dashboards/&#34;&gt;gallery of community dashboard templates&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, open source technologies provide unhindered access to data. This may sound trivial, but it’s not uncommon for traditional historians — which are storage and visualization solutions for manufacturing data — to save their data in a proprietary file format, hampering the ability to transfer data to an external system, including those in the public cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main reason, however, that Grafana became so popular is its ease of use. Given Grafana’s single-pane-of-glass approach to data integration, visualizing data from disparate sources is very convenient: there is no need to combine the data in a backend store or some other vendor’s database — you can unify all your data wherever it lives. Once the data is made available in Grafana, it’s easy to create beautiful visualizations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Grafana is a powerful visualization solution for real-time data, it’s not possible to directly send information from Grafana back to an industrial controller (as you can with some specialized industrial solutions). This isn’t a dealbreaker, however. With the &lt;a href=&#34;https://volkovlabs.io/plugins/volkovlabs-form-panel/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Business Forms panel&lt;/a&gt; (previously called the &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/plugins/volkovlabs-form-panel/&#34;&gt;Data Manipulation panel&lt;/a&gt;) plugin for Grafana, data can be sent from the dashboard to a database. This workaround allows communication between the Grafana dashboard and the underlying process by means of the database.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-grafana-helps-power-the-umh-stack&#34;&gt;How Grafana helps power the UMH stack&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana is a core component of UMH’s open source &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umh.app/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;IT/OT Integration Platform&lt;/a&gt;. The UMH system operates by initially extracting data from various sources, such as Programmable Logic Controllers (PLCs), which is then streamlined into a central integration point known as the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.umh.app/lesson/chapter-2-the-rise-of-the-unified-namespace/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Unified Namespace&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. This framework utilizes &lt;a href=&#34;https://mqtt.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MQTT&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://kafka.apache.org/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Kafka&lt;/a&gt; to ensure robust data handling. Within this Unified Namespace, time series data — commonly referred to in the industry as &lt;em&gt;tags&lt;/em&gt; (unique identifiers for data points) — is systematically organized and subsequently stored in the open source historian.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Together with the open source &lt;a href=&#34;https://timescale.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;TimescaleDB database&lt;/a&gt;, which is based on PostgreSQL, Grafana forms an essential part of this open source historian setup. The setup not only stores, but elegantly visualizes, time series data from manufacturing and IIoT devices. Grafana excels at making beautiful, real time visualizations of important process metrics and KPIs, such as temperature, flow rates, and overall equipment effectiveness. This way, operators can quickly inspect and diagnose the production process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The UMH platform acts as an invisible interface between Grafana and the TimescaleDB database, making it easy to retrieve the desired data. The platform exposes a “data model” to Grafana that a user can leverage to make graphs without having to write complex SQL queries. This is important in manufacturing, because operational technology (OT) workers are often not comfortable using SQL — plus, you don’t have time to write a query when a machine malfunctions!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1652px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;A diagram of UMH&amp;#39;s platform architecture. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1652&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;802&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*The software architecture of the UMH stack, demonstrating the role of Grafana.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/united-manufacturing-hub/umh-IIoT-and-grafana-architecture-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A diagram of UMH&amp;#39;s platform architecture. &#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1652&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;802&#34;&#xA;title=&#34;*The software architecture of the UMH stack, demonstrating the role of Grafana.*&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The software architecture of the UMH stack, demonstrating the role of Grafana.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-umh-uses-grafana-cloud-to-monitor-internal-systems&#34;&gt;How UMH uses Grafana Cloud to monitor internal systems&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition to using Grafana OSS as part of our IIoT platform, UMH has also leveraged Grafana Cloud for several years to monitor the internal services that underpin our Management Console. This Management Console enables our users to access their instances from any location, which requires a robust suite of services, including PostgreSQL, Kafka, Redis, and our front end and back end APIs. As long-time users of Grafana Cloud, we channel the logs and metrics from these services into it, setting up alerts and employing Grafana OnCall to address any issues that might affect our service availability.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-learn-more&#34;&gt;How to learn more&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to learn more about UMH’s open source &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umh.app/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;IT/OT Integration Platform&lt;/a&gt;, and the role of Grafana, you can explore the &lt;a href=&#34;https://learn.umh.app/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;UMH Learning Center&lt;/a&gt;. And if you’re interested in checking out a real industrial use case with Grafana, you can watch this &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MTgIp-yqbEY&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;YouTube video&lt;/a&gt; from UMH, which demonstrates how to build a Grafana dashboard to visualize PackML data in under 20 minutes, simply by clicking, dragging, and dropping.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana 11.1 release: new visualization features, Grafana Alerting updates, and more】Grafana 11.1 版本：新的可视化功能、Grafana 警报更新等</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/06/25/grafana-11.1-release-new-visualization-features-grafana-alerting-updates-and-more/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;The Grafana 11.1 minor release comes on the heels of unveiling &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=96ZXShRyMB8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana 11&lt;/a&gt; at GrafanaCON, but it packs in some ease of use visualization improvements, updates to Grafana Alerting (I spy a new settings page), and some impactful changes to the overall accessibility of Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;btn-row &#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn--primary &#34; href=&#34;https://grafana.com/grafana/download/11.1.0/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt-btn&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana 11.1: download now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gjQX9-7Hsfs&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For even more details about all the changes in this release, refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;changelog&lt;/a&gt; or the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/whatsnew/whats-new-in-v11-1/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s New documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-in-grafana-dashboards-and-visualizations&#34;&gt;New in Grafana dashboards and visualizations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;text-wrapping-in-table-panel&#34;&gt;Text wrapping in table panel&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Available in public preview across all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most requested features among the Grafana community is here! We&amp;rsquo;ve enabled text wrapping within cells for the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/table/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;table panel&lt;/a&gt;, making convoluted, long lines of text easier to read without the need to scroll across the screen or expand the column size.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, the column with the longest text will be selected for wrapping. Alternatively, you can manually configure wrapping using field overrides.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wBLxYp2BLAU&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;customize-percent-change-colors-in-stat-panels&#34;&gt;Customize percent change colors in stat panels&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available across all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/stat/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;stat visualizations&lt;/a&gt;, the standard behavior for a percent change is to display positive changes in green and negative changes in red. Depending on your use case, however, we realize you might want to customize the colors that represent percent changes. Now, you have the option to &lt;strong&gt;invert&lt;/strong&gt; the percent change color, showing positive changes in red and negative changes in green. You can also select &lt;strong&gt;same as value&lt;/strong&gt;, which would have the percent change stat match the color of its associated value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/LrkR6_hcqPc&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;visualize-x-and-y-values-in-the-xy-chart&#34;&gt;Visualize x and y values in the XY chart&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;XY charts — which are now generally available in Grafana 11.1 — help you visualize arbitrary x and y values in a graph so you can easily show the relationship between two variables. XY charts are typically used to create scatter plots, but you can also use them to create bubble charts where field values determine the size of each bubble.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3d3Lx-Jz_kM&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the panel, refer to &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/xy-chart/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;our XY charts documentation&lt;/a&gt;. To use the new XY chart visualization, you must first enable the &lt;code&gt;autoMigrateXYChartPanel&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-grafana/feature-toggles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;feature toggle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana visualizations&lt;/a&gt; documentation to learn more about these visualization features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-alerting-new-and-improved-features&#34;&gt;Grafana Alerting: new and improved features&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;new-holistic-view-of-grafana-managed-alert-instances&#34;&gt;New holistic view of Grafana-managed alert instances&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The redesigned settings page provides you with a holistic view of where Grafana-managed alert instances are forwarded, which allows you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Manage which Alertmanagers receive alert instances from Grafana-managed rules without navigating and editing data sources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Manage version snapshots for the built-in Alertmanager, which allows administrators to roll back unintentional changes or mistakes in the Alertmanager configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use a visual diff to compare the historical snapshot with the latest configuration to see which changes were made.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1342px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=320 320w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=550 550w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=750 750w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=900 900w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Alert settings page&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1342&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1106&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Alert settings page&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1342&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1106&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;alert-templates-for-notification-messages&#34;&gt;Alert templates for notification messages&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The alert template selector enables you to easily choose which templates you want to use in your alert notification messages by adding a template selector in the Contact Points form.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can select from existing templates or enter a custom one for your specific needs. And to make things easier, you can switch between the two tabs to access the list of available templates and copy them across to the customized version.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;oauth2-authentication-for-alertmanager-or-grafana-mimir&#34;&gt;OAuth2 authentication for Alertmanager or Grafana Mimir&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Grafana 11.1, you can configure OAuth2 authentication for any Alertmanager or Mimir receiver (called Contact Points in Grafana) through the user interface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: OAuth2 is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; implemented for the Grafana built-in Alertmanager.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;improved-paused-alert-visibility&#34;&gt;Improved paused alert visibility&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pause and resume alert rule evaluation directly from the Alert rules list and details view. This helps improve visibility of when alert rules have been paused by displaying “Paused” as the alert rule state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rule-specific-silences-with-permissions&#34;&gt;Rule-specific silences with permissions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now easily create alert silences directly from the Alert rule list view or detail page. These rule-specific silences are guaranteed to only apply to a single rule and permissions to read, create, update, or delete are tied to a user’s permissions for that rule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rule-specific-silences-with-rbac&#34;&gt;Rule-specific silences with RBAC&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in Grafana Enterprise and Grafana Cloud&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Manage silences through Role-Based Access Control (RBAC). In addition to the Grafana open source functionality in &lt;strong&gt;Rule-specific silences with permissions&lt;/strong&gt;, you can choose who can create, edit, and read silences using the following permissions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users with the &lt;strong&gt;alert.silences:create permission&lt;/strong&gt;, scoped within a folder, are able to create silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users with the &lt;strong&gt;alert.silences:read permission&lt;/strong&gt;, scoped within a folder, are able to read silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders, and general silences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users with the &lt;strong&gt;alert.silences:write permission&lt;/strong&gt;, scoped within a folder, are able to expire and recreate silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;accessibility-improvements-in-grafana&#34;&gt;Accessibility improvements in Grafana&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Grafana team is dedicated to improving our user interfaces and overall experience so that our product becomes usable and accessible for everyone. With Grafana 11.1, we are proud to make the following features generally available in all editions of Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Tc0pTXtCsKQ&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;geomap-keyboard-support&#34;&gt;Geomap keyboard support&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/geomap/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;geomap panel&lt;/a&gt; can now be used with a keyboard! Focus the map area, move around with the arrows keys and zoom in and out using &lt;code&gt;+&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;-&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;panel-shortcut-keyboard-support&#34;&gt;Panel shortcut keyboard support&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/use-dashboards/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#keyboard-shortcuts&#34;&gt;panel shortcuts&lt;/a&gt;, which previously only worked on a panel you hovered over. It now also takes into account the keyboard focus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;heading-improvements&#34;&gt;Heading improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The majority of screen reader users &lt;a href=&#34;https://webaim.org/projects/screenreadersurvey10/#finding&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;find things on a web page using headings&lt;/a&gt;. Recently, we have added missing headings and corrected heading levels in some places, most notably panel titles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reduced-motion-support&#34;&gt;Reduced motion support&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users who are affected by a lot of animations on a web site have the possibility to configure &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/CSS/@media/prefers-reduced-motion&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;reduced motion settings&lt;/a&gt;. Grafana now supports this, either by making animations simpler or removing them altogether. We have &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana/tree/main/packages/grafana-eslint-rules#no-unreduced-motion&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;implemented a rule&lt;/a&gt; that prohibits unhandled transitions and animations, ensuring that we can continuously support reduced motion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more-about-grafana-111&#34;&gt;Learn more about Grafana 11.1&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a list of all the new features in Grafana 11.1, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana documentation&lt;/a&gt;, the Grafana &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;changelog&lt;/a&gt;, or our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/whatsnew/whats-new-in-v11-1/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;What’s New documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;join-the-grafana-labs-community&#34;&gt;Join the Grafana Labs community&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We invite you to engage with the Grafana Labs &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;community forums&lt;/a&gt;. Share your experiences with the new features, discuss best practices, and explore creative ways to integrate these updates into your workflows. Your insights and use cases are invaluable in enriching the Grafana ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;upgrade-to-grafana-111&#34;&gt;Upgrade to Grafana 11.1&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/download/11.1.0/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Download Grafana 11.1&lt;/a&gt; today or try out all the new features by signing up for &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;, which offers an actually useful Cloud free tier and plans for every use case. Sign up for a &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;free Grafana Cloud account&lt;/a&gt; today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/upgrade-guide/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana upgrade guide&lt;/a&gt; also provides step-by-step instructions for those looking to upgrade from an earlier version to ensure a smooth transition.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-special-thanks-to-our-community&#34;&gt;A special thanks to our community&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We extend our heartfelt gratitude to the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-the-community-behind-the-code/&#34;&gt;Grafana community&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your contributions, ranging from pull requests to valuable feedback, are crucial in continually enhancing Grafana. And your enthusiasm and dedication inspire us at Grafana Labs to continually innovate and elevate Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous Cloud free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;The Grafana 11.1 minor release comes on the heels of unveiling &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=96ZXShRyMB8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana 11&lt;/a&gt; at GrafanaCON, but it packs in some ease of use visualization improvements, updates to Grafana Alerting (I spy a new settings page), and some impactful changes to the overall accessibility of Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;btn-row &#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;btn btn--primary &#34; href=&#34;https://grafana.com/grafana/download/11.1.0/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt-btn&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana 11.1: download now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/gjQX9-7Hsfs&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For even more details about all the changes in this release, refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;changelog&lt;/a&gt; or the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/whatsnew/whats-new-in-v11-1/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s New documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-in-grafana-dashboards-and-visualizations&#34;&gt;New in Grafana dashboards and visualizations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;text-wrapping-in-table-panel&#34;&gt;Text wrapping in table panel&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Available in public preview across all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most requested features among the Grafana community is here! We&amp;rsquo;ve enabled text wrapping within cells for the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/table/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;table panel&lt;/a&gt;, making convoluted, long lines of text easier to read without the need to scroll across the screen or expand the column size.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, the column with the longest text will be selected for wrapping. Alternatively, you can manually configure wrapping using field overrides.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/wBLxYp2BLAU&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;customize-percent-change-colors-in-stat-panels&#34;&gt;Customize percent change colors in stat panels&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available across all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/stat/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;stat visualizations&lt;/a&gt;, the standard behavior for a percent change is to display positive changes in green and negative changes in red. Depending on your use case, however, we realize you might want to customize the colors that represent percent changes. Now, you have the option to &lt;strong&gt;invert&lt;/strong&gt; the percent change color, showing positive changes in red and negative changes in green. You can also select &lt;strong&gt;same as value&lt;/strong&gt;, which would have the percent change stat match the color of its associated value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/LrkR6_hcqPc&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;visualize-x-and-y-values-in-the-xy-chart&#34;&gt;Visualize x and y values in the XY chart&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;XY charts — which are now generally available in Grafana 11.1 — help you visualize arbitrary x and y values in a graph so you can easily show the relationship between two variables. XY charts are typically used to create scatter plots, but you can also use them to create bubble charts where field values determine the size of each bubble.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/3d3Lx-Jz_kM&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about the panel, refer to &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/xy-chart/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;our XY charts documentation&lt;/a&gt;. To use the new XY chart visualization, you must first enable the &lt;code&gt;autoMigrateXYChartPanel&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-grafana/feature-toggles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;feature toggle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana visualizations&lt;/a&gt; documentation to learn more about these visualization features.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;grafana-alerting-new-and-improved-features&#34;&gt;Grafana Alerting: new and improved features&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;new-holistic-view-of-grafana-managed-alert-instances&#34;&gt;New holistic view of Grafana-managed alert instances&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The redesigned settings page provides you with a holistic view of where Grafana-managed alert instances are forwarded, which allows you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Manage which Alertmanagers receive alert instances from Grafana-managed rules without navigating and editing data sources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Manage version snapshots for the built-in Alertmanager, which allows administrators to roll back unintentional changes or mistakes in the Alertmanager configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use a visual diff to compare the historical snapshot with the latest configuration to see which changes were made.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1342px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=320 320w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=550 550w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=750 750w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=900 900w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Alert settings page&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1342&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1106&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/docs/alerting/alert-settings.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Alert settings page&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1342&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1106&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;alert-templates-for-notification-messages&#34;&gt;Alert templates for notification messages&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The alert template selector enables you to easily choose which templates you want to use in your alert notification messages by adding a template selector in the Contact Points form.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can select from existing templates or enter a custom one for your specific needs. And to make things easier, you can switch between the two tabs to access the list of available templates and copy them across to the customized version.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;oauth2-authentication-for-alertmanager-or-grafana-mimir&#34;&gt;OAuth2 authentication for Alertmanager or Grafana Mimir&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Grafana 11.1, you can configure OAuth2 authentication for any Alertmanager or Mimir receiver (called Contact Points in Grafana) through the user interface.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: OAuth2 is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; implemented for the Grafana built-in Alertmanager.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;improved-paused-alert-visibility&#34;&gt;Improved paused alert visibility&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pause and resume alert rule evaluation directly from the Alert rules list and details view. This helps improve visibility of when alert rules have been paused by displaying “Paused” as the alert rule state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rule-specific-silences-with-permissions&#34;&gt;Rule-specific silences with permissions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in all editions of Grafana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can now easily create alert silences directly from the Alert rule list view or detail page. These rule-specific silences are guaranteed to only apply to a single rule and permissions to read, create, update, or delete are tied to a user’s permissions for that rule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;rule-specific-silences-with-rbac&#34;&gt;Rule-specific silences with RBAC&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Generally available in Grafana Enterprise and Grafana Cloud&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Manage silences through Role-Based Access Control (RBAC). In addition to the Grafana open source functionality in &lt;strong&gt;Rule-specific silences with permissions&lt;/strong&gt;, you can choose who can create, edit, and read silences using the following permissions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users with the &lt;strong&gt;alert.silences:create permission&lt;/strong&gt;, scoped within a folder, are able to create silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users with the &lt;strong&gt;alert.silences:read permission&lt;/strong&gt;, scoped within a folder, are able to read silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders, and general silences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users with the &lt;strong&gt;alert.silences:write permission&lt;/strong&gt;, scoped within a folder, are able to expire and recreate silences for rules contained within that folder and its subfolders.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;accessibility-improvements-in-grafana&#34;&gt;Accessibility improvements in Grafana&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Grafana team is dedicated to improving our user interfaces and overall experience so that our product becomes usable and accessible for everyone. With Grafana 11.1, we are proud to make the following features generally available in all editions of Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;shortcode youtube&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Tc0pTXtCsKQ&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;geomap-keyboard-support&#34;&gt;Geomap keyboard support&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/geomap/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;geomap panel&lt;/a&gt; can now be used with a keyboard! Focus the map area, move around with the arrows keys and zoom in and out using &lt;code&gt;+&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;-&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;panel-shortcut-keyboard-support&#34;&gt;Panel shortcut keyboard support&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/use-dashboards/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#keyboard-shortcuts&#34;&gt;panel shortcuts&lt;/a&gt;, which previously only worked on a panel you hovered over. It now also takes into account the keyboard focus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;heading-improvements&#34;&gt;Heading improvements&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The majority of screen reader users &lt;a href=&#34;https://webaim.org/projects/screenreadersurvey10/#finding&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;find things on a web page using headings&lt;/a&gt;. Recently, we have added missing headings and corrected heading levels in some places, most notably panel titles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;reduced-motion-support&#34;&gt;Reduced motion support&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Users who are affected by a lot of animations on a web site have the possibility to configure &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/docs/Web/CSS/@media/prefers-reduced-motion&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;reduced motion settings&lt;/a&gt;. Grafana now supports this, either by making animations simpler or removing them altogether. We have &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana/tree/main/packages/grafana-eslint-rules#no-unreduced-motion&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;implemented a rule&lt;/a&gt; that prohibits unhandled transitions and animations, ensuring that we can continuously support reduced motion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more-about-grafana-111&#34;&gt;Learn more about Grafana 11.1&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a list of all the new features in Grafana 11.1, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana documentation&lt;/a&gt;, the Grafana &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/grafana/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;changelog&lt;/a&gt;, or our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/whatsnew/whats-new-in-v11-1/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;What’s New documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;join-the-grafana-labs-community&#34;&gt;Join the Grafana Labs community&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We invite you to engage with the Grafana Labs &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;community forums&lt;/a&gt;. Share your experiences with the new features, discuss best practices, and explore creative ways to integrate these updates into your workflows. Your insights and use cases are invaluable in enriching the Grafana ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;upgrade-to-grafana-111&#34;&gt;Upgrade to Grafana 11.1&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/download/11.1.0/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Download Grafana 11.1&lt;/a&gt; today or try out all the new features by signing up for &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;, which offers an actually useful Cloud free tier and plans for every use case. Sign up for a &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;free Grafana Cloud account&lt;/a&gt; today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/upgrade-guide/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana upgrade guide&lt;/a&gt; also provides step-by-step instructions for those looking to upgrade from an earlier version to ensure a smooth transition.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-special-thanks-to-our-community&#34;&gt;A special thanks to our community&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We extend our heartfelt gratitude to the &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/12/the-story-of-grafana-documentary-the-community-behind-the-code/&#34;&gt;Grafana community&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your contributions, ranging from pull requests to valuable feedback, are crucial in continually enhancing Grafana. And your enthusiasm and dedication inspire us at Grafana Labs to continually innovate and elevate Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous Cloud free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Shorten your feedback loop: Java observability with OpenTelemetry, Grafana Cloud, and Digma.ai】缩短反馈循环：使用 OpenTelemetry、Grafana Cloud 和 Digma.ai 实现 Java 可观察性</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/06/21/shorten-your-feedback-loop-java-observability-with-opentelemetry-grafana-cloud-and-digma.ai/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ron Dover is CTO and co-founder of &lt;a href=&#34;http://digma.ai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Digma.ai&lt;/a&gt;, an IDE plugin for code runtime AI analysis to help accelerate development in complex code bases. Ron is a big believer in evidence-based development and a proponent of continuous feedback in all aspects of software engineering.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, software developers have relied on simple logs to understand code execution and troubleshoot issues. Metrics, traces, dashboards, and gauges have predominantly been the domain of IT and infrastructure teams, leaving developers with limited visibility into their application&amp;rsquo;s performance. This division of responsibilities often meant developers only used observability tools reactively when problems arose.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The landscape is shifting with the advent of modern observability solutions. Tools such as &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/opentelemetry/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; have simplified tracing for Java applications, and platforms like Grafana provide a clearer view of application performance, making observability more developer-friendly. Furthermore, specialized tooling like &lt;a href=&#34;http://digma.ai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Digma.ai&lt;/a&gt; is bridging the gap between dashboards and daily coding workflows, empowering developers to utilize observability proactively throughout the entire development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But how does this work in practice? Observability doesn’t do anyone any good if all it does is aggregate data. So our goal in this blog will be to demonstrate how developers can put observability to practical use by &lt;strong&gt;shortening the feedback loop&lt;/strong&gt;. Specifically, we want to shorten the duration between the time a bug or problem is introduced and the time the developer becomes aware of the problem and its source.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;connecting-a-java-app-to-grafana-cloud-and-digmaai&#34;&gt;Connecting a Java app to Grafana Cloud and Digma.ai&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For our example scenario, we’ll connect a sample Spring Boot application to &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;ll also use Digma.ai, a continuous feedback tool that can analyze the app traces right in the IDE. To make this more interesting, we’ll use a new technology called &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/alloy-opentelemetry-collector/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt;, a component-based and easy-to-use open source distribution of &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/collector/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector.&lt;/a&gt; Using Alloy is a simple way to configure which data we want to collect and where we want to send it. The complete pipeline will look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1462px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Workflow diagram&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1462&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;464&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Workflow diagram&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1462&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;464&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The code for this example is located in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/doppleware/spring-petclinic-cf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-connect-your-java-app-to-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;How to connect your Java app to Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll need a Grafana Cloud account to get started. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one already, you can sign up for the free tier using this &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; ( it should take about five seconds).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once that&amp;rsquo;s done, there are a bunch of inputs we’ll need to grab to continue our setup and send data to your newly created application observability instance! On your Grafana homepage, click on the &lt;strong&gt;Configure&lt;/strong&gt; button in the OpenTelemetry box:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 502px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OpenTelemetry configure button&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;502&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;148&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;OpenTelemetry configure button&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;502&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;148&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the OTel page, we’ll need to copy down a few parameters we’ll need later, as you can see in the screenshot below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 926px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OTLP endpoint menu&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;926&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;565&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;OTLP endpoint menu&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;926&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;565&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;OTLP endpoint&lt;/strong&gt;: We’ll be sending all of the application observability to that destination.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Grafana instance ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create an &lt;strong&gt;API token&lt;/strong&gt;, which we’ll use later when connecting to the Grafana Cloud instance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Copy these values to a safe place; we’ll make use of them later in our setup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;start-and-configure-the-grafana-alloy-container&#34;&gt;Start and configure the Grafana Alloy container&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Grafana Alloy container will act as our observability &amp;ldquo;router,&amp;rdquo; collecting and aggregating our observability data before transmitting it to the Grafana Cloud instance and Digma.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ll start by creating an “observability” subfolder under the sample application. We’ll store everything related to configuring our observability pipeline here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create a new file called &lt;code&gt;config.river&lt;/code&gt; under the new observability subfolder. This Alloy configuration uses a Terraform-inspired configuration language. Paste in the following text and save the file:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;//Basic authentication&#xA;otelcol.auth.basic &amp;#34;grafana_auth&amp;#34; {&#xA;username = env(&amp;#34;GRAFANA_CLOUD_INSTANCE_ID&amp;#34;)&#xA;password = env(&amp;#34;GRAFANA_CLOUD_API_TOKEN&amp;#34;)&#xA;}&#xA;// Define the &amp;#39;Receiver&amp;#39; ingesting the data sent out from our app&#xA;otelcol.receiver.otlp &amp;#34;default&amp;#34; {&#xA;// configures the default grpc endpoint &amp;#34;0.0.0.0:4317&amp;#34;&#xA;grpc { }&#xA;// configures the default http/protobuf endpoint &amp;#34;0.0.0.0:4318&amp;#34;&#xA;http { }&#xA;output {&#xA;traces = [otelcol.processor.batch.default.input]&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;//The &amp;#39;processor&amp;#39; optimizes the network throughput by batching the output&#xA;otelcol.processor.batch &amp;#34;default&amp;#34; {&#xA;output {&#xA;traces = [otelcol.exporter.otlp.digma.input,otelcol.exporter.otlphttp.grafana_cloud.input]&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;//Our two exporters will send the data both to Digma (to analytize our code observability, and to our Grafana cloud instance&#xA;otelcol.exporter.otlp &amp;#34;digma&amp;#34; {&#xA;// Send traces to Digma without TLS enabled.&#xA;client {&#xA;endpoint = env(&amp;#34;DIGMA_OTLP_ENDPOINT&amp;#34;)&#xA;tls {&#xA;insecure = true&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;otelcol.exporter.otlphttp &amp;#34;grafana_cloud&amp;#34; {&#xA;client {&#xA;endpoint = env(&amp;#34;GRAFANA_CLOUD_OTLP_ENDPOINT&amp;#34;)&#xA;auth = otelcol.auth.basic.grafana_auth.handler&#xA;}&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this file, we define our observability pipeline as code with the following structure:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1116px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OTLP workflow&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1116&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;486&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;OTLP workflow&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1116&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;486&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OTLP receiver&lt;/strong&gt;. This component will receive the traces emitted by our Java application.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OTLP processor&lt;/strong&gt;. This will be used to optimize our output using a batching strategy to send traces together instead of one by one.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exporters&lt;/strong&gt;. These will send out the traces for storage and processing. We’ll send our traces to two destinations: our Grafana Cloud instance and Digma, which we’ll use to analyze our code.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create a new “docker-compose.yaml” file. This file will define the Alloy container and mount our configuration file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;version: &amp;#34;3.6&amp;#34;&#xA;services:&#xA;grafana-agent:&#xA;image: grafana/agent:latest&#xA;restart: always&#xA;command:&#xA;- run&#xA;- --server.http.listen-addr=0.0.0.0:12345&#xA;- /etc/agent/config.river&#xA;volumes:&#xA;- ./config.river:/etc/agent/config.river&#xA;ports:&#xA;- &amp;#34;12345:12345&amp;#34;&#xA;- &amp;#34;4317:4317&amp;#34;&#xA;extra_hosts:&#xA;- &amp;#34;host.docker.internal:host-gateway&amp;#34;&#xA;environment:&#xA;- AGENT_MODE=flow&#xA;- OTLP_EXPORTER_DIGMA_COLLECTOR_API=host.docker.internal:5050&#xA;- GRAFANA_CLOUD_OTLP_ENDPOINT=--REPLACE_WITH_GRAFANA_ENDPOINT--&#xA;- GRAFANA_CLOUD_API_TOKEN=${GRAFANA_CLOUD_API_TOKEN}&#xA;- GRAFANA_CLOUD_INSTANCE_ID=--REPLACE_WITH_GRAFNA_INSTANCE_ID--&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Replace the values under the “environment” element using the information collected from Grafana Cloud. We’ll want to set the API token as an argument to avoid storing it locally in any file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Run the Docker Compose file as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;cd observability&#xA;docker compose up -e GRAFANA_CLOUD_API_TOKEN=--REPLACE_WITH_TOKEN--&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Alloy includes a UI for debugging the state of a pipeline, which is accessible from &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:12345&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this URL&lt;/a&gt;. From there, we can see the state and configuration of each component of the pipeline, and there&amp;rsquo;s also a nice graph that shows us the relationship between the different components of the pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1198px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Relationship graph&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1198&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;795&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Relationship graph&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1198&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;795&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;install-the-digma-plugin&#34;&gt;Install the Digma plugin&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now we need to install the Digma plugin to start collecting data from our Java application right away. You can install it from the IntelliJ marketplace in your IDE:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1452px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Digma Continuous Feedback plugin in the IntelliJ marketplace&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1452&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;879&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Digma Continuous Feedback plugin in the IntelliJ marketplace&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1452&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;879&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, configure the Digma plugin to send our local traces to the Alloy container we created in the previous steps. Go to the &lt;strong&gt;Settings&lt;/strong&gt; page of the IntelliJ IDE and search for &amp;ldquo;Digma&amp;rdquo; to bring up the Digma plugin configuration page:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1451px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Digma plugin form&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1451&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;890&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Digma plugin form&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1451&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;890&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit the “Runtime observability backend URL” field and set it to &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:4317&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;http://localhost:4317&lt;/a&gt;. This is the default port used by the Alloy collector.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;run-your-code-and-validate-that-everything-works-as-expected&#34;&gt;Run your code and validate that everything works as expected!&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Digma installed, your code will be automatically instrumented.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can open the Digma observability panel in the IDE to validate that everything is in working order. This panel will always reflect the latest captured observability data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1403px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Traces dashboard&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1403&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;619&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Traces dashboard&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1403&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;619&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-use-observability-data-when-developing-code&#34;&gt;How to use observability data when developing code&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you work — run, debug, or run tests — the Digma plugin is busy analyzing the observability data, looking for issues, and creating useful usage analytics. It then integrates that data into the IDE. The data will also be tightly integrated into the code itself so you’ll be able to quickly jump between traces and corresponding lines of code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are three main areas where you can see that data in play:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-observability-panel&#34;&gt;The observability panel&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve already reviewed this area when we health-checked the data pipeline. Here you’ll be able to quickly jump to see the trace of a recent action or navigate to the relevant endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-insights-panel&#34;&gt;The insights panel&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This panel is dedicated to a more in-depth analysis of each code location, asset, database query endpoint, etc. It interacts with the code in the IDE and can either take you to the relevant code locations or show the insights (issues and analytics) related to the currently selected code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 559px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Digma insights panel&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;559&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;800&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Digma insights panel&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;559&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;800&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;code-annotations&#34;&gt;Code annotations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the plugin installed, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to see CodeLens overlayed on the code itself indicating runtime usage, dead code, and critical insights:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1088px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Code example&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1088&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;591&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Code example&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1088&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;591&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bonus-open-the-tracing-visualization-in-grafana-cloud-from-your-ide&#34;&gt;Bonus: Open the tracing visualization in Grafana Cloud from your IDE&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we saw in the previous section, we can see the tracing visualization inside the IDE. However, we can also connect Digma with Grafana Cloud to open traces directly in your instance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 700px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Digma plugin entry form&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;700&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;478&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Digma plugin entry form&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;700&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;478&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To enable this behavior:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open the Digma settings page.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Change the &amp;ldquo;Jaeger link mode&amp;rdquo; settings for the Digma IntelliJ plugin to external&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Change the &amp;ldquo;Jaeger URL&amp;rdquo; setting to point to your Grafana Cloud Tracese page. You can use the following URL template (and replace [Your_Account]):&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;https://[YOUR_ACCOUNT].grafana.net/explore?left=%7B%22range%22%3A%7B%22from%22%3A%22now-5m%22%2C%22to%22%3A%22now%22%7D%2C%22datasource%22%3A%22grafanacloud-traces%22%2C%22queries%22%3A%5B%7B%22query%22%3A%&lt;code&gt;{TRACE_ID}&lt;/code&gt;%22%2C%22queryType%22%3A%22traceql%22%7D%5D%7D&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, in the Digma Observability view in IntelliJ, If you click on the trace button, you will see the trace visualization in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-with-feedback&#34;&gt;Code with feedback&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that everything is up and running, you can start experimenting with the new development practice of &lt;a href=&#34;https://digma.ai/continuous-feedback/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;continuous feedback&lt;/a&gt; (CF), which provides immediate code feedback and analysis. As developers, we notice plenty of useful data we can easily collect about code runtime; however, making that data useful is another matter entirely. That’s why integrating code observability closer to the dev cycle can accelerate code releases and help catch issues much earlier than before. Watch &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3wgQl69WSvw&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this video&lt;/a&gt; to see how CF works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ping us on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://continuous-feedback.slack.com/ssb/redirect&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Slack channel&lt;/a&gt; to let us know how your miles vary and what type of feedback you were able to leverage!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ron Dover is CTO and co-founder of &lt;a href=&#34;http://digma.ai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Digma.ai&lt;/a&gt;, an IDE plugin for code runtime AI analysis to help accelerate development in complex code bases. Ron is a big believer in evidence-based development and a proponent of continuous feedback in all aspects of software engineering.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, software developers have relied on simple logs to understand code execution and troubleshoot issues. Metrics, traces, dashboards, and gauges have predominantly been the domain of IT and infrastructure teams, leaving developers with limited visibility into their application&amp;rsquo;s performance. This division of responsibilities often meant developers only used observability tools reactively when problems arose.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The landscape is shifting with the advent of modern observability solutions. Tools such as &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/opentelemetry/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry&lt;/a&gt; have simplified tracing for Java applications, and platforms like Grafana provide a clearer view of application performance, making observability more developer-friendly. Furthermore, specialized tooling like &lt;a href=&#34;http://digma.ai&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Digma.ai&lt;/a&gt; is bridging the gap between dashboards and daily coding workflows, empowering developers to utilize observability proactively throughout the entire development lifecycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But how does this work in practice? Observability doesn’t do anyone any good if all it does is aggregate data. So our goal in this blog will be to demonstrate how developers can put observability to practical use by &lt;strong&gt;shortening the feedback loop&lt;/strong&gt;. Specifically, we want to shorten the duration between the time a bug or problem is introduced and the time the developer becomes aware of the problem and its source.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;connecting-a-java-app-to-grafana-cloud-and-digmaai&#34;&gt;Connecting a Java app to Grafana Cloud and Digma.ai&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For our example scenario, we’ll connect a sample Spring Boot application to &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;. We&amp;rsquo;ll also use Digma.ai, a continuous feedback tool that can analyze the app traces right in the IDE. To make this more interesting, we’ll use a new technology called &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/alloy-opentelemetry-collector/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Alloy&lt;/a&gt;, a component-based and easy-to-use open source distribution of &lt;a href=&#34;https://opentelemetry.io/docs/collector/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;OpenTelemetry Collector.&lt;/a&gt; Using Alloy is a simple way to configure which data we want to collect and where we want to send it. The complete pipeline will look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1462px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Workflow diagram&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1462&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;464&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/java-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Workflow diagram&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1462&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;464&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The code for this example is located in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/doppleware/spring-petclinic-cf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-connect-your-java-app-to-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;How to connect your Java app to Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll need a Grafana Cloud account to get started. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one already, you can sign up for the free tier using this &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; ( it should take about five seconds).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once that&amp;rsquo;s done, there are a bunch of inputs we’ll need to grab to continue our setup and send data to your newly created application observability instance! On your Grafana homepage, click on the &lt;strong&gt;Configure&lt;/strong&gt; button in the OpenTelemetry box:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 502px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OpenTelemetry configure button&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;502&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;148&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otel-configure.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;OpenTelemetry configure button&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;502&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;148&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the OTel page, we’ll need to copy down a few parameters we’ll need later, as you can see in the screenshot below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 926px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OTLP endpoint menu&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;926&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;565&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-endpoint.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;OTLP endpoint menu&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;926&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;565&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;OTLP endpoint&lt;/strong&gt;: We’ll be sending all of the application observability to that destination.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Grafana instance ID&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create an &lt;strong&gt;API token&lt;/strong&gt;, which we’ll use later when connecting to the Grafana Cloud instance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Copy these values to a safe place; we’ll make use of them later in our setup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;start-and-configure-the-grafana-alloy-container&#34;&gt;Start and configure the Grafana Alloy container&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Grafana Alloy container will act as our observability &amp;ldquo;router,&amp;rdquo; collecting and aggregating our observability data before transmitting it to the Grafana Cloud instance and Digma.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ll start by creating an “observability” subfolder under the sample application. We’ll store everything related to configuring our observability pipeline here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create a new file called &lt;code&gt;config.river&lt;/code&gt; under the new observability subfolder. This Alloy configuration uses a Terraform-inspired configuration language. Paste in the following text and save the file:&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;//Basic authentication&#xA;otelcol.auth.basic &amp;#34;grafana_auth&amp;#34; {&#xA;username = env(&amp;#34;GRAFANA_CLOUD_INSTANCE_ID&amp;#34;)&#xA;password = env(&amp;#34;GRAFANA_CLOUD_API_TOKEN&amp;#34;)&#xA;}&#xA;// Define the &amp;#39;Receiver&amp;#39; ingesting the data sent out from our app&#xA;otelcol.receiver.otlp &amp;#34;default&amp;#34; {&#xA;// configures the default grpc endpoint &amp;#34;0.0.0.0:4317&amp;#34;&#xA;grpc { }&#xA;// configures the default http/protobuf endpoint &amp;#34;0.0.0.0:4318&amp;#34;&#xA;http { }&#xA;output {&#xA;traces = [otelcol.processor.batch.default.input]&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;//The &amp;#39;processor&amp;#39; optimizes the network throughput by batching the output&#xA;otelcol.processor.batch &amp;#34;default&amp;#34; {&#xA;output {&#xA;traces = [otelcol.exporter.otlp.digma.input,otelcol.exporter.otlphttp.grafana_cloud.input]&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;//Our two exporters will send the data both to Digma (to analytize our code observability, and to our Grafana cloud instance&#xA;otelcol.exporter.otlp &amp;#34;digma&amp;#34; {&#xA;// Send traces to Digma without TLS enabled.&#xA;client {&#xA;endpoint = env(&amp;#34;DIGMA_OTLP_ENDPOINT&amp;#34;)&#xA;tls {&#xA;insecure = true&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;}&#xA;otelcol.exporter.otlphttp &amp;#34;grafana_cloud&amp;#34; {&#xA;client {&#xA;endpoint = env(&amp;#34;GRAFANA_CLOUD_OTLP_ENDPOINT&amp;#34;)&#xA;auth = otelcol.auth.basic.grafana_auth.handler&#xA;}&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this file, we define our observability pipeline as code with the following structure:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1116px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;OTLP workflow&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1116&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;486&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/otlp-workflow.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;OTLP workflow&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1116&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;486&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OTLP receiver&lt;/strong&gt;. This component will receive the traces emitted by our Java application.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OTLP processor&lt;/strong&gt;. This will be used to optimize our output using a batching strategy to send traces together instead of one by one.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exporters&lt;/strong&gt;. These will send out the traces for storage and processing. We’ll send our traces to two destinations: our Grafana Cloud instance and Digma, which we’ll use to analyze our code.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create a new “docker-compose.yaml” file. This file will define the Alloy container and mount our configuration file.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;version: &amp;#34;3.6&amp;#34;&#xA;services:&#xA;grafana-agent:&#xA;image: grafana/agent:latest&#xA;restart: always&#xA;command:&#xA;- run&#xA;- --server.http.listen-addr=0.0.0.0:12345&#xA;- /etc/agent/config.river&#xA;volumes:&#xA;- ./config.river:/etc/agent/config.river&#xA;ports:&#xA;- &amp;#34;12345:12345&amp;#34;&#xA;- &amp;#34;4317:4317&amp;#34;&#xA;extra_hosts:&#xA;- &amp;#34;host.docker.internal:host-gateway&amp;#34;&#xA;environment:&#xA;- AGENT_MODE=flow&#xA;- OTLP_EXPORTER_DIGMA_COLLECTOR_API=host.docker.internal:5050&#xA;- GRAFANA_CLOUD_OTLP_ENDPOINT=--REPLACE_WITH_GRAFANA_ENDPOINT--&#xA;- GRAFANA_CLOUD_API_TOKEN=${GRAFANA_CLOUD_API_TOKEN}&#xA;- GRAFANA_CLOUD_INSTANCE_ID=--REPLACE_WITH_GRAFNA_INSTANCE_ID--&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Replace the values under the “environment” element using the information collected from Grafana Cloud. We’ll want to set the API token as an argument to avoid storing it locally in any file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Run the Docker Compose file as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;cd observability&#xA;docker compose up -e GRAFANA_CLOUD_API_TOKEN=--REPLACE_WITH_TOKEN--&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Alloy includes a UI for debugging the state of a pipeline, which is accessible from &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:12345&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this URL&lt;/a&gt;. From there, we can see the state and configuration of each component of the pipeline, and there&amp;rsquo;s also a nice graph that shows us the relationship between the different components of the pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1198px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Relationship graph&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1198&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;795&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/relationship-graph.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Relationship graph&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1198&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;795&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;install-the-digma-plugin&#34;&gt;Install the Digma plugin&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now we need to install the Digma plugin to start collecting data from our Java application right away. You can install it from the IntelliJ marketplace in your IDE:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1452px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Digma Continuous Feedback plugin in the IntelliJ marketplace&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1452&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;879&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-cf.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Digma Continuous Feedback plugin in the IntelliJ marketplace&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1452&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;879&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, configure the Digma plugin to send our local traces to the Alloy container we created in the previous steps. Go to the &lt;strong&gt;Settings&lt;/strong&gt; page of the IntelliJ IDE and search for &amp;ldquo;Digma&amp;rdquo; to bring up the Digma plugin configuration page:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1451px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Digma plugin form&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1451&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;890&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Digma plugin form&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1451&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;890&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit the “Runtime observability backend URL” field and set it to &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:4317&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;http://localhost:4317&lt;/a&gt;. This is the default port used by the Alloy collector.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;run-your-code-and-validate-that-everything-works-as-expected&#34;&gt;Run your code and validate that everything works as expected!&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With Digma installed, your code will be automatically instrumented.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can open the Digma observability panel in the IDE to validate that everything is in working order. This panel will always reflect the latest captured observability data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1403px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Traces dashboard&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1403&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;619&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/grafana-cloud-traces.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Traces dashboard&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1403&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;619&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-use-observability-data-when-developing-code&#34;&gt;How to use observability data when developing code&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you work — run, debug, or run tests — the Digma plugin is busy analyzing the observability data, looking for issues, and creating useful usage analytics. It then integrates that data into the IDE. The data will also be tightly integrated into the code itself so you’ll be able to quickly jump between traces and corresponding lines of code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are three main areas where you can see that data in play:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-observability-panel&#34;&gt;The observability panel&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve already reviewed this area when we health-checked the data pipeline. Here you’ll be able to quickly jump to see the trace of a recent action or navigate to the relevant endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-insights-panel&#34;&gt;The insights panel&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This panel is dedicated to a more in-depth analysis of each code location, asset, database query endpoint, etc. It interacts with the code in the IDE and can either take you to the relevant code locations or show the insights (issues and analytics) related to the currently selected code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 559px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Digma insights panel&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;559&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;800&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-insights.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Digma insights panel&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;559&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;800&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;code-annotations&#34;&gt;Code annotations&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With the plugin installed, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to see CodeLens overlayed on the code itself indicating runtime usage, dead code, and critical insights:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 1088px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Code example&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1088&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;591&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/code-sample.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Code example&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;1088&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;591&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;bonus-open-the-tracing-visualization-in-grafana-cloud-from-your-ide&#34;&gt;Bonus: Open the tracing visualization in Grafana Cloud from your IDE&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we saw in the previous section, we can see the tracing visualization inside the IDE. However, we can also connect Digma with Grafana Cloud to open traces directly in your instance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: 700px;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png&#34;data-srcset=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=320 320w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=550 550w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=750 750w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=900 900w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=1040 1040w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=1240 1240w, /media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png?w=1920 1920w&#34;&#xA;data-sizes=&#34;auto&#34;alt=&#34;Digma plugin entry form&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;700&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;478&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;/media/blog/java-digma/digma-plugin.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Digma plugin entry form&#34;&#xA;width=&#34;700&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;478&#34;&#xA;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To enable this behavior:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Open the Digma settings page.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Change the &amp;ldquo;Jaeger link mode&amp;rdquo; settings for the Digma IntelliJ plugin to external&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Change the &amp;ldquo;Jaeger URL&amp;rdquo; setting to point to your Grafana Cloud Tracese page. You can use the following URL template (and replace [Your_Account]):&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;https://[YOUR_ACCOUNT].grafana.net/explore?left=%7B%22range%22%3A%7B%22from%22%3A%22now-5m%22%2C%22to%22%3A%22now%22%7D%2C%22datasource%22%3A%22grafanacloud-traces%22%2C%22queries%22%3A%5B%7B%22query%22%3A%&lt;code&gt;{TRACE_ID}&lt;/code&gt;%22%2C%22queryType%22%3A%22traceql%22%7D%5D%7D&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, in the Digma Observability view in IntelliJ, If you click on the trace button, you will see the trace visualization in &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/traces/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Traces&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-with-feedback&#34;&gt;Code with feedback&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that everything is up and running, you can start experimenting with the new development practice of &lt;a href=&#34;https://digma.ai/continuous-feedback/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;continuous feedback&lt;/a&gt; (CF), which provides immediate code feedback and analysis. As developers, we notice plenty of useful data we can easily collect about code runtime; however, making that data useful is another matter entirely. That’s why integrating code observability closer to the dev cycle can accelerate code releases and help catch issues much earlier than before. Watch &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3wgQl69WSvw&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this video&lt;/a&gt; to see how CF works.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ping us on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://continuous-feedback.slack.com/ssb/redirect&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Slack channel&lt;/a&gt; to let us know how your miles vary and what type of feedback you were able to leverage!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Grafana security update: Grafana Loki and unintended data write attempts to Amazon S3 buckets】Grafana 安全更新：Grafana Loki 和意外数据写入 Amazon S3 存储桶的尝试</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/06/27/grafana-security-update-grafana-loki-and-unintended-data-write-attempts-to-amazon-s3-buckets/</link>
      <description>【&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Editor&amp;rsquo;s note: We have updated the copy to reflect changes from our partners at Google. (June 27 19:00 UTC)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Out of an abundance of caution, we are publishing this as a security advisory.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You may have read or heard about the Medium blog post, &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@maciej.pocwierz/how-an-empty-s3-bucket-can-make-your-aws-bill-explode-934a383cb8b1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;How an empty S3 bucket can make your AWS bill explode&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; which described how unauthorized write attempts to an Amazon S3 storage bucket led to a $1,300 bill, and the news that AWS subsequently made a change to S3 in which unauthorized requests that customers did not initiate are free of charge. In the initial report, &lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@maciej.pocwierz?source=post_page-----934a383cb8b1--------------------------------&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Maciej Pocwierz&lt;/a&gt; said that the unauthorized writes were the result of an unnamed open source project&amp;rsquo;s default configuration for storing backups in S3 buckets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The open source project in question is Grafana Loki, our log aggregation tool. Part of the root cause was the use of the default value &lt;code&gt;chunks&lt;/code&gt; in our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/setup/install/helm/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Loki Helm chart&lt;/a&gt; for convenience when using MinIO. When Maciej created an AWS bucket named &lt;code&gt;chunks&lt;/code&gt;, it appeared as a valid target for other AWS customers. This bucket was created without world-writeable permissions, but the rejected write attempts were still billed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In response to the issue, we have updated the Loki Helm chart to remove default bucket names except when using MinIO.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that our investigation has concluded, we are publishing this blog post. We&amp;rsquo;d like to thank Maciej for responsibly disclosing this issue to us via our &lt;a href=&#34;https://app.intigriti.com/programs/grafanalabs/grafanaossbbp/detail&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;bug bounty program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-is-impacted&#34;&gt;Who is impacted&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS supports bucket namespaces that go beyond organizational boundaries; therefore, third parties can create a bucket name that appears as a valid target to others and you. We have worked with AWS to confirm that these default bucket names are currently claimed by legitimate entities and have been configured in a way that does not allow for data collection. Out of an abundance of caution, we advise that users with Loki or Grafana Enterprise Logs (GEL) deployments on AWS upgrade their Helm charts or change the names of their buckets, as outlined in the solutions and mitigations section below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud supports globally unique bucket namespaces. We have worked with Google to confirm that Google Cloud users have not been impacted. Out of an abundance of caution, we advise that users with Loki or GEL deployments on Google Cloud upgrade their Helm charts or change the names of their buckets, as outlined in the solutions and mitigations section.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Azure does not support bucket namespaces that go beyond organizational boundaries, so users who have Loki or GEL deployments on Azure are &lt;strong&gt;not affected&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud customers are &lt;strong&gt;not affected&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Loki stores its data in an S3-compatible object storage. For convenience in local installations, the Loki Helm chart contained default values for a local MinIO installation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@maciej.pocwierz?source=post_page-----934a383cb8b1--------------------------------&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Maciej Pocwierz&lt;/a&gt;, a Senior Software Engineer at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.semantive.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Semantive&lt;/a&gt; and the author of &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@maciej.pocwierz/how-an-empty-s3-bucket-can-make-your-aws-bill-explode-934a383cb8b1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;How an empty S3 bucket can make your AWS bill explode&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; reported that he incurred $1,300 in charges for unauthorized write attempts. In configuring his S3 storage, he used the same name as the Loki Helm chart default. This created a data path within AWS that Loki clusters could attempt to write to if those clusters were installed via Helm using the default bucket configuration. According to Maciej, he later made his bucket world-writeable for 30 seconds and collected roughly 10GB of data. He reached out to companies that were the source of this data, but at the time he published his blog post, he had not heard back.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS has since &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/05/amazon-s3-no-charge-http-error-codes/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;announced a billing change for Amazon S3&lt;/a&gt;, and no longer charges for any unauthorized PUT requests from outside their AWS account or AWS organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prior to this point, any Loki or GEL deployments running with these default bucket names on AWS didn’t have a valid write target. These clusters could query locally cached data only, which would have made the cluster largely useless. As such, we have relatively high confidence that no one would have run an unconfigured cluster for long, not even as a trial.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;impacted-versions&#34;&gt;Impacted versions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Loki Helm charts for Grafana Loki and Grafana Enterprise Logs from 3.0.0 until 5.47.2, and additionally 6.0.0&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a functional check: The default buckets in the Helm chart are not configured for global writes, so clusters in this misconfigured state can only return data from the last two hours. As such, clusters that return more than two hours of data are unlikely to be impacted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;patched-versions&#34;&gt;Patched versions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Loki Helm charts for Grafana Loki and Grafana Enterprise Logs version &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/helm-charts/releases/download/helm-loki-5.48.0/loki-5.48.0.tgz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;5.48.0&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/helm-charts/releases/download/helm-loki-6.1.0/loki-6.1.0.tgz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;6.1.0&lt;/a&gt; have been patched.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;solutions-and-mitigations&#34;&gt;Solutions and mitigations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are several solutions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade the Loki Helm chart to version &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/helm-charts/releases/download/helm-loki-5.48.0/loki-5.48.0.tgz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;5.48.0&lt;/a&gt; or to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/helm-charts/releases/download/helm-loki-6.1.0/loki-6.1.0.tgz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;6.1.0&lt;/a&gt; or higher.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/setup/install/helm/configure-storage/&#34;&gt;Configure your storage&lt;/a&gt;: In your &lt;code&gt;values.yaml&lt;/code&gt;, change all that apply to your instance to the below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.storage.bucketNames.chunks&lt;/code&gt; away from &lt;code&gt;chunks&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.storage.bucketNames.ruler&lt;/code&gt; away from &lt;code&gt;ruler&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.storage.bucketNames.admin&lt;/code&gt; away from &lt;code&gt;admin&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The upstream fix was to no longer provide default values in the Loki Helm chart. The Loki Helm chart will only configure MinIO default values when the user spins up a MinIO instance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For contracted customers, we have reached out to help mitigate any issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;Timeline&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All times in UTC&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2024-04-09 15:34: Maciej Pocwierz reported to Grafana Labs via our bug bounty program.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 17:04: Report triaged.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 17:04: Escalated to the Loki team to investigate and confirm.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 19:27: Incident declared.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 20:32: Partial replication by Loki team.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 22:35: PR merged to Loki Helm chart version 6.1.0 fixing the issue.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 22:35: Loki Helm chart version 6.1.0 released.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-10 19:01: AWS and Google Cloud contacted.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-11 06:24: AWS confirmed all unauthorized third party requests other than 5xx are billed.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-03 01:28: Google Cloud confirmed failed requests are not billed.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-06 15:43: PR merged to Loki Helm chart version 5.48.0 fixing the issue.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-06 15:43: Loki Helm chart version 5.48.0 released.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-08 14:20: Google Cloud confirmed that the buckets are claimed by legitimate entities and have been configured in a way that prevents data collection.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-13 17:30: AWS made a change to Amazon S3 in which unauthorized requests that customers did not initiate are free of charge.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-31 17:43: AWS confirmed that the buckets are claimed by legitimate entities and have been configured in a way that does not allow for data collection.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-06-27 05:30: All cloud partner reviews of this blog post finished.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-06-27 17:00: Blog published.&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-06-27 19:00: Blog updated to reflect changes from our partners at Google.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;reporting-security-issues&#34;&gt;Reporting security issues&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you think you have found a security vulnerability, please go to our &lt;a href=&#34;/legal/report-a-security-issue/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Report a security issue page&lt;/a&gt; to learn how to send a security report.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs will send you a response indicating the next steps in handling your report. After the initial reply to your report, the security team will keep you informed of the progress towards a fix and full announcement, and may ask for additional information or guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Important: We ask you to not disclose the vulnerability before it has been fixed and announced, unless you received a response from the Grafana Labs security team that you can do so.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;security-announcements&#34;&gt;Security announcements&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We maintain a &lt;a href=&#34;/tags/security/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;security category&lt;/a&gt; on our blog, where we will always post a summary, remediation, and mitigation details for any patch containing security fixes. You can also subscribe to our &lt;a href=&#34;/tags/security/index.xml&#34;&gt;RSS feed&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;编者注：我们更新了副本以反映 Google 合作伙伴的更改。 （世界标准时间 6 月 27 日 19:00）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/块引用&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;出于谨慎考虑，我们将此作为安全建议发布。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可能读过或听说过 Medium 博客文章“&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@maciej.pocwierz/how-an-empty-s3-bucket-can-make-your- aws-bill-explode-934a383cb8b1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;空的 S3 存储桶如何让您的 AWS 账单爆炸&lt;/a&gt;”，其中描述了对 Amazon S3 存储桶进行未经授权的写入尝试如何导致一张 1,300 美元的账单，还有消息称 AWS 随后对 S3 进行了更改，其中客户未发起的未经授权的请求是免费的。在初始报告中，&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@maciej.pocwierz?source=post_page-----934a383cb8b1----------------- --------------&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Maciej Pocwierz&lt;/a&gt; 表示未经授权的写入是一个未命名的开源项目的默认配置的结果将备份存储在 S3 存储桶中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所讨论的开源项目是 Grafana Loki，我们的日志聚合工具。部分根本原因是在我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/setup/install/helm/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt; 中使用了默认值 &lt;code&gt;chunks&lt;/code&gt; Loki Helm 图表&lt;/a&gt;，以方便使用 MinIO。当 Maciej 创建名为 &lt;code&gt;chunks&lt;/code&gt; 的 AWS 存储桶时，它显示为其他 AWS 客户的有效目标。该存储桶是在没有全局可写权限的情况下创建的，但被拒绝的写入尝试仍会计费。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了解决该问题，我们更新了 Loki Helm 图表，删除了默认存储桶名称（使用 MinIO 时除外）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;既然我们的调查已经结束，我们将发布这篇博文。我们要感谢 Maciej 通过我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;https://app.intigriti.com/programs/grafanalabs/grafanaossbbp/detail&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; 负责任地向我们披露了此问题&gt;错误赏金计划&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-is-impacted&#34;&gt;谁受到影响&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS 支持超越组织边界的存储桶命名空间；因此，第三方可以创建一个对其他人和您而言显示为有效目标的存储桶名称。我们已与 AWS 合作，确认这些默认存储桶名称当前由合法实体声明，并且配置方式不允许进行数据收集。出于谨慎考虑，我们建议在 AWS 上部署 Loki 或 Grafana Enterprise Logs (GEL) 的用户升级其 Helm 图表或更改其存储桶名称，如下面的解决方案和缓解措施部分所述。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Google Cloud 支持全局唯一的存储桶命名空间。我们已与 Google 合作，确认 Google Cloud 用户未受到影响。出于谨慎考虑，我们建议在 Google Cloud 上部署 Loki 或 GEL 的用户升级其 Helm 图表或更改其存储桶名称，如解决方案和缓解措施部分中所述。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft Azure 不支持超出组织边界的存储桶命名空间，因此在 Azure 上部署 Loki 或 GEL 的用户&lt;strong&gt;不受影响&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud 客户&lt;strong&gt;不受影响&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;​​背景&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Loki 将其数据存储在 S3 兼容的对象存储中。为了方便本地安装，Loki Helm 图表包含本地 MinIO 安装的默认值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@maciej.pocwierz?source=post_page-----934a383cb8b1-------------------- ------------&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Maciej Pocwierz&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.semantive. com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Semantive&lt;/a&gt; 和“&lt;a href=&#34;https://medium.com/@maciej.pocwierz/how-an-empty-s3”的作者-bucket-can-make-your-aws-bill-explode-934a383cb8b1&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;空的 S3 存储桶如何让您的 AWS 账单爆炸&lt;/a&gt;”，报告称他招致了未经授权的写入尝试将收取 1,300 美元的费用。在配置 S3 存储时，他使用了与 Loki Helm 图表默认名称相同的名称。这在 AWS 中创建了一条数据路径，如果 Loki 集群是使用默认存储桶配置通过 Helm 安装的，则 Loki 集群可以尝试写入该数据路径。根据 Maciej 的说法，他后来将他的存储桶设置为世界可写 30 秒，并收集了大约 10GB 的数据。他联系了这些数据的来源公司，但在他发表博客文章时，他还没有收到回复。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AWS 自 &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/whats-new/2024/05/amazon-s3-no-charge-http-error-codes/&#34; target= &#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;宣布 Amazon S3 的账单变更&lt;/a&gt;，不再对来自其 AWS 账户或 AWS 组织外部的任何未经授权的 PUT 请求收费。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在此之前，在 AWS 上使用这些默认存储桶名称运行的任何 Loki 或 GEL 部署都没有有效的写入目标。这些集群只能查询本地缓存的数据，这会使集群基本上毫无用处。因此，我们有相对较高的信心，没有人会长期运行未配置的集群，即使是作为试验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;impacted-versions&#34;&gt;受影响的版本&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Loki 和 Grafana Enterprise Logs 的 Loki Helm 图表从 3.0.0 到 5.47.2，另外还有 6.0.0&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为功能检查：Helm 图表中的默认存储桶未配置为全局写入，因此处于此错误配置状态的集群只能返回过去两个小时的数据。因此，返回超过两个小时数据的集群不太可能受到影响。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;patched-versions&#34;&gt;修补版本&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Loki 和 Grafana Enterprise Logs 版本的 Loki Helm 图表 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/helm-charts/releases/download/helm-loki-5.48.0/loki-5.48.0 .tgz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;5.48.0&lt;/a&gt; 和 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/helm-charts/releases/download/helm-loki- 6.1.0/loki-6.1.0.tgz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;6.1.0&lt;/a&gt; 已修补。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;solutions-and-mitigations&#34;&gt;解决方案和缓解措施&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有几种解决方案：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;将 Loki Helm 图表升级到版本 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/helm-charts/releases/download/helm-loki-5.48.0/loki-5.48.0.tgz&#34; 目标=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;5.48.0&lt;/a&gt; 或 &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/helm-charts/releases/download/helm-loki-6.1.0 /loki-6.1.0.tgz&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;6.1.0&lt;/a&gt; 或更高版本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/loki/latest/setup/install/helm/configure-storage/&#34;&gt;配置您的存储&lt;/a&gt;：在您的 &lt;code&gt;values.yaml&lt;/code&gt; 中，更改所有适用于您的实例的内容如下：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.storage.bucketNames.chunks&lt;/code&gt; 远离 &lt;code&gt;chunks&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.storage.bucketNames.ruler&lt;/code&gt; 远离 &lt;code&gt;ruler&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;loki.storage.bucketNames.admin&lt;/code&gt; 远离 &lt;code&gt;admin&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上游修复是不再在 Loki Helm 图表中提供默认值。 Loki Helm 图表只会在用户启动 MinIO 实例时配置 MinIO 默认值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;对于签约客户，我们已联系以帮助缓解任何问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;timeline&#34;&gt;时间轴&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所有时间均采用 UTC 时间&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2024-04-09 15:34：Maciej Pocwierz 通过我们的错误赏金计划向 Grafana Labs 报告。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 17:04：报告已分类。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 17:04：升级至Loki团队调查确认。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 19:27：宣布事件。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 20:32：Loki团队部分复制。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 22:35：PR 合并到 Loki Helm 图表版本 6.1.0 修复了该问题。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-09 22:35：Loki Helm 图表版本 6.1.0 发布。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-10 19:01：AWS 与 Google Cloud 取得联系。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-04-11 06:24：AWS 确认除 5xx 之外的所有未经授权的第三方请求都会计费。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-03 01:28：Google Cloud 确认失败的请求不会计费。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-06 15:43：PR 合并到 Loki Helm 图表版本 5.48.0 修复了该问题。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-06 15:43：Loki Helm 图表版本 5.48.0 发布。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-08 14:20：Google Cloud 确认这些存储桶已由合法实体认领，并且配置方式已阻止数据收集。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-13 17:30：AWS 对 Amazon S3 进行了更改，其中客户未发起的未经授权的请求是免费的。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-05-31 17:43：AWS 确认这些存储桶已由合法实体声明，并且配置方式不允许进行数据收集。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-06-27 05:30：本博文所有云合作伙伴评论完毕。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-06-27 17:00: 博客发布。&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;2024-06-27 19:00：博客已更新，以反映 Google 合作伙伴的更改。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;reporting-security-issues&#34;&gt;报告安全问题&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您认为发现了安全漏洞，请访问我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/legal/report-a-security-issue/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;报告安全问题页面&lt;/ a&gt; 了解如何发送安全报告。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Labs 将向您发送回复，指示处理您的报告的后续步骤。在对您的报告进行初步回复后，安全团队将随时向您通报修复进度和完整公告，并可能要求您提供其他信息或指导。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;重要提示：我们要求您在漏洞修复和公布之前不要披露该漏洞，除非您收到 Grafana Labs 安全团队的回复表明您可以这样做。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;security-announcements&#34;&gt;安全公告&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们在博客上维护一个&lt;a href=&#34;/tags/security/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;安全类别&lt;/a&gt;，我们将始终在其中发布以下内容的摘要、补救措施和缓解详细信息：任何包含安全修复程序的补丁。您还可以订阅我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/tags/security/index.xml&#34;&gt;RSS 源&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting started with Grafana: best practices to design your first dashboard】Grafana 入门：设计第一个仪表板的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/03/getting-started-with-grafana-best-practices-to-design-your-first-dashboard/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;At its core, observability is about helping humans understand and optimize complex systems. It enables engineering teams to ask questions on the fly, and to learn not only when something goes wrong but &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt;. Observability also allows organizations to proactively identify and address performance issues — before their end users even have a chance to notice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/07/14/celebrating-grafana-10-top-10-grafana-features-you-need-to-know-about/&#34;&gt;over a decade&lt;/a&gt;, Grafana dashboards have empowered organizations to achieve these (and more) observability goals by unifying and displaying data in beautiful graphs, charts, and other visualizations. And while Grafana is well-known for its ease-of-use, we also realize that a little guidance can go a long way when it’s time to build your first dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, which is geared towards those getting started with Grafana, we break down some of the key principles behind effective dashboard design. From knowing your audience to choosing which metrics to include, here are some helpful guidelines to start creating stunning and informative Grafana dashboards — and transform your data into actionable insights — today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: To learn more about Grafana dashboard design and see demonstrations, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/go/webinar/getting-started-with-grafana-dashboard-design/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;“Getting started with Grafana dashboard design” webinar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;know-your-audience-and-what-they-want-to-know&#34;&gt;Know your audience (and what &lt;em&gt;they&lt;/em&gt; want to know)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the golden rules of designing a Grafana dashboard is to do so with a specific purpose or use case in mind. Your dashboard should either tell a story through a logical progression of data (such as large to small or general to specific), answer a question, or both. To do this effectively, you need to understand the intended users or audience for your dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, an engineer has a very different goal when using a Grafana dashboard compared to a product manager. The engineer likely wants visualizations that can quickly convey whether their service or system is performing as expected and help them pinpoint the cause of an issue if degradation occurs. A product manager, on the other hand, might use a Grafana dashboard to understand how customers are accessing and interacting with their app. Bottom line? There’s an incredibly &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/27/grafana-dashboards-in-2023-memorable-use-cases-of-the-year/&#34;&gt;wide range of use cases&lt;/a&gt; for Grafana dashboards, both in professional and personal settings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This means, before you start designing your dashboard, you should put yourself in the shoes of your intended user, outlining their specific goals and needs when it comes to data visualization. As part of that exercise, also consider the delivery method and level of interaction required — a dashboard shown in a PDF report, for example, won’t be interactive, but it could be the best way to send a monthly performance report to your leadership team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;take-advantage-of-visual-hierarchies&#34;&gt;Take advantage of visual hierarchies&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After defining your audience and their goals, it’s time to think about how to most effectively display information in your dashboard. This is where the concept of &lt;em&gt;visual hierarchies&lt;/em&gt; comes into play.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A visual hierarchy is a pattern in which some elements stand out and attract attention more than others, thereby suggesting a hierarchy of importance. By using a visual hierarchy, you can guide your viewer to the information you want them to focus on the most.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are several categories of visual hierarchy to consider:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alignment:&lt;/strong&gt; This is the order in which you present or organize your content, which has a significant influence on engagement. In English-speaking countries, for example, users tend to scan page content — whether in a book, on the web, or in a Grafana dashboard — in a “Z” pattern from left to right and top to bottom. Knowing this, you’d likely want to place key content in the top left corner of your dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Size:&lt;/strong&gt; This one is fairly straightforward: the bigger the size of the component, the greater the perception of importance. For example, you could emphasize key metrics in a large &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/stat/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;stat panel&lt;/a&gt;, and then place supporting data and other details beneath it in smaller &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;panels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload d-inline-block&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/dashboard-beginner/size.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Diagram demonstrating the importance of size&#34; width=&#34;960&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;540&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Color&lt;/strong&gt;: Our eyes are drawn to bright, saturated colors. If the color of an object is visually distinct from its background, the viewer will likely notice it first. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re forced to use larger panels in the middle of your dashboard — for a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/geomap/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;geomap&lt;/a&gt;, for example — but want to emphasize information in the top panels, you could use color to direct a user’s attention back to the top.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload d-inline-block&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/dashboard-beginner/color.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Diagram demonstrating the importance of color&#34; width=&#34;960&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;540&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shape:&lt;/strong&gt; Complex shapes that stick out from their surroundings also help draw attention.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember that everything in your dashboard should be important, but not everything will be &lt;em&gt;equally&lt;/em&gt; important. Again, the power of visual hierarchies is that they can help guide your users to the most important information in your dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, in thinking about these visual cues, accessibility is always important. For instance, to accommodate colorblind users, avoid red and green color combinations, as these can be difficult for them to see.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;choose-the-right-metrics&#34;&gt;Choose the right metrics&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Metrics are another important consideration in dashboard design. In order to choose the right metrics to highlight, you again should think about your intended user and the information they need to draw conclusions and take action.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Operations and engineering teams, for example, tend to prioritize metrics that can help them maintain consistent SLOs, improve uptime, and reduce MTTR. For these types of dashboard users, it’s helpful to use the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/build-dashboards/best-practices/#red-method&#34;&gt;RED method&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to define your metrics. RED stands for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rate:&lt;/strong&gt; requests per second&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Errors:&lt;/strong&gt; number of requests that are failing&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duration:&lt;/strong&gt; amount of time these requests take, and distribution of latency measurements&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The RED method can help you gauge how happy your customers are when using your service. In the dashboard below, our service consists of three tiers: a load balancing tier, a web application tier, and a backend database, and we&amp;rsquo;re tracking RED metrics for each tier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload d-inline-block&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/dashboard-beginner/beginner-red.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard displaying RED metrics&#34; width=&#34;4072&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;2134&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While the RED method is meant to observe the service layer, there’s also the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/build-dashboards/best-practices/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#use-method&#34;&gt;USE method&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to observe the infrastructure layer. This method helps track the underlying infrastructure resources, such as CPUs, memory, disk, and network components, that support a service or application. USE stands for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Utilization&lt;/strong&gt;: the percentage of time a resource, such as a CPU, is busy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturation&lt;/strong&gt;: the amount of work a resource has to do, often represented by queue length or node load&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Errors:&lt;/strong&gt; the count of error events&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The USE method is something a network admin or engineer, for example, may use to ensure resources don’t get oversaturated and lead to performance issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload d-inline-block&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/dashboard-beginner/beginner-use.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard for USE metrics&#34; width=&#34;1200&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;651&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another set of metrics to consider is the Four Golden Signals of Monitoring. Defined in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sre.google/sre-book/monitoring-distributed-systems/#xref_monitoring_golden-signals&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Google SRE handbook&lt;/a&gt;, these metrics include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Latency:&lt;/strong&gt; the time taken to serve a request&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traffic:&lt;/strong&gt; a measure of how much demand is being placed on your system. For a web service, this is typically reflected by HTTP requests per second.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Errors:&lt;/strong&gt; the rate of requests that fail (e.g., with an HTTP 500 status code)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Saturation:&lt;/strong&gt; how “full” your system is, in terms of memory and I/O, for example. This is important because many systems experience performance degradation before they reach 100% utilization.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These are core, baseline metrics to monitor system performance. As Google puts it, if you can only measure four metrics of your user-facing system, these are the four to focus on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;iterate-iterate-iterate&#34;&gt;Iterate, iterate, iterate&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Observability is a journey, not a destination. It requires careful planning, effective feedback loops, and continuous improvement. The same applies to dashboard design: you will (and should) always be iterating.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The definition of a “bad” metric or a “good” metric, or even a positive state vs. a negative state, may change for you and your users over time. Even if you feel like you’ve built that perfect dashboard, remember there’s always an opportunity to evolve or improve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more and see demos related to dashboard design, watch our on-demand webinar, &lt;a href=&#34;/go/webinar/getting-started-with-grafana-dashboard-design/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;“Getting started with Grafana dashboard design.”&lt;/a&gt; You can also reference our &lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/dashboards/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;gallery of dashboard templates&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/getting-started/build-first-dashboard/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Happy designing!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, and dashboards. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;可观察性的核心是帮助人类理解和优化复杂系统。它使工程团队能够即时提出问题，不仅可以了解出现问题的时间，还可以了解原因。可观察性还允许组织在最终用户有机会注意到之前主动识别和解决性能问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/07/14/celebating-grafana-10-top-10-grafana-features-you-need-to-know-about/&#34;&gt;十多年来&lt;/a &gt;，Grafana 仪表板通过以漂亮的图形、图表和其他可视化形式统一和显示数据，使组织能够实现这些（以及更多）可观察性目标。尽管 Grafana 以其易用性而闻名，但我们也意识到，在构建您的第一个仪表板时，一些指导可以大有帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇针对 Grafana 入门者的博文中，我们详细分析了有效仪表板设计背后的一些关键原则。从了解您的受众到选择要包含的指标，这里有一些有用的指南，可帮助您立即开始创建令人惊叹且信息丰富的 Grafana 仪表板，并将您的数据转化为可行的见解。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;注意：要了解有关 Grafana 仪表板设计的更多信息并观看演示，请查看我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/go/webinar/getting-started-with-grafana-dashboard-design/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body -txt&#34;&gt;“Grafana 仪表板设计入门”网络研讨会&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;know-your-audience-and-what-they-want-to-know&#34;&gt;了解您的受众（以及他们想知道什么）&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;设计 Grafana 仪表板的黄金规则之一是考虑特定目的或用例。您的仪表板应该通过数据的逻辑进展（例如从大到小或从一般到具体）来讲述一个故事，回答一个问题，或两者兼而有之。为了有效地做到这一点，您需要了解仪表板的目标用户或受众。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，与产品经理相比，工程师在使用 Grafana 仪表板时的目标非常不同。工程师可能希望可视化能够快速传达他们的服务或系统是否按预期运行，并在发生性能下降时帮助他们查明问题的原因。另一方面，产品经理可能会使用 Grafana 仪表板来了解客户如何访问其应用程序并与之交互。底线？ Grafana 有令人难以置信的&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/12/27/grafana-dashboards-in-2023-memorable-use-cases-of-the-year/&#34;&gt;广泛的用例&lt;/a&gt;专业和个人设置中的仪表板。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这意味着，在开始设计仪表板之前，您应该设身处地为目标用户着想，概述他们在数据可视化方面的具体目标和需求。作为该练习的一部分，还要考虑交付方法和所需的交互级别 - 例如，PDF 报告中显示的仪表板不会是交互式的，但它可能是向领导层发送每月绩效报告的最佳方式团队。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;take-advantage-of-visual-hierarchies&#34;&gt;利用视觉层次结构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;定义受众群体及其目标后，是时候考虑如何在仪表板中最有效地显示信息了。这就是&lt;em&gt;视觉层次结构&lt;/em&gt;的概念发挥作用的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;视觉层次结构是一种模式，其中某些元素比其他元素更突出并更能吸引注意力，从而表明重要性的层次结构。通过使用视觉层次结构，您可以引导观看者找到您希望他们最关注的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有几个类别的视觉层次结构需要考虑：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;对齐&lt;/strong&gt;：这是您呈现或组织内容的顺序，这对参与度有重大影响。例如，在英语国家，用户倾向于从左到右、从上到下以“Z”模式扫描页面内容——无论是在书中、在网络上还是在 Grafana 仪表板中。了解这一点后，您可能希望将关键内容放置在仪表板的左上角。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;大小：&lt;/strong&gt;这一点相当简单：组件的大小越大，重要性的感知就越大。例如，您可以在大型&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/stat/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;统计面板&lt;/a&gt;中强调关键指标，然后将支持数据和其他详细信息放在较小的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;面板&lt;/a&gt;中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;图片&#xA;类=“lazyload d-inline-block”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/dashboard-beginner/size.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;展示尺寸重要性的图表&#34; width=&#34;960&#34;&#xA;高度=“540”/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol开始=“3”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;颜色&lt;/strong&gt;：我们的眼睛容易被明亮、饱和的颜色所吸引。如果物体的颜色在视觉上与其背景不同，观看者可能会首先注意到它。因此，如果您被迫在仪表板中间使用较大的面板 - 对于 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/geomap/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;例如，地理地图&lt;/a&gt; - 但想要强调顶部面板中的信息，您可以使用颜色将用户的注意力引导回顶部。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;图片&#xA;类=“lazyload d-inline-block”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/dashboard-beginner/color.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;展示颜色重要性的图表&#34; width=&#34;960&#34;&#xA;高度=“540”/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol开始=“4”&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;形状：&lt;/strong&gt;从周围环境中脱颖而出的复杂形状也有助于吸引注意力。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请记住，仪表板中的所有内容都应该很重要，但并非所有内容都&lt;em&gt;同样&lt;/em&gt;重要。同样，视觉层次结构的强大之处在于它们可以帮助引导用户找到仪表板中最重要的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，在考虑这些视觉提示时，可访问性始终很重要。例如，为了适应色盲用户，请避免红色和绿色的颜色组合，因为这些颜色对他们来说很难看到。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;choose-the-right-metrics&#34;&gt;选择正确的指标&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;指标是仪表板设计中的另一个重要考虑因素。为了选择要突出显示的正确指标，您应该再次考虑您的目标用户以及他们得出结论和采取行动所需的信息。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，运营和工程团队倾向于优先考虑能够帮助他们保持一致的 SLO、延长正常运行时间并缩短 MTTR 的指标。对于这些类型的仪表板用户，使用&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/build-dashboards/best-practices/#red-method&#34;&gt;RED 方法&lt;/a&gt;&lt; /strong&gt; 定义您的指标。红色代表：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;速率：&lt;/strong&gt;每秒请求数&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;错误：&lt;/strong&gt;失败的请求数&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;持续时间&lt;/strong&gt;：这些请求所花费的时间以及延迟测量的分布&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;RED 方法可以帮助您衡量客户在使用您的服务时的满意度。在下面的仪表板中，我们的服务由三层组成：负载平衡层、Web 应用程序层和后端数据库，并且我们正在跟踪每个层的 RED 指标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;图片&#xA;类=“lazyload d-inline-block”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/dashboard-beginner/beginner-red.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板显示红色指标&#34; width=&#34;4072&#34;&#xA;高度=“2134”/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;虽然 RED 方法旨在观察服务层，但还有&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/build-dashboards/best-practices/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body- txt#use-method&#34;&gt;使用方法&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;观察基础设施层。此方法有助于跟踪支持服务或应用程序的底层基础设施资源，例如 CPU、内存、磁盘和网络组件。 USE 代表：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;利用率&lt;/strong&gt;：资源（例如 CPU）繁忙的时间百分比&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;饱和度&lt;/strong&gt;：资源必须完成的工作量，通常以队列长度或节点负载表示&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;错误：&lt;/strong&gt;错误事件的计数&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，网络管理员或工程师可以使用 USE 方法来确保资源不会过度饱和并导致性能问题。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;图片&#xA;类=“lazyload d-inline-block”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/dashboard-beginner/beginner-use.png”&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana 仪表板用于使用指标&#34; width=&#34;1200&#34;&#xA;高度=“651”/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一组需要考虑的指标是监控的四个黄金信号。在 &lt;a href=&#34;https://sre.google/sre-book/monitoring-distributed-systems/#xref_monitoring_golden-signals&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Google SRE 手册&lt;/a&gt;中定义，这些指标包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;延迟：&lt;/strong&gt;处理请求所需的时间&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;流量：&lt;/strong&gt;衡量系统上的需求量。对于 Web 服务，这通常通过每秒 HTTP 请求数来反映。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;错误：&lt;/strong&gt;失败请求的比率（例如，带有 HTTP 500 状态代码的请求）&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;饱和度：&lt;/strong&gt;系统的“满”程度，例如在内存和 I/O 方面。这很重要，因为许多系统在达到 100% 利用率之前都会经历性能下降。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些是监控系统性能的核心基准指标。正如 Google 所说，如果您只能衡量面向用户的系统的四个指标，那么这四个指标就是需要重点关注的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;iterate-iterate-iterate&#34;&gt;迭代，迭代，迭代&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;可观察性是一个旅程，而不是目的地。它需要仔细的规划、有效的反馈循环和持续改进。这同样适用于仪表板设计：您将（并且应该）始终进行迭代。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;随着时间的推移，“坏”指标或“好”指标，甚至积极状态与消极状态的定义可能会因您和您的用户而发生变化。即使您觉得自己已经构建了完美的仪表板，请记住始终有发展或改进的机会。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解更多信息并观看与仪表板设计相关的演示，请观看我们的点播网络研讨会，&lt;a href=&#34;/go/webinar/getting-started-with-grafana-dashboard-design/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body- txt&#34;&gt;“Grafana 仪表板设计入门。”&lt;/a&gt; 您还可以参考我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/grafana/dashboards/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;仪表板模板库&lt;/a&gt;和我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/getting-started/build-first-dashboard/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;技术文档&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;设计愉快！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪和仪表板的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册&lt;/a&gt;！&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Identify anomalies, outlier detection, forecasting: How Grafana Cloud uses AI/ML to make observability easier】识别异常、异常值检测、预测：Grafana Cloud 如何使用 AI/ML 使可观察性变得更容易</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2024/07/02/identify-anomalies-outlier-detection-forecasting-how-grafana-cloud-uses-ai/ml-to-make-observability-easier/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;At Grafana Labs, our No. 1 approach when building AI/ML tools is to enable humans (a.k.a. all of us!) to understand complex systems. In other words, we want to make observability still human, but less complicated. (Our second use case? &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/grafana-labs_the-5-worstbest-rejected-grafana-labs-marketing-activity-7146940548048707584-AynS/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Making social media more fun&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We believe that AI/ML tools in observability should work towards minimizing toil and the need for everyone in your organization to have the same deep domain knowledge about your increasingly complex stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After all, AI/ML should ultimately make it easier and less stressful for teams to run your services and to help you find and resolve issues effectively and efficiently — sometimes even &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; they impact users. Here&amp;rsquo;s how we do that in Grafana Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-why-your-system-isnt-working-sift-investigations&#34;&gt;Learn why your system &lt;em&gt;isn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/em&gt; working: Sift investigations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload d-inline-block&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/ai-ml-grafana-cloud/sift.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Sift investigation&#34; width=&#34;1000&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;625&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Something wrong in your application? Sift is a diagnostic tool that uses machine learning to help teams identify anomalies and investigate issues. It reduces toil and speeds up response times by offering:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/09/14/announcing-sift-automated-system-checks-for-faster-incident-response-times-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;Automated checks across metrics, logs, and traces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to uncover anomalies in logs, patterns in your HTTP errors, slow requests via traces, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explanations of log errors&lt;/strong&gt; that summarize anomalies and offer potential fixes in easy-to-follow steps.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can start a Sift investigation anywhere in Grafana Cloud, including in your dashboards and Explore, and run Sift across many workflows. You can also trigger Sift automatically from &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/06/grafana-incident-new-tools-for-faster-simpler-incident-response/&#34;&gt;Grafana Incident&lt;/a&gt;, which automates the time-consuming tasks of incident management so you can actually fix the issue faster, and &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/03/29/a-better-grafana-oncall-seamless-workflows-with-the-rest-of-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;Grafana OnCall&lt;/a&gt;, our on-call management tool that integrates with all parts of the Grafana LGTM Stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Best of all? Sift is available across all Grafana Cloud tiers at &lt;em&gt;no additional cost&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn more in our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/sift/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sift documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;predict-anomalies-forecasting--outlier-detection&#34;&gt;Predict anomalies: Forecasting &amp;amp; outlier detection&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload d-inline-block&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/ai-ml-grafana-cloud/predict-anomalies.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Anomaly detection sensitivity setting&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;396&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These features tell you &lt;em&gt;when&lt;/em&gt; your system is not healthy — now and in the future. Forecasting and outlier detection in Grafana Cloud help you learn the expected values of metrics over time and apply dynamic alerting to predict and detect anomalies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;forecasting&#34;&gt;Forecasting&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/forecasts/tutorial/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt; forecasting&lt;/a&gt; in Grafana Cloud, you can learn from the historical performance of a time series and predict values for your current usage and in the future. Instead of tuning thresholds on alerts, you can simply alert on when a metric is out of bounds. You can also capture daily and weekly seasonality to help set thresholds for peak and off-peak hours.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Forecasting also helps you with capacity planning and autoscaling so you can look into the future and confidently predict what your usage will look like in a week or a month.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;outlier-detection&#34;&gt;Outlier detection&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/forecasts/outlier-detection/&#34;&gt;outlier detection&lt;/a&gt;, you can monitor a group of services and identify when a feature is not performing at the same level as the others. (Cue the memory leaks, noisy neighbors, and other headaches.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more, check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/forecasts/outlier-detection/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;outlier detection documentation&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/forecasts/tutorial/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;forecasting tutorial&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;simplify-your-workflows-and-your-life-grafana-llm-plugin&#34;&gt;Simplify your workflows (and your life): Grafana LLM plugin&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When your observability stack produces &lt;em&gt;a ton&lt;/em&gt; of data, sometimes you just need to get to the point. By adding the Grafana LLM plugin to your stack, here’s how you can do just that:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;understand-flame-graphs-faster&#34;&gt;Understand flame graphs faster&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/15/ai-powered-insights-for-continuous-profiling-introducing-flame-graph-ai-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;Flame graph AI&lt;/a&gt; uses LLM to assist with flame graph data interpretation so you can identify bottlenecks, root causes, and suggested fixes faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload d-inline-block&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/ai-ml-grafana-cloud/flame-graph-ai.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Flame graph AI&#34; width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;height=&#34;1353&#34;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;summarize-incidents-in-one-click&#34;&gt;Summarize incidents in one click&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/06/grafana-incident-new-tools-for-faster-simpler-incident-response/#ai-driven-summaries-with-openai-integration&#34;&gt;OpenAI integration&lt;/a&gt; automatically generates concise, actionable summaries of incidents. This analysis not only captures the essence of the incident quickly but also helps teams ensure no critical details are overlooked when documenting and communicating incident impacts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;ai-generated-titles-and-descriptions-for-grafana-dashboards&#34;&gt;AI-generated titles and descriptions for Grafana dashboards&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No more wondering how to summarize all the data you packed into your dashboard in one title. Grafana includes a new &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-11-release-all-the-new-features/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#faster-ai-powered-titles-and-descriptions&#34;&gt;AI-powered tool that automatically summarizes &lt;/a&gt;the information in your panels and dashboards and creates detailed titles and descriptions for your dashboards.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/llm/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;how to enable the Grafana LLM plugin&lt;/a&gt; — and get started with all of these tools and more — in your Grafana Cloud stack today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about AI/ML and Grafana, check out our GrafanaCON 2024 session &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/creating-intelligent-grafana-apps-using-llms-large-language-models/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AI/ML + Grafana: How to create intelligent Grafana apps leveraging LLMs&lt;/a&gt;&amp;rdquo; available on demand now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case. &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在 Grafana Labs，我们构建 AI/ML 工具时的首要方法是让人类（也就是我们所有人！）能够理解复杂的系统。换句话说，我们希望使可观察性仍然是人性化的，但不那么复杂。 （我们的第二个用例？&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/posts/grafana-labs_the-5-worstbest-rejected-grafana-labs-marketing-activity-7146940548048707584-AynS/&#34; target=&#34;_blank “ rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;让社交媒体变得更有趣&lt;/a&gt;。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们认为，可观察性方面的 AI/ML 工具应该致力于最大限度地减少工作量，并减少组织中每个人对日益复杂的堆栈拥有相同深入领域知识的需求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;毕竟，AI/ML 最终应该让团队更轻松、更轻松地运行您的服务，并帮助您有效且高效地发现和解决问题 — 有时甚至在问题影响用户之前。以下是我们在 Grafana Cloud 中执行此操作的方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-why-your-system-isnt-working-sift-investigations&#34;&gt;了解您的系统为何无法运行：Sift 调查&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;图片&#xA;类=“lazyload d-inline-block”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/ai-ml-grafana-cloud/sift.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;筛选调查&#34; width=&#34;1000&#34;&#xA;高度=“625”/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您的应用程序有问题吗？ Sift 是一种诊断工具，利用机器学习帮助团队识别异常并调查问题。它通过提供以下功能来减少工作量并加快响应时间：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2023/09/14/announcing-sift-automated-system-checks-for-faster-incident-response-times-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;自动检查跨指标、日志和跟踪&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;发现日志中的异常、HTTP 错误的模式、通过跟踪的缓慢请求等等。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;日志错误说明&lt;/strong&gt;，总结异常情况并通过易于遵循的步骤提供潜在的修复方法。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在 Grafana Cloud 中的任何位置（包括在仪表板和 Explore 中）开始 Sift 调查，并在多个工作流程中运行 Sift。您还可以从 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/06/grafana-incident-new-tools-for-faster-simpler-incident-response/&#34;&gt;Grafana Incident&lt;/a&gt; 自动触发 Sift，从而自动执行事件管理的耗时任务，以便您实际上可以更快地解决问题，并且&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/03/29/a-better-grafana-oncall-seamless-workflows-with-the-rest- of-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;Grafana OnCall&lt;/a&gt;，我们的待命管理工具，与 Grafana LGTM Stack 的所有部分集成。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最重要的是？ Sift 可在所有 Grafana Cloud 层使用，&lt;em&gt;无需额外付费&lt;/em&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;请参阅我们的 &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/sift/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sift 文档&lt;/a&gt;了解更多信息。&lt;/ p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;predict-anomalies-forecasting--outlier-detection&#34;&gt;预测异常：预测和异常值检测&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;图片&#xA;类=“lazyload d-inline-block”&#xA;data-src=&#34;/media/blog/ai-ml-grafana-cloud/predict-anomalies.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;异常检测灵敏度设置&#34; width=&#34;800&#34;&#xA;高度=“396”/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些功能会告诉您系统何时不健康 - 现在和将来。 Grafana Cloud 中的预测和异常值检测可帮助您了解指标随时间变化的预期值，并应用动态警报来预测和检测异常。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;forecasting&#34;&gt;预测&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过 Grafana Cloud 中的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/forecasts/tutorial/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;预测&lt;/a&gt;，您可以从时间序列的历史表现中学习并预测当前和未来的使用值。您无需调整警报阈值，只需在指标超出范围时发出警报即可。您还可以捕获每日和每周的季节性，以帮助设置高峰和非高峰时段的阈值。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;预测还可以帮助您进行容量规划和自动扩展，以便您可以展望未来并自信地预测一周或一个月后的使用情况。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;outlier-detection&#34;&gt;异常值检测&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通过&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/forecasts/outlier-detection/&#34;&gt;异常值检测&lt;/a&gt;，您可以监控一组服务并识别当某项功能的性能与其他功能不同时。 （提示内存泄漏、吵闹的邻居和其他令人头痛的问题。）&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解更多信息，请查看我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/forecasts/outlier-detection/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;异常值检测文档&lt;/a&gt;和我们的&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/forecasts/tutorial/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;预测教程&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;simplify-your-workflows-and-your-life-grafana-llm-plugin&#34;&gt;简化您的工作流程（和您的生活）：Grafana LLM 插件&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您的可观察性堆栈产生&lt;em&gt;大量&lt;/em&gt;数据时，有时您只需要切入要点。通过将 Grafana LLM 插件添加到您的堆栈中，您可以执行以下操作：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;understand-flame-graphs-faster&#34;&gt;更快地理解火焰图&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/15/ai-powered-insights-for-continuous-profiling-introducing-flame-graph-ai-in-grafana-cloud/&#34;&gt;火焰图人工智能&lt;/ a&gt; 使用 LLM 协助火焰图数据解释，以便您可以更快地识别瓶颈、根本原因和建议的修复措施。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;图片&#xA;类=“lazyload d-inline-block”&#xA;data-src =“/media/blog/ai-ml-grafana-cloud/flame-graph-ai.gif”&#xA;alt=&#34;火焰图AI&#34; width=&#34;1999&#34;&#xA;高度=“1353”/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;summarize-incidents-in-one-click&#34;&gt;一键汇总事件&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/06/grafana-incident-new-tools-for-faster-simpler-incident-response/#ai-driven-summaries-with-openai-integration&#34;&gt; OpenAI 集成&lt;/a&gt;自动生成简洁、可操作的事件摘要。这种分析不仅可以快速捕获事件的本质，还可以帮助团队确保在记录和传达事件影响时不会忽略任何关键细节。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;ai- generated-titles-and-descriptions-for-grafana-dashboards&#34;&gt;人工智能为 Grafana 仪表板生成的标题和描述&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;不再想知道如何将您打包到仪表板中的所有数据汇总到一个标题中。 Grafana 包括新的 &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/04/09/grafana-11-release-all-the-new-features/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt#faster-ai-powered-titles-and -descriptions&#34;&gt;人工智能驱动的工具，自动总结&lt;/a&gt;面板和仪表板中的信息，并为仪表板创建详细的标题和描述。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;了解&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/machine-learning/llm/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;如何启用 Grafana LLM 插件&lt;/a&gt; —立即开始使用 Grafana Cloud 堆栈中的所有这些工具及更多工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关 AI/ML 和 Grafana 的更多信息，请查看我们的 GrafanaCON 2024 会议“&lt;a href=&#34;/events/grafanacon/2024/creating-intelligent-grafana-apps-using-llms-large-language-models/ ?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;AI/ML + Grafana：如何利用法学硕士创建智能 Grafana 应用&lt;/a&gt;”现已按需提供。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt; 是开始使用指标、日志、跟踪、仪表板等的最简单方法。我们为每个用例提供慷慨的永久免费套餐和计划。 &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;立即免费注册&lt;/a&gt;！&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>