<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</title>
    <link>/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grafana Labs blog on Grafana Labs</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Single-tenant vs. multi-tenant architecture with Grafana Cloud: A guide to choosing the right approach】带有Grafana Cloud的单租户与多租户建筑：选择正确方法的指南</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/18/single-tenant-vs-multi-tenant-architecture-with-grafana-cloud-how-to-choose-the-right-approach/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud’s flexibility is one of its greatest strengths, but the breadth of choices can sometimes be overwhelming. We see this a lot when it comes to selecting the right architectural approach, with organizations unsure of how many stacks they need to host their environment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud provides robust features for managing tenancy, enabling organizations to effectively handle diverse teams and projects. In this blog, we’ll explore the advantages and disadvantages of managing Grafana Cloud tenants through multiple stacks for data isolation and permission control. We&amp;rsquo;ll also look at the pros and cons of maintaining a single stack and managing permissions via role-based access control (RBAC) and labeling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And while we recommend using a single-stack approach in most cases, this should help you and your organization come to an informed decision about the architectural approach that best fits your specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-pros-and-cons-of-maintaining-a-single-stack-architecture-with-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;The pros and cons of maintaining a single-stack architecture with Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Role-based access control, or &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/roles-and-permissions/access-control/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;RBAC&lt;/a&gt;, paired with a single-stack approach provides a standardized way of granting, changing, and revoking access when it comes to viewing and modifying Grafana Cloud resources such as dashboards, reports, and administrative settings. RBAC also provides the ability to create custom roles that go beyond “Admin,” “Editor,” and “Viewer” to control who can access which resources d on a more granular level.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taking that a step further, you can use label-based access control, or &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/account-management/authentication-and-permissions/access-policies/label-access-policies/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;LBAC&lt;/a&gt;, to create access policies so users can only query the metrics or logs data that meet specific label requirements. LBAC is useful if you want to separate access to the telemetry backends within a single stack. Instead of giving someone access to all of the metrics or logs within a stack, you only give them access to a specific label set of the metrics or logs in that stack. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The LBAC feature allows you to associate multiple sets of Prometheus label selectors with a policy. As a result, queries only return data that match at least one of the provided selectors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;advantages&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advantages&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organized configuration&lt;/strong&gt;: LBAC rules can easily be attached to Cloud Access Policies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Centralized management&lt;/strong&gt;: Managing users, roles, and permissions in one place is easier than configuring and maintaining multiple instances. This reduces administrative overhead.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified maintenance:&lt;/strong&gt; Updates, backups, and maintenance tasks are simplified with a single instance. You can apply changes across all dashboards without having to replicate efforts across multiple stacks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easier integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Integrating with other tools and systems (like authentication providers) is more straightforward in a single stack, reducing complexity in the overall architecture.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;disadvantages&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disadvantages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Risks of misconfiguration&lt;/strong&gt;: If LBAC is misconfigured, it could lead to potential data leaks.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limited granularity&lt;/strong&gt;: Different teams and departments may have unique requirements for their dashboards, and labels and RBAC don’t provide the level of granularity around managing permissions that having multiple stacks does. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-a-multi-tenant-architecture-with-grafana-cloud&#34;&gt;The advantages and disadvantages of a multi-tenant architecture with Grafana Cloud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/security-and-account-management/cloud-stacks/stack-architecture-guidance/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;multi-tenant architecture approach&lt;/a&gt;, you create a stack with a distinct UI frontend for every team that needs one. Each team logs into the same Grafana Cloud instance, accessing their distinct stack backends as data sources. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multiple production stacks are recommended when the goal is complete isolation among departments or teams and you don&amp;rsquo;t expect any need to combine data or resources from different stacks. This is typically used by resellers and managed service providers that have customers who shouldn’t have access to one another’s data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;advantages-1&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advantages&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance&lt;/strong&gt;: This approach ensures better query performance and limits the impact of teams, departments, or clients on one another.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cost attribution&lt;/strong&gt;: When you’re using multiple stacks and each stack belongs to a team, it’s easy to attribute costs to each team, client, or department.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Centralized billing&lt;/strong&gt;: Each Grafana Cloud instance of each stack includes a &lt;code&gt;grafanacloud-usage&lt;/code&gt; data source that powers the included &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/cost-management-and-billing/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;billing dashboard&lt;/a&gt;. On the central billing dashboard it’s easy to see the usage of each telemetry signal per stack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data segregation&lt;/strong&gt;: Each team, department, or client can have its own stack, ensuring sensitive data isn&amp;rsquo;t accessible to unauthorized users from other teams.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance&lt;/strong&gt;: Isolating data can help meet regulatory requirements. It’s easier to control data access and ensure compliance within distinct environments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customizability&lt;/strong&gt;: Teams can customize their own stack settings, plugins, and dashboards without impacting others, allowing for tailored solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Easier dashboard sharing&lt;/strong&gt;: You have several options to share dashboards. If all stacks are in the same region, you can leverage &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/connect-externally-hosted/multi-stack-data-sources/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;multi-stack querying&lt;/a&gt;, so you can centralize visibility across environments without duplicating data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;disadvantages-1&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disadvantages&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cross-tenant querying&lt;/strong&gt;: Querying all tenants together by the admin team requires additional configurations, and the admin team may need to log into each Grafana Cloud instance or consolidate metrics tenants into one stack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correlation challenges&lt;/strong&gt;: Grafana Labs recommends customers use a single stack as their production observability environment because cross-stack correlation won&amp;rsquo;t function properly.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consistency and best practices&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensuring consistent practices and standards across multiple stacks can be challenging, potentially leading to varying levels of quality and performance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;make-the-choice-that&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make the choice that&amp;rsquo;s right for your organization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Choosing the right architectural approach in Grafana Cloud ultimately depends on your organization’s priorities around isolation, collaboration, compliance, and administrative overhead. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multiple stacks provide strong boundaries, cost attribution, and customization, making them well-suited for scenarios where complete isolation is non-negotiable, such as with managed service providers or highly regulated environments. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, a single-stack architecture with RBAC and LBAC offers simplicity, centralized management, and easier integrations, which often aligns better with organizations seeking operational efficiency and cross-team visibility. This approach is recommended for most Grafana Cloud customers, since they are managing their own stacks and aren&amp;rsquo;t under strict regulatory requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s no one-size-fits-all answer, but by weighing the trade-offs outlined here, you can select the model that best balances your technical requirements with your business goals.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt; Grafana Cloud的灵活性是其最大的优势之一，但是选择的广度有时会令人不知所措。在选择正确的建筑方法时，我们会看到很多事情，组织不确定他们需要多少堆栈来托管环境。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana Cloud为管理租赁提供了强大的功能，使组织能够有效地处理各种团队和项目。在此博客中，我们将通过多个堆栈进行数据隔离和权限控制来管理Grafana Cloud租户的优点和缺点。我们还将研究通过基于角色的访问控制（RBAC）和标签来维护单个堆栈和管理权限的利弊。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，尽管我们建议在大多数情况下使用单栈方法，但这应该帮助您和您的组织做出有关最适合您特定需求的建筑方法的明智决定。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“维持grafana-cloud-a-single-a-single-single-single-stack-architecture”&gt;使用grafana cloud &lt;/h2&gt;维护单栈架构的优点和缺点&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;基于角色的访问控制，或&lt;a href =“/doc/grafana/grafana/最新/管理/角色及permissions/访问权利/访问控制/？ 设置。 RBAC还提供了创建超出“管理员”，“编辑器”和“查看器”的自定义角色的能力，以控制谁可以在更精细的层面上访问哪些资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taking that a step further, you can use label-based access control, or &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/account-management/authentication-and-permissions/access-policies/label-access-policies/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;LBAC&lt;/a&gt;, to create access policies so users can only query the metrics or logs data that meet specific label requirements.如果要分开单个堆栈中遥测后端的访问权限，LBAC将很有用。与其让某人访问堆栈中的所有指标或日志，还只能让他们访问该堆栈中特定标签集或日志的特定标签集。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; LBAC功能使您可以将多个Prometheus标签选择器与策略相关联。结果，查询仅返回与至少一个提供的选择器之一匹配的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“优势”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;优点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;有组织的配置&lt;/strong&gt;：LBAC规则很容易附加到云访问策略&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;集中管理&lt;/strong&gt;：在一个地方管理用户，角色和权限比配置和维护多个实例更容易。这减少了管理开销。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;简化的维护：&lt;/strong&gt;更新，备份和维护任务可简化单个姿态。您可以在所有仪表板上应用更改，而不必复制多个堆栈的努力。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;更轻松的集成&lt;/strong&gt;：与其他工具和系统集成（例如身份验证提供商）在单个堆栈中更加简单，从而降低了整体体系结构的复杂性。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“缺点”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;缺点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;错误配置的风险&lt;/strong&gt;：如果LBAC被错误配置，则可能导致潜在的数据泄漏。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;有限的粒度&lt;/strong&gt;：不同的团队和部门可能对其仪表板有独特的要求，标签和RBAC并不能在管理拥有多个堆栈的权限的管理权限上提供粒度水平。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“  - 及以 - 偏见 - 居住 - 统计结构与grafana-cloud”&gt;与Grafana Cloud cloud &lt;/h2&gt;的优势和缺点的优势和缺点&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/security-and-account-managements/cloud-stacks/stack-architecture-guidance/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;多居式体系结构方法&lt;/a&gt;，您可以为每个团队创建一个独特的ui un stack for a of a ui for a tem of a team for a tem of a ui for n os of a ui for n os of ceers of每个团队的前端。每个团队都会登录相同的Grafana云实例，访问其独特的堆栈后端作为数据源。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当目标是在部门或团队之间完全隔离时，建议进行多个生产堆栈，并且您预计您不需要将数据或资源从不同堆栈组合起来。经销商和托管服务提供商通常使用这一点，这些客户不应该访问彼此的数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“ Advantages-1”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;优点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;绩效&lt;/strong&gt;：这种方法确保了更好的查询性能，并限制了团队，部门或客户的影响。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;成本归因&lt;/strong&gt;：当您使用多个堆栈并且每个堆栈属于一个团队时，很容易将成本归因于每个团队，客户或部门。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;集中计费&lt;/strong&gt;：每个堆栈的每个grafana云实例都包含一个&lt;code&gt; grafanacloud-usage &lt;/code&gt;数据源，该数据源将为包括&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/grafana-cloud/cost-management-management-management-management-management-management-management-management-ang-billing/？在中央计费仪表板上，很容易看到每个堆栈的每个遥测信号的用法。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;数据隔离&lt;/strong&gt;：每个团队，部门或客户都可以拥有自己的堆栈，确保其他团队未经授权的用户无法访问敏感数据。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;合规性&lt;/strong&gt;：隔离数据可以帮助满足监管要求。控制数据访问并确保在不同环境中的合规性更容易。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;自定义性&lt;/strong&gt;：团队可以自定义自己的堆栈设置，插件和仪表板，而不会影响他人，从而允许量身定制的解决方案。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;更轻松的仪表板共享&lt;/strong&gt;：您有几种共享仪表板的选项。如果所有堆栈都位于同一区域，则可以利用&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/connect-externally-externely-host hosted/multi-stack-data-sources/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt; multi-stack查询&lt;/a&gt;，因此您可以跨环境跨环境中心化，而无需仔细研究。&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“缺点-1”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;缺点&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;跨租户查询&lt;/strong&gt;：管理团队一起查询所有租户需要其他配置，管理员团队可能需要登录每个Grafana Cloud实例或将指标租户合并到一个堆栈中。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;相关性挑战&lt;/strong&gt;：Grafana Labs建议客户使用单个堆栈作为生产可观察性环境，因为交叉堆栈相关性无法正常运行。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;一致性和最佳实践&lt;/strong&gt;：确保多个堆栈中的一致实践和标准可能具有挑战性，可能导致质量和性能的水平不同。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ make-the-the-that”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;做出适合您组织的选择&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Grafana Cloud中选择正确的建筑方法最终取决于您组织在隔离，协作，合规和管理开销方面的优先事项。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多个堆栈提供强大的界限，成本归因和自定义，使其非常适合完全隔离的场景，例如与托管服务提供商或高度监管的环境。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;另一方面，具有RBAC和LBAC的单栈体系结构提供了简单，集中管理和更容易的集成，这通常与寻求运营效率和跨团队可见性的组织更加一致。建议大多数Grafana Cloud客户使用这种方法，因为他们正在管理自己的堆栈，并且不受严格的监管要求。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;没有一种适合的答案，但是通过权衡此处概述的权衡，您可以选择最能平衡技术要求与业务目标的模型。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Faster, more memory-efficient performance in Grafana Mimir: a closer look at Mimir Query Engine】Grafana Mimir中更快，更高的记忆提高性能：仔细查看Mimir查询引擎</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/17/faster-more-memory-efficient-performance-in-grafana-mimir-a-closer-look-at-mimir-query-engine/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Until recently, &lt;a href=&#34;/oss/mimir/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Mimir&lt;/a&gt; — our open source, horizontally scalable, multi-tenant time series database (TSDB) — has exclusively used &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus/prometheus/tree/main/promql&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Prometheus’ PromQL engine&lt;/a&gt; to evaluate queries. While the PromQL engine works great, it sometimes needs a lot of memory to run, specifically in the Mimir querier component. To address this memory consumption issue, we recently introduced Mimir Query Engine (MQE).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rolled out in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mimir/releases&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafama Mimir 2.17&lt;/a&gt;, MQE is also a foundational feature for the upcoming Mimir 3.0 release, offering faster, more memory-efficient performance for our users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we offer a peek under the hood of MQE, how it works compared to the PromQL engine, and how we developed it. You can also learn more about MQE, and other features planned for Grafana Mimir 3.0, in the GrafanaCON 2025 talk below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yabtVakeqc8&#39; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: While MQE is the default query engine as of Grafana Mimir 2.17, we are not removing support for the Prometheus query engine. You can still&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/references/architecture/mimir-query-engine/#fallback-to-prometheus-engine&#34;&gt;use this engine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;via a command line argument or configuration setting.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mimir-memory-consumption-and-the-promql-engine-an-overview&#34;&gt;Mimir memory consumption and the PromQL engine: an overview  &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To understand why we developed MQE, it’s helpful to first understand some basics about memory consumption in Mimir and the PromQL engine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Mimir, the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/references/architecture/components/querier/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;querier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is the component that evaluates queries. At Grafana Labs, we run a number of large Mimir clusters internally. We noticed that the queriers often consume varying amounts of memory because different queries will load a different number of samples. We have to set sufficient memory requests and limits to minimize the probability that a querier pod gets killed by the Kubernetes scheduler when the actual memory utilization exceeds the memory limit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1288x433/f45c8911aa/mqe_memory-request-and-limit-3.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1288x433/f45c8911aa/mqe_memory-request-and-limit-3.png&#34;alt=&#34;A graph showing memory usage over time with annotations indicating memory limits, requests, and utilization spikes.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1288x433/f45c8911aa/mqe_memory-request-and-limit-3.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A graph showing memory usage over time with annotations indicating memory limits, requests, and utilization spikes.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The visualization above shows the graph of querier memory utilization compared with the memory request and memory limit. While setting the memory limit and request on the high side can work, it is inefficient if the querier component is not utilizing the memory requested. Despite plenty of memory utilization spikes here and there, at different times, memory utilization can also go very low below the memory request. Grafana Mimir operators are paying for the memory request at the dashed yellow line, but the actual utilization is often below that. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, let’s dig into how Prometheus’ engine evaluates queries to understand the memory utilization behavior described above.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consider the query &lt;code&gt;sum by(namespace) (http_requests_total{method=&amp;quot;GET&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;. Prometheus’ engine will break this down into an operation for the metric selector &lt;code&gt;http_requests_total{method=&amp;quot;GET&amp;quot;}&lt;/code&gt;, and an operation for the &lt;code&gt;sum by&lt;/code&gt; aggregation operator that consumes the result of the first operation. First, the engine evaluates the first operation, loading samples from the first selector at each time step for every selected series into memory. After that, it applies the &lt;code&gt;sum by&lt;/code&gt; operator over this intermediate result, and returns the final result to the user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1080x475/faab18641e/mqe_sum-by-operator-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1080x475/faab18641e/mqe_sum-by-operator-2.png&#34;alt=&#34;Table showing HTTP GET requests by namespace and pod, with totals summed by namespace.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1080x475/faab18641e/mqe_sum-by-operator-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Table showing HTTP GET requests by namespace and pod, with totals summed by namespace.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can see that the peak memory consumption of a query is proportional to the product of the number of series selected and the number of time steps being evaluated. If it needs to load 10 series, it will load them into memory. Likewise, if the first selector matches 1 million series, it will load all of their samples into memory at once. This results in the varying memory utilization in the graph above. In a heavily used time series database, users run many different kinds of queries that can fetch only a few samples or a lot of samples.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;initial-improvements-to-mimir-memory-consumption&#34;&gt;Initial improvements to Mimir memory consumption&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the years, we’ve introduced a number of techniques in Mimir to reduce the peak memory consumption of queriers while evaluating queries. For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time splitting:&lt;/strong&gt; This approach reduces the number of time steps evaluated by a single querier. Range queries are split into multiple, day-long queries that are evaluated independently by queriers and then stitched back together by &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/references/architecture/components/query-frontend/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;query frontends&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharding&lt;/strong&gt;: This reduces the number of series selected by a single querier by splitting the query’s input series into multiple shards, each of which are evaluated independently by queriers and then combined by query-frontends.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chunks streaming&lt;/strong&gt;: This reduces the memory consumed by chunks as they are read from ingesters and store-gateways as needed in queriers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about time splitting and query sharding, please check out &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2022/07/20/how-we-improved-grafana-mimir-query-performance-by-up-to-10x/&#34;&gt;this blog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One point we haven’t mentioned here is limits, which can be set to block queries that load too many series or have too wide a time range. But limits are the last line of defence. We want to avoid users hitting them as much as possible because they can be frustrating, often non-actionable, and prevent users from running the queries they expect to run.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, despite all the techniques above, these improvements still didn’t completely solve the memory utilization issues we were seeing. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mqe-streaming-queries-for-greater-efficiency&#34;&gt;MQE: Streaming queries for greater efficiency &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We discovered that the best solution to the unpredictable memory consumption in Mimir with Prometheus’ engine is to process queries in a streaming manner without loading all samples at once. This is the core premise of what Mimir Query Engine does. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The key way the engine achieves this is by not loading all the input series into memory at once, and instead loading them into memory only when needed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s revisit the example query from before: &lt;code&gt;sum by(namespace) (http_requests_total{method=&amp;quot;GET&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;. MQE will execute the same selector &lt;code&gt;http_requests_total{method=&amp;quot;GET&amp;quot;)&lt;/code&gt;, but instead of getting all the results at once, the engine will load the series one by one, while doing the running sum and the grouping using a streaming model.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1105x574/acee91111c/mqe_queries-by-streaming-model-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1105x574/acee91111c/mqe_queries-by-streaming-model-2.png&#34;alt=&#34;Diagram showing a table of HTTP GET requests by namespace and pod, with arrows pointing to a summarized table by namespace.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1105x574/acee91111c/mqe_queries-by-streaming-model-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Diagram showing a table of HTTP GET requests by namespace and pod, with arrows pointing to a summarized table by namespace.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The inputs to a query executed by MQE are series with their samples that match one or more query selectors. These series are passed to zero or more operators. At its peak memory utilization, MQE in this example will only hold samples for one input series and samples for the sole output series at once, a significant reduction compared to Prometheus&amp;rsquo; PromQL engine, particularly when the selector selects many series.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1465x548/63295391e0/mqe-toggle-the-engine-3.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1465x548/63295391e0/mqe-toggle-the-engine-3.png&#34;alt=&#34;Graph comparing data usage of Prometheus engine and MQE over time, with a notable drop at 11:00 labeled &amp;#39;Toggle the engine.&amp;#39;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1465x548/63295391e0/mqe-toggle-the-engine-3.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Graph comparing data usage of Prometheus engine and MQE over time, with a notable drop at 11:00 labeled &amp;#39;Toggle the engine.&amp;#39;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The graph above shows the querier memory consumption and how it looks as we toggle the engine from Prometheus to MQE after 11:00, resulting in a significant drop in memory consumption. MQE has proven that it reduces querier memory fluctuations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;MQE is also now used in the Mimir query-frontend, the component that helps to accelerate queries. Using MQE in the query-frontend brings similar improvements as it does to the querier, such as reduced memory consumption and latency. Furthermore, MQE&amp;rsquo;s common subexpression elimination is also applied in query-frontends, eliminating unnecessary, repeated work. Without going too much into the details, common subexpression elimination is already working for some common use cases and being improved to handle more scenarios with query sharding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;more-detailed-results&#34;&gt;More detailed results&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the obvious reduction in memory consumption, MQE also performs better at scale. For example, evaluating &lt;code&gt;sum by (group) (metric{...})&lt;/code&gt; with 100k input series and 10 distinct values of group sees 92% lower peak memory utilization and runs 39% faster than Prometheus’ PromQL engine: 75 MB instead of 954 MB, and 4.2 seconds instead of 7 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On top of this, the peak memory utilization of the engine scales much better with increasing numbers of input series. The graph below shows the peak memory consumption when evaluating &lt;code&gt;sum by (group) (metric{...})&lt;/code&gt; with different numbers of input series:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x745/d6e85f6888/mqe_number-of-series-selected-chart-2.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x745/d6e85f6888/mqe_number-of-series-selected-chart-2.png&#34;alt=&#34;Line graph comparing memory utilization of Prometheus&amp;#39; engine and Mimir Query Engine across series counts, with Prometheus using more memory.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x745/d6e85f6888/mqe_number-of-series-selected-chart-2.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Line graph comparing memory utilization of Prometheus&amp;#39; engine and Mimir Query Engine across series counts, with Prometheus using more memory.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s important to note that MQE is 100% compatible with all stable PromQL features, which means we can still run all existing queries, dashboards, and alerts using the Mimir Query Engine while getting the benefit of faster execution and better memory utilization. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;testing-correctness&#34;&gt;Testing correctness&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most important property of a good query engine is the &lt;em&gt;correctness&lt;/em&gt;, meaning its ability to produce results that are accurate and complete. Afterall, what’s the point of having a faster and more memory-efficient query engine if it produces the wrong result?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While building MQE, we used the existing query engine — PromQL engine — as the reference for correctness. We knew the result of each query sent to MQE must match the output from Prometheus’ engine. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We tested correctness in two ways. First, we had different unit tests run the same query against two query engines and made sure they had a consistent result. Prometheus provides the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus/prometheus/tree/main/promql/promqltest&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;PromQL test scripting language&lt;/a&gt;, which is a very useful tool for setting up different time series and samples, and helped us test query engine correctness precisely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, we ran a parallel query path in Grafana Cloud’s staging environment using &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/manage/tools/query-tee/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Mimir query-tee&lt;/a&gt; to compare the results from real, live queries. This helped us catch possible correctness issues and edge cases that might be missed from the unit tests alone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/763x612/0d6ad320c4/mqe_query-tee-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/763x612/0d6ad320c4/mqe_query-tee-diagram.png&#34;alt=&#34;Flowchart showing a system architecture with &amp;#39;query-tee&amp;#39; at the top, connected to two &amp;#39;query-frontend&amp;#39; boxes, each linked to a &amp;#39;querier.&amp;#39;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/763x612/0d6ad320c4/mqe_query-tee-diagram.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Flowchart showing a system architecture with &amp;#39;query-tee&amp;#39; at the top, connected to two &amp;#39;query-frontend&amp;#39; boxes, each linked to a &amp;#39;querier.&amp;#39;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The diagram above shows how the parallel query path works. The same query comes to query-tee which is fanned out to a Prometheus read path and MQE read path. Each query-frontend will forward the request downstream and return each result back to query-tee, which will perform a comparison, alerting us to discrepancies between the two engines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;learn-more&#34;&gt;Learn more  &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As mentioned above, Mimir Query Engine is available now and is the default engine as of Grafana Mimir 2.17. To learn more, please check out our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/mimir/latest/references/architecture/mimir-query-engine/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yabtVakeqc8&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this talk at GrafanaCON 2025&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;直到最近，&lt;a href =“/oss/mimir/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana mimir &lt;/a&gt;  - 我们的开源，水平可扩展的，多二个租赁时间序列数据库（TSDB） href =“ https://github.com/prometheus/prometheus/tree/main/main/promql” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; prometheus&#39;prometheus&#39;prometheus&#39;promql Engine &lt;/a&gt;以评估查询。尽管Promql引擎效果很好，但有时需要大量内存才能运行，特别是在Mimir Querier组件中。为了解决此内存消耗问题，我们最近引入了Mimir查询引擎（MQE）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/grafana/mimir/releases” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; Grafama mimir 2.17 &lt;/a&gt;中，MQE也是即将到来的Mimir 3.0释放，&lt;03.0 promence &lt;0 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;0&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们在MQE的引擎盖下提供了一个窥视，与Promql引擎相比，它的工作原理以及我们的开发方式。您还可以在下面的Grafanacon 2025演讲中了解更多有关MQE的信息，以及针对Grafana Mimir 3.0计划的其他功能。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“ 560” height =“ 315” src =&#39;https：//www.youtube.com/embed/yabtvakeqc8&#39;title =“ youtube视频播放器” frameborder =“ 0”允许=“ Accelerometer; Accelerometer; Autoplay; AutoPlay; Autoplay; Autoplay; AutoPlay; clipboard-write; clipboard-write; encrypted-mecia; exprypted-media; referrerpolicy =“ strict-origin-cross-origin” glasefullscreen&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;注意：虽然MQE是Grafana Mimir 2.17的默认查询引擎，但我们并未删除对Prometheus查询引擎的支持。您仍然可以&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/docs/mimir/festment/cotrences/architection/mimir-query-entection/＃halldback to-prometheus-engine”&gt;使用此引擎&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;通过命令行参数或配置设置。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解我们为什么开发MQE，首先了解Mimir和Promql Engine的内存消耗基本知识很有帮助。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在mimir中，&lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/doc/mimir/最终/corepences/corepences/components/querier/querier/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt&#39;&gt; Querier &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;是评估查询的组件。在Grafana Labs，我们在内部运行许多大型Mimir集群。我们注意到查询器通常会消耗不同数量的内存，因为不同的查询会加载不同数量的样本。我们必须设置足够的内存请求和限制，以最大程度地减少当实际内存利用率超过内存限制时，Querier Pod被Kubernetes调度程序杀死的概率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1288x433/f45c8911aa/mqe_memory-request-request-and-limit-3.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper w-100p h-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1288x4333/f45c8911aa/mqe_memory-request-request-request-and-limit-3.png” alt =“显示内存使用的图表，表示记忆使用，表示记忆的时间，表示记忆限制，请求限制，和upits spises，and ulips and uliptizatization。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1288x433/f45c8911aa/mqe_memory-request-request-and-limit-3.png”&#xA;alt =“随着时间的时间显示内存使用的图表，带有注释，指示内存限制，请求和利用率。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上面的可视化显示了与内存请求和内存限制相比，查看更查询的内存利用率图。在设置内存限制并在高侧的请求中可以工作时，如果查询较高的组件不利用所请求的内存，则效率低下。尽管在这里和那里有大量的内存利用率峰值，但在不同的时间，内存利用率也可能低于内存请求。 Grafana Mimir操作员在虚线的黄线上为内存请求付费，但实际利用通常低于此。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，让我们研究Prometheus的引擎如何评估查询以了解上述记忆利用率行为。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;考虑查询&lt;code&gt;总和（命名空间）（http_requests_total {method =“ get”）&lt;/code&gt;。 Prometheus的引擎将将其分解为公制选择器&lt;code&gt; http_requests_total {method =“ get“ get”} &lt;/code&gt;的操作，以及&lt;/code&gt;通过&lt;/code&gt; contregation操作员为&lt;code&gt; sum的操作，该操作员消耗了第一个操作的结果。首先，发动机评估第一个操作，每个时间步骤从第一个选择器中加载样本，每个选定系列中的每个时间步骤中的记忆中。之后，它在此中间结果上使用&lt;/code&gt;运算符的&lt;code&gt;总和，并将最终结果返回给用户。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1080x475/faab18641e/mqe_sum-by-operator-2.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1022730/1080x475/faab18641e/mqe_sum-sum-by-operator-2.png” alt =“ Alt =”表显示http http获取http的请求，并通过namesspace and pod＆pod tatm namnespace and pod by namnespace summand namnamespace。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1080x475/faab18641e/mqe_sum-by-operator-2.png”&#xA;alt =“表显示http fet命名空间和pod的http get请求，并以名称空间汇总。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们可以看到，查询的峰值存储器消耗与所选串联数量的乘积和所评估的时间步数的乘积成正比。如果需要加载10系列，则将它们加载到内存中。同样，如果第一个选择器匹配100万个系列，则将其所有样本一次加载到内存中。这导致t他在上图中改变了内存利用。在大量使用的时间序列数据库中，用户运行了许多不同类型的查询，这些查询只能获取几个示例或很多示例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“初始提高到米米尔 - 内存 - 消费”&gt;对Mimir内存消耗的初步改进&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;多年来，我们在米米尔（Mimir）中引入了许多技术，以在评估查询时减少查询器的峰值记忆消耗。例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;时间分割：&lt;/strong&gt;这种方法减少了单个查询者评估的时间步骤的数量。范围查询分为多个为期一天的查询，这些查询由Querier独立评估，然后由&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/mimir/最终/cometences/cometection/query-frontents/query-frontend/？&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; sharding &lt;/strong&gt;：这通过将查询的输入序列分为多个碎片来减少单个查询选择的串联数量，每个碎片通过查询器独立评估，然后通过查询 - 范围进行组合。&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;块流&lt;/strong&gt;：这减少了块中块所消耗的记忆，因为它们是根据需要在Queriers中从摄入剂和商店门上读取的。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关分裂和查询碎片的更多信息，请查看&lt;a href =“/blog/2022/07/20/how-we-we-we-we-we-we-rafafana-mimir-query-query-query-query-performance-comperformance-by-to-up-10x/”&gt;此博客&lt;/a&gt;。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们在这里没有提到的一个点是限制，可以将其设置为阻止加载太多系列或时间范围太大的查询。但是限制是最后的防线。我们希望避免用户尽可能多地击中他们，因为他们可能会令人沮丧，通常不可动作，并阻止用户运行他们期望运行的查询。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;也就是说，尽管上述所有技术，但这些改进仍未完全解决我们所看到的内存利用问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们发现，使用Prometheus的发动机在Mimir中无法预测的记忆消耗的最佳解决方案是以流方式处理查询，而不一次加载所有样品。这是Mimir查询引擎所做的核心前提。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;引擎实现这一目标的关键方法是不立即将所有输入系列加载到内存中，而仅在需要时将它们加载到内存中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们从之前重新访问示例查询：&lt;code&gt; by（namesspace）总和（http_requests_total {method =“ get”）&lt;/code&gt;。 MQE将执行相同的选择器&lt;code&gt; http_requests_total {method =“ get”）&lt;/code&gt;，但是在执行运行总和和使用流模型进行分组时，发动机不会立即获得所有结果。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ ryedimi一个”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1105x574/acee91111c/mqe_queries-byby-streaming-model-model-2.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a/a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1105x574/acee911111c/mqe_quer_queries-by-streaming-model-model-model-model-model-2.png” alt =” Alt =“显示http获取请求的http get cepts of namesspace和pod/pod/pod cons/name name name name，&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1105x574/acee91111c/mqe_queris-beries-by-streaming-model-model-2.png”&#xA;Alt =“图表显示了命名空间和POD的HTTP获取请求表，箭头指向命名空间的汇总表。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;由MQE执行的查询的输入是与一个或多个查询选择器匹配的样本的系列。这些系列传递到零或更多操作员。在此示例中，MQE在其峰值内存利用率下，仅将一个输入系列的样品和唯一输出系列的样品保存，与Prometheus的Promql Engine相比，显着降低，尤其是当Selector选择许多系列时。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1465x548/63295391E0/MQE-TOGGLE--TOGGLE--ENGINE-THE--ENGINE-3.PNG”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1465x548/63295391E0/MQE-TOGGLEGLLE---ENGINE-3.PNG” ALT =“图形比较Prometheus Engine和Prometheus Engine和MQE的数据使用情况，并在11:00 nab nab a Strige a Prometheus Engine and Mqe drop prom a Progetheus and Mqe drop nib nab/nab in oferted。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1465X548/63295391E0/MQE-TOGGLE--TOGGLE--ENGINE-THE--ENGINE-3.PNG”&#xA;alt =“比较Prometheus Engine和MQE的数据用法，随着时间的推移，标有11:00的著名下降，标记为&#39;切换引擎。&#39;”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上图显示了更查询的内存消耗及其在11:00后从Prometheus切换到MQE时的外观，导致内存消耗大幅下降。 MQE已证明它减少了更查询的内存波动。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; MQE现在也用于Mimir Query-Frontend，这是有助于加速查询的组件。在查询范围内使用MQE带来的改进与查询更加相似，例如减少内存消耗和延迟。此外，MQE的常见子表达消除也被应用于查询范围内，从而消除了不必要的重复工作。不用太多细节，消除常见的子表达已经在某些常见用例中起作用，并且可以通过查询碎片来处理更多方案。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“更详细的补充”&gt;更详细的结果&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;超出了明显的还原在内存消耗中，MQE的表现也更好。例如，通过（组）（metric {...}）评估&lt;code&gt;总和100K输入系列和10个不同的组值，比Prometheus的Prometheus的PromeqQL Engine低92％，低于Prometheus的峰值39％：75 MB，而不是954 MB，而不是7.2秒，而不是7秒。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最重要的是，随着输入系列的增加，发动机尺度的峰值存储器利用率更好。下图显示了使用不同数量的输入系列的评估&lt;code&gt;总和（组）（group）（metric {...}）&lt;/code&gt;时的峰值内存消耗：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x745/d6e85f68888/mqe_number-of-series-series-series-series-select-selected-chart-chart-chart-chart-chart-cng”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x745/d6e85f6888/mqe_number-of-series-selected-chart-2.png&#34;alt=&#34;Line graph comparing memory utilization of Prometheus&#39; engine and Mimir Query Engine across series counts, with Prometheus using more memory.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1159x745/d6e85f68888/mqe_number-of-series-series-series-series-select-select-selected-chart-chart-chart-chart-chart-cng”&#xA;alt =“线图比较了Prometheus的引擎和Mimir查询引擎的内存利用，而Prometheus则使用更多内存。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;重要的是要注意，MQE与所有稳定的PROMQL功能100％兼容，这意味着我们仍然可以使用Mimir查询引擎运行所有现有查询，仪表板和警报，同时可以从更快的执行和更好的内存利用中获得好处。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“测试校正性”&gt;测试正确性&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;良好的查询引擎的最重要属性是&lt;em&gt;正确性&lt;/em&gt;，这意味着其能够产生准确和完整的结果。毕竟，如果产生错误的结果，那么拥有更快，更快的记忆效率查询引擎有什么意义？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;构建MQE时，我们使用了现有的查询引擎（Promql Engine）作为正确性的参考。我们知道发送到MQE的每个查询的结果必须与Prometheus的发动机的输出相匹配。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们通过两种方式测试了正确性。首先，我们对两个查询引擎进行了相同的查询，并确保它们具有一致的结果。 Prometheus provides the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/prometheus/prometheus/tree/main/promql/promqltest&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;PromQL test scripting language&lt;/a&gt;, which is a very useful tool for setting up different time series and samples, and helped us test query engine correctness正是。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第二，我们使用&lt;a href =“/docs/mimir/最终/管理/工具/q，我们在Grafana Cloud的登台环境中运行了平行查询路径uery-tee/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt“&gt; mimir Query-tee &lt;/a&gt;比较来自真实的实时查询的结果。这有助于我们发现可能仅通过单位测试而错过的可能问题。&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/763x612/0d6ad320c4/mqe_query-tee-deegram.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/763x612/0d612/0d6ad320c4/mqe_query-tee-diagram.png.png” alt =“ flowchart显示出一个系统体系结构，带有&#39;query-tee&#39;的系统体系结构，与&#39;query-tee&#39;相关，可连接到最高点，每个Query-Frontend&#39;s Query-cooly-query-query do yer&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/763x612/0d6ad320c4/mqe_query-tee-dee-diagram.png”&#xA;alt =“流程图在顶部显示带有&#39;Query-tee&#39;的系统体系结构，连接到两个&#39;Query-Frontend&#39;框，每个框都链接到&#39;Querier。&#39;”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上图显示了并行查询路径的工作原理。查询tee的查询也相同，该查询是在Prometheus读取路径和MQE读取路径的情况下。每个查询额定版本都会将请求转发下游，并将每个结果退回查询-TEE，该查询将进行比较，以提醒我们两个引擎之间的差异。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ Learn-More”&gt;了解更多&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如上所述，Mimir查询引擎现已上市，并且是Grafana Mimir 2.17的默认引擎。要了解更多信息，请查看我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/mimir/最新/参考/架构/mimir-query-enchine/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;技术文档&lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“ Noreferrer“&gt;在Grafanacon 2025 &lt;/a&gt;上进行了演讲。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Distributed performance testing for Kubernetes environments: Grafana k6 Operator 1.0 is here】Kubernetes环境的分布式性能测试：Grafana K6操作员1.0在这里</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/16/distributed-performance-testing-for-kubernetes-environments-grafana-k6-operator-1-0-is-here/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Performance testing is critical to build reliable applications, but testing at scale, especially inside modern Kubernetes environments, can be a challenge. For example, how do you coordinate tests across multiple nodes, test private services without compromising security, or even do both at once? And most importantly, how do you do all this without adding too much operational complexity to your stack?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is where &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;k6 Operator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; comes in. What started as an experiment by k6 developer advocate &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/simskij&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Simon Aronsson&lt;/a&gt; back in 2020 has grown into a powerful open source project that makes it easier to run, manage, and scale distributed performance tests directly on your Kubernetes clusters. And today, we’re proud to share that k6 Operator has officially reached its &lt;strong&gt;1.0 release.&lt;/strong&gt; 🎉&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this post, we’ll walk you through how k6 Operator works, how it’s evolved over the years, and what’s new in the 1.0 release.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-k6-operator-and-how-does-it-work&#34;&gt;What is k6 Operator and how does it work?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana k6&lt;/a&gt; is an open source load and performance testing platform. &lt;em&gt;k6 Operator&lt;/em&gt;, specifically, is a &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/extend-kubernetes/operator/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Kubernetes operator&lt;/a&gt; that you can use to run distributed k6 tests in your Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When your applications are deployed in Kubernetes, k6 Operator makes it easy to deploy and manage k6 tests in that same environment. It works by using a &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/extend-kubernetes/api-extension/custom-resources/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Custom Resource Definition (CRD)&lt;/a&gt; to describe a test run, then bootstrapping the necessary pods to execute it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The k6 Operator defines two main CRDs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;TestRun&lt;/code&gt;: Declaratively &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/set-up/set-up-distributed-k6/usage/executing-k6-scripts-with-testrun-crd/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;runs a k6 test&lt;/a&gt; in Kubernetes. As of now, the &lt;code&gt;TestRun&lt;/code&gt; CRD (depicted in the diagram below) is the simplest way to run a distributed k6 test with OSS tooling, assuming you have a Kubernetes cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1280x1098/6e7e8ccada/testrun-crd-diagram.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1280x1098/6e7e8ccada/testrun-crd-diagram.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A diagram depicting the workflow of a TestRun CRD, showing a Kubernetes cluster with k6 Operator, an initializer pod, starter pod, runner pods, and private service with HTTP and log connections.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1280x1098/6e7e8ccada/testrun-crd-diagram.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A diagram depicting the workflow of a TestRun CRD, showing a Kubernetes cluster with k6 Operator, an initializer pod, starter pod, runner pods, and private service with HTTP and log connections.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;PrivateLoadZone&lt;/code&gt;: Registers a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/k6/author-run/private-load-zone/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#set-up-private-load-zones&#34;&gt;Private Load Zone (PLZ)&lt;/a&gt; so that &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/k6/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/a&gt; — the fully managed performance testing platform powered by k6 OSS — can run tests inside your Kubernetes cluster. This allows you to perform tests with a simple &lt;code&gt;k6 cloud run&lt;/code&gt; command rather than create a &lt;code&gt;TestRun&lt;/code&gt; Kubernetes resource manually. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1473x822/cd70329f20/private-load-zones-grafana-cloud-k6.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1473x822/cd70329f20/private-load-zones-grafana-cloud-k6.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud k6 dashboard displaying web performance metrics: LCP, FID, CLS, FCP, INP, TTFB with graphs and scores.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1473x822/cd70329f20/private-load-zones-grafana-cloud-k6.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud k6 dashboard displaying web performance metrics: LCP, FID, CLS, FCP, INP, TTFB with graphs and scores.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Overall, k6 Operator’s biggest advantage is that it &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/set-up/set-up-distributed-k6/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;simplifies running distributed k6 tests&lt;/a&gt; across multiple machines. These tests stay fully synchronized, ensuring accurate and reliable results at scale. It also simplifies the testing of applications within a private network, without breaking security or privacy policies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, as mentioned above, k6 Operator &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/set-up/set-up-distributed-k6/usage/k6-operator-to-gck6/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;integrates with Grafana Cloud k6&lt;/a&gt;, allowing you to combine all these benefits with the additional &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/k6/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;feature set&lt;/a&gt; of Grafana Cloud k6. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-evolution-of-k6-operator-a-community-driven-project&#34;&gt;The evolution of k6 Operator: a community-driven project&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kubernetes operators are a relatively new technology, and there are no formal guidelines on how they should be implemented. It’s safe to say we’ve been growing our knowledge of them alongside our expanding community of users. As more people used k6 Operator over the years, and kindly provided their feedback, it became more and more clear what was missing or could be improved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There were several major changes in the course of developing k6 Operator. One of the biggest hurdles came in 2023 with what we internally called the “idempotency epic.” Kubernetes operators are expected to be idempotent, but the API that k6 Operator interacts with isn’t. The full fix, released in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/releases/tag/v0.0.9&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;v0.0.9&lt;/a&gt; with help from a community contributor, remains the most complex challenge the project has overcome to date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other major changes were for usability improvements, with support for modern installation methods: a simple &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/set-up/set-up-distributed-k6/install-k6-operator/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#deploy-with-bundle&#34;&gt;bundle file&lt;/a&gt;, including one CLI command, for quick prototyping or complex setups, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/set-up/set-up-distributed-k6/install-k6-operator/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#deploy-with-helm&#34;&gt;Helm chart&lt;/a&gt; for managing Kubernetes applications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The OSS community has played a critical role in the evolution of k6 Operator. At the time of writing, there are 63 external contributors to the k6 Operator code base, and 99 out of 328 merged PRs are from those community members. They’ve extended CRDs with new features, fixed bugs, polished the Helm chart, and often implemented the very features they requested — from &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/pull/184&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;init containers&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/issues/168&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;enhanced affinity rules&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Special thanks to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/knechtionscoding&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Hans Knecht&lt;/a&gt;, who laid the groundwork for k6 Operator in 2021 with initial Istio support and CI pipelines, and to &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/knmsk&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Rogerio Kino&lt;/a&gt;, who authored the largest PR from an external contributor with the initial implementation of the Helm chart.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And of course, countless others have shaped k6 Operator along the way, so we extend a heartfelt thank you to everyone who has contributed. 💛💙&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-new-with-k6-operator-10&#34;&gt;What’s new with k6 Operator 1.0?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Preparation of k6 Operator 1.0 came with some breaking changes, but they were all released in previous versions of the operator.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The 1.0 release itself contains bug fixes and other improvements, like new configurations to Helm chart and the ability to pass organization-specific metrics aggregation variables in &lt;code&gt;PrivateLoadZone&lt;/code&gt; tests. But the main change is in our commitment to improve versioning, release schedules, and maintenance updates. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;regular-maintenance-updates&#34;&gt;Regular maintenance updates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k6 Operator does not depend on the latest version of Kubernetes to run. This is because our goal with the operator is to simplify your k6 testing journey, not force you into Kubernetes updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, we recognize that the Kubernetes ecosystem is constantly evolving, so there will be regular maintenance updates to ensure k6 Operator includes recent bug fixes and major improvements from the Kubernetes community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If there is a new feature released by Kubernetes that makes sense to reuse in the k6 Operator setting, it&amp;rsquo;ll be considered during a maintenance update or upon a user feature request. To learn more about our approach to maintenance, check out &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/blob/main/docs/maintenance.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this doc&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;support-for-semantic-versioning&#34;&gt;Support for Semantic Versioning&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;k6 Operator now follows &lt;a href=&#34;https://semver.org/#semantic-versioning-200&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Semantic Versioning 2.0&lt;/a&gt;. Overall, this means there’s greater stability in how we approach the future development of k6 Operator. Additionally, semantic versioning will now convey the impact of a release via an increase of a corresponding version. Let’s briefly summarize what that means for k6 Operator, specifically.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The increase of a major version can happen in the following instances:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Version upgrade of the existing CRD type.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Major backwards incompatible change of the existing CRD type, no matter its version.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Major change in functionality of the application.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Other major changes as determined by internal Grafana Labs priorities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;New features or improvements will be released with an increase of a minor version. If there are preparations happening for a major breaking change, there will be a prior deprecation warning included in one of the previous minor versions. Bug fixes will be released as patch versions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It should be noted that there can be different types of breaking changes and the meaning of a “breaking change” may depend on one’s definition. In the k6 Operator project, specifically, there are several types of APIs. We’re reserving the right to release a minor version with a breaking change when that breaking change is small and is limited to a CRD type with &lt;code&gt;v1alpha1&lt;/code&gt; version. However, any major breaking change will warrant a major release version.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To read more about our approach to versioning and stability guarantees, please visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/blob/main/docs/releases.md&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this doc&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-more-predictable-release-schedule&#34;&gt;A more predictable release schedule&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the past, k6 Operator releases were usually driven by the amount of work merged into the main branch. If there was an insufficient number of merges, there was no release. Now, we are committing to a more predictable schedule, releasing a new minor version every 8 weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, we don’t promise that each minor release will contain new features: it might be as small as a simple maintenance update, but it will be released as a minor release on schedule. Regularity of new features depends on our users’ requests and internal prioritization, and is viable to change.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Patch releases, especially in the case of bugs, can be released more frequently. If there’s a critical bug, we’ll aim to have a patch release as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Major releases do not have a regular schedule at this time. Once there are plans about the next major release, we’ll share them with the community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even as we evolve our release process, we remain committed to our user-first approach and direct communication via issues, PRs, and release notes. We’ll still pay close attention and carefully evaluate each use case before adding new features, especially in case of breaking changes to a CRD.  We’ll continue to announce any deprecations or major changes via GitHub — and don’t worry, the release notes will still be hand-written and contain emojis!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;next-steps&#34;&gt;Next steps &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve published a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/set-up/set-up-distributed-k6/upgrade-k6-operator/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;guide&lt;/a&gt; on how to update k6 Operator — something that’s been long-requested by our users. You can also refer to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/releases/tag/v1.0.0&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;1.0 release notes&lt;/a&gt; for more details on the latest release.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, thank you again to all our community members for helping shape the k6 Operator over the years. We’re excited to share this milestone with you, and look forward to our continued collaboration. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Happy testing!&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;性能测试对于构建可靠的应用程序至关重要，但是大规模的测试，尤其是在现代Kubernetes环境中，可能是一个挑战。例如，您如何协调多个节点的测试，测试私人服务而不会损害安全性，甚至同时进行一次？最重要的是，您如何在不增加堆栈的操作复杂性的情况下完成所有这些操作？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是&lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; grafana &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/afraf&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a href = a href =“ noreferrer“&gt; &lt;grong&gt; &lt;a href =” https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator“ target =” _ black“ rel =” noopener noreferrer“&gt; k6 oterator &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;是由K6 Developeriment。 target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; Simon Aronsson &lt;/a&gt;回到2020年的tocal =“ 2020年”已经发展成为一个功能强大的开源项目，该项目使直接在Kubernetes群集上直接运行，管理和扩展分布式性能测试。今天，我们很自豪地分享K6运营商已正式到达其&lt;strong&gt; 1.0版本。&lt;/strong&gt;🎉&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇文章中，我们将介绍K6操作员的工作方式，多年来的发展方式以及1.0版本中的新功能。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ What-is-k6-operator and-h--do-does-it-work”&gt;什么是K6运算符，它如何工作？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“/docs/k6/最终/？ &lt;em&gt; k6运算符&lt;/em&gt;，具体来说，是&lt;a href =“ https://kubernetes.io/docs/docs/concepts/extend-kubernetes/operator/” target =“ _ black” _ black“ rel =” noopener noreferrer noreferrer noreferrer“群集。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您的应用程序部署在Kubernetes中时，K6运算符使在同一环境中部署和管理K6测试变得容易。 It works by using a &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/docs/concepts/extend-kubernetes/api-extension/custom-resources/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Custom Resource Definition (CRD)&lt;/a&gt; to describe a test run, then bootstrapping the necessary pods to execute it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; K6操作员定义了两个主要CRD：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;code&gt; testrun &lt;/code&gt;：声明&lt;a href =“/docs/k6/k6/最新设置/设置/设置distributed-k6/usage/recuting-k6-scripts-with-testrun-crd/？pg = pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-tod = body-tex = body-tex = body-tex = body-test of k6 test &lt;/a&gt; in kubernetesses in kubernetes。截至目前，&lt;code&gt; testrun &lt;/code&gt; crd（在下图中描绘）是使用kubernetes群集运行带有OSS工具的分布式K6测试的最简单方法。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1280x1098/6e7e8ccada/testrun-crd-diagram.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1280x1098/6e7e8ccada/testrun-crd-diagram.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A diagram depicting the workflow of a TestRun CRD, showing a Kubernetes cluster with k6 Operator, an initializer pod, starter pod, runner pods, and private service使用HTTP和日志连接。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1280x1098/6e7e8ccada/testrun-crd-diagram.jpg”&#xA;alt =“描绘TestRun CRD工作流程的图表，显示了带有K6运算符的Kubernetes群集，初始化器POD，入门POD，Runner Pod和http and Log Connections的私人服务。”/&gt;。”/&gt;。&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;code&gt; privateloadzone &lt;/code&gt;：寄存器href =“/products/cloud/k6/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud k6 &lt;/a&gt;  - 由K6 OSS供电的完全管理的性能测试平台 - 可以在Kubernetes群集内进行测试。这使您可以使用简单的&lt;code&gt; k6云运行&lt;/code&gt;命令进行测试，而不是手动创建&lt;code&gt; testrun &lt;/code&gt; kubernetes资源。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1473x822/cd70329f20/private-load-load-load-zones-grafana-cloud-k6.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1473x8222/cd70329f20/private-load-load-load-load-zones-grafana-cloud-k6.png” alt =“ alt =” Alt =“ grafana cloud kn Cloud knd dashboard kl k6 dashboard web web with web webs complate web web tergrapt and fids and fidf，lc，lc，lc，cl grbragn f. lc，cl glbr，cl grbra分数。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1473x8222/cd70329f20/private-load-load-load-zones-grafana-cloud-k6.png”&#xA;Alt =“ Grafana Cloud K6仪表板显示Web性能指标：LCP，FID，CLS，FCP，INP，INP，TTFB，带有图形和分数。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;总的来说，K6运营商的最大优势是它&lt;a href =“/docs/k6/k6/最终设置/设置/设置 -  distributed-k6/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;简化了跨多个机器的运行分布式K6测试&lt;/a&gt;跨多个机器。这些测试保持完全同步，以确保大规模准确和可靠的结果。它还简化了专用网络中应用程序的测试，而不会破坏安全性或隐私政策。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，如上所述，K6操作员&lt;a href =“/doc/k6/k6/最新/设置/设置/设置 -  distributed-k6/usage/k6-operator to-gck6/？pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt&#39;&gt;与grafana cloud k6 &lt;/a&gt;相结合href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/k6/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud K6的功能集&lt;/a&gt;。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ k6-operator-a-a-community-driven-proJECT“&gt; K6运营商的演变：社区驱动的项目&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; kubernetes运营商是一项相对较新的技术，没有关于如何实施的正式准则。可以肯定地说，我们一直在与不断扩大的用户社区一起提高对他们的了解。多年来，越来越多的人使用K6运营商，并提供了反馈，因此越来越清楚的是缺少或可以改进的。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;开发K6操作员的过程中有几个重大变化。最大的障碍之一是在2023年，我们内部称为“势力史诗”。预计Kubernetes操作员将是势力，但是K6操作员与之互动的API不是。完整的修复程序，以&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/releases/tag/tag/v0.0.9” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; v0.0.9 &lt;/a&gt;在社区撰稿人的帮助下，&lt;/&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other major changes were for usability improvements, with support for modern installation methods: a simple &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/k6/latest/set-up/set-up-distributed-k6/install-k6-operator/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt/#deploy-with-bundle&#34;&gt;bundle file&lt;/a&gt;, including one CLI command, for quick prototyping or complex setups, along with a &lt;a href =“/docs/k6/最新/设置/设置/设置 -  distributed-k6/install-k6-operator/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt/＃deploy-with-helm”&gt; helm图表&lt;/a&gt;用于管理Kubernets应用程序。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; OSS社区在K6操作员的发展中发挥了关键作用。在撰写本文时，K6操作员代码库有63个外部贡献者，其中328个合并的PR中有99个来自这些社区成员。他们扩大了CRD的新功能，固定的错误，抛光了头盔图表，并经常实现他们要求的功能 - 从&lt;a a href =“ https：//github.com/grafana/k6-operator/k6-operator/pullator/pull/pull/184” target =“ _ black” href =“ https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/issues/168” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;增强的亲和力规则&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;特别感谢&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/knechtionscoding” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; hans knecht &lt;/a&gt;，他在2021年对K6运营商的接地构建了2021年的接地，并具有初始的ISTIO支持和CI Pipeelines和CI Pipeelines和CI Pipelines and Ci/knm ub。 target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; rogerio kino &lt;/a&gt;，他从外部贡献者中撰写了最大的PR，并以HELM图表的初始实现。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当然，其他无数其他人在此过程中塑造了K6操作员，因此我们对所有贡献的人表示衷心的感谢。 💛💙&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ Whats-new-with-with-k6-operator-10”&gt; K6运算符1.0的新功能？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; K6操作员的准备1.0带有一些破裂的更改，但它们都在运算符的先前版本中发布。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; 1.0版本本身包含错误修复程序，并且其他改进，例如掌舵图表的新配置以及在&lt;code&gt; privateloadzone &lt;/code&gt;测试中传递组织特定指标聚合变量的能力。但是，主要更改是我们致力于改善版本控制，发布时间表和维护更新。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“常规维护更新”&gt;常规维护更新&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; K6运算符不取决于最新版本的Kubernetes运行。这是因为我们使用运营商的目标是简化您的K6测试旅程，而不是迫使您进入Kubernetes更新。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，我们认识到Kubernetes生态系统正在不断发展，因此将进行定期维护更新，以确保K6运营商包括最近的错误修复程序和Kubernetes社区的重大改进。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果Kubernetes发布了一项新功能，可以在K6操作员设置中重复使用有意义，则在维护更新或用户功能请求时将考虑它。要了解有关我们维护方法的更多信息，请查看&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/blob/main/main/docs/maintance.mdance.md” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ rel =” noopener noreferrer noreferrer“ nooreferrer”&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“支持 - 语义上的反复”&gt;对语义版本的支持&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; k6运算符现在遵循&lt;a href =“ https://semver.org/#semantic-versioning-200” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;语义版本2.0 2.0 &lt;/a&gt;。总体而言，这意味着我们如何处理K6运营商的未来开发方面具有更大的稳定性。此外，语义版本现在将通过增加相应版本传达发行版的影响。让我们简要总结这对K6操作员的含义，特别是。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主要版本的增加可能会在以下情况下发生：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;现有CRD类型的版本升级。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;无论其版本如何&#xA;&lt;li&gt;应用程序功能的重大变化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;由内部Grafana实验室确定的其他重大变化。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;新功能或改进将随着次要版本的增加而发布。如果正在进行重大破坏变化的准备工作，则先前的次要版本之一将包含先前的折旧警告。错误修复将以补丁版本发布。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;应该注意的是，破裂的变化可能不同，“破坏变化”的含义可能取决于一个人的定义。特别是在K6运算符项目中，有几种类型的API。当破裂变化很小时，我们保留发布具有破坏性更改的次要版本的权利，并且仅限于具有&lt;code&gt; v1alpha1 &lt;/code&gt;版本的CRD类型。但是，任何重大的打破变化都将保留主要发布版本。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关我们的版本管理和稳定性保证方法的更多信息，请访问&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/blob/main/docs/releses.md“ target =” _ blank“ rel =” noopener noreferrer&#39;&gt; this doc &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“ a more-rore-prefials-Release-schedule”&gt;更可预测的发布时间表&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;过去，K6操作员的发布通常是由合并到主分支的工作量驱动的。如果合并数量不足，则没有释放。现在，我们承诺制定更可预测的时间表，每8周发布一个新的次要版本。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;相反，我们不保证每个次要版本都包含新功能：它可能与简单的维护更新一样小，但它将按计划作为次要版本发布。新功能的规律性取决于我们用户的请求和内部优先级，并且可行。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;补丁发布，尤其是在错误的情况下，可以更频繁地发布。如果有关键的错误，我们将尽快发布补丁。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;主要版本目前没有定期时间表。一旦有关于下一个主要版本的计划，我们将与社区分享。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使我们发展了发布过程，我们仍然致力于通过问题，PRS和发行说明进行直接通信。在添加新功能之前，我们仍然会密切注意并仔细评估每个用例，尤其是在破坏CRD的变化的情况下。  我们将继续通过GitHub宣布任何折旧或重大更改 - 不用担心，发行说明仍然会被手写并包含表情符号！&lt;/p&gt;！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ NextSteps”&gt;下一步&lt;/H2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们已经发布了a &lt;a href =“/docs/k6/最新/设置/设置/设置 -  distibuted-k6/upgrade-k6-operator/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;指南&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;如何更新K6运算符（我们的用户长期以来的K6操作员）。您还可以参考&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/grafana/k6-operator/ReleAses/tag/v1.0.0” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，再次感谢我们所有社区成员多年来帮助塑造K6运营商的。我们很高兴与您分享这个里程碑，并期待我们的持续合作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;快乐测试！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to connect ServiceNow to Grafana Cloud IRM incidents】如何将ServiceNow连接到Grafana Cloud IRM事件</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/15/how-to-connect-servicenow-to-grafana-cloud-irm-incidents/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Companies rely on a variety of services to streamline their workflows, which often requires data synchronization or information sharing across platforms. But are your tools flexible enough to connect with external systems?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ServiceNow is widely recognized for its robust and complex workflow support for enterprises. However, it may not always offer the most intuitive or user-friendly experience when handling incidents. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;ve updated &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/irm/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud IRM&lt;/a&gt; to give you one place to manage your incidents and ensure your ServiceNow instance stays up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We recently released a new way to set up webhooks based on IRM incident events so that you can now template URLs, headers, and data, as well as chain different events by combining data from previous responses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With that in mind, and to show an example of how this works, let&amp;rsquo;s implement a bidirectional status sync between IRM incidents and ServiceNow incidents.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/621x129/3212d47aab/advanced-webhook-servicenow.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/621x129/3212d47aab/advanced-webhook-servicenow.png&#34;alt=&#34;Dark interface showing &amp;#39;Advanced webhook for incidents&amp;#39; with a description about customizable settings and template options.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/621x129/3212d47aab/advanced-webhook-servicenow.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Dark interface showing &amp;#39;Advanced webhook for incidents&amp;#39; with a description about customizable settings and template options.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;webhooks-for-incidents&#34;&gt;Webhooks for incidents&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IRM outgoing webhooks now support incident events, providing a unified experience for automating alert group and incident workflows. You can trigger requests based on key incident lifecycle events, such as when an incident is declared, updated, or resolved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What does advanced mean in this context? With this updated feature you can:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Customize webhook requests with support for any HTTP method&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use templated URLs, headers, and request bodies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dynamically reference incident data and prior webhook responses&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;View webhook execution details directly from the incident or alert group timeline&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manage incident-related webhook configurations using Terraform&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;from-irm-to-servicenow&#34;&gt;From IRM to ServiceNow&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a first step, let&amp;rsquo;s make sure there is a &lt;code&gt;grafana-irm&lt;/code&gt; user configured in ServiceNow, as &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/configure/integrations/integration-reference/oncall/servicenow/#before-you-begin&#34;&gt;described&lt;/a&gt; in our documentation for the IRM ServiceNow integration for alert groups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To create a ServiceNow incident when an IRM incident is declared, and to set it to closed when incident is resolved, we are going to define a couple of IRM incident webhooks:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident declared&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name:&lt;/strong&gt; Incident declared&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger type:&lt;/strong&gt; Incident Declared&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HTTP method:&lt;/strong&gt; POST&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webhook URL:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://devxxxxxx.service-now.com/api/now/table/incident&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;https://devXXXXXX.service-now.com/api/now/table/incident&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Username:&lt;/strong&gt; grafana-irm&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Password:&lt;/strong&gt; [grafana-irm-snow-password]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger template:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;{{ incident.createdByUser.name.lower() != &amp;#34;service account: snow&amp;#34; }}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[x]&lt;/strong&gt; Customize forwarded data&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;{&#xA;&amp;#34;short_description&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;{{ incident.title }}&amp;#34;,&#xA;&amp;#34;description&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;This incident is created automatically by Grafana IRM:\n{{ incident.overviewURL }}&amp;#34;,&#xA;&amp;#34;state&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;1&amp;#34;,&#xA;&amp;#34;u_irm_incident_id&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;{{ incident_id }}&amp;#34;,&#xA;&amp;#34;caller_id&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;grafana-irm&amp;#34;&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note the trigger template above. It&amp;rsquo;s there to avoid triggering the webhook when the incident being declared was created by the &lt;code&gt;snow&lt;/code&gt; Service account, which we will set up in the next section. This is important because otherwise an incident created in ServiceNow would also trigger the webhook, and we don&amp;rsquo;t want to create a new incident there in that case.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We also set a special field—&lt;code&gt;u_irm_incident_id&lt;/code&gt; (with the &lt;code&gt;incident_id&lt;/code&gt; value)—in the data payload, so we keep a connection between the IRM incident and the ServiceNow incident (this will also be important in the next section).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident resolved&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name:&lt;/strong&gt; Incident resolved&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger type:&lt;/strong&gt; Incident Resolved&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HTTP method:&lt;/strong&gt; PUT&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Webhook URL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;{%- for label in incident.labels -%}&#xA;{%- if label.key == &amp;#34;ServiceNow&amp;#34; -%}&#xA;https://devXXXXXX.service-now.com/api/now/table/incident/{{ label.label }}&#xA;{%- endif -%}&#xA;{%- endfor -%}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Username:&lt;/strong&gt; grafana-irm&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Password:&lt;/strong&gt; [grafana-irm-snow-password]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;[x]&lt;/strong&gt; Customize forwarded data&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__mini&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;lang-toolbar__mini&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class=&#34;code-clipboard&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data=&#34;app_code_snippet()&#34; x-init=&#34;init()&#34; @click=&#34;copy()&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class=&#34;code-clipboard__icon&#34; src=&#34;/media/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg&#34; alt=&#34;Copy code to clipboard&#34; width=&#34;14&#34; height=&#34;13&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;Copy&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;code-snippet code-snippet__border&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded=&#34;false&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-none&#34;&gt;{&#xA;&amp;#34;close_code&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Resolved by caller&amp;#34;,&#xA;&amp;#34;close_notes&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;{{ incident.summary }}&amp;#34;,&#xA;&amp;#34;state&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;6&amp;#34;&#xA;}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;An important bit here is the URL template. It gets its value from an incident label that will contain the ServiceNow incident ID, which will be set by the ServiceNow business rule defined below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;from-servicenow-to-irm&#34;&gt;From ServiceNow to IRM&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before defining a ServiceNow business rule to push updates to IRM, we will need a few things set up:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In Grafana Cloud:&lt;/strong&gt; Create a service account with the Admin role (name: &lt;code&gt;snow&lt;/code&gt;; it should match the name in the trigger template filter in the previous section), and a corresponding service account token.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In IRM:&lt;/strong&gt; Confirm the &lt;code&gt;ServiceNow&lt;/code&gt; label is available in &lt;strong&gt;IRM settings&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;gt; &lt;strong&gt;Incident&lt;/strong&gt; (the label key should match the label referenced in the URL template in the previous section; you can add the label with any random value here).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In ServiceNow:&lt;/strong&gt; Create a custom field in the incident table with the name &lt;code&gt;u_irm_incident_id&lt;/code&gt; to store the IRM incident ID sent by the IRM webhook.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then, we can create the ServiceNow business rule. For that, you can follow the instructions defined in the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/configure/integrations/integration-reference/oncall/servicenow/#generate-business-rule-script&#34;&gt;docs&lt;/a&gt; for the IRM-ServiceNow integration, but using the &lt;a href=&#34;https://gist.github.com/matiasb/d3b2ebe39a0fdb3ec5354bda222d649d&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;script found here&lt;/a&gt; instead (where you should replace &lt;code&gt;AUTH_TOKEN&lt;/code&gt; value with your service account token and &lt;code&gt;API_BASE_URL&lt;/code&gt; with your Grafana stack URL).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The script will send updates to the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/reference/incident-api/reference/&#34;&gt;IRM Incident API&lt;/a&gt; to create, label, and update IRM incidents every time a ServiceNow incident changes, handling status updates and linking both incidents between them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can see the final outcome in the demo below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x494/4f5a0cbad2/servicenow-setup-irm.gif&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x494/4f5a0cbad2/servicenow-setup-irm.gif&#34;alt=&#34;GIF showing the steps outlined above&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x494/4f5a0cbad2/servicenow-setup-irm.gif&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;GIF showing the steps outlined above&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;going-further&#34;&gt;Going further&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Flexible webhook setup for incident-related events opens a wide set of options for integrations, allowing you to do things like announcing incidents in a different &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/05/20/grafana-oncall-connect-to-discord-mattermost-and-more-with-webhooks/&#34;&gt;ChatOps service&lt;/a&gt; (e.g., Mattermost, Discord, etc), triggering an external workflow when a specific label is applied, or keeping a third-party service in sync on incident status changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more, check out the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/alerting-and-irm/irm/configure/integrations/webhooks/outgoing-webhooks/&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud IRM docs&lt;/a&gt; and start finding all the ways you can extend your incident response workflows by integrating IRM with your own services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;公司依靠各种服务来简化其工作流，这通常需要数据同步或跨平台的信息共享。但是您的工具是否足够灵活以与外部系统连接？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; ServiceNow因其对企业的强大而复杂的工作流支持而被广泛认可。但是，在处理事件时，它可能并不总是提供最直观或用户友好的体验。这就是为什么我们更新&lt;a href =“/products/products/cloud/irm/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud irm &lt;/a&gt;为您提供一个管理事件的地方，并确保您的ServiceNow实例保持最新状态。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们最近发布了一种基于IRM事件事件的Webhooks设置的新方法，以便您现在可以通过组合以前的响应中的数据来模板，标题和数据以及链条不同的事件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;考虑到这一点，并展示了它的工作原理，让我们实现IRM事件和ServiceNow事件之间的双向状态同步。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/621x129/3212d47aab/advanced-webhook-servicenow.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/621x129/32129/3212d47aab/advanced-webhook-servicenow.png” alt =“ Alt =” Dark界面显示&#39;高级Webhook for Issents for Issents for Isspects for Isspect for Idcestents&#39;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/621x129/3212d47aab/advanced-webhook-servicenow.png”&#xA;alt =“黑暗接口显示&#39;高级Webhook for Divestents&#39;，其中包含有关可自定义设置和模板选项的描述。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ webhooks for-incentents”&gt;事件的webhooks &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; IRM即将发出的Webhooks现在支持事件事件，为自动化警报组和事件工作流提供了统一的体验。您可以根据关键事件生命周期事件触发请求，例如声明，更新或解决事件时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这种情况下，高级意味着什么？使用此更新的功能，您可以：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自定义Webhook请求，并支持任何HTTP方法&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用模板的URL，标题和请求尸体&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;动态参考事件数据和先前的Webhook响应&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;查看Webhook执行直接从事件或警报组时间表中&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使用Terraform管理与事件相关的Webhook配置&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“从IRM到ServiceNow &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为第一步，让我们确保在ServiceNow中配置的用户&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/artering and-irm/irm/integure/intementions/intementation/intempration/intempration/intermation-referenation-ectiCeNow/ oncall/onciceNow/＃在您的irm ServiceNow集成的文档中描述之前，请先描述&lt;/a&gt;警报组。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在宣布IRM事件时创建ServiceNow事件，并在解决事件时将其设置为关闭，我们将定义几个IRM事件webhooks：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;事件声明为&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;名称：&lt;/strong&gt;声明为&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;触发类型：&lt;/strong&gt;事件声明为&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; http方法：&lt;/strong&gt; post &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; webhook url：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://devxxxxxx.service-now.com/api/now/table/table/incident/incident” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; https://devxxxxxxxxxxxxxx.service-now.com/api/now/table/incident/incident &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;用户名：&lt;/strong&gt; grafana-imm &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;密码：&lt;/strong&gt; [grafana-snow-password] &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;触发模板：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class =“ code-snippet code-snippet__mini”&gt; &lt;div class =“ lang-toolbar__mini”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class =“ code-clipboard”&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data =“ app_code_snippet（）” x-init =“ init（）” @click =“ copy（）”&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class =“ code-clipboard__icon” src =“/媒体/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg” alt =“复制代码到剪贴板” width =“ 14”高度=“ 13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class =“代码 - 尼珀代码snippet__border”&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded =“ false”&gt; &lt;code class =“ language-none”&gt; {{indist.creatededbyuser.name.lower（）！=“服务帐户：snow”}}}} &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; [x] &lt;/strong&gt;自定义转发数据&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;数据：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class =“ code-snippet code-snippet__mini”&gt; &lt;div class =“ lang-toolbar__mini”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class =“ code-clipboard”&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data =“ app_code_snippet（）” x-init =“ init（）” @click =“ copy（）”&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class =“ code-clipboard__icon” src =“/媒体/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg” alt =“复制代码到剪贴板” width =“ 14”高度=“ 13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class =“代码 - 尼珀代码snippet__border”&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded =“ false”&gt; &lt;code class =“ language-none”&gt; {&#xA;“ short_description”：“ {{indist.title}}”，&#xA;“描述”：“此事件是由Grafana IRM自动创建的&#xA;“状态”：“ 1”，&#xA;“ u_irm_incident_id”：“ {{incount_id}}”，&#xA;“ caller_id”：“ grafana-imm”&#xA;} &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;注意上面的触发模板。在那里避免触发Webhook时，当被声明的事件声明是由&lt;code&gt; snow &lt;/code&gt;服务帐户创建的，我们将在下一节中设置。这很重要，因为否则在ServiceNow中创建的事件也会触发Webhook，我们不想在这种情况下创建一个新事件。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还设置了一个特殊字段 -  &lt;code&gt; u_irm_incident_id &lt;/code&gt;（使用&lt;code&gt; Invest_id &lt;/code&gt;值） - 在数据有效载荷中，因此我们在IRM事件和ServiceNow事件之间保持连接（这在下一节中也很重要）。&lt;/p&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;）。&lt;/p&gt;）。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;事件已解决&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;名称：&lt;/strong&gt; incident解决&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;触发类型：&lt;/strong&gt;事件已解决&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; http方法：&lt;/strong&gt; put &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; webhook url：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class =“ code-snippet code-snippet__mini”&gt; &lt;div class =“ lang-toolbar__mini”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class =“ code-clipboard”&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data =“ app_code_snippet（）” x-init =“ init（）” @click =“ copy（）”&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class =“ code-clipboard__icon” src =“/媒体/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg” alt =“复制代码到剪贴板” width =“ 14”高度=“ 13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class =“代码 - 尼珀代码snippet__border”&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded =“ false”&gt; &lt;code class =“ language-none”&gt; {％ -  in Idcent.labels-％}中的标签&#xA;{％ - 如果label.key ==“ serviceNow”  - ％}&#xA;https://devxxxxx.service-now.com/api/now/table/incident/ {{label.label}}}&#xA;{％ -  endif-％}&#xA;{％ -  endfor-％} &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;用户名：&lt;/strong&gt; grafana-irm &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;密码：&lt;/strong&gt; [grafana-snow-password] &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; [x] &lt;/strong&gt;自定义转发数据&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;数据：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class =“ code-snippet code-snippet__mini”&gt; &lt;div class =“ lang-toolbar__mini”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span class =“ code-clipboard”&gt;&#xA;&lt;button x-data =“ app_code_snippet（）” x-init =“ init（）” @click =“ copy（）”&gt;&#xA;&lt;img class =“ code-clipboard__icon” src =“/媒体/images/icons/icon-copy-small-2.svg” alt =“复制代码到剪贴板” width =“ 14”高度=“ 13”&gt;&#xA;&lt;span&gt;复制&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/button&gt;&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class =“代码 - 尼珀代码snippet__border”&gt;&#xA;&lt;pre data-expanded =“ false”&gt; &lt;code class =“ language-none”&gt; {&#xA;“ close_code”：“由呼叫者解决”，&#xA;“ close_notes”：“ {{incount.summary}}”，&#xA;“状态”：“ 6”&#xA;} &lt;/code&gt; &lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;这里重要的是URL模板。它从包含ServiceNow事件ID的事件标签中获取其价值，该标签将由下面定义的ServiceNow业务规则设置。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“从serviceNow到irm &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在定义ServiceNow业务规则以将更新推向IRM之前，我们将需要一些设置：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在Grafana Cloud中：&lt;/strong&gt;创建一个带有管理员角色的服务帐户（名称：&lt;code&gt; snow &lt;/code&gt;;它应该匹配上一节中的触发模板过滤器中的名称），以及一个相应的服务帐户令牌。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在IRM中：&lt;/strong&gt;确认&lt;code&gt; serviceNow &lt;/code&gt;标签可在&lt;strong&gt; irm设置中可用&lt;/strong&gt;&gt;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;事件&lt;/strong&gt;（标签键应匹配上一节中URL模板中的标签；您可以在此处添加任何随机值；&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在serviceNow中：&lt;/strong&gt;在事件表中创建一个自定义字段，名称&lt;code&gt; u_irm_incident_id &lt;/code&gt;存储IRM Webhook发送的IRM事件ID。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;然后，我们可以创建ServiceNow业务规则。为此，您可以按照&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/artering-and-imm/irm/configure/intementions/intement-referenation-reference-reference/oncall/serviceNow/＃generate-business-rule-scripts”中定义的说明&#39;&gt; docs &lt;/a&gt;对于IRM-ServiceNow集成，但使用&lt;a href =“ https://gist.github.com/matiasb/d3b2ebe39a0fb354bda22222222649d &lt;code&gt; auth_token &lt;/code&gt;使用您的服务帐户令牌和&lt;code&gt; api_base_url &lt;/code&gt;带有grafana stack url）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;该脚本将向&lt;a href =“/doc/docs/grafana-cloud/nervering-and-mirm/irm/coruest/coruest/adverion-api/refersion/”&gt; irm事件api &lt;/a&gt;创建，标签和更新IRM事件，每次使用ServiceNow事件更改，处理和链接到两个Incistentes之间，并更新IRM事件。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在下面的演示中看到最终结果：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x494/4f5a0cbad2/servicenow-setup-irm.gif”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x494/4f5a0cbad2/servicenow-setup-irm.gif”&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/800x494/4f5a0cbad2/servicenow-setup-irm.gif”&#xA;alt =“ gif显示上面概述的步骤”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ got-further”&gt;进一步&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;针对事件相关事件的灵活的Webhook设置为集成打开了广泛的选项，使您可以执行诸如在不同的&lt;a href =“/blog/2024/2024/05/20/grafana-oncall-colnect-connect-connect-connect-matter-matter-matter-matter-matter-matter-matter-maters-matter-mater-master-mose-more-withith-webhooks/webhooks/weebhooks/caterport &lt;chatops etcord efcord efcrord &lt;/a）中，&lt;/a）当应用特定标签时，外部工作流程或将第三方服务保持在事件状态更改时。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解更多信息，请查看&lt;a href =“/doc/docs/grafana-cloud/nervering-and-inm/irm/irm/configure/intermations/webhooks/tust-toutwewebhooks/“&gt; grafana cloud irm docs &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，并开始找到所有可以通过与您自己的服务集成IRM的方式来扩展IRM的方式。&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data storytelling at HackUPC 2025: Celebrating 3 student hackathon projects powered by Grafana】Hackupc 2025的数据讲故事：庆祝3个学生Hackathon项目由Grafana提供支持</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/12/data-storytelling-at-hackupc-2025-celebrating-3-student-hackathon-projects-powered-by-grafana/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Grafana Labs was a proud sponsor of &lt;a href=&#34;https://hackupc.com/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;HackUPC&lt;/a&gt; — one of the biggest student hackathons in Europe — at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.upc.edu/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;BarcelonaTech&lt;/a&gt;. The event drew more than 700 passionate tech students from around the globe, all racing the clock in a 36-hour burst of creativity to build web, mobile, and hardware projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a developer advocate here at Grafana Labs — where we are &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/03/01/grafana-labs-hackathon-projects-where-are-they-now/&#34;&gt;big believers in hackathons&lt;/a&gt; — it was a privilege to participate as mentor and judge in the HackUPC 2025 event. For our challenge, we focused primarily on the theme of sustainability, and asked a set of students to leverage Grafana to raise awareness of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://sdgs.un.org/goals&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;UN Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs).&lt;/a&gt; Shout out to Niki Manoledaki, senior software engineer at Grafana Labs and a contributor to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://tag-env-sustainability.cncf.io/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;CNCF Environmental Sustainability Technical Advisory Group (TAG ENV)&lt;/a&gt;, for inspiring this sustainability-related challenge! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The students in our group could approach the challenge in two ways: create compelling &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/panels-visualizations/visualizations/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;data visualizations&lt;/a&gt; using open data to reveal meaningful trends or develop an innovative &lt;a href=&#34;/developers/plugin-tools/key-concepts/plugin-types-usage/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt/#app-plugins&#34;&gt;Grafana app plugin&lt;/a&gt; to provide unique insights or functionalities related to their chosen SDG(s). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1120/37ac405eca/green-grafana-slide.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1120/37ac405eca/green-grafana-slide.png&#34;alt=&#34;A slide from Grafana Labs&amp;#39; slide deck for HackUPC with the text: &amp;#39;Green Grafana Essentials: Data, Visualizations, and Plugins&amp;#39; on a dark grid background.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1120/37ac405eca/green-grafana-slide.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A slide from Grafana Labs&amp;#39; slide deck for HackUPC with the text: &amp;#39;Green Grafana Essentials: Data, Visualizations, and Plugins&amp;#39; on a dark grid background.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It was so inspiring to see how the hackers used their creativity to tackle global issues and showcase the power of data. In this post, we recap and celebrate some of the Grafana hackathon projects that came out of the event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-graf-anna-tracking-global-climate-and-health-trends&#34;&gt;Project Graf-Anna: tracking global climate and health trends &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team behind &lt;a href=&#34;https://devpost.com/software/graf-anna&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Graf-Anna&lt;/a&gt; wanted to tell a data-driven story to illustrate the urgency of climate change, as outlined by the SDGs, and recognized Grafana as a powerful tool to help achieve this goal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In particular, this team of hackers wanted to explore the connections between industrial development (&lt;a href=&#34;https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goal9&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SDG 9&lt;/a&gt;), responsible consumption (&lt;a href=&#34;https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goal12&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SDG 12&lt;/a&gt;), climate change action (&lt;a href=&#34;https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goal13&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SDG 13&lt;/a&gt;), and their effects on the planet and human health. The result was a comprehensive Grafana dashboard that visualizes the historical impact of the Industrial Revolution and human activity on CO2 emissions, climate trends, and health. It’s an excellent educational tool that uses both historical and live data to create a compelling narrative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the Grafana dashboard below, the team tracked trends in global emissions, temperature variation, natural disasters, CO2 per capita, and life expectancy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x814/e79bcbd1c4/graf-anna-health-and-global-trends-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x814/e79bcbd1c4/graf-anna-health-and-global-trends-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for project Graf-Anna, showing industrial impact on CO2, health, global trends, and sustainable goals with graphs on CO2 levels, disasters, and life expectancy.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x814/e79bcbd1c4/graf-anna-health-and-global-trends-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for project Graf-Anna, showing industrial impact on CO2, health, global trends, and sustainable goals with graphs on CO2 levels, disasters, and life expectancy.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They also tracked land usage, current world emissions per country, and CO2 emissions from deforestation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x550/8ebfed3285/land-use-and-emissions-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x550/8ebfed3285/land-use-and-emissions-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for project Graf-Anne showing a world map with green markers for emissions. Bar charts display CO2 emissions from deforestation for Spain, U.S., Canada, and China.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x550/8ebfed3285/land-use-and-emissions-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for project Graf-Anne showing a world map with green markers for emissions. Bar charts display CO2 emissions from deforestation for Spain, U.S., Canada, and China.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, they built a conclusion panel to breakdown key takeaways from the data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1447x555/0785ce0d8c/graf-anna-conclusion-panel.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1447x555/0785ce0d8c/graf-anna-conclusion-panel.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana panel detailing climate change impacts: emissions, global emissions trajectory, life expectancy, deforestation, and sustainability actions.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1447x555/0785ce0d8c/graf-anna-conclusion-panel.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana panel detailing climate change impacts: emissions, global emissions trajectory, life expectancy, deforestation, and sustainability actions.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team behind Graf-Anna had some pretty ambitious goals from the start. They initially wanted to build a custom Grafana app plugin with advanced features, including the integration of LLMs for insights. However, they hit some technical difficulties and ran into time constraints, which forced them to pivot their strategy. They decided to source, integrate, and visualize existing data to tell a clear story — which was still a big accomplishment on its own. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Their project reinforced the power of Grafana data visualization as a storytelling tool, even without custom code. It&amp;rsquo;s a great example of learning and adapting on the fly, which hackathons are all about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;peaceful-protest-tracker-insights-for-sustainable-development&#34;&gt;Peaceful Protest Tracker: insights for sustainable development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While Graf-Anna focused on global climate trends, another team used data to tackle a different real-world issue. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://devpost.com/software/peaceful-protest-tracker-headlines-vs-reality&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Peaceful Protest Tracker: Headlines vs. Reality&lt;/a&gt; project promoted peaceful and inclusive societies for sustainable development with accountable institutions, in line with &lt;a href=&#34;https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goal16&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;SDG 16&lt;/a&gt;. The team wanted to apply their skills in web development, AI, and data visualization to a compelling and personal topic, inspired by the confusing and often contradictory news coverage following a tragic railway collapse in Serbia. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Their solution was a dynamic Grafana dashboard that visualizes how protests unfolded in near-real-time, pulling data from various media outlets. The dashboard used a semi-live map to pinpoint protest locations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x886/c9b1af44f7/location-of-protests-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x886/c9b1af44f7/location-of-protests-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard showing protest data in Serbia with a map, protest details, and a line graph comparing government and independent media coverage.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x886/c9b1af44f7/location-of-protests-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard showing protest data in Serbia with a map, protest details, and a line graph comparing government and independent media coverage.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It also included features like sentiment analysis and keyword usage comparisons to create a powerful example of storytelling with data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x806/0c300e0e76/sentiment-analysis-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x806/0c300e0e76/sentiment-analysis-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard displaying pie charts, line graphs, and statistics on student metrics, state mentions, and attendance estimations in media.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x806/0c300e0e76/sentiment-analysis-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard displaying pie charts, line graphs, and statistics on student metrics, state mentions, and attendance estimations in media.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This was a seriously ambitious project, and the team faced the major challenge of designing a complex system architecture connecting various technologies. They used Python for web scraping, the Gemini 2.5 Flash API for sentiment analysis, a Spring Boot backend, and MongoDB Atlas to store the data before visualizing it all in Grafana. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team learned how to work with Grafana from scratch, and should be incredibly proud of their persistence in bringing such a complex idea to life in 36 hours. It’s a fantastic example of using technology to address a critical real-world issue and what can be accomplished with a lot of determination (and probably a few too many potato chips!).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-musigrafs-visualizing-global-music-trends&#34;&gt;Project Musigrafs: visualizing global music trends  &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We wrap our hackathon highlights with a project that was unrelated to the sustainability theme, but still showed a lot of creativity and told a powerful story through data. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://devpost.com/software/musigrafs&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Musigrafs&lt;/a&gt; project was inspired by the fast-paced nature of the music world and the difficulty of tracking emerging trends using existing apps like Spotify or YouTube Music. The team set out to build a data-driven web app that captures the &amp;ldquo;pulse of global music trends — live.&amp;rdquo; The result was a Grafana dashboard that visualizes top genres by country, common musical keys, and real-time audio features like energy and tempo for top hits. It&amp;rsquo;s an excellent tool for aspiring musicians to understand the market and kickstart their careers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x933/0647d5d26a/musigraf-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x933/0647d5d26a/musigraf-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard showing a world map with music genre data, bar charts of key usage, and a list of most listened-to songs and genres.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x933/0647d5d26a/musigraf-dashboard.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard showing a world map with music genre data, bar charts of key usage, and a list of most listened-to songs and genres.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The team initially struggled to display the map in their desired format and had to explore other repositories for inspiration. To get the global information just right, they used GeoJSON, which helped them represent the countries’ borders. Connecting their &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/AlexVal03/hackupc2025/blob/main/data/genres.geojson&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;GitHub custom GeoJSON&lt;/a&gt; to Grafana presented a hurdle, but the team managed to get the raw GeoJSON file contents with help from mentors and &lt;a href=&#34;/grot/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grot AI&lt;/a&gt;. Ultimately, they were proud of the visual quality and clarity of their plots and successfully integrated real-time data, which was a core goal of their project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;closing-thoughts&#34;&gt;Closing thoughts &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Grafana support and judging team at HackUPC was so impressed by how quickly hackers grasped complex concepts, and we learned so much from their approaches and challenges. What made their projects successful was their fantastic storytelling and best practices in creating beautiful and impactful visualizations. And their great time management skills under pressure! We felt privileged to be there and connect with the next generation of tech talent and data storytellers. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We want to thank the HackUPC volunteer organization, all the participating students, and all the fellow judges. Without your efforts, this would not have been possible. We can’t wait for HackUPC next year! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, you can find us at &lt;a href=&#34;https://hacksheffield.uk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;HackSheffield10&lt;/a&gt; — another student hackathon event taking place at The University of Sheffield in November — where we&amp;rsquo;ll keep celebrating students&amp;rsquo; passions and the power of data to make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;今年早些时候，格拉法纳实验室是&lt;a href =“ https://hackupc.com/”的骄傲赞助商rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; barcelonatech &lt;/a&gt;。该活动吸引了来自全球的700多名热情的科技学生，所有这些都以36小时的创造力进行了时钟，以构建网络，移动和硬件项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a developer advocate here at Grafana Labs — where we are &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/03/01/grafana-labs-hackathon-projects-where-are-they-now/&#34;&gt;big believers in hackathons&lt;/a&gt; — it was a privilege to participate as mentor and judge in the HackUPC 2025 event.在我们的挑战中，我们主要关注可持续性的主题，并要求一组学生利用Grafana提高人们对&lt;a href =“ https：//sdgs.un.org/goals” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ rel =” noopener noreferrer“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; Un Costalable Development Asspome（noake of Engine of Engional of Engian of Shi agi ati agi agi agii niki&gt; n iki a niki，实验室和&lt;a a href =“ https://tag-env-sustainability.cncf.io/” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; CNCF环境可持续性技术咨询小组（TAG INV）&lt;/a&gt;，激发这一可持续性与可持续性的挑战！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们小组中的学生可以通过两种方式应对挑战：创建引人注目的&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana/最终/面板-Visualizations/sutuarizations/sutuarizations/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;数据可视化&lt;/a&gt;使用开放的数据来揭示有意义的趋势或开发有意义的趋势&lt;a href =“/developers/plugin-tools/键 - 概念/插件型 -  usage/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt/＃app-plugins”&gt; grafana应用程序插件&lt;/a&gt;提供与所选SDG（SDG）相关的独特见解或功能。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1120/37AC405ECA/GREEN-GREEN-GRAFANA-SLIDE.PNG”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1120/37ac405eca/green-grafana-slide.png&#34;alt=&#34;A slide from Grafana Labs&#39; slide deck for HackUPC with the text: &#39;Green Grafana Essentials: Data, Visualizations, and Plugins&#39; on a dark grid background.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1120/37AC405ECA/GREEN-GREEN-GRAFANA-SLIDE.PNG”&#xA;alt =“ grafana Labs的幻灯片幻灯片，用于hackupc，上面有文本：&#39;绿色grafana Essentials：数据，可视化和插件在深色网格背景上。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;看到黑客如何利用他们的创造力来解决全球问题并展示数据的力量真是令人鼓舞。在这篇文章中，我们回顾并庆祝活动中出来的一些Grafana Hackathon项目。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 iD =“ Project-Graf-Anna-tracking-Global-Climate-climate and-Health-trends”&gt;项目Graf-Anna：跟踪全球气候和健康趋势&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://devpost.com/software/graf-anna” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; graf-anna &lt;/a&gt;想讲述一个数据驱动的故事以说明气候变化的紧迫性，如Sugnly of Sught ofer the Sphile the Spect of the Spect of the Spect of the Spect of the suf the swana &lt;suf the swana &lt;aft aft of s the s.&#xA;&lt;p&gt;特别是，这支黑客团队想探索工业发展之间的联系（&lt;a href =“ https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goals/goals/goal9” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; sdg 9&gt; sdg 9 &lt;/a&gt;） href =“ https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goals/goal12” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; sdg 12 &lt;/a&gt;），气候变化行动（&lt;a href =“ https:/ https：//sdgs.un.org/goals/goals/goals/goals/goal/goal13” Noreferrer“&gt; SDG 13 &lt;/a&gt;）及其对地球和人类健康的影响。结果是一个全面的Grafana仪表板，它可视化工业革命和人类活动对CO2排放，气候趋势和健康的历史影响。这是一种出色的教育工具，同时使用历史数据和实时数据来创建引人入胜的叙事。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在下面的Grafana仪表板中，团队跟踪了全球排放，温度变化，自然灾害，人均二氧化碳和寿命的趋势。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x814/e79bcbd1c4/graf-anna-health-health-and-health-and-and-global-trends-dashboard.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x814/e79bcbd1c4/graf-anna-health-and-global-trends-dashboard.png&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana dashboard for project Graf-Anna, showing industrial impact on CO2, health, global trends, and sustainable goals with graphs on CO2 levels,灾难和预期寿命。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x814/e79bcbd1c4/graf-anna-health-health-health-and-and-global-trends-dashboard.png”&#xA;Alt =“用于Graf-Anna项目的Grafana仪表板，显示了二氧化碳，全球趋势和可持续目标的工业影响，并在二氧化碳水平，灾难和预期寿命上进行图表。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他们还追踪了土地使用情况，每个国家的当前世界排放以及森林砍伐的二氧化碳排放。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x550/8ebfed3285/land-use-use-and-ymissions-dashboard.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x550/8ebfed3285/land - 使用且发电机dashboard.png“ alt =”一个用于graf-anne项目的grafana仪表板，显示了带有绿色标记的世界地图。条形图显示西班牙，美国，加拿大和中国森林砍伐的二氧化碳排放。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1450x550/8ebfed3285/land-use-use-and-ymissions-dashboard.png”&#xA;alt =“用于Graf-Anne项目的Grafana仪表板，显示了带有绿色标记的世界地图。条形图显示了西班牙，美国，美国，加拿大和中国森林砍伐的二氧化碳排放。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最后，他们建立了一个结论面板，以从数据中分解密钥外卖。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1447x5555555555555CE0D8C/GRAF-NANGE-CONCLUSION-CONCLUSION-panel.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a/a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1447x555555555555555555CE0D8C/GRAF-ANHANN-CONCLUSION-PANEL.PNG” ALT =“ ALT =” GRAFANA面板详细的气候变化的影响：全球范围，全球的预期，生活预期，境外，&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1447x5555555555555CE0D8C/graf-anna-conclusion-panel.png”&#xA;alt =“详细详细介绍气候变化影响的Grafana面板：排放，全球排放轨迹，预期寿命，森林砍伐和可持续性行动。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Graf-Anna背后的团队从一开始就实现了一些雄心勃勃的目标。他们最初想构建具有高级功能的自定义Grafana应用程序插件，包括LLM的集成以供见解。但是，他们遇到了一些技术困难，并遇到了时间限制，这迫使他们旋转他们的策略。他们决定采购，集成和可视化现有数据以讲述一个清晰的故事 - 这本身仍然是一项巨大的成就。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;即使没有自定义代码，他们的项目也加强了Grafana数据可视化作为讲故事工具的力量。这是一个即时学习和适应的一个很好的例子，黑客马拉松全部。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“和平 - 预防轨道 - 直觉 - 可持续发展”&gt;和平抗议追踪器：可持续发展的见解&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Graf-Anna专注于全球气候趋势，但另一个团队使用数据来解决另一个现实世界中的问题。 The &lt;a href=&#34;https://devpost.com/software/peaceful-protest-tracker-headlines-vs-reality&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Peaceful Protest Tracker: Headlines vs. Reality&lt;/a&gt; project promoted peaceful and inclusive societies for sustainable development with accountable institutions, in line with &lt;a href =“ https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goal16” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; sdg 16 &lt;/a&gt;。该团队想在网络开发，AI和数据中运用他们的技能在塞尔维亚悲剧性的铁路崩溃之后，可视化成为一个引人入胜且个人的主题，受到令人困惑且经常矛盾的新闻报道的启发。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;他们的解决方案是一个充满活力的Grafana仪表板，可视化抗议活动如何在近实时展开，从各种媒体中提取数据。仪表板使用半寿命地图来查明抗议地点。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a/a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x886/c9b1af44444f7/location-uctoc-of-protests-dashboard.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a/a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x886/c9b1af4444f7/location-oct-protests-dashboard.png” Alt =“ Alt =” Alt =“ grafana dashboard，在塞尔维亚抗议数据中显示抗议数据，该数据与塞尔维亚的抗议数据，抗议，抗议案例，抗议详细信息和独立的政府和独立的媒体，并与独立媒体覆盖。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a/a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x886/c9b1af4444f7/location-uccor-oc-protests-dashboard.png”&#xA;Alt =“ Grafana仪表板，显示塞尔维亚抗议数据，并通过地图，抗议细节以及比较政府和独立媒体报道的线图。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;它还包含了情感分析和关键字用法比较等功能，以创建与数据的讲故事的有力示例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x806/0c300E0E76/sentiment-analysis-dashboard.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999X806/0C300EE0E76/SENTIMENT-ANALYSISS-ANALISS-DASHBOOD.PNG” ALT =“ ALT =” Grafana dashboard，显示饼图，线图，统计数据，表现图表，统计数据，以及学生指标，状态指标，参与/进入，概述，并估计&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x806/0c300E0E76/sentiment-analysis-dashboard.png”&#xA;alt =“有关学生指标，州提及和媒体出勤估计的饼图，线图和统计数据的Grafana仪表板。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这是一个非常雄心勃勃的项目，团队面临着设计连接各种技术的复杂系统体系结构的主要挑战。他们使用Python进行网络刮擦，Gemini 2.5 Flash API进行情感分析，春季启动后端和MongoDB Atlas存储数据，然后在Grafana中可视化所有内容。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;团队学会了如何从头开始与Grafana合作，应该为他们在36小时内将如此复杂的想法带入生活中的坚持而感到自豪。这是使用技术来解决关键现实世界问题的绝佳例子可以通过大量决心来完成（可能有太多的薯片！）。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ Project-Musigrafs-Visalized-Global-Music-Trends”&gt; Project Musigrafs：可视化全球音乐趋势&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将与可持续性主题无关的项目包裹着我们的Hackathon亮点，但仍然表现出很多创造力，并通过数据讲述了一个有力的故事。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“ https://devpost.com/software/musigrafs” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; musigrafs &lt;/a&gt;项目的启发是受音乐世界快节奏的性质和使用现有应用程序的困难来吸引现有应用程序的难度。该团队着手构建一个以数据驱动的Web应用程序，该应用程序捕获了“全球音乐趋势的脉搏 - 现场”。结果是Grafana仪表板，它可视化最佳流派，Common Musical Keys以及Energe和Tempo的实时音频功能。这是有抱负的音乐家了解市场并启动职业生涯的绝佳工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999933/0647D55D26A/Musigraf-dashboard.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999333/0647d55d26a/musigraf-dashboard.png” Alt =“ Alt =” Grafana Dashboard显示世界地图，带有音乐流派的世界图，最关键的用法，以及大多数听起来像是听听的，又是一首歌和类别。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999933/0647D55D26A/Musigraf-dashboard.png”&#xA;alt =“一个Grafana仪表板显示了带有音乐流派数据的世界地图，关键用法的条形图以及最听的歌曲和流派的列表。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最初努力以其所需的格式显示地图，不得不探索其他存储库来获得灵感。为了正确获取全球信息，他们使用了Geojson，这帮助他们代表了国家的边界​​。连接他们的&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/alexval03/hackupc2025/blob/blob/main/main/data/genres.geojson“ target =” _ blank =“ _空白” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt;导师和&lt;a href =“/grot/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grot ai &lt;/a&gt;。最终，他们为自己的图的视觉质量和清晰度和成功整合的实时数据感到自豪，这是他们项目的核心目标。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“闭幕式思想”&gt;闭幕思想&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Hackupc的Grafana支持和评审团队对黑客掌握了复杂概念的速度给人留下了深刻的印象，我们从他们的方法和挑战中学到了很多东西。使他们的项目成功的是他们出色的讲故事和最好的公关创建美丽而有影响力的可视化的作用。以及他们在压力下的伟大时间管理技能！我们很荣幸能够在那里并与下一代技术人才和数据讲故事的人建立联系。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们要感谢Hackupc志愿组织，所有参与的学生和所有法官。没有您的努力，这将是不可能的。我们等不及明年的Hackupc！ &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, you can find us at &lt;a href=&#34;https://hacksheffield.uk/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;HackSheffield10&lt;/a&gt; — another student hackathon event taking place at The University of Sheffield in November — where we’ll keep celebrating students’ passions and the power of data to make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Debug, query, and build faster with AI: How we use Grafana Assistant at Grafana Labs】调试，查询和使用AI更快地建造：我们如何在Grafana Labs使用Grafana助手</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/11/debug-query-and-build-faster-with-grafana-assistant/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;We recently released &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-for-grafana-onboarding-get-your-teams-started-quicker-with-grafana-assistant&#34;&gt;Grafana Assistant into public preview&lt;/a&gt; for Grafana Cloud, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been excited to see how our customers have already made it part of their daily observability routines. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, Assistant is becoming a go-to companion for developers right here at Grafana Labs, whether they&amp;rsquo;re debugging on-call issues, helping customers, or trying to remember tricky PromQL syntax. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our developers love how it fits naturally into their existing workflows, helping them save time and reduce friction. And in the spirit of transparency, we want to give you a peek behind the scenes to share how they&amp;rsquo;re getting the most from our integrated chat agent. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Specifically, you&amp;rsquo;ll read real-world testimonials about how Assistant: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Saves time when you know the data exists but cannot recall the query or the corresponding label names&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Simplifies writing queries you don&amp;rsquo;t quite remember&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Explains cryptic logs in plain English&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Speeds up onboarding for new users&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Makes creating or editing dashboards faster and easier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;finding-the-information-you-know-exists&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finding the information you know exists&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes the hardest part isn’t running a query—it’s knowing which query to run. This is especially true when you know the data must be there &lt;em&gt;somewhere&lt;/em&gt;, but you can&amp;rsquo;t quite remember how to get to it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assistant can save time by suggesting the right path forward. To make its answers even more accurate, it helps if you include important context such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The data source you are using&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The metrics or labels you care about&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Any specific filters you want to apply &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The more detail you provide, the more useful the results will be.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;As Grafana Labs has scaled, it is harder to remember all the metrics and labels across data sources. I knew the data I needed was in the logs, but I had no idea what query to write. I wanted to find customers in a specific region running a certain version of Grafana, but I was stuck on how to get there.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grafana Assistant gave me the explanation I needed in seconds, saving me 30 minutes or more.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;It turned a frustrating problem into something I could solve quickly without bothering teammates.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;a href=&#34;/author/sarah_zinger/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sarah Zinger&lt;/a&gt;, Staff Software Engineer for Grafana Core Services&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1165/f74128499f/find-query-slugs-prometheus.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1165/f74128499f/find-query-slugs-prometheus.png&#34;alt=&#34;Dashboard interface showing a Grafana query for Prometheus data on a dev cluster, with a line graph displaying request activity by slug.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1165/f74128499f/find-query-slugs-prometheus.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Dashboard interface showing a Grafana query for Prometheus data on a dev cluster, with a line graph displaying request activity by slug.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I was helping a user size a Pyroscope deployment and needed to know how much S3 storage our production bucket was using. I knew the data existed somewhere in our metrics or logs, but finding it would have taken time with either Grafana or the AWS CLI.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a last attempt, I asked the Assistant and it worked. It gave me the number right away and saved me about an hour of digging.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The best part is that it is always right there, wherever I go in Grafana.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- Bryan Huhta, Senior Software Engineer for Grafana Pyroscope&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Takeaway:&lt;/strong&gt; When you know the data is there but not how to get to it, Assistant can bridge the gap in seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;explaining-logs-traces-and-profiles-in-plain-language&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explaining logs, traces, and profiles in plain language&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you&amp;rsquo;re on call, every minute matters. Telemetry signals such as logs, profiles, and traces often contain the answers, but interpreting them can be slow—and overwhelming. All these signals now come with &amp;ldquo;Analyze in Assistant&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Explain this log line&amp;rdquo; options right from the visualization, so you can interact with them directly instead of digging through raw data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Assistant speeds up the process by breaking errors and performance data into plain language and pointing directly to what matters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“This one was a bit funny because Assistant actually helped me debug an issue with the Assistant backend services itself. We got an error alert for a spike in request errors, so we began our investigation. The key moment came when we looked at some traces from our backend service and used&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&amp;lsquo;Analyze this trace.&amp;rsquo; Instead of piecing together spans and timings on our own,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assistant translated the trace into plain language, highlighted where time was being lost, and even correlated the data with other spikes in latency we were seeing in metrics.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;That quickly pointed us to the root cause: a newly released feature that consumed an unprecedented amount of resources, causing our databases to run out of connections, memory, and CPU.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;a href=&#34;/author/sven-grossmann/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sven Großmann&lt;/a&gt;, Staff Software Engineer for Grafana Assistant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x917/6e72ff7479/trace-analysis.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x917/6e72ff7479/trace-analysis.png&#34;alt=&#34;Screenshot of the Grafana Cloud UI displaying a performance analysis with graphs, metrics, and a summary of HTTP POST operations.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x917/6e72ff7479/trace-analysis.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Screenshot of the Grafana Cloud UI displaying a performance analysis with graphs, metrics, and a summary of HTTP POST operations.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Takeaway:&lt;/strong&gt; Assistant makes traces and spans easier to understand, helping you move from alert to root cause much faster.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“While on call, I hit a cryptic error in the logs that mentioned an invalid UUID but gave no real context. Instead of combing through the raw output, I used &amp;lsquo;Explain this log line,&amp;rsquo; which I found in the log line menu dropdown.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The assistant pinpointed the exact field with the invalid value, explained why it caused the error, and suggested how to fix it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;What could have taken a long time to debug manually turned into a quick resolution.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;a href=&#34;/author/ivana/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Ivana Huckova&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Software Engineer for Grafana Data Sources (and co-author of this blog post)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Takeaway:&lt;/strong&gt; Assistant helps you understand errors in plain language, saving you from staring at confusing logs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;dashboard-creation-and-editing&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dashboard creation and editing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Building and maintaining dashboards can be one of the more time-consuming parts of working with Grafana. Assistant makes it easier by handling tasks like bulk editing queries or panels, saving time and cutting down on repetitive work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“One of the most helpful ways I’ve used Assistant was when I needed to update a dashboard that tracks usage of new features I’m working on.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I wanted to change the thresholds that highlight adoption across all panels, and instead of manually editing each one, I simply described the change.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Assistant generated the updates for me, turning a task that would normally take several minutes of tedious work into something I finished almost instantly.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-  &lt;a href=&#34;/author/piotr_jamroz/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Piotr Jamróz&lt;/a&gt;, Staff Software Engineer for Observability Traces and Profiling&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1012/1b852a112c/feature-tracking.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1012/1b852a112c/feature-tracking.png&#34;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard with multiple data panels showing percentages in green, yellow, and red. Chat conversation on the right with user feedback.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1012/1b852a112c/feature-tracking.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Grafana dashboard with multiple data panels showing percentages in green, yellow, and red. Chat conversation on the right with user feedback.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“We’re using a lot of SQL tables internally to look at our usage data. Grafana Assistant helps me to sift through these tables quickly to find the content I’m interested in and also gets me started on writing queries to build my panels.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adoption, retention, churn and other business KPIs are only one sentence away using the assistant.&lt;/strong&gt;__”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-  &lt;a href=&#34;/author/maurice-rochau/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Maurice Rochau&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Product Manager for Grafana AI (and co-author of this blog)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Takeaway:&lt;/strong&gt; Grafana Assistant automates tedious dashboard work for you so that you can focus on other work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;turning-questions-into-queries-faster&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turning questions into queries faster&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you are a beginner or an experienced user, it is easy to forget the exact query syntax or struggle to translate practices between tools. Assistant helps in both cases by providing the right syntax and surfacing best practices when they are needed most.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I use the Assistant a lot for query help, especially with PromQL syntax I never remember like&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;label_replace&lt;/code&gt; &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;group_left&lt;/code&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instead of digging through docs, I just describe what I want and get the correct query right where I am writing it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;For example, I used it to group status codes by their first digit with&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;label_replace&lt;/code&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and another time to join metrics with&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;group_left&lt;/code&gt; &lt;em&gt;to pull labels from an info metric. Having this built into Grafana means I never lose flow when building queries.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- &lt;a href=&#34;/author/dafydd-thomas/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Dafydd Thomas&lt;/a&gt;, Staff Software Engineer in Grafana Core Services&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x958/66c16562f5/syntax-question-answer.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x958/66c16562f5/syntax-question-answer.png&#34;alt=&#34;Split-screen showing code editor with PromQL code on the left and documentation on the right, including syntax explanations.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x958/66c16562f5/syntax-question-answer.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Split-screen showing code editor with PromQL code on the left and documentation on the right, including syntax explanations.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Oftentimes as solutions engineers we work with customers who want to understand what a migration from one observability vendor to another would look like. It is always a challenging task given the breadth of different tools out there. In the past, this usually meant relying on my own experience or pulling in subject matter experts. For example, I once asked on Slack how to search across all log lines in Loki, and while I eventually got a good answer, it took time and was not scalable. With the Assistant, I was able to get the same answer immediately and even ask for best practices as the customer planned their migration from their vendor to Grafana Cloud Logs.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It wasn&amp;rsquo;t just a translation of syntax, it guided the conversation toward recommended practices,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;which made the discussion with the customer much more valuable.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- David Tupper, Associate Solutions Engineer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Takeaway:&lt;/strong&gt; Assistant helps answer questions, no matter what they are, as long as the data is there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;onboarding-to-grafana-made-easier&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Onboarding to Grafana made easier&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learning a new platform can be overwhelming. There are new concepts to understand and unfamiliar tools to configure. Assistant makes onboarding interactive and contextual by letting you ask questions directly about your setup and guiding you step by step through real workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“As someone new to Grafana, Assistant made getting started much smoother and more efficient.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instead of spending hours reading documentation or asking teammates basic questions, I could ask the Assistant directly about my setup.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;For example, when creating a dashboard for my home server’s Nextcloud instance, it guided me through the query syntax and panel configuration. What would have taken me hours of trial and error was done in a fraction of the time.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- Kevin Adams, Senior Software Engineer for Grafana Assistant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Takeaway:&lt;/strong&gt; For new hires or users, Assistant turns onboarding from overwhelming into empowering. If you want to dig into this deeper, check our deep dive on &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-for-grafana-onboarding-get-your-teams-started-quicker-with-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;using the assistant to help your teams get started quicker with Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;start-usingassistant-today&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start using Assistant today&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant is here to amplify knowledge. Developers drive the process, but with Assistant by their side, they spend less time stuck and more time solving problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The next time you are debugging, writing a tricky query, or onboarding a new workflow, let Assistant lend a hand. Grafana Assistant is currently in &lt;strong&gt;public preview&lt;/strong&gt; and is available in every Grafana Cloud instance. You don’t need to install anything extra,  just log in to Grafana Cloud and look for the pulsar icon. You’ll see Assistant ready to use in your dashboards, Explore, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And if you haven’t tried Grafana Cloud yet, you can &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;sign up for a forever-free account&lt;/a&gt; today and start exploring with Grafana Assistant right away!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;faq-grafana-cloud-ai--assistant&#34;&gt;FAQ: Grafana Cloud AI &amp;amp; Assistant&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Grafana Assistant?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant is an AI-powered agent in Grafana Cloud that helps you query, build, and troubleshoot faster using natural language. It simplifies common workflows like writing PromQL, LogQL, or TraceQL queries, and creating dashboards — all while keeping you in control. Learn more &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/07/llm-grafana-assistant/&#34;&gt;in our blog post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does Grafana Cloud use AI in observability?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud’s AI features support engineers and operators throughout the observability lifecycle — from detection and triage to explanation and resolution. We focus on explainable, assistive AI that enhances your workflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What problems does Grafana Assistant solve?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant helps reduce toil and improve productivity by enabling you to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write and debug queries faster&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Build and optimize dashboards&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Investigate issues and anomalies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand telemetry trends and patterns&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Navigate Grafana more intuitively&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Grafana Labs&amp;rsquo; approach to building AI into observability?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We build around:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Human-in-the-loop interaction for trust and transparency&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Outcome-first experiences that focus on real user value&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-signal support, including correlating data across metrics, logs, traces, and profiles&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does Grafana OSS have AI capabilities?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By default, Grafana OSS doesn’t include built-in AI features found in Grafana Cloud, but you can enable AI-powered workflows using the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM app plugin&lt;/a&gt;. This open source plugin connects to providers like OpenAI or Azure OpenAI securely, allowing you to generate queries, explore dashboards, and interact with Grafana using natural language. It also provides a &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP (Model Context Protocol) server&lt;/a&gt;, which allows you to grant your favourite AI application access to your Grafana instance. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why isn’t Assistant open source?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Assistant runs in Grafana Cloud to support enterprise needs and manage infrastructure at scale. We’re committed to OSS and continue to invest heavily in it — including open sourcing tools like the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/&#34;&gt;LLM plugin&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;MCP server&lt;/a&gt;, so the community can build their own AI-powered experiences into Grafana OSS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does Grafana Cloud’s AI capabilities take actions on its own?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we focus on human-in-the-loop workflows that keep engineers in control while reducing toil. But as AI systems mature and prove more reliable, some tasks may require less oversight. We&amp;rsquo;re building a foundation that supports both: transparent, assistive AI now, with the flexibility to evolve into more autonomous capabilities where it makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where can I learn more about Grafana’s AI strategy?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/08/14/ai-in-observability-at-grafana-labs-making-observability-easy-and-accessible-for-everyone/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Check out our blog post&lt;/a&gt; to hear directly from our engineers.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;我们最近发行了&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/08/08/08/ai-for-for-for-for-for-get-get-get-your-teams-start-quicker-quicker-quicker-with-with-grafana-assistant”&gt; grafana助手进入公共预览&lt;/a&gt; for grafana cloud for grafana cloud，我们很高兴看到我们的客户已经使他们的每日一部分都可以实现。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同时，助理正在成为Grafana Labs的开发人员的首选伴侣，无论他们是在调试呼叫问题，帮助客户还是试图记住棘手的Promql语法。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的开发人员喜欢它自然地适合现有的工作流程，帮助他们节省时间并减少摩擦。本着透明度的精神，我们想为您提供幕后窥视，以分享它们如何从我们的集成聊天代理那里获得最大收益。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;具体来说，您将阅读有关助手的真实报道：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;当您知道数据存在但无法召回查询或相应标签名称&lt;/li&gt;时节省时间&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;简化了写作查询，您不太记得&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;用普通英语解释了隐秘的日志&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;为新用户加快登机速度&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;使创建或编辑仪表板更快，更容易&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;有时最困难的部分没有运行查询 - 它知道要运行哪个查询。当您知道数据必须在&lt;/em&gt;的某个地方&lt;em&gt;时，这尤其如此，但是您不太记得如何了解数据。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;助手可以通过建议正确的道路来节省时间。为了使其答案更加准确，如果您包含重要上下文，例如：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;您正在使用的数据源&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;您关心的指标或标签&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;您要应用的任何特定过滤器&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您提供的细节越多，结果就越有用。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“ &lt;em&gt;作为Grafana Labs的缩放，很难记住所有数据源的所有指标和标签。我知道我需要的数据是在日志中，但是我不知道要写什么疑问。我想在特定的区域中找到某个特定版本的grafana的客户，但是我呆在那里，我需要秒数30分钟，我需要elfection。或更多。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;它使一个令人沮丧的问题变成了我可以在不打扰队友的情况下可以解决的问题。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;a href =“/rution/sarah_zinger/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; sarah Zinger &lt;/a&gt;，Grafana Core Services的员工软件工程师&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x1165/f74128499f/find-query-slugs-prometheus.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl“&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1165/f74128499f/find-query-slugs-prometheus.png” alt =“ dashboard界面，显示grafana query in Deplode cloge cloge cloge cloge cloge clodetheus clogetheus clug clug cllug clage cllug clug cllaug cllaf.&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x1165/f741284999f/find-query-slugs-prometheus.png”&#xA;alt =“仪表板接口在开发集群上显示Prometheus数据的Grafana查询，并用SLUG显示请求活动的行图。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我正在帮助用户大小的载速仪的部署，需要知道我们的生产存储桶正在使用多少s3存储。我知道数据存在于我们的指标或日志中的某个地方，但是发现它需要花费时间与grafana或aws cli或AWS Cli。挖掘。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;最好的部分是它总是就在那里，无论我在grafana走到哪里。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; -Bryan Huhta，Grafana Pyroscope的高级软件工程师&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;要点：&lt;/strong&gt;当您知道数据在那里，但不知道该数据时，助手可以在几秒钟内弥合差距。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“解释logs-trace and-profiles in-plain语言”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;用普通语言解释日志，痕迹和配置文件&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当您打电话时，每一分钟都很重要。遥测信号（例如日志，配置文件和痕迹）通常包含答案，但是解释它们可能会很慢，而且压倒性。现在，所有这些信号都带有“助手分析”或“解释此日志线”选项，因此您可以直接与它们进行交互，而不是通过原始数据进行挖掘。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;助手通过将错误和绩效数据分解为普通语言，并直接指向重要的事情来加快该过程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“这是有点有趣的，因为助手实际上帮助我与助手后端服务本身进行了问题。我们在请求错误中获得了错误警报，因此我们开始调查。关键时刻是我们从后端服务中查看一些痕迹的关键时刻，并使用了&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;“分析此踪迹”，而不是插入助手和助手的助手，并在我们的语言上进行了拼凑而成。突出显示了浪费时间的位置，甚至将数据与我们在指标中看到的其他延迟相关联。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;很快将我们指向了根本原因：新发布的功能，它消耗了空前的资源，使我们的数据库耗尽了连接，记忆和CPU。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;a href =“/rution/sven-grossmann/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; svengroßmann&lt;/a&gt;，Grafana Assistant的员工软件工程师&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999X917/6E72FF7479/trace-analysis.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999917/6e72ff7479/trace-analysis.png” Alt =“ Grafana Cloud UI的ScreenShot”&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x917/6e72ff7479/trace-analysis.png”&#xA;alt =“ Grafana Cloud UI的屏幕截图，显示具有图形，指标和HTTP Post Operations摘要的性能分析。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;要点：&lt;/strong&gt;助手使痕迹和跨越易于理解，从而帮助您从警报转移到根本原因更快。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“While on call, I hit a cryptic error in the logs that mentioned an invalid UUID but gave no real context. Instead of combing through the raw output, I used ‘Explain this log line,’ which I found in the log line menu dropdown.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The assistant pinpointed the exact field with the invalid value, explained why it caused the error, and suggested how to fix it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;可能需要很长时间手动调试转变为快速分辨率。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;a href =“/作者/ivana/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; ivana huckova &lt;/a&gt;，Grafana数据源的高级软件工程师（此博客文章的合着者）&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;要点：&lt;/strong&gt;助手可以帮助您了解普通语言的错误，使您免于凝视着混乱的日志。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“仪表板 - 创建和编辑”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;仪表板创建和编辑&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;构建和维护仪表板可能是与Grafana合作的更耗时的部分之一。助理通过处理诸如批量编辑查询或面板之类的任务，节省时间并减少重复性工作来更容易。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我使用助手最有用的方式之一是我需要更新一个仪表板，该仪表板跟踪我正在努力的新功能的使用。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我想更改突出所有面板中采用的阈值，而不是手动编辑每个面板的阈值，而不是简单地描述了几个更新的时间。乏味的工作几乎立即完成。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;a href =“/rutiot/piotr_jamroz/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;piotrjamróz&lt;/a&gt;，可观察性迹线的员工软件工程师&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http：// schema.org/imageObject“&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1012/1b852a112c/feature-tracking.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x1012/1b852a112c/feature-tracking.png” alt =“ grafana dashboard，带有多个数据面板，显示了绿色，黄色和红色的聊天对话。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1012/1b852a112c/feature-tracking.png”&#xA;alt =“带有多个数据面板的Grafana仪表板显示绿色，黄色和红色的百分比。右侧的聊天对话都会与用户反馈。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“我们正在内部使用许多SQL表来查看我们的用法数据。GrafanaAssistant可以帮助我快速筛选这些表格，以找到我感兴趣的内容，还可以让我开始编写查询来构建面板。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;mstront&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;strong，retention，retention，Churn，Churn and Churn and Churn and Churn and kpis homker kpis homent kpiS sossist aistsy poss aisssist aistss aimply por &lt;/qutt/por &lt;/em pol &lt;/em pos &lt;/qutt &lt;/em&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;a href =“/ruter/aurice-rochau/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;莫里斯·罗丘（Maurice Rochau）&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;要点：&lt;/strong&gt; grafana助手为您自动化乏味的仪表板工作，以便您可以专注于其他工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ turning-questions-into-into-queries-faster”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;将问题更快地转换为查询&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是初学者还是经验丰富的用户，很容易忘记确切的查询语法或难以在工具之间翻译实践。在两种情况下，助手在两种情况下都提供了正确的语法，并在最需要的情况下提供最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I use the Assistant a lot for query help, especially with PromQL syntax I never remember like&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;label_replace&lt;/code&gt; &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt;group_left&lt;/code&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instead of digging through docs, I just describe what I want and get the correct query right where I am writing it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;For例如，我用它的第一个数字使用&lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt; label_replace &lt;/code&gt; &lt;em&gt;，另一个时间与&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;code&gt; group_left &lt;/code&gt; &lt;em&gt;一起加入指标，从而将其从grafana中吸引到grafana中。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  &lt;a href =“/rution/dafydd-thomas/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; dafydd thomas &lt;/a&gt;，Grafana Core Services的员工软件工程师&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x958/66c16562f5/syntax-question-question-question-ander.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https：//a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999958/66c16562f5/syntax-question-question-question-swer.png&#34;Alt=&#34;split=&#34;split-screen显示代码编辑器，带有promql代码的代码编辑器，左侧和右图（包括syntax demendations）。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x958/66c16562f5/syntax-question-question-question-aswer.png”&#xA;alt =“拆分屏幕在左侧显示promql代码，右侧的文档（包括语法说明）显示代码编辑器。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt;“通常作为解决方案工程师，我们与客户合作，他们想了解从一个可观察性供应商迁移到另一个供应商的迁移将是一项艰巨的任务。考虑到那里的不同工具的广度，这始终是一项具有挑战性的任务。在过去，这通常意味着要依靠我自己的经验或在主题上搜索所有的努力。与助手相比，我能够立即获得相同的答案，甚至要求客户从供应商到Grafana Cloud Logs的迁移。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;mstrong&gt;这不仅是构成的翻译，它将对话带入推荐实践，&lt;/em em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;/&#xA;&lt;p&gt; -David Tupper，副解决方案工程师&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;要点：&lt;/strong&gt;助手有助于回答问题，无论它们是什么，只要有数据。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“登机至格拉法纳​​（Grafana-Made-easier）”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;登上grafana的登机使&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;变得更容易&#xA;&lt;p&gt;学习一个新平台可能是压倒性的。有新的概念要理解和不熟悉的工具要配置。助手通过让您直接提出有关设置的问题并逐步指导您浏览真实的工作流程，从而使互动和上下文成为上下文。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“As someone new to Grafana, Assistant made getting started much smoother and more efficient.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Instead of spending hours reading documentation or asking teammates basic questions, I could ask the Assistant directly about my setup.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;For example, when creating a dashboard for my home server’s Nextcloud instance, it guided me through the query syntax and panel configuration. What would have taken me在很短的时间内进行了反复试验。” &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;  -  Grafana Assistant的高级软件工程师Kevin Adams &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;要点：&lt;/strong&gt;对于新员工或用户，助手从压倒性转向授权。如果您想更深入地研究，请在&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/08/14/ai-for-for-for-grafana-onboarding-get-your-teams-start-with-quicker-quicker-with-with-with-with-with-with-with-grafana-assistant/“”&gt;中，请使用助手帮助您的团队开始使用Grafaana Cloud &lt;/a&gt;。&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ start-usingAssistant-today”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;开始使用a今天&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana助手在这里放大知识。开发人员推动了这一过程，但是随着助手的身份，他们花费的时间更少，而解决问题的时间则更多。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;下次您进行调试，编写棘手的查询或登上新工作流程时，助手伸出援手。 Grafana Assistant目前正在&lt;strong&gt;公共预览&lt;/strong&gt;中，并且在每个Grafana Cloud实例中都可以使用。您无需安装任何额外的东西，只需登录到Grafana Cloud并查找Pulsar图标即可。您会看到助手准备在仪表板中使用，探索等等。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;，如果您还没有尝试过Grafana Cloud，则可以&lt;a href =“/auth/auth/cign-up/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;注册永远免费的帐户&lt;/a&gt;今天，并立即与Grafana Assistant探索！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是Grafana助手？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana Assistant是Grafana Cloud中的AI驱动代理商，可帮助您使用自然语言查询，构建和对解决方向进行更快的排除。它简化了常见的工作流，例如编写Promql，LogQL或TraceQl查询，并创建仪表板，同时使您可以控制。了解更多&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/05/07/llm-grafana-rassistant/”&gt;在我们的博客文章&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;中&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana Cloud如何使用AI可观察性？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana Cloud的AI在整个可观察性生命周期中为工程师和操作员提供了支持 - 从检测和分类到解释和解决方案。我们专注于可解释的辅助AI，以增强您的工作流程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana助手解决了哪些问题？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana助手通过使您能够：&lt;/p&gt;来帮助降低劳力和提高生产率&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更快地写和调试查询&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;构建和优化仪表板&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;调查问题和异常&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;了解遥测趋势和模式&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;更直观地导航grafana &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana Labs将AI构建为可观察性的方法是什么？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们周围建立：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;信任和透明度的人类互动&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;关注实际用户价值的结果优先经验&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;多信号支持，包括将跨指标，日志，痕迹和配置文件的数据相关联&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana OSS是否具有AI功能？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;默认情况下，Grafana OSS不包含Grafana Cloud中的内置AI功能，但是您可以使用&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/”&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;a&gt; &lt;a href =“ href =” href =“此开源插件可安全地连接到OpenAI或Azure OpenAI等提供商，使您可以使用自然语言来生成查询，探索仪表板并与Grafana进行交互。它还提供&lt;a href =“ https://github.com/grafana/mcp-grafana” target =“ _ blank“ rel =” noopener noreferrer“&gt; mcp（模型上下文协议）服务器&lt;/a&gt;，它允许您授予您喜欢的AI应用程序访问Grafana实例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;为什么不开放源代码？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana Assistant在Grafana Cloud中运行，以支持企业需求并大规模管理基础架构。我们致力于OSS并继续在其中进行大量投资 - 包括&lt;a a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/machine-learning/llm/”&gt; llm plugin &lt;/a&gt;和&lt;a href =“服务器&lt;/a&gt;，因此社区可以在Grafana OSS中建立自己的AI驱动体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Grafana Cloud的AI功能是否可以自己采取行动？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们关注的是人类的工作流程，这些工作流程使工程师在减少辛劳的同时保持控制。但是，随着AI系统成熟并证明更可靠，某些任务可能需要更少的监督。我们正在建立一个支持这两者的基础：现在透明，辅助AI，灵活地发展成为更有意义的更自主功能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;我在哪里可以了解有关Grafana的AI策略的更多信息？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“/blog/2025/08/14/ai in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-in-at-at-at-at-at-labs-labs-babs-maberservibility-easy and-easy and-cossible-cossible-for-everyone/？pg = pg = blog＆plcmt＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt = body-txt“&gt;查看我们的博客文章&lt;//a&gt;直接听取我们的博客文章&lt;/a&gt;直接听取我们的机器人的信息。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A smarter filter for Grafana Alerting: Introducing a new way to find your alerts】Grafana警报的智能过滤器：引入一种新的方法来查找您的警报</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/10/a-smarter-filter-for-grafana-alerting-introducing-a-new-way-to-find-your-alerts/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;At Grafana Labs, we believe that effective alerting is the cornerstone of any robust observability strategy. That&amp;rsquo;s why we&amp;rsquo;re constantly listening to your feedback and working to improve the Grafana user experience so it&amp;rsquo;s easier for you to manage and interact with your alert rules. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Today, we’ve excited to tell you about an update in Grafana Alerting that&amp;rsquo;s built to address some of your biggest pain points. We&amp;rsquo;re releasing a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/next/alerting/monitor-status/view-alert-rules/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;brand new filtering experience&lt;/a&gt; for the alert rules list view that&amp;rsquo;s designed to help you quickly and easily find the alert rules you need, with a cleaner UI, more filtering options, and a solid foundation for future enhancements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-cleaner-more-powerful-solution&#34;&gt;A cleaner, more powerful solution&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The previous filtering function for alert rules presented some challenges. We heard from many of you that the filter fields took up valuable screen space and that you wanted more ways to narrow down your searches. It was clear that the user experience needed to be more intuitive and less cluttered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our goal was to create a filtering system that reduces cognitive load and gives you greater control:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More filtering options:&lt;/strong&gt; You can now filter by additional criteria that users have been asking for: Namespace, Label, Evaluation group, and Rule Source. This provides more granular control over your searches.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cleaner UI:&lt;/strong&gt; By moving the filters into a popup, we&amp;rsquo;ve reduced screen clutter and given you more room to view your alert rules, making the page more efficient and less overwhelming.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improved user experience:&lt;/strong&gt; The new filter features dropdowns, making it easier to select the criteria you want to search by. It also reduces the need for familiarity with the search field syntax.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Foundation for the future:&lt;/strong&gt; This new filtering system is a crucial step towards more advanced search functionality. It lays the groundwork for powerful features like saved searches, which we plan to explore in future releases.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This new feature is already being rolled out across Grafana Cloud, and it will be included as a generally available feature in the Grafana 12.3 release this October.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-side-by-side-look&#34;&gt;A side-by-side look&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you can see from the two screenshots below, the new UI offers a cleaner and more cohesive experience. While the previous filter took up valuable screen space, the new filter is now contained within a popup.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ve kept the search field for manual filtering, but you can also click the &lt;strong&gt;Filter&lt;/strong&gt; button to access a full list of additional dropdowns, including Namespace, Labels, Evaluation group, and Rule source, giving you more control over your search.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Old filter:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1025/43243b38b8/new-alert-list-filter-old.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1025/43243b38b8/new-alert-list-filter-old.png&#34;alt=&#34;Screenshot of Grafana&amp;#39;s old alert rules page, showing a list of alert rules with options to configure, search, and create new alerts.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1025/43243b38b8/new-alert-list-filter-old.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Screenshot of Grafana&amp;#39;s old alert rules page, showing a list of alert rules with options to configure, search, and create new alerts.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New filter:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1026/cfe00b6077/new-alert-list-filter-new.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1026/cfe00b6077/new-alert-list-filter-new.png&#34;alt=&#34;Screenshot of Grafana&amp;#39;s new alert rules interface showing a list of alert rules and a form for creating a new alert rule.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1026/cfe00b6077/new-alert-list-filter-new.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Screenshot of Grafana&amp;#39;s new alert rules interface showing a list of alert rules and a form for creating a new alert rule.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;use-cases&#34;&gt;Use cases&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now that we&amp;rsquo;ve shown you how the new filtering experience works, let&amp;rsquo;s look at a few examples of how you can use the new filter to solve both old and new problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the old search experience, some of the properties (Label, Namespace, Evaluation group, etc.) had no individual filters, so the only filtering option was to type your search string in the search field. This meant that you had to obey the exact search syntax. But with the new filters, you can just directly interact with the selectors. And don’t mind the syntax—it&amp;rsquo;s automatically populated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In addition, if you wanted to filter by label in the old search experience, you had to type the exact key/value in the search field. This means you had to know the available key-value pairs and keep to the right spelling. With the new filters you can now use a dropdown to browse all available labels and just pick the one you need.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, all existing functionality is preserved. So if you prefer typing, or you’d like to send a search string to a colleague, you can use the search field the same as you did before.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-to-get-started&#34;&gt;How to get started&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The new filter is available in the alert rules list view today. Simply click the &lt;strong&gt;Filter&lt;/strong&gt; button at the top of the list to get started. We encourage you to try it out and share your feedback with us on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://community.grafana.com/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;Grafana Community Forums&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re committed to building tools that are not only powerful but also intuitive and a pleasure to use. Stay tuned for more updates!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;在Grafana Labs，我们认为有效的警报是任何强大的可观察性策略的基石。这就是为什么我们不断听取您的反馈并努力改善Grafana用户体验，以便您更容易管理和与警报规则进行交互。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天，我们很高兴向您介绍Grafana警报中的更新，该更新是为了解决您最大的痛苦点的构建。我们正在发布a &lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/next/nervering/monitor-status/view-alert-rules/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt“&gt;全新的过滤体验”&gt;“警报规则”列表视图&lt;/a&gt;旨在快速地帮助您使用Cleaner proffortss的precters &lt;/porthers prefters putornect &lt;/porthers prefters &lt;/porters profforts &lt;/porters &lt;precters &lt;precters &lt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;警报规则的先前过滤功能提出了一些挑战。我们从你们许多人那里听到过滤场占据了宝贵的屏幕空间，并且您想要更多的方法来缩小搜索范围。显然，用户体验需要更直观，更混乱。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的目标是创建一个减少认知负载并为您提供更大控制的过滤系统：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;更多的过滤选项：&lt;/strong&gt;您现在可以按其他用户要求的其他条件过滤：名称空间，标签，评估组和规则源。这为您的搜索提供了更详细的控制。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;清洁ui：&lt;/strong&gt;通过将过滤器移动到弹出窗口中，我们减少了屏幕混乱，并为您提供了更多的空间来查看您的警报规则，使页面更加有效，更不重要。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;改进的用户体验：&lt;/strong&gt;新的过滤器功能下拉菜单，使选择要搜索的标准变得更加容易。它还减少了熟悉搜索字段语法的需求。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;未来的基础：&lt;/strong&gt;这个新的过滤系统是迈向更先进的搜索功能的关键步骤。它为诸如保存搜索之类的强大功能奠定了基础，我们计划在将来发行中探索。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此新功能已经在Grafana Cloud上推出，它将作为今年10月的Grafana 12.3版本中的一般功能。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“ A旁边的景观”&gt;并排外观&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;从下面的两个屏幕截图中可以看到，新的UI提供了更清洁，更具凝聚力的体验。虽然先前的过滤器占据了宝贵的屏幕空间，但新过滤器现在包含在弹出窗口中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们保留了手动过滤的搜索字段，但是您也可以单击&lt;strong&gt;过滤器&lt;/strong&gt;按钮以访问其他下拉列表的完整列表，包括命名空间，标签，评估组和规则源，使您对搜索进行更多控制。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;旧过滤器：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1025/43243b38b8/new-alert-list-filter over.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x1025/43243b38b8/new-alert-list-list-filter over.png“ alt =” Grafana screenshot of Grafana screenshot of Grafana的旧警报规则，显示了一个旧的警报规则，显示了一份警报规则，并创建了新的，并创建新的，并创建新的。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x1025/43243b38b8/new-alert-list-filter over.png”&#xA;Alt =“ Grafana的旧警报规则页面的屏幕截图，显示具有配置，搜索和创建新警报的选项的警报规则列表。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;strong&gt;新滤镜：&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x1026/cfe00b6077/new-alert-list-filter-new.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x1026/cfe00b6077//new-alert-list-filter-new.png”&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1026/cfe00b6077/new-alert-list-filter-new.png”&#xA;alt =“ Grafana的新警报规则接口的屏幕截图，显示警报规则列表和一个创建新警报规则的表格。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“用例”&gt;用例&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;现在，我们向您展示了新的过滤体验的工作原理，让我们看一些如何使用新过滤器解决旧问题和新问题的示例。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在旧的搜索体验中，某些属性（标签，命名空间，评估组等）没有单独的过滤器，因此唯一的过滤选项是在搜索字段中键入搜索字符串。这意味着您必须遵守确切的搜索语法。但是使用新过滤器，您可以直接与选择器进行交互。而且不要介意语法 - 它会自动填充。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此外，如果您想在旧搜索体验中通过标签过滤，则必须在搜索字段中键入确切的键/值。这意味着您必须知道可用的键值对并保持正确的拼写。使用新过滤器，您现在可以使用下拉列表来浏览所有可用的标签，只选择您需要的标签。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;同时保留了所有现有功能。因此，如果您喜欢打字，或者想向同事发送搜索字符串，则可以与以前相同的搜索字段。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“如何开始&lt;/h2&gt;如何开始&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今天的“警报规则列表”视图可用。只需单击列表顶部的&lt;strong&gt;过滤器&lt;/strong&gt;按钮即可开始。我们鼓励您尝试一下，并在&lt;a a href =“ https://community.grafana.com/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt = body-txt” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; href =“ https://community.grafana.com/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; grafana社区论坛&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们致力于构建不仅强大而且也很直观且享受使用的工具。请继续关注更多更新！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Measuring service response time and latency: How to perform a TCP check in Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring】测量服务响应时间和延迟：如何在Grafana云合成监视中执行TCP检查</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/09/measuring-service-response-time-and-latency-how-to-perform-a-tcp-check-in-grafana-cloud-synthetic-monitoring/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When your database stops accepting connections or your mail server becomes unreachable during business hours, the impact is immediate and costly. Fortunately, the right monitoring strategy can help you detect these TCP connection failures early on, and prevent them from impacting the user experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With &lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/synthetic-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/a&gt; — a solution that lets you proactively monitor the performance of your critical applications from locations around the world — &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/tcp/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;TCP checks&lt;/a&gt; can be your first line of defense against service failures and network connectivity issues. With TCP checks, you can test connections on specific ports, simulate real user interactions, and measure the availability and performance of your services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You might use TCP checks when you&amp;rsquo;re:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Monitoring database connections and availability&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Verifying mail server accessibility and performance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ensuring FTP servers are accepting file transfers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Checking message queue connectivity and response times&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through how TCP checks work and show you how to set one up in Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring. You can also follow along with our step-by-step video tutorial below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#39;https://www.youtube.com/embed/FzM8F-qdgtI&#39; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-are-tcp-checks&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are TCP checks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring enables you to proactively monitor the performance of your applications and services from &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/public-probes/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;public and private probes&lt;/a&gt; located around the world. It allows you to set up a variety of &lt;em&gt;checks&lt;/em&gt;, including &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/02/27/how-to-perform-a-ping-check-with-grafana-cloud-synthetic-monitoring/&#34;&gt;ping checks&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/06/03/optimizing-the-end-user-experience-how-to-perform-a-browser-check-in-grafana-cloud-synthetic-monitoring/&#34;&gt;browser checks&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/k6/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;scripted checks&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/dns/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;DNS checks&lt;/a&gt;, and TCP checks. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TCP checks connect to endpoints on specified hostnames, IP addresses, and ports to verify that the servers accept a connection. Unlike HTTP checks, which focus on web services, TCP checks work at the transport layer, making them ideal for monitoring any service that communicates over TCP. The key benefits of TCP checks include:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Real-time monitoring to quickly diagnose network connectivity issues&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Security monitoring to detect unusual port behavior&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Global TCP validation, which provides valuable insights into connection success rates, response times, and service availability from locations around the world&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;setting-up-your-first-tcp-check&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Setting up your first TCP check&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;run-a-tcp-check&#34;&gt;Run a TCP check &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s walk through setting up a TCP check. This process involves a few key configuration steps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-create-a-grafana-cloud-account&#34;&gt;1. Create a Grafana Cloud account&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you don’t already have one, sign up for a &lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;free Grafana Cloud account&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;2-navigate-to-synthetic-monitoring&#34;&gt;2. Navigate to Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the Grafana Cloud UI, go to &lt;strong&gt;Testing &amp;amp; synthetics&lt;/strong&gt; to access tools for performance testing and optimization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1229x1125/740ba63688/synthetics-on-menu_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1229x1125/740ba63688/synthetics-on-menu_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface showing a menu with options like Dashboards, Alerts, and Performance. &amp;#39;Synthetics&amp;#39; under Performance is highlighted.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1229x1125/740ba63688/synthetics-on-menu_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface showing a menu with options like Dashboards, Alerts, and Performance. &amp;#39;Synthetics&amp;#39; under Performance is highlighted.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;3-select-synthetic-monitoring-and-create-a-check&#34;&gt;3. Select Synthetic Monitoring and create a check&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, click &lt;strong&gt;Synthetics&lt;/strong&gt; and choose &lt;strong&gt;Create check&lt;/strong&gt;. Select &lt;strong&gt;API Endpoint&lt;/strong&gt; as the check type. This is where you find HTTP, Ping, DNS, TCP and Traceroute checks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1600x554/6a5dcc588d/choose-a-check-type_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1600x554/6a5dcc588d/choose-a-check-type_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface showing options for choosing a check type: API Endpoint, Multi Step, and Scripted.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1600x554/6a5dcc588d/choose-a-check-type_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface showing options for choosing a check type: API Endpoint, Multi Step, and Scripted.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;4-add-a-request&#34;&gt;4. Add a request &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, provide a job name. We’ll use the name &lt;strong&gt;Example:TCP&lt;/strong&gt;. For our request type, we’ll select &lt;strong&gt;TCP&lt;/strong&gt; and for the request target we’ll type &lt;strong&gt;smtp.gmail.com:587&lt;/strong&gt;. When you are specifying your request target you can also include additional options like a TLS config.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x1125/9c1718a6bb/job-name-and-request-target_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x1125/9c1718a6bb/job-name-and-request-target_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface displaying a request form for testing a TCP connection to smtp.gmail.com on port 587, with a &amp;#39;Request&amp;#39; button below.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x1125/9c1718a6bb/job-name-and-request-target_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface displaying a request form for testing a TCP connection to smtp.gmail.com on port 587, with a &amp;#39;Request&amp;#39; button below.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;5-set-a-timeout&#34;&gt;5. Set a timeout &lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With our TCP check added, select &lt;strong&gt;Add query/response&lt;/strong&gt; button. The query will be “&lt;strong&gt;^220 ([^ ]+) ESMTP (.+)$&lt;/strong&gt;” and the response will be “&lt;strong&gt;EHLO prober\r&lt;/strong&gt;”&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We’ll also specify the maximum execution time for this check. If the check takes longer than this period to run, the check will be marked as failed. For this example, we’ll choose 10 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x625/e9200706f0/add-query-and-response_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x625/e9200706f0/add-query-and-response_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of Grafana Cloud configuration interface for defining uptime, showing query/response fields, StartTLS option, and a timeout set to 10 seconds.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x625/e9200706f0/add-query-and-response_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of Grafana Cloud configuration interface for defining uptime, showing query/response fields, StartTLS option, and a timeout set to 10 seconds.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;6-add-labels&#34;&gt;6. Add labels&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/analyze-results/custom-labels/&#34;&gt;Labels&lt;/a&gt; help you organize and filter your checks. Adding a label makes it easier to segment results by environment or use case in the future. For this example, we’ll use the label &lt;strong&gt;env:test.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1664x659/6243bf33d1/add-labels_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1664x659/6243bf33d1/add-labels_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana Cloud interface titled &amp;#39;API Endpoint.&amp;#39; It shows a section on &amp;#39;Labels&amp;#39; with a button labeled &amp;#39;&amp;#43; Add label&amp;#39; highlighted.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1664x659/6243bf33d1/add-labels_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana Cloud interface titled &amp;#39;API Endpoint.&amp;#39; It shows a section on &amp;#39;Labels&amp;#39; with a button labeled &amp;#39;&amp;#43; Add label&amp;#39; highlighted.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;7-choose-a-probe-location&#34;&gt;7. Choose a probe location&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud offers access to over 20 globally distributed &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/public-probes/&#34;&gt;probe locations&lt;/a&gt;. For this example, we’ll select &lt;strong&gt;Calgary, Canada&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Stockholm, Sweden&lt;/strong&gt;. We advise that you choose the location closest to your users or infrastructure to best reflect their experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1555x1125/3798e5b14c/choose-probe-locations_tcp-check.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1555x1125/3798e5b14c/choose-probe-locations_tcp-check.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface showing selectable probe locations across regions including AMER, APAC, and EMEA.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1555x1125/3798e5b14c/choose-probe-locations_tcp-check.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface showing selectable probe locations across regions including AMER, APAC, and EMEA.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;8-set-your-test-frequency&#34;&gt;8. Set your test frequency&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Determine how frequently you want your TCP check to run. We chose a one-minute interval, so our check will run every minute. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1562x775/4f9b45f76a/select-frequency-of-check_tcp-check.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1562x775/4f9b45f76a/select-frequency-of-check_tcp-check.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface for setting probe frequency, with options from 30 seconds to 1 hour.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1562x775/4f9b45f76a/select-frequency-of-check_tcp-check.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud interface for setting probe frequency, with options from 30 seconds to 1 hour.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;9-create-an-alert&#34;&gt;9. Create an alert&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Alerting is an essential part of synthetic monitoring. When metrics deviate from expected performance, alerts are the most effective way to trigger necessary actions based on those metrics. For this example, we’ll use &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/configure-alerts/configure-default-alerts/&#34;&gt;per-check alerts&lt;/a&gt; and choose &lt;strong&gt;2 of 10&lt;/strong&gt; executions that fail in the last five minutes as the threshold to get alerted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x649/aaf984d4b5/per-check-alerts_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x649/aaf984d4b5/per-check-alerts_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana Cloud interface for configuring alerting options using Grafana Alerting.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x649/aaf984d4b5/per-check-alerts_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A screenshot of a Grafana Cloud interface for configuring alerting options using Grafana Alerting.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;10-save-and-run-the-check&#34;&gt;10. Save and run the check&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Save&lt;/strong&gt; to initiate the TCP check. Grafana Cloud will begin executing based on your configuration. You can also click the &lt;strong&gt;Test&lt;/strong&gt; button to validate the check before saving.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;visualizing-the-check-results&#34;&gt;Visualizing the check results&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After letting our TCP check run for a few hours, it’s time to review the results. &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/analyze-results/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring&lt;/a&gt; provides a preconfigured dashboard for each check, providing key insights to evaluate performance. On this dashboard, you’ll find important metrics like uptime, reachability, average latency, SSL Chain Expiry, and frequency.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1364/ed29b35314/example-dashboard_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload &#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1364/ed29b35314/example-dashboard_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring dashboard displaying network performance metrics including error rate, reachability, and latency over time.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1364/ed29b35314/example-dashboard_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring dashboard displaying network performance metrics including error rate, reachability, and latency over time.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you scroll through the dashboard, you’ll find additional charts that offer deeper visibility, including response latency by probe location. All data and visualizations are updated in real time as the test continues to run, allowing for continuous performance monitoring and faster issue detection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;wrapping-up&#34;&gt;Wrapping up &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TCP checks can provide additional visibility into the connectivity and performance of your non-HTTP services. By leveraging Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring, you can effortlessly implement and manage TCP checks to ensure the reliability of your most critical backend services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about Synthetic Monitoring in Grafana Cloud, please refer to our &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;technical docs&lt;/a&gt;. You can also explore &lt;a href=&#34;https://play.grafana.org/a/grafana-synthetic-monitoring-app/home?var-region=$__all&amp;amp;var-probe=$__all&amp;amp;var-check_type=$__all&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;this dashboard on Grafana Play&lt;/a&gt;, which features example checks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with synthetic monitoring. We have a generous free tier that includes 100k test executions per month and more.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user?pg=plugins&amp;amp;plcmt=grafana-synthetic-monitoring-app&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当您的数据库停止接受连接或您的邮件服务器在工作时间内无法到达时，影响是直接且昂贵的。幸运的是，正确的监视策略可以帮助您尽早检测这些TCP连接失败，并防止它们影响用户体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; with &lt;a href =“/products/products/cloud/synthetic-monitoring/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana云合成监视&lt;/a&gt;  - 一种解决方案，可以主动监视来自世界各地的关键应用程序的性能 -  &lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/checks/tcp/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt“&gt; tcp checks &lt;/a&gt;可以是您针对服务故障和网络连接性问题的第一道防线。使用TCP检查，您可以在特定端口上测试连接，模拟真实的用户交互并测量服务的可用性和性能。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;您可以在以下方面使用TCP检查：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;监视数据库连接和可用性&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;验证邮件服务器可访问性和性能&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;确保FTP服务器接受文件传输&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;检查消息队列连接和响应时间&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在这篇博客文章中，我们将介绍TCP检查的工作方式，并向您展示如何在Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring中设置一个。您也可以关注下面的分步视频教程。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe width =“ 560” height =“ 315” src =&#39;https：//www.youtube.com/embed/fzm8f-qdgti&#39;title =“ youtube视频播放器” frameborder =“ 0” 0“ 0”允许=“ AcceLeremer; AspoPlay; autoplay; Autoplay; Autoplay; autoplay; autoplay; autoplay; clipboard-write; clipboard-write; exprypter; exprypthed-media; expryptic-media; referrerpolicy =“ strict-origin-cross-origin” glasefullscreen&gt; &lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ What-are-tcp-checks”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;什么是TCP检查？&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring enables you to proactively monitor the performance of your applications and services from &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/public-probes/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;public and private probes&lt;/a&gt; located around the world.它允许您设置各种&lt;em&gt;检查&lt;/em&gt;，包括&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/02/27/how-to-to-perform-a-ping-check-with-with-grafana-cloud-cloud-synthetic-monoritoring/”&gt; ping pings &lt;/a&gt; href =“/blog/2025/06/03/优化the-end-user-userience-how-a-a-a-browser-a-browser-check-ingrafana-check-ingrafana-clafana-cloud-cloud-synththetic-monoritoring/&gt;浏览器检查&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/checks/checks/k6/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;脚本检查&lt;/a&gt;，&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monoritoring/create-checks/checks/checks/dns/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt“&gt; dns checks &lt;/a&gt;和TCP检查。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; TCP检查连接到指定的主机名，IP地址和端口上的端点，以验证服务器是否接受连接。与专注于Web服务的HTTP检查不同，TCP检查在运输层上工作，使其非常适合Monitor inG任何通过TCP通信的服务。 TCP检查的主要好处包括：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;实时监控以快速诊断网络连接问题&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;安全监视以检测异常端口行为&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;全球TCP验证，该验证提供了有关连接成功率，响应时间和服务可用性的宝贵见解&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“设置您的优点-TCP-CHACK”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;设置您的第一个TCP检查&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“ Run-A-TCP-Check”&gt;运行TCP检查&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们通过设置TCP检查。此过程涉及一些关键配置步骤。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ 1-acreate-a-a-grafana-cloud-account”&gt; 1。创建一个grafana云帐户&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;如果您还没有一个，请注册a &lt;a href =“/auth/ign-up/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; free grafana cloud帐户&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ 2-Navigate to synthetic-Monitoring”&gt; 2。导航到合成监视&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Grafana Cloud UI中，转到&lt;strong&gt;测试和合成&lt;/strong&gt;访问性能测试和优化的工具。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1229x1125/740ba63688/synthetics-menu_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/12229x1125/740ba63688/synthetics-on-menu_tcp-checks.jpg” alt =“ Alt =” grafana云界面与dashboards and and and and and and commands and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and synics and and and and and and and and and and and and and and and insict。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1229x1125/740ba63688/synthetics-on-menu_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;alt =“ grafana云界面显示菜单，其中包括仪表板，警报和性能等选项。“合成&#39;&#39;的性能&#39;被突出显示。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“ 3选择合成 - 仪式和创建-A-Check”&gt; 3。选择合成监视并创建检查&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，单击&lt;strong&gt;合成&lt;/strong&gt;，然后选择&lt;strong&gt;创建检查&lt;/strong&gt;。选择&lt;strong&gt; API端点&lt;/strong&gt;作为检查类型。这是您找到http，ping，dns，tcp和traceroute检查的地方。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1600x554/6a5dcc5888d/choose-choose-a-check-check-type_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1600X554/6A5DCC588D/CHOOSE-CHOOSE-CHOOSE-A-CHECK-CHECK-TYPE_TCP-CHECKS.JPGS.jpg” ALT =“ ALT =” Grafana云界面显示一个用于选择检查的选项：&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1600x554/6a5dcc588d/choose-a-check-ceck-type_tcp-checks.jpg“&#xA;alt =“ Grafana云接口显示用于选择检查类型的选项：API端点，多步骤和脚本。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ 4-ADD-A-REQUEST”&gt; 4。添加请求&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，提供一个工作名称。我们将使用名称&lt;strong&gt;示例：TCP &lt;/strong&gt;。对于我们的请求类型，我们将选择&lt;strong&gt; tcp &lt;/strong&gt;，对于请求目标，我们将键入&lt;strong&gt; smtp.gmail.com:587 &lt;/strong&gt;。指定您的请求目标时，您还可以包括其他选项，例如TLS Config。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x1125/9c1718a6bb/job-name-and-name-and-request-target-target_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x1125/9c1718a6bb/job-name-name-and-request-target_tcp-checks.jpgs.jpgs.jpgs.jpg” alt =“ Alt =” grafana云界面，以port.s&#39;port.s&#39;smt.s&#39;smt.s&#39;smt.s&#39;&#39;下面的按钮。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1554x1125/9c1718a6bb/job-name-hame-and-request-target-target_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;alt =“ grafana云接口，显示用于测试TCP连接到smtp.gmail.com上的请求表格，端口587，下面有&#39;请求&#39;按钮。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ 5-Set-a-pereout”&gt; 5。设置超时&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;添加了TCP检查后，选择&lt;strong&gt;添加查询/响应&lt;/strong&gt;按钮。查询将为“ &lt;strong&gt;^ 220（[^]+）esmtp（。+）$ &lt;/strong&gt;”，响应将为“ &lt;strong&gt; ehlo Prober \ r &lt;/strong&gt;” &lt;strong&gt;。&lt;/strong&gt;。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们还将指定此检查的最大执行时间。如果支票花费的时间长于此期间，则支票将被标记为失败。对于此示例，我们将选择10秒。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x625/e9200706f0/add-query-and-andd-query-and-response_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x625/e9200706f0/add-query-and-response_tcp-checks.jpg”秒。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x625/e9200706f0/add-query-and-andd-query-and-response_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;alt =“用于定义正常运行时间的Grafana Cloud配置接口的屏幕截图，显示查询/响应字段，startTLS选项以及设置为10秒的超时。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ 6-Add-Labels”&gt; 6。添加标签&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monoritoring/andaryze-results/custom-labels/“&gt;标签”&gt;标签&lt;/a&gt;帮助您组织和过滤支票。添加标签使得将来可以更轻松地按环境或用例细分结果。在此示例中，我们将使用标签&lt;strong&gt; env：test。&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1664x659/6243bf33d1/add-labels_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1664x659/6243bf33d1/add-labels_tcp-checks.jpg” alt =“ Alt =” Grafana Cloud Interface Interface Interface title&#39;api Endpoint的屏幕截图。它在“标签”上显示了一个标记为“标签”的部分。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1664x659/6243bf33d1/add-labels_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;Alt =“ Grafana云接口的屏幕截图，名为“ API端点”。它在“标签”上显示了一个标记为“标签”的部分。&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ 7- choose-a-probe-Location”&gt; 7。选择一个探针位置&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; Grafana Cloud提供了20多个全球分布式&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/create-checks/public-probes/“”&gt;探针位置&lt;/a&gt;。在此示例中，我们将选择&lt;strong&gt;卡尔加里，加拿大&lt;/strong&gt;和&lt;strong&gt;斯德哥尔摩，瑞典&lt;/strong&gt;。我们建议您选择最接近用户或基础架构的位置来最佳反映他们的体验。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1555X1125/3798E5B14C/CHOOSE-PROBE-LOCATIONS_TCP-CHECK.JPG”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/15555x1125/3798e5b14c/choose-probe-locations_tcp-check.jpg.jpg” alt =“ Alt =” Grafana云界面显示了跨型号的范围内的跨区域&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1555X1125/3798E5B14C/choose-probe-locations_tcp-check.jpg”&#xA;alt =“ grafana云接口显示跨区域，包括Amer，Apac和EMEA的可选探针位置。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;H4 ID =“ 8-Set-Your检测频率”&gt; 8。设置测试频率&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;确定您希望运行TCP检查的频率。我们选择了一分钟的间隔，因此我们的支票每分钟都会运行。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http：//schema.org/imageObject“&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1562x775/4f9b45f76a/select-frequency-frequency-of-check_tcp-check.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1562x775/4f9b45f76a/select-frequency-of-check_tcp-check.tcp-check.jpg” alt =“ Alt =” Grafana云界面，以设置探针频率，并设置30秒秒秒。&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1562x775/4f9b45f76a/select-frequency-frequency-of-check_tcp-check.jpg”&#xA;alt =“用于设置探针频率的Grafana云接口，选项为30秒至1小时。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“ 9-CREATE-AN-ALERT”&gt; 9。创建一个警报&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;警报是合成监测的重要组成部分。当指标偏离预期性能时，警报是触发基于这些指标的必要操作的最有效方法。在此示例中，我们将使用&lt;a href =“/doc/grafana-cloud/testing/synthetic-monitoring/configure-alerts/configure-alerts/configure-default-alerts/“&gt; per-check near-check nervers &lt;/a&gt;，然后选择&lt;strong&gt; 2的10 &lt;/strong&gt;执行在最后五分钟内，因为thereshold the thereshold the thereshold fe thereshold fe nerthold fe nerthold ofer nerthold ofer nerfe nerter nerter nerfer naper。&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x649/aaf984d4b5/per-check-alerts_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x649/aaf984d4b5/per-check-alerts_tcp-checks.jpg” alt =“ Alt =” Alt =“用于配置Grafana Cloud Interface的屏幕截图，用于配置Grafana Cloud Interface使用GrafaNa Nolering Optifs使用Grafaana Notering Option&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1693x649/aaf984d4b5/per-check-alerts_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;alt =“用于使用Grafana警报配置警报选项的Grafana Cloud接口的屏幕截图。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id =“ 10个储备和跑步检查”&gt; 10。保存并运行支票&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;单击&lt;strong&gt;保存&lt;/strong&gt;以启动TCP检查。 Grafana Cloud将根据您的配置开始执行。您也可以单击&lt;strong&gt;测试&lt;/strong&gt;按钮以在保存之前验证支票。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;在&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们的TCP检查运行几个小时后，是时候检查结果了。 &lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/santthetic-monoritoring/andaryze-results/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana云综合监视&lt;/a&gt;为每张支票提供了预配置的仪表板，以提供关键的洞察力来评估性能。在此仪表板上，您会发现重要指标，例如正常时间，可及性，平均延迟，SSL链到期和频率。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-link”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1364/Ed29b35314/example-dashboard_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1364/ed29b35314/example-dashboard_tcp-checks.jpg&#34;alt=&#34;A Grafana Cloud Synthetic Monitoring dashboard displaying network performance metrics including error rate, reachability, and latency over time.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999X1364/ED29B35314/Example-dashboard_tcp-checks.jpg”&#xA;alt =“ Grafana云合成监视仪表板显示网络性能指标，包括错误率，到达性和延迟随着时间的推移。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;滚动浏览仪表板时，您会发现其他图表，可提供更深的可见性，包括通过探针位置进行响应延迟。随着测试的继续进行，所有数据和可视化都会实时更新，从而可以进行连续的性能监视和更快的问题检测。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“包装”&gt;包装&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; TCP检查可以为您的非HTTP服务的连接性和性能提供额外的可见性。通过利用Grafana Cloud合成监控，您可以毫不费力地实施和管理TCP检查以确保最关键的后端服务的可靠性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;要了解有关Grafana Cloud中合成监视的更多信息，请参阅我们的&lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana-cloud/testing/testing/synthetic-monitoring/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;技术文档&lt;/a&gt;。您也可以探索&lt;a href =“ https://play.grafana.org/a/grafana-synthetic-monitoring-monitoring-monitoring-app/home?var-region=qul = $ ___________________哪个功能示例检查。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始合成监视的最简单方法。我们有一个宽敞的免费层，包括每月100k测试执行，以及更多。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insib-up/create-user？pg = plugins＆plcmt = grafana-synthetic-monoritoring-app-</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Managing access in Grafana: a single stack journey with teams, roles, and real-world patterns】管理Grafana的访问：带有团队，角色和现实世界模式的单个堆栈旅程</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/08/managing-access-in-grafana-a-single-stack-journey-with-teams-roles-and-real-world-patterns/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;When multiple teams use Grafana, it can start to feel a bit messy. Dashboards pile up, permissions become unclear, and teams accidentally overwrite each other’s work. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To help you and your organization stay clear, collaborative, and secure, we recommend putting all users in a single Grafana Cloud stack and managing access with teams, roles, and folders. To illustrate this, I&amp;rsquo;ll share a hypothetical example of how you can put this into practice across three teams. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;three-teams-one-stack&#34;&gt;Three teams, one stack&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let’s imagine that it’s Monday morning, and I’m sitting down with my coffee ready to start the work day. In this hypothetical, I&amp;rsquo;m part of the observability team serving an engineering organization of 50 people, and my goal today is to set up Grafana for our various engineering teams. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As part of this process, I want to reduce setup and maintenance work. I also want to make sure teams can access the right dashboards and data, avoid stepping on each other’s work, and still collaborate when needed. I do all of this in a single Grafana Cloud stack—no multi-stack complexity required.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In our setup, we have three teams:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team A&lt;/strong&gt; builds product features and needs autonomy with their own dashboards and data sources. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team B&lt;/strong&gt; handles data engineering and needs autonomy with their own dashboards.  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Team C&lt;/strong&gt; is our observability team (that’s us), and we act as admins of the Grafana stack.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: For the purpose of this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll focus on the steps you&amp;rsquo;d need to follow in Grafana Cloud. However, the same basic concepts can be followed in Grafana Enterprise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-create-the-stack&#34;&gt;1. Create the stack&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/security-and-account-management/cloud-stacks/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;a single stack&lt;/a&gt;, I get unified SSO, centralized configuration, and plugin management.  Equally important: Having everything under one stack means teams are not isolated in silos. They can discover each other’s dashboards, share work, and learn from one another. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When everyone works in a single stack, collaboration becomes much easier. A dashboard built by one team can be shared directly with others, without duplicating it across stacks. Teams can choose to open specific folders or dashboards, encouraging re-use and cross-learning while still maintaining ownership of their own work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shared spaces, like an “Everyone” folder, make it simple to publish executive dashboards or cross-team metrics that all groups can benefit from. And because everything lives in one environment, users are easily set up to adapt when teams reorganize, collaborate across groups, or swarm together on new projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-create-teams-and-their-folders&#34;&gt;2. Create teams and their folders&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I start by adding new users with the Viewer role &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-grafana/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#auto_assign_org_role&#34;&gt;by default&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a safe baseline: they can see everything, but they can&amp;rsquo;t change anything.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each team needs to be added to the same stack and to a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/team-management/configure-grafana-teams/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#create-a-grafana-team&#34;&gt;Grafana Team&lt;/a&gt;. To do this, I create a &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/dashboards/manage-dashboards/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#create-a-dashboard-folder&#34;&gt;folder&lt;/a&gt; for each team that they can manage and grant them the &lt;code&gt;fixed:teams:read&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/roles-and-permissions/access-control/rbac-fixed-basic-role-definitions/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#fixed-role-definitions&#34;&gt;fixed role&lt;/a&gt;.  This means they can share items in their team folder with other teams, to encourage collaboration and learning from each other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I upgrade Team C to the Admin role so that they can manage all resources in the instance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To encourage creativity while keeping things tidy, I create a personal folder for each team member that they can manage for drafting content and then moving it into their team folder when ready.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x697/b5243d5528/iam-teams-folders.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x697/b5243d5528/iam-teams-folders.png&#34;alt=&#34;Diagram showing Teams and folders in the stack, and the permissions Team A has been granted.&#34;title=&#34;Teams and folders in the stack, and the permissions Team A has been granted&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x697/b5243d5528/iam-teams-folders.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Diagram showing Teams and folders in the stack, and the permissions Team A has been granted.&#34;title=&#34;Teams and folders in the stack, and the permissions Team A has been granted&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;Teams and folders in the stack, and the permissions Team A has been granted&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-design-top-level-folder-structure&#34;&gt;3. Design top-level folder structure&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I will limit the number of top-level folders to keep things organized and secure. We will have an &amp;ldquo;Everyone&amp;rdquo; folder for shared items that all teams can manage, an &amp;ldquo;Admins&amp;rdquo; folder for sensitive content only we can access (Team C’s folder), and one folder per team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This setup helps users quickly understand where to go, what they can access, and what they can manage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x731/5bae6f18ed/iam-folder-structure.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x731/5bae6f18ed/iam-folder-structure.png&#34;alt=&#34;Diagram showing teams and folders in the stack, and the related admin permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;title=&#34;Teams and folders in the stack, and the related admin permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x731/5bae6f18ed/iam-folder-structure.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Diagram showing teams and folders in the stack, and the related admin permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;title=&#34;Teams and folders in the stack, and the related admin permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;Teams and folders in the stack, and the related admin permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-configure-data-access&#34;&gt;4. Configure data access &lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Next, I focus on how teams interact with data. All teams forward metrics to a shared database tenant, but not everyone should see all of the data. I create one shared metrics &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/connect-externally-hosted/data-sources/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#add-a-data-source&#34;&gt;data source&lt;/a&gt; and grant each team &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/data-source-management/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#assign-data-source-permissions-to-users-service-accounts-teams-or-roles&#34;&gt;query access&lt;/a&gt; only to their slice of the data, based on &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/data-source-management/teamlbac/create-teamlbac-rules/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#create-a-lbac-for-data-sources-rule-for-a-team&#34;&gt;label based access controls (LBAC) per team&lt;/a&gt;. This way, we maintain a central observability pipeline but still preserve data separation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I grant the &lt;code&gt;datasources:explorer&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/roles-and-permissions/access-control/rbac-fixed-basic-role-definitions/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#fixed-role-definitions&#34;&gt;fixed role&lt;/a&gt; to all teams so they can use the Drilldown app for easily exploring data sources.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Team A, however, needs to build and manage their own data sources for product-specific use cases. For them, I grant the &lt;code&gt;datasources:creator&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/roles-and-permissions/access-control/assign-rbac-roles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#assign-fixed-roles-in-the-ui-using-the-role-picker&#34;&gt;fixed role&lt;/a&gt; so they can create and manage their own data sources independently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x749/192046b141/iam-configure-data-access.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x749/192046b141/iam-configure-data-access.png&#34;alt=&#34;Diagram showing teams and data sources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;title=&#34;Teams and data sources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x749/192046b141/iam-configure-data-access.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;Diagram showing teams and data sources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;title=&#34;Teams and data sources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;Teams and data sources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-consider-non-folder-resources-and-stack-wide-permissions&#34;&gt;5. Consider non-folder resources and stack-wide permissions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not all Grafana resources live in folders. Service accounts, alert contact points, &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/fleet-management/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Fleet Management&lt;/a&gt; collectors, and other feature resources are managed at the stack level. For these, I check the role options in the team management UI and assign &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/roles-and-permissions/access-control/assign-rbac-roles/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#assign-fixed-roles-in-the-ui-using-the-role-picker&#34;&gt;fixed roles&lt;/a&gt; to teams carefully.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, I grant teams the &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observability/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Frontend Observability&lt;/a&gt; writer fixed role so that they can create and manage services.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1344/b011474747/iam-nonfolder-resources.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1344/b011474747/iam-nonfolder-resources.png&#34;alt=&#34;A diagram showing Frontend O11y resources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A have been granted.&#34;title=&#34;Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability resources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A have been granted.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1344/b011474747/iam-nonfolder-resources.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A diagram showing Frontend O11y resources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A have been granted.&#34;title=&#34;Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability resources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A have been granted.&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud Frontend Observability resources in the stack, and the related permissions Team A have been granted.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;6-scale-it-with-terraform-and-sso&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Scale it with Terraform and SSO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once the model is working, I codify it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All new users get added from an Identity Provider through &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-scim-provisioning/manage-users-teams/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#manage-users-and-teams-with-scim&#34;&gt;SCIM&lt;/a&gt; (I use Okta in this example). As they sync they are automatically assigned to the right team based on their Okta group membership. I use &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-authentication/saml/configure-saml-team-role-mapping/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt#configure-role-sync-for-saml&#34;&gt;role sync&lt;/a&gt; logic to assign the Admin role for our team instead of the default, which I’ve set to the Viewer role.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I use Terraform to provision teams their &lt;a href=&#34;https://registry.terraform.io/providers/grafana/grafana/latest/docs/resources/folder_permission&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;folders&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://registry.terraform.io/providers/grafana/grafana/latest/docs/resources/role_assignment&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;fixed roles&lt;/a&gt;, and shared datasource &lt;a href=&#34;https://registry.terraform.io/providers/grafana/grafana/latest/docs/resources/data_source_config_lbac_rules&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;LBAC rules&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s say I need to add a new team called Team D.  Now I’ll only need to push new Okta groups to Grafana and run my Terraform script, and then they’ll automatically be set up and ready to start using Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&#xA;class=&#34;figure-wrapper figure-wrapper__lightbox w-100p &#34;&#xA;style=&#34;max-width: none;&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34;&#xA;itemscope=&#34;&#34;&#xA;itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;a&#xA;class=&#34;lightbox-link captioned&#34;&#xA;href=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x760/2d66109666/iam-terraform-sso.png&#34;&#xA;itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&#xA;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;img-wrapper w-100p h-auto&#34;&gt;&lt;img&#xA;class=&#34;lazyload mb-0&#34;&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x760/2d66109666/iam-terraform-sso.png&#34;alt=&#34;A diagram showing the addition of Team D from Okta and automation of the rest of their IAM setup using Terraform&#34;title=&#34;Add new Team D from Okta and automate the rest of their IAM setup using Terraform&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;noscript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x760/2d66109666/iam-terraform-sso.png&#34;&#xA;alt=&#34;A diagram showing the addition of Team D from Okta and automation of the rest of their IAM setup using Terraform&#34;title=&#34;Add new Team D from Okta and automate the rest of their IAM setup using Terraform&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class=&#34;w-100p caption text-gray-13 &#34;&gt;Add new Team D from Okta and automate the rest of their IAM setup using Terraform&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;where-to-go-from-here&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where to go from here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Getting access and permissions right in Grafana is one of the best ways to unlock its full potential. With the right structure in place, teams can collaborate more easily, stay secure without extra overhead, and build on each other’s work instead of starting from scratch. To really get a deeper understanding of these ideas, here are a few resources that can help.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2024/09/10/grafana-access-management-how-to-use-teams-for-seamless-user-and-permission-management/&#34;&gt;least privilege custom role explainer blog&lt;/a&gt; walks through how to design roles that keep things simple and safe, so people have just the access they need. My &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gj27qKPSVsM&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;LBAC for metrics data sources demo&lt;/a&gt; shows how you can give every team a clear view of their own data while still benefiting from a shared pipeline. And our &lt;a href=&#34;/blog/2025/05/14/introducing-scim-provisioning-in-grafana-enterprise-grade-user-management-made-simple/&#34;&gt;introducing SCIM blog&lt;/a&gt; covers how to connect Grafana to your identity provider, making it easy to bring new users on board and keep permissions in sync as your organization grows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, these resources will help you put the single-stack model into practice and set your teams up to get the very most from Grafana.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;当多个团队使用Grafana时，它可能会感到有些混乱。仪表板堆积，权限变得不清楚，团队不小心覆盖了彼此的工作。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了帮助您和您的组织保持清晰，协作和安全，我们建议将所有用户放入一个Grafana Cloud堆栈中，并使用团队，角色和文件夹来管理访问权限。为了说明这一点，我将分享一个假设的例子，说明如何在三个团队中将其付诸实践。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们潜入！&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“三支球队 - 一堆”&gt;三支球队，一个堆栈&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;让我们想象是星期一早上，我准备好坐在工作日开始的咖啡。在这个假设的情况下，我是为有50人组成的工程组织服务的可观察性团队的一部分，今天我的目标是为我们的各个工程团队建立Grafana。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;作为此过程的一部分，我想减少设置和维护工作。我还想确保团队可以访问正确的仪表板和数据，避免踏上彼此的工作，并在需要时进行协作。我在一个Grafana Cloud堆栈中完成所有这些，而无需多堆的复杂性。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在我们的设置中，我们有三个团队：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;团队A &lt;/strong&gt;通过自己的仪表板和数据源来构建产品功能，并且需要自主权。 &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;团队B &lt;/strong&gt;处理数据工程，并需要使用自己的仪表板自治。  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;团队C &lt;/strong&gt;是我们的观察力团队（就是我们），我们充当Grafana堆栈的管理员。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;BlockQuote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;注意：就本博客文章而言，我们将重点介绍您在Grafana Cloud中需要遵循的步骤。但是，在Grafana Enterprise中可以遵循相同的基本概念。 &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ 1-Create-the-stack”&gt; 1。创建堆栈&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;使用&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/security-and-account-managements/cloud-stacks/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;一个堆栈&lt;/a&gt;，我得到了统一的SSO，集中配置和插件管理。  同样重要的是：在一个堆栈之下，所有东西都意味着团队在孤岛中并不孤立。他们可以发现彼此的仪表板，分享工作并互相学习。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当每个人在一个堆栈中工作时，协作变得更加容易。一个团队建造的仪表板可以直接与他人共享，而无需跨堆栈重复。团队可以选择打开特定的文件夹或仪表板，鼓励重新使用和交叉学习，同时仍保持自己的工作所有权。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;共享的空间，例如“每个人”文件夹，使发布所有团体都可以从中受益的执行仪表板或跨团队指标变得容易。而且，由于所有事物都生活在一个环境中，因此在团队重组，跨小组合作或在新项目上群体时，很容易设置用户。&lt;/p&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ 2-Create-Teams and-the-The-Er-Folders”&gt; 2。创建团队及其文件夹&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我首先将新用户添加使用查看器角色&lt;a href =“/doc/grafana/最新/setup-grafana/configure-grafana/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt＃auto_assign_org_role”&gt;默认情况下&lt;/a&gt;。这是一个安全的基准：他们可以看到一切，但他们不能改变任何东西。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;需要将每个团队添加到同一堆栈中，然后添加到&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/grafana/最终/管理/团队管理/配置grafana-teams/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt＃create-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-agrafana-team”&gt; grafana team &lt;/a&gt;。为此，我创建a &lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最终/dashboards/manage-dashboards/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt＃create-a-dashboard-folder”&gt;文件夹“&gt;文件夹”&gt;文件夹&lt;/a&gt;对于他们可以管理并授予他们的团队并授予他们的&lt;code&gt; filect&gt; preecs&gt; preecs&gt; &lt;/code&gt; age &lt;/code&gt; &lt;a &lt;/code&gt; &lt;a &lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最终/管理/roles-and-permissions/access-control/rbac-fixed-basic-basic-lole-definitions/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-plcmt = body-txt＃固定 - 固定 - 固定 - 定义”&gt;固定角色&lt;/a&gt;。  这意味着他们可以在团队文件夹中与其他团队共享项目，以鼓励彼此合作和学习。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我将C团队C升级为管理员角色，以便他们可以在实例中管理所有资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;为了鼓励创造力在保持整洁的同时，我为每个团队成员创建一个个人文件夹，他们可以管理起草内容，然后在准备就绪时将其移至他们的团队文件夹中。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x697/b5243d5528/iam-teams-folders.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x697/b5243d5528/iam-teams-folders.png&#34;alt=&#34;Diagram showing Teams and folders in the stack, and the permissions Team A has been granted.&#34;title=&#34;Teams and folders in the stack, and the permissions Team A has been授予“/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x697/b5243d5528/iam-teams-folders.png”&#xA;alt =“堆栈中显示团队和文件夹的图表，并且A级许可团队A都被授予。” Title =“堆栈中的团队和文件夹，并且许可团队A已获得A/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noScript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ W-100P字幕Text-Gray-13”&gt;堆栈中的团队和文件夹，并且权限团队A已获得&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&lt;H2 ID =“ 3-Design-Top级别的折线结构”&gt; 3。设计顶级文件夹结构&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我将限制顶级文件夹的数量，以保持井井有条和安全。我们将为所有团队都能管理的共享项目提供一个“每个人”文件夹，只有我们可以访问的敏感内容的“管理员”文件夹（团队C的文件夹）和每个团队的一个文件夹。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;此设置可帮助用户快速了解去哪里，他们可以访问什么以及他们可以管理什么。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;英石yle =“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x731/5bae6f18ed/iam-folder-sstructure.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src=&#34;https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x731/5bae6f18ed/iam-folder-structure.png&#34;alt=&#34;Diagram showing teams and folders in the stack, and the related admin permissions Team A and Team B have been granted&#34;title=&#34;Teams and folders in the stack, and the related admin permissions Team A and Team b已被授予“/&gt;”&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x731/5bae6f18ed/iam-folder-sstructure.png”&#xA;alt =“堆栈中显示团队和文件夹的图，以及相关的管理许可团队A和B团队已获得“标题=”堆栈中的团队和文件夹，相关的管理许可团队A和B团队B已获得”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ W-100P字幕text-gray-13”&gt;堆栈中的团队和文件夹，相关的管理权限团队A和B团队B已获得&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figic&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ 4- configure-data-access”&gt; 4。配置数据访问&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;接下来，我关注团队如何与数据互动。所有团队都将指标转发到共享数据库租户，但并非每个人都应该看到所有数据。我创建一个共享指标&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/connect-externally-externelly-data-sources/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt＃add-a-data-source”&gt; data source&gt; data source&#39;&gt; data source &lt;/a&gt;并授予每个团队&lt;a &lt;a &lt;a &lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最新/管理/数据源管理/？ href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/data-source-management/teamlbac/create-teamlbac-rules/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt#create-a-lbac-for-data-sources-rule-for-a-team&#34;&gt;label based access controls (LBAC) per team&lt;/a&gt;.这样，我们维护中心可观察性管道，但仍保留数据分离。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我授予&lt;code&gt; dataSources：explorer &lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href =“/docs/docs/grafana/grafana/最终/管理/roles-and-permissions/access-control/rbac-fixed-bac-fix-bac-fix-bas-lole-definitions/？探索数据源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;但是，A团队A需要为特定于产品的用例构建和管理自己的数据源。 For them, I grant the &lt;code&gt;datasources:creator&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/roles-and-permissions/access-control/assign-rbac-roles/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt#assign-fixed-roles-in-the-ui-using-the-role-picker&#34;&gt;fixed role&lt;/a&gt; so they can create and manage their own data sources独立。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http：//schema.org/imageObject“&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x749/192046b141/iam-configure-data-access.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/199999x749/192046b141/iam-configure-data-access.png” alt =“ alt =”图表，显示了团队和数据源的团队和团队的团队，并与之相关的数据，并与之相关的数据=``标题&#39;&#39;和Statik and start sip nation and toption and toption native of titter Inters sip。许可团队A和B团队已被授予“/&gt;”&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/199999X749/192046B141/IAM-CONFIGURE-DATA-ACCESS.PNG”&#xA;alt =“堆栈中显示团队和数据源的图，以及相关的权限团队A和B团队被授予“ title =”堆栈中的团队和数据源，相关的权限团队A和B团队B已获得”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ W-100P字幕text-gray-13”&gt;堆栈中的团队和数据源，并且已授予了相关的权限团队A和B团队B &lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/fige&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id =“ 5-辅助者 - 折叠式资源和堆叠范围的遍布”&gt; 5。考虑非档案资源和堆栈范围的权限&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;并非所有Grafana资源都活在文件夹中。服务帐户，警报联系点，&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana-cloud/send-data/fleet-management/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt;车队管理&lt;/a&gt;收藏家，其他功能资源在堆栈级别进行管理。 For these, I check the role options in the team management UI and assign &lt;a href=&#34;/docs/grafana/latest/administration/roles-and-permissions/access-control/assign-rbac-roles/?pg=blog&amp;plcmt=body-txt#assign-fixed-roles-in-the-ui-using-the-role-picker&#34;&gt;fixed roles&lt;/a&gt; to teams carefully.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;例如，我授予团队&lt;a href =“/doc/grafana-cloud/monitor-applications/frontend-observipity/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt; frontend可观察性&lt;/a&gt;作者&lt;/a&gt;作者固定角色，以便他们可以创建和管理服务。  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999X1344/B011474747/IAM-NONONFOLDER-RESOURCES.PNG”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x1344/b011474747/iam-nonfolder-resources.png” Alt =“ Alt =” Alt =“显示了堆栈中的前端资源，以及相关的Permistions and Prestions and the STACK and the STACK and the Station and Strencand and thit stity =“标题”。相关权限团队已被授予。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999X1344/B011474747/IAM-NONONFOLDER-RESOURCES.PNG”&#xA;alt =“堆栈中显示前端o11y资源的图，并且已授予了相关权限团队。” title =“ Grafana堆栈中的云前端可观察性资源以及相关的权限团队已授予。”/&gt;&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ W-100P字幕Text-Gray-13”&gt; Grafana Cloud cloud前端可观察性资源，并且已授予了相关的权限团队。&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“ 6级 -  it-with-with-with-with-sso”&gt; &lt;strong&gt; 6。用Terraform和SSO &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;缩放它&#xA;&lt;p&gt;模型工作后，我将其编纂。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;所有新用户都会通过&lt;a href =“/doc/grafana/最终/setup-grafana/configure-security/configure-scim-provisioning/manage-users-teams/？pg = blog＆plcmt = bogl＆plcmt = body-users-users-users-and-users-and-teams-with-scim with-scim&gt; accim oke oke &lt;/a&gt;当他们同步时，他们会根据其Okta组成员自动分配给合适的团队。我使用&lt;a href =“/docs/grafana/最新/设置/设置/配置/configure-security/configure-authentication/saml/configure-saml-saml-team-role-mapple/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body＆plcmt = body-txt＃configure-sync-sync-for-sync-for-saml“角色。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我使用Terraform来提供他们的&lt;a href =“ https://registry.terraform.io/providers/grafana/grafana/grafana/grafana/grafana/latest/docs/docs/resources/folder_perristion/folder_permistion” target =“ _ black” href =“ https://registry.io/providers/grafana/grafana/grafana/latest/latest/docs/Resources/Role_Assignment” target =“ _ blank” rel =“ noopener noreferrer” href =“ https://registry.terraform.io/providers/grafana/grafana/grafana/latest/docs/resources/data_source_source_config_lbac_rules” target =“ _ black” &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;假设我需要添加一个名为D的新团队D。现在，我只需要将新的Okta组推向Grafana并运行我的Terraform脚本，然后他们将自动设置并准备好使用Grafana。&lt;/p&gt;。&#xA;&lt;图&#xA;class =“ figup-wrapper figuper-wrapper__lightbox W-100P”&#xA;样式=“最大宽度：无;”&#xA;itemprop =“ iSsectedmedia”&#xA;itemScope =“”&#xA;itemType =“ http://schema.org/imageObject”&#xA;&gt; &lt;a&#xA;class =“ Lightbox-Link字幕”&#xA;href =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x760/2d66109666/iam--terraform-sso.png”&#xA;itemprop =“ contenturl”&#xA;&gt; &lt;div class =“ img-wrapper W-100P H-auto”&gt; &lt;img&#xA;class =“ Lazyload MB-0”&#xA;data-src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/1999x760/2d66109666/iam--terraform-sso.png” Alt =“ Alt =” Alt =“显示了D团队D的添加到OKTA中的D团队的添加和使用Terra Restum的自动化的New tera new Terra and of Terra and of Terra and of Terra and tera ntar and tera n tita tita =” title =&#39;titar =&#39;tita =&#39;使用Terraform“/&gt;进行设置&#xA;&lt;NoScript&gt;&#xA;&lt;img&#xA;src =“ https://a-us.storyblok.com/f/1022730/19999x760/2d66109666/iam--terraform-sso.png”&#xA;alt =“显示了OKTA的D团队D的添加以及使用Terraform的其余IAM设置自动化” title =“添加Okta的新团队D。&#xA;&lt;/noscript&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;figcaption class =“ W-100P字幕文本grAY-13“&gt;添加Okta的新团队D，并使用Terraform &lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figie&gt;自动化其其余的IAM设置&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“从here-from-here”&gt; &lt;strong&gt;从这里去哪里&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Grafana中获得访问权限和权限是解锁其全部潜力的最佳方法之一。有了正确的结构，团队可以更轻松地协作，保持安全而无需额外的开销，并以彼此的工作为基础而不是从头开始。为了真正了解这些想法，这里有一些可以帮助的资源。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的&lt;p&gt; href =“/blog/2024/09/10/grafana-access-management-how-to-how-to-how-to-to-for-seam-seam-seam-user-user-and-persimersion-crise-management/“&gt;最低特权自定义角色blog Blog &lt;/a&gt;步行&lt;/a&gt;漫游&lt;/a&gt;浏览如何使事物保持简单和安全的角色，因此人们可以访问这些角色，因此人们可以使用访问权限。我的&lt;a href =“ https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gj27qkpsvsm” target =“ _ black” rel =“ noopener noreferrer”&gt; lbac for Meterrics数据源demo demo demo demo &lt;/a&gt;显示您如何使每个团队都能清晰地从共享数据中造福他们的数据，同时还可以使自己的数据保持在同时的管道中。和我们的&lt;a href =“/blog/2025/05/14/介绍 -  scim-provisioning in-grafana-enterprise grade-grade-user-user-user-management-made-made-simple/”&gt;介绍scim blog &lt;/a&gt;涵盖如何将grafana连接到您的身份提供者，使其易于将新的用户连接到您的董事会上，并将其与您的董事会保持范围，并保持&lt;/comply &lt;/comply &lt;/comply &lt;/novery &lt;/&#xA;&lt;p&gt;综上所述，这些资源将帮助您将单栈模型付诸实践，并使您的团队从Grafana中获得最大的收益。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个宽敞的永远的层次和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/insip/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tiger teams: How we tackle urgent, cross-functional challenges at Grafana Labs】老虎队：我们如何应对Grafana Labs的紧急，跨职能挑战</title>
      <link>https://grafana.com/blog/2025/09/05/tiger-teams-how-we-tackle-urgent-cross-functional-challenges-at-grafana-labs/</link>
      <description>【&lt;p&gt;A year ago, we hit a wall. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our Grafana OSS releases were excruciating to execute. The process was confusing and hard to follow, security patches were non-trivial, and many engineering hours were lost to an overly manual process. We needed to move fast, cut through ambiguity, and pull in just the right people without waiting on roadmaps or org charts. That’s when I pitched the idea of forming the first ever &amp;ldquo;tiger team&amp;rdquo; at Grafana Labs, a small and focused group designed to tackle high-priority, cross-functional problems with speed and clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A year later, tiger teams have greatly improved the release cycle process, and they&amp;rsquo;ve quickly become our go-to model for tackling urgent, high-impact issues that don’t fit neatly into a single team’s backlog. In this post, I’ll share what tiger teams are, examples of how we’ve used this model at Grafana Labs, hard lessons learned along the way, and my recommended best practices.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you&amp;rsquo;re facing a deep technical challenge, landing a major deal, or just need a way to unblock cross-functional work, I hope our approach gives you a few ideas to take back to your own organization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-a-tiger-team&#34;&gt;What is a tiger team?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The term &amp;ldquo;tiger team&amp;rdquo; &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tiger_team#Origin_of_the_term&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34;&gt;originated at NASA&lt;/a&gt; in the 1960s during the Apollo 13 mission. In Walter C. Williams’ paper, &amp;ldquo;Program Management in Design and Development,&amp;rdquo; the NASA Manned Spacecraft Center engineer defined a tiger team as a &amp;ldquo;team of undomesticated and uninhibited technical specialists, selected for their experience, energy, and imagination, and assigned to track down relentlessly every possible source of failure in a spacecraft subsystem or simulation.&amp;ldquo;​&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This approach was put to the test when an explosion in the spacecraft&amp;rsquo;s service module put the lives of the Apollo 13 astronauts in jeopardy. NASA&amp;rsquo;s flight director Gene Kranz assembled a group of specialists, later dubbed the tiger team, to find a way to safely return the astronauts to Earth. The success of this effort proved how powerful a temporary cross-functional team of experts can be when united by urgency and a singular focus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Grafana Labs, we use the tiger team model to tackle complex, time-sensitive challenges that our org structure is not currently set up to handle. Unlike traditional engineering teams, which are often organized around long-term product areas or services, tiger teams are temporary, goal-oriented groups formed to address specific issues. They are typically composed of three to five specialized engineers, and they last for one to two quarters, or until the targeted goal is reached. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;a-grafana-labs-example-the-release-tiger-team&#34;&gt;A Grafana Labs example: The Release Tiger Team&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking back at that wall we hit a year ago with releasing Grafana, the formation of the Release Tiger Team marked a turning point. At the time the challenges we faced didn’t fall neatly within the scope of any single team. Ownership was ambiguous, and the expertise needed to fix our build and release pipelines was scattered across the org. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We brought together engineers from different teams who had the right mix of experience in CI/CD, and deep familiarity with our systems. These were the engineers that had been vocal about the problems, already hacking at them on the side, and were best positioned to drive real change. We banded together, blatantly ignoring our current organizational structures to focus solely on the one unified goal of fixing our build and release pipelines. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our company had put trust in us that we could deliver on this goal in a single quarter. We were a team of just three senior engineers, with myself as lead. I soon realized we needed laser focus to achieve this on such a short timescale. I drafted a roadmap with three major milestones: simplify the release process, add the ability to patch our Grafana Cloud release channels directly, and fully automate our builds. With this plan in place, we got to work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;tiger-team-take-2&#34;&gt;Tiger team, take 2&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, the problem with the best laid plans is that they never go exactly as expected. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We tried our best to stay singularly focused on our goals, but there were still releases that needed our immediate attention. This included unexpected security releases that quarter, and those releases had their own unique issues that needed our expertise to fix. This took valuable time away from our project, but also served as a real-world user test that highlighted our most critical issues, and what was most urgent for us to address. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We reorganized and rallied behind our first milestone to simplify our release process by reducing the amount of manual, and thus error prone, steps involved. Originally responsibilities were too fragmented, and no single team had clear ownership of the release process. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taking a critical look at who was actually doing the work, who understood the system best, and who had the drive to fix it, we restructured engineers from various teams into this singularly focused tiger team, cutting across squads and reporting lines while doing so. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These engineers knew how the current release process worked, where steps could be combined, what documentation was missing, how we built and packaged the release artifacts, and where the pipelines most commonly failed. With this, we had the momentum we needed to move quickly and make meaningful progress.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the quarter came to a close we had drastically reduced the manual steps involved in our release process. The engineers running the releases did so effectively and independently, and suddenly security releases were not so intimidating. We even made good progress on our other milestones, such as Grafana Cloud version patching. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But then what? Our tiger team was set to dissolve at the end of the quarter, so what did that mean for the work still outstanding, or the tooling we had built? Who would own this moving forward? Thankfully, due to the success of the Release Tiger Team, we were able to advocate for a full-time dedicated team that would continue to iterate on our release issues and take full ownership in this area.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, this is not always possible—or even advisable. Our team fit a specific, long-term need, so it made sense to keep it around. But if your tiger team has achieved its goal and no longer serves a purpose, then it can be dissolved and everyone can return to their normal responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-can-you-run-effective-tiger-teams&#34;&gt;How can you run effective tiger teams?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Running effective tiger teams is a delicate act, and it requires some forethought. I can only speak from my experience with the Release Tiger Team, and other tiger teams we have since created. However, I did learn some valuable lessons in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be strategic.&lt;/strong&gt; Be more strategic than you even think you need to be. Prioritize, and reprioritize, and reduce your ambitions down to a single laser-focused goal. With this goal you should be able to say: If this is all we achieved, our mission was still successful.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get the right people.&lt;/strong&gt; The power of tiger teams is that you can pull people to your cause regardless of the constraints of existing organizational and team structures. You have high priority needs, ambitious goals, and a short amount of time to execute on them. None of this is possible without the right people by your side.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Define the end state at the beginning.&lt;/strong&gt; When is the tiger team complete? When can the people involved go back to their original teams? What happens to the code, tooling, features, or processes that were created? Who will own these long-term? Don’t wait for the project to end to find this out. The sooner these can be laid out in the process the better. No one wants their project suddenly dropped or thrown over the wall at someone else.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In closing, I hope my own journey in this space has offered you some insight. Tiger teams are a powerful tool for rallying to solve critical failures, or land big deals, or address systemic issues that otherwise cannot be solved within the existing organizational structure of the company. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We at Grafana have continued to lean into the power of tiger teams. Another of our tiger teams successfully landed a big Fortune 500 technology partner, and yet another is trailblazing greenfield opportunities that could expand our offerings. What can a tiger team accomplish at your company?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/products/cloud/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Grafana Cloud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;is the easiest way to get started with metrics, logs, traces, dashboards, and more. We have a generous forever-free tier and plans for every use case.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/auth/sign-up/create-user/?pg=blog&amp;amp;plcmt=body-txt&#34;&gt;Sign up for free now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;】&lt;p&gt;一年前，我们撞墙了。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的Grafana OSS版本令人难以置信。该过程令人困惑，很难遵循，安全补丁是非平凡的，并且许多工程时间都因手动过度流程而丢失了。我们需要快速移动，削减歧义，并吸引恰到好处的人，而无需等待路线图或组织图表。那时，我提出了在Grafana Labs组成有史以来第一个“老虎团队”的想法，Grafana Labs是一个小型而专注的小组，旨在解决高优先级，跨功能问题的速度和清晰度。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一年后，老虎团队大大改善了发行周期的过程，并且很快就成为我们解决紧急，高影响力问题的首选模式，这些问题并不完全适合单个团队的积压。在这篇文章中，我将分享什么是老虎团队，示例我们如何在Grafana Labs使用此模型，一路上学到了艰难的教训，以及我推荐的最佳实践。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;无论您是面临着深厚的技术挑战，达成重大交易，还是只需要一种解开跨职能工作的方法，我希望我们的方法能给您一些想法，可以带回自己的组织。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“什么是老虎队”&gt;什么是老虎队？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;术语“老虎团队” &lt;a href =“ https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/wiki/tiger_team/team/team/team#origin_of_term_term“ target =” _ black“ rel =” noopener noreferrer“&gt;在1​​960年代在NASA &lt;/a&gt;中，在1960年代的Apollo 13 Mission。在沃尔特·C·威廉姆斯（Walter C. Williams）的论文中，“设计与开发计划管理”，NASA载有航天器中心工程师将一支老虎团队定义为“一支由未营造的和不受欢迎的技术专家组成的团队，他们为他们的经验，精力和想象力而被选中，并分配了无与伦比的所有可能的失败来源，以无限地跟踪Spacececraft Supsedystem或Simulation of Spacececraft Supsedem或Simpulation of Sypleulation或Simulation。&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当航天器的服务模块中的爆炸使阿波罗13宇航员的生命陷入困境时，这种方法进行了测试。美国宇航局的飞行总监吉恩·克兰兹（Gene Kranz）组建了一群专家，后来被称为老虎队，以找到一种安全将宇航员归还地球的方法。这项努力的成功证明了一个临时的跨职能专家团队在紧迫感和一个单一的重点时会多么强大。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;在Grafana Labs，我们使用Tiger Team模型来应对目前尚未设置组织的组织结构的复杂，时间敏感的挑战。与通常围绕长期产品区域或服务组织的传统工程团队不同，老虎团队是临时的，面向目标的小组，以解决特定问题。它们通常由三到五名专业工程师组成，并且持续一到两个季度，或者直到达到目标目标为止。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“ a-grafana-labs-示例 - 释放 - 老虎队”&gt; grafana Labs示例：发行Tiger Team &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;回头看那堵墙，我们一年前打了释放Grafana的释放Tiger Team的形成标志着一个转折点。当时，我们面临的挑战并没有整齐地落在任何一支球队的范围之内。所有权是模棱两可的，修复我们的构建和释放管道所需的专业知识散布在组织中。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们将来自不同团队的工程师汇集在一起​​，他们在CI/CD方面具有正确的经验，并且对我们的系统非常熟悉。这些工程师一直在发声问题，已经在侧面攻击了他们，并且最好是推动真正的变化。我们团结起来，公然忽略了当前的组织结构，只专注于修复我们的构建和释放管道的一个统一目标。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们的公司对我们可以在一个季度内实现这一目标信任。我们是一支由三名高级工程师组成的团队，我自己是领导者。我很快意识到，我们需要激光专注于如此短的时间表。我起草了一个具有三个主要里程碑的路线图：简化发布过程，添加直接修补Grafana Cloud释放频道的能力，并完全自动化我们的构建。有了这个计划，我们开始工作。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;H3 ID =“ Tiger-Team-Take-2”&gt; Tiger Team，取2 &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当然，最佳计划的问题是它们永远不会完全按预期进行。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们尽力保持专注于我们的目标，但仍然有一些释放需要我们立即关注。这包括该季度的意外安全性发布，这些发行版具有自己的独特问题，需要我们的专业知识来解决。这花费了宝贵的时间，但也充当了现实世界中的用户测试，突出了我们最关键的问题，以及最迫切需要解决的问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们通过减少涉及的步骤，重新组织并集结了第一个里程碑，以减少手动数量，从而简化释放过程，从而简化我们的释放过程。最初的责任太分散了，没有一支团队对发行过程有明确的所有权。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;批判性地看着谁实际上正在做这项工作，谁最了解系统，谁有修复该系统的人，我们将各个团队的工程师重组为这个奇特的小型老虎团队，在这样做的同时跨越了小队和报告线路。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;这些工程师知道当前发布过程如何工作，可以将步骤组合起来，缺少哪些文档，我们如何构建和打包释放工件以及最常见的管道中最常见的地方。这样，我们拥有需要快速行动并取得有意义进步的动力。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;当季度结束时，我们大大减少了发行过程中涉及的手动步骤。运行发行版的工程师如此有效，独立地做到了，突然安全版本并没有那么令人生畏。我们甚至在其他里程碑上取得了良好的进步，例如Grafana C大声版本修补。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是那是什么？我们的老虎团队将在本季度结束时解散，那么这对于仍然出色的工作或我们建造的工具意味着什么？谁能拥有这个前进？值得庆幸的是，由于发行老虎团队的成功，我们能够为一个全职专用团队倡导，该团队将继续迭代我们的发行问题并在该领域获得全部所有权。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;但是，这并不总是可能的，甚至不可能。我们的团队满足了特定的长期需求，因此保持围绕它是有意义的。但是，如果您的老虎团队实现了目标，并且不再有目的，那么它可以解散，每个人都可以恢复正常的责任。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id =“如何运行您运行的老虎队”&gt;您如何运行有效的老虎队？&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;运行有效的老虎团队是一种微妙的举动，它需要一些前瞻性。我只能根据发行老虎团队以及我们创建的其他老虎团队的经验。但是，我确实在此过程中学习了一些有价值的教训。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;具有战略性。&lt;/strong&gt;比您认为您需要的更具战略意义。优先考虑，重新定位，并将您的野心降低到一个以激光为中心的目标。有了这个目标，您应该能够说：如果这是我们所取得的全部成就，我们的使命仍然成功。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;得到合适的人。&lt;/strong&gt;老虎团队的力量是，无论现有组织和团队结构的限制如何，您都可以将人们拉到您的事业上。您有很高的优先级需求，雄心勃勃的目标以及对他们执行的时间很短的时间。如果没有合适的人，这是不可能的。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;在开始时定义终端状态。&lt;/strong&gt;老虎队何时完成？涉及的人什么时候可以回到他们的原始团队？创建的代码，工具，功能或过程会发生什么？谁将拥有这些长期？不要等待该项目结束才能找到这个问题。这些过程越早可以在此过程中布置越好。没有人希望他们的项目突然掉落或扔在别人的墙上。&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;结束时，我希望我自己在这个领域的旅程为您提供了一些见识。老虎团队是解决重大失败或大量交易的强大工具，或解决否则在公司现有组织结构中无法解决的系统性问题。 &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;我们在格拉法纳（Grafana）继续依靠老虎队的力量。我们的另一个老虎团队成功地建立了一个大型财富500技术合作伙伴，而另一个是开拓性的绿地机会，可以扩大我们的产品。老虎团队可以在贵公司完成什么？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/products/cloud/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt”&gt; grafana cloud &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;是开始使用指标，日志，痕迹，仪表，仪表板等最简单的方法。我们有一个慷慨的每种用例的越来越级别和计划。&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt; &lt;a href =“/auth/auth/nig-up/create-user/？pg = blog＆plcmt = body-txt = body-txt”&gt;现在免费注册！&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>