<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>&lt;![CDATA[ Gremlin RSS Feed ]]&gt;</title>
    <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/rss.xml</link>
    <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Prevent outages, innovate faster, and earn customer trust with Gremlin’s Reliability Management and Chaos Engineering platform. ]]&gt;</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Interpreting your reliability test results】解释您的可靠性测试结果</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/interpreting-your-reliability-test-results</link>
      <description>【You’ve run your reliability tests and got your results…now what? This blog explains how to turn your insights into actions and, ultimately, into more reliable services.】您已经运行了可靠性测试并得到了结果……现在怎么办？该博客解释了如何将您的见解转化为行动，并最终转化为更可靠的服务。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reliable AI models, simulations, and more with Gremlin&#39;s GPU experiment】通过 Gremlin 的 GPU 实验实现可靠的 AI 模型、模拟等</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/how-gremlins-gpu-experiment-makes-ai-models-simulations-and-video-encoding-more-resilient</link>
      <description>【Build more resilient machine learning and AI models, video streaming, simulations, and more with Gremlin’s GPU experiment.】利用 Gremlin 的 GPU 实验构建更具弹性的机器学习和 AI 模型、视频流、模拟等。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Seven tests to measure and improve reliability: what matters and how it works】衡量和提高可靠性的七项测试：重要因素及其工作原理</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/four-reliability-tests</link>
      <description>【Learn how to take reliability from a &#34;nice to have&#34; to a standard operating practice within your organization. We&#39;ll show you seven easy tests you can use to start building resilient systems.】了解如何将可靠性从“可有可无”转变为组织内的标准操作实践。我们将向您展示七个可用于开始构建弹性系统的简单测试。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Best Practices for Testing Zone Redundancy】测试区冗余的最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/best-practices-for-testing-zone-redundancy</link>
      <description>【Gremlin Principal Software Engineer Sam Rossoff shares key best practices and strategies for effectively testing zone redundancy.】Gremlin 首席软件工程师 Sam Rossoff 分享了有效测试区域冗余的关键最佳实践和策略。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How reliability engineering can verify disaster recovery plans】可靠性工程如何验证灾难恢复计划</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/how-reliability-engineering-can-verify-disaster-recovery-plans</link>
      <description>【Learn how reliability engineering and Gremlin can help test your disaster recovery plans to make sure you’re prepared—and compliant with regulations.】了解可靠性工程和 Gremlin 如何帮助测试您的灾难恢复计划，以确保您做好准备并遵守法规。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Three serverless reliability risks you can solve today using Failure Flags】您现在可以使用故障标志解决三个无服务器可靠性风险</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/three-serverless-reliability-risks-you-can-solve-today-using-failure-flags</link>
      <description>【Just because your app is serverless doesn’t mean you don’t need to think about reliability. Learn three of the top causes of serverless failures—and how to prevent them—in our latest blog.】仅仅因为您的应用程序是无服务器的，并不意味着您不需要考虑可靠性。在我们最新的博客中了解无服务器故障的三个主要原因以及如何预防它们。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Release Roundup August 2024: Set experiment guardrails with customizable RBAC】2024 年 8 月发布综述：使用可定制的 RBAC 设置实验护栏</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/release-roundup-august-2024</link>
      <description>【Custom role-based access controls (RBAC), improved proxy support, zone tags for Failure Flags, and much more! It’s all here in our August 2024 release roundup.】自定义基于角色的访问控制 (RBAC)、改进的代理支持、故障标志的区域标签等等！这一切都在我们的 2024 年 8 月版本综述中。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Now in private beta: Gremlin Service Mesh Extension】现在处于私人测试版：Gremlin Service Mesh Extension</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/private-beta-gremlin-service-mesh-extension</link>
      <description>【Find out how to safely test applications and services behind service meshes with the Gremlin Service Mesh Extension.】了解如何使用 Gremlin 服务网格扩展安全地测试服务网格背后的应用程序和服务。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Chaos Engineering and Resilience Testing Tools: Build vs Buy】混沌工程和弹性测试工具：构建与购买</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/chaos-engineering-tools-build-vs-buy</link>
      <description>【Not sure whether you should build or buy a Fault Injection tool for Chaos Engineering and resilience testing? Check out the pros and cons of building vs buying.】不确定是否应该构建或购买用于混沌工程和弹性测试的故障注入工具？查看建造与购买的优缺点。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Release Roundup November 2024: Reliability in the serverless and AI era】2024 年 11 月发布综述：无服务器和人工智能时代的可靠性</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/release-roundup-november-2024-reliability-in-the-serverless-and-ai-era</link>
      <description>【A review of the major product and feature releases from September to November 2024, including Service Mesh via Failure Flags, AWS PrivateLink in Marketplace, RM &amp; FI scheduling improvements, and agent updates.】对 2024 年 9 月至 11 月主要产品和功能版本的回顾，包括通过故障标志的服务网格、Marketplace 中的 AWS PrivateLink、RM 和 FI 调度改进以及代理更新。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>