<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>&lt;![CDATA[ Gremlin RSS Feed ]]&gt;</title>
    <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/rss.xml</link>
    <description>&lt;![CDATA[ Prevent outages, innovate faster, and earn customer trust with Gremlin’s Reliability Management and Chaos Engineering platform. ]]&gt;</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Reliability lessons from the 2025 AWS DynamoDB outage】2025 年 AWS DynamoDB 中断带来的可靠性教训</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/reliability-lessons-from-the-2025-aws-dynamodb-outage</link>
      <description>【In October 2025, Amazon DynamoDB had a massive outage that took down hundreds of systems. Find out what your team can do to minimize the impact of similar outages in the future.】2025 年 10 月，Amazon DynamoDB 发生大规模停机，导致数百个系统瘫痪。了解您的团队可以采取哪些措施来最大程度地减少未来类似中断的影响。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Gremlin’s KubeCon ‘25 reliability track】Gremlin 的 KubeCon ‘25 可靠性轨道</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/gremlins-kubecon-25-reliability-track</link>
      <description>【Check out the Gremlin-curated unofficial track of reliability talks at KubeCon North America 2025.】查看 Gremlin 在 2025 年 KubeCon 北美会议上策划的非官方可靠性会谈。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to test the reliability of a Point of Sale (POS) system】如何测试销售点 (POS) 系统的可靠性</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/how-to-test-the-reliability-of-a-point-of-sale-pos-system</link>
      <description>【Find out how to use Gremlin and Chaos Engineering to make sure your Point of Sale system is reliable.】了解如何使用 Gremlin 和 Chaos Engineering 确保您的销售点系统可靠。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Chaos Engineering works, but it has to scale】混沌工程有效，但必须规模化</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/chaos-engineering-works-but-it-has-to-scale</link>
      <description>【Chaos Engineering effectively improves the reliability of systems, but it can run into snags when you try to scale. Build on Chaos Engineering with these key actions.】混沌工程有效地提高了系统的可靠性，但当您尝试扩展时，它可能会遇到障碍。通过这些关键行动以混沌工程为基础。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【3 things you can do to get closer to five nines】您可以做三件事来接近五个九</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/3-things-you-can-do-to-get-closer-to-five-nines</link>
      <description>【3 proven practices to achieve 99.999% uptime. Learn how teams reach five nines through weekly testing, on-call rotations, and visibility.】3 个经过验证的实践可实现 99.999% 的正常运行时间。了解团队如何通过每周测试、待命轮换和可见性达到五个九。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to get fast, easy insights with the Gremlin MCP Server】如何使用 Gremlin MCP 服务器快速、轻松地获得见解</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/how-to-get-fast-easy-insights-with-the-gremlin-mcp-server</link>
      <description>【Find out how to quickly and easily uncover new reliability insights by using the Gremlin MCP Server and your favorite LLM.】了解如何使用 Gremlin MCP 服务器和您最喜欢的法学硕士快速轻松地发现新的可靠性见解。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fix issues faster with Recommended Remediations】使用建议的补救措施更快地解决问题</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/fix-issues-faster-with-recommended-remediations</link>
      <description>【Recommended Remediation speeds up teams with tailored suggestions to help you address reliability risks before they cause failures.】建议的补救措施通过量身定制的建议加快团队速度，帮助您在可靠性风险导致故障之前解决它们。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Experiment Analysis uncovers the cause behind failures】实验分析如何揭示失败背后的原因</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/how-experiment-analysis-uncovers-the-cause-behind-failures</link>
      <description>【Using knowledge of your data and your systems, Experiment Analysis connects the cause with the effect to help you pinpoint the root problem faster.】利用您的数据和系统知识，实验分析将原因与结果联系起来，帮助您更快地查明根本问题。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reliability Intelligence: your reliability expert】可靠性情报：您的可靠性专家</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/reliability-intelligence-your-reliability-expert</link>
      <description>【Gremlin’s Reliability Intelligence combines Experiment Analysis, Recommended Remediation, and an MCP Server to help teams increase reliability faster than ever.】Gremlin 的可靠性智能结合了实验分析、建议修复和 MCP 服务器，可帮助团队比以往更快地提高可靠性。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Lessons from Alaska’s outage: Redundant ≠ resilient】阿拉斯加停电的教训：冗余≠有弹性</title>
      <link>https://www.gremlin.com/blog/lessons-from-alaskas-outage-redundant-resilient</link>
      <description>【Redundancy is a core part of designing resilient architectures, but only if you build the right amount of redundancy. Find that sweet spot of redundancy with resilience testing.】冗余是设计弹性架构的核心部分，但前提是您构建了适量的冗余。通过弹性测试找到冗余的最佳点。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>