<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【PIX 2503.24: misc bug fixes】PIX 2503.24：MISC错误修复</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pix/pix-2503-24</link>
      <description>【Today we released PIX version 2503.24, which can be downloaded here. This release includes everything in the previous 2501.30 release, plus the following bug fixes: Fix capture-time crash introduced in 2501.30 in CPU write tracking code Fix capture-time issue with reserved resources, that could cause replay-time corruption for some UE5 captures Fix PIXBeginCapture() deadlocking for Timing [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们发布了PIX版本2503.24，可以在此处下载。此版本包括上一版本中的所有内容，以及以下错误修复：修复捕获时间崩溃在2501.30中引入的CPU写入跟踪代码修复了使用保留资源的捕获时间问题，这可能会导致某些UE5捕获的重播时间损坏fix fix fix pixbegincapture（pixbebegincapture（</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 22:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Semantic Kernel Agent Framework RC2】语义内核代理框架RC2</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/semantic-kernel-agent-framework-rc2</link>
      <description>【Three weeks ago we released the Release the Agents! SK Agents Framework RC1 | Semantic Kernel and we’ve been thrilled to see the momentum grow. Thank you to everyone who has shared feedback, filed issues, and started building with agents in Semantic Kernel—we’re seeing more developers try agents than ever before. Today, we’re declaring build [&amp;hellip;]】三个星期前，我们发布了发行版《代理商》！ SK代理框架RC1 |语义内核，我们很高兴看到动量增长。感谢所有共享反馈，提出问题并开始与代理商在语义内核中建立的人 - 我们看到开发人员比以往任何时候都多尝试代理。今天，我们宣布建造[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 23:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【On how different Windows ABIs choose how to pass 32-bit values in 64-bit registers】关于不同的Windows Abis如何选择如何通过64位寄存器中的32位值</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250324-00/?p=110988</link>
      <description>【Surveying the options and looking for commonalities.】调查选项并寻找共同点。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Xbox + .NET Aspire: Transforming Local Development Practices】Xbox + .Net Aspire：改变本地发展实践</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/xboxs-usage-of-aspire-transforming-development-practices</link>
      <description>【Learn how the Xbox services team leveraged .NET Aspire to boost their team&#39;s productivity.】了解Xbox服务团队如何利用.NET渴望提高团队的生产力。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enable continuous backup for multi-region write account】启用多区域写入帐户的连续备份</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/enable-continuous-backup-for-multi-region-write-account</link>
      <description>【Azure Cosmos DB already delivers 99.999% availability with multi-region write capability and continuous backup for point-in-time restores within a 7 or 30 day retention period. Now, we’re making it even better! Going forward &amp;#8211; You can migrate existing single region write region with point in time restore capability to support multi-region write. You can enable [&amp;hellip;]】Azure Cosmos DB已经提供了99.999％的可用性，具有多区域写入能力，并在7或30天的保留期内进行了恢复时间恢复的连续备份。现在，我们使它变得更好！展望未来 - 您可以迁移现有的单个区域写入区域，具有时间恢复功能以支持多区域写作。您可以启用[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 12:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB Conf 2025: Learn, Build, and Connect with the Community】Azure Cosmos DB Conf 2025：学习，建立和与社区建立和联系</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-conf-2025-learn-build-and-connect-with-the-community</link>
      <description>【Join us for the 5th annual Azure Cosmos DB Conf, a free virtual developer event co-hosted by Microsoft and the Azure Cosmos DB community. This is your opportunity to learn from Microsoft product managers, industry experts, and real-world customers who are building applications with Azure Cosmos DB. This year, we received over 100 session proposals [&amp;hellip;]】加入我们，参加第五届年度Azure Cosmos DB Conf，这是由Microsoft和Azure Cosmos DB社区共同主持的免费虚拟开发人员活动。这是您向Microsoft产品经理，行业专家和正在使用Azure Cosmos DB构建应用程序的现实世界客户学习的机会。今年，我们收到了100多个会议建议[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 21:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Visual Studio Hub】引入视觉工作室中心</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-hub</link>
      <description>【The Visual Studio Hub is here! Keeping up with the latest Visual Studio updates, features, and resources can feel like a full-time job. We’ve heard it time and time again—you want a simpler way to stay informed without digging through scattered blog posts, release notes, and social media updates. That’s why we created Visual Studio [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio Hub在这里！跟上最新的Visual Studio更新，功能和资源，感觉就像是一项全职工作。我们一次又一次地听到了它 - 您想要一种更简单的方法来保持知情，而无需挖掘分散的博客文章，发行说明和社交媒体更新。这就是为什么我们创建Visual Studio […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 14:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Teams Toolkit for Visual Studio Code update – March 2025】Visual Studio代码更新的团队工具包 -  2025年3月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/teams-toolkit-for-visual-studio-code-update-march-2025</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce the latest updates for Teams Toolkit for Visual Studio Code featuring tenant switching, new capabilities for declarative agents, and more.】我们很高兴地宣布，用于Visual Studio代码的Teams Toolkit的最新更新，其中包含租户交换，宣言代理的新功能等等。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 14:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Secure APIs with Data API Builder, Keycloak, and SQL Server】使用数据API构建器，KeyCloak和SQL Server固定API</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/secure-apis-with-data-api-builder-keycloak-and-sql-server</link>
      <description>【In this article, we&amp;#8217;ll explore how to create a secure, on-premises API using Data API Builder (DAB), Keycloak, and SQL Server. You&amp;#8217;ll learn to set up JSON Web Token (JWT) authentication with Role-Based Access Control (RBAC), Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC), and Row-Level Security (RLS), ideal for secure business scenarios. Want to replicate this setup?All the [&amp;hellip;]】在本文中，我们将探讨如何使用数据API构建器（DAB），KeyCloak和SQL Server创建安全的本地API。您将学习设置具有基于角色的访问控制（RBAC），基于属性的访问控制（ABAC）和行级安全性（RLS）（RLS）的JSON Web令牌（JWT）身份验证，非常适合安全业务方案。想要复制此设置？所有[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 14:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Comment l’IA générative impacte-t-elle l’expérience développeur?】生成性如何影响开发人员的体验？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/comment-lia-generative-impacte-t-elle-lexperience-developpeur</link>
      <description>【Adlene Sifi explore l&amp;#8217;impact de l&amp;#8217;IA générative sur l&amp;#8217;expérience des développeurs. Dans cet article, nous allons tenter de déterminer s’il existe un lien entre l’utilisation de l’IA générative (ex. : GitHub Copilot) et l’expérience développeur (DevEx). Nous souhaitons vérifier plus précisément si l’utilisation de l’IA générative a un impact positif sur l’expérience développeur. Nous tenterons même [&amp;hellip;]】Adlene Sifi探索了生成AI对开发人员体验的影响。在本文中，我们将尝试确定使用生成AI（例如Github Copilot）和开发人员体验（DEVEX）之间是否存在联系。我们要更准确地验证使用生成AI是否对开发人员体验产生积极影响。我们甚至会尝试[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 07:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>