<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Accelerate C++ Debugging with Enhanced Conditional Breakpoints】使用增强的条件断点加速 C++ 调试</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/accelerate-c-debugging-with-enhanced-conditional-breakpoints</link>
      <description>【Are you tired of waiting for your conditional breakpoints to hit in C++? Do you wish there was a way to speed up the debugging process and get to the root of the problem faster? If so, you&amp;#8217;re in luck! We have some exciting news for you: Visual Studio 2022 has significantly improved the performance [&amp;hellip;]】您是否厌倦了在 C++ 中等待条件断点命中？您是否希望有一种方法可以加快调试过程并更快地找到问题的根源？如果是这样，那么您很幸运！我们有一些令人兴奋的消息给您：Visual Studio 2022 显着提高了性能 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamlining Error Handling in Power Automate for Better Workflow Performance】简化 Power Automate 中的错误处理以提高工作流程性能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/power-automate-error-handling</link>
      <description>【This post explores effective error handling strategies in Power Automate to enhance workflow reliability and maintainability through practical techniques and integrations.】本文探讨了 Power Automate 中有效的错误处理策略，以通过实用技术和集成来增强工作流的可靠性和可维护性。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How does the linker decide whether to call WinMain or wWinMain?】链接器如何决定是调用WinMain 还是wWinMain？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241004-00/?p=110338</link>
      <description>【If you don&#39;t tell it, it will try to figure it out.】如果你不告诉它，它会尝试找出答案。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Azure Cosmos DB Integration with LangChain.js!】宣布 Azure Cosmos DB 与 LangChain.js 集成！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/announcing-azure-cosmos-db-integration-with-langchain-js</link>
      <description>【Announcing Azure Cosmos DB Vector Store Integration with LangChain.js! We&amp;#8217;re simplifying AI app development by integrating Azure Cosmos DB&amp;#8217;s cost-effective and scalable vector search directly with LangChain.js! This powerful combination empowers JavaScript developers to efficiently manage fast and accurate data retrieval with Azure Cosmos DB&amp;#8217;s scalability and efficient vector search capabilities. This offers a powerful [&amp;hellip;]】宣布 Azure Cosmos DB 矢量存储与 LangChain.js 集成！我们通过将 Azure Cosmos DB 经济高效且可扩展的矢量搜索直接与 LangChain.js 集成来简化 AI 应用程序开发！这种强大的组合使 JavaScript 开发人员能够利用 Azure Cosmos DB 的可扩展性和高效的矢量搜索功能来高效管理快速、准确的数据检索。这提供了强大的[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scale Your Database Workloads with Multishard Clusters in vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB】在基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB 中使用多分片群集扩展数据库工作负载</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/scale-your-database-workloads-with-multishard-clusters-in-vcore-based-azure-cosmos-db-for-mongodb</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to introduce significant enhancements to vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB with the release of multishard clusters preview, designed to take scalability and performance to the next level. This update brings several new capabilities that address the needs of demanding database workloads, making it easier than ever to manage large datasets and handle high-throughput [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴通过发布多分片集群预览版为基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB 引入重大增强功能，旨在将可扩展性和性能提升到新的水平。此更新带来了多项新功能，可以满足苛刻的数据库工作负载的需求，使管理大型数据集和处理高吞吐量变得比以往更容易[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Hackathon: Project Micronaire using Semantic Kernel】微软黑客马拉松：使用语义内核的马克隆项目</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/microsoft-hackathon-project-micronaire-using-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【During our internal Microsoft Hackathon, there were a number of projects using Semantic Kernel. Today we&amp;#8217;d like to highlight one of the projects focused on using Semantic Kernel and the new Vector Store abstraction. I&amp;#8217;m going to turn it over to the Hackathon team to share more about their project and work using Semantic Kernel. [&amp;hellip;]】在我们内部的 Microsoft Hackathon 期间，有许多项目使用 Semantic Kernel。今天我们想重点介绍一个专注于使用语义内核和新的矢量存储抽象的项目。我将把它交给 Hackathon 团队，分享更多关于他们使用语义内核的项目和工作的信息。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 21:19:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Configure GitHub Copilot Access via Content Exclusion】通过内容排除配置 GitHub Copilot 访问</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/configure-github-copilot-access-via-content-exclusion</link>
      <description>【Have you ever wanted greater control over the sensitive content AI-powered tools can access in your repositories? You can now customize Copilot’s access to your files with the newly announced GitHub Copilot Content Exclusion in both Visual Studio and Visual Studio Code. Through this new process you can configure Copilot to ignore certain files in your [&amp;hellip;]】您是否曾经想要更好地控制人工智能支持的工具可以在您的存储库中访问的敏感内容？现在，您可以使用 Visual Studio 和 Visual Studio Code 中新发布的 GitHub Copilot 内容排除功能自定义 Copilot 对文件的访问权限。通过这个新过程，您可以将 Copilot 配置为忽略 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 23:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A popular but wrong way to convert a string to uppercase or lowercase】将字符串转换为大写或小写的一种流行但错误的方法</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241007-00/?p=110345</link>
      <description>【Converting character by character isn&#39;t good enough any more.】逐个字符地转换已经不够了。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Configuring your Azure Function with External ID as an identity provider】使用外部 ID 作为身份提供者配置 Azure Function</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/azure-function-with-external-id</link>
      <description>【Learn how to configure Microsoft Entra External ID as an identity provider for Azure Functions. This blog post shows you how to integrate External ID seamlessly, allowing you to focus on building app features without worrying about infrastructure or authentication.】了解如何将 Microsoft Entra 外部 ID 配置为 Azure Functions 的身份提供程序。这篇博文向您展示了如何无缝集成外部 ID，使您能够专注于构建应用程序功能，而无需担心基础设施或身份验证。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python in Visual Studio Code – October 2024 Release】Visual Studio Code 中的 Python – 2024 年 10 月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/python-in-visual-studio-code-october-2024-release</link>
      <description>【The October 2024 release of the Python and Jupyter extensions for Visual Studio Code are now available. This month&#39;s updates include Python test coverage support and a default Python problem matcher. Keep reading to learn more!】2024 年 10 月发布的 Visual Studio Code 的 Python 和 Jupyter 扩展现已推出。本月的更新包括 Python 测试覆盖率支持和默认的 Python 问题匹配器。继续阅读以了解更多信息！</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 14:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>