<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Java OpenJDK October 2024 Patch &amp; Security Updates】Java OpenJDK 2024 年 10 月补丁和安全更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/java-openjdk-oct-2024-patch-security-updates</link>
      <description>【Hello Java customers! We are happy to announce the latest October 2024 patch &amp;amp; security update release for the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK. Download and install the binaries today. OpenJDK 21.0.5 OpenJDK 17.0.13 OpenJDK 11.0.25 Check our release notes page for details on fixes and enhancements. The source code of our builds is available now [&amp;hellip;]】Java 客户您好！我们很高兴地宣布 Microsoft Build of OpenJDK 的最新 2024 年 10 月补丁和安全更新版本。立即下载并安装二进制文件。 OpenJDK 21.0.5 OpenJDK 17.0.13 OpenJDK 11.0.25 请查看我们的发行说明页面，了解有关修复和增强功能的详细信息。我们构建的源代码现已可用 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 00:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET Conf 2024 Student Zone】.NET Conf 2024 学生专区</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnetconf-2024-student-zone</link>
      <description>【The .NET Conf Student Zone is a beginner-friendly, virtual event where experts will teach you how to build amazing projects - all using C# and .NET!】.NET Conf 学生区是一个适合初学者的虚拟活动，专家将教您如何构建令人惊叹的项目 - 全部使用 C# 和 .NET！</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhanced Breakpoint Expressions for C++ Debugging in Visual Studio】Visual Studio 中 C++ 调试的增强断点表达式</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/enhanced-breakpoint-expressions-for-c-debugging-in-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【Conditional Breakpoints Performance Improvement Debugging C++ code can be a time-consuming process, especially when dealing with complex scenarios. As a developer, it&amp;#8217;s frustrating to go through extensive setup and wait for a specific conditional breakpoint to trigger so you can analyze your application in a specific state. In Visual Studio 2022 version 17.10, we optimized [&amp;hellip;]】条件断点性能改进 调试 C++ 代码可能是一个耗时的过程，尤其是在处理复杂场景时。作为开发人员，进行大量设置并等待特定条件断点触发以便您可以在特定状态下分析应用程序是令人沮丧的。在 Visual Studio 2022 版本 17.10 中，我们优化了 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Updates to Azure Cosmos DB’s Portal Networking Settings】Azure Cosmos DB 门户网络设置的更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/updates-to-azure-cosmos-dbs-portal-networking-settings</link>
      <description>【We are happy to share with you an update to the Azure Cosmos DB networking configuration options within the Azure Portal. This update introduces a split in the IP address list, now presented as two distinct categories: user IP addresses and Portal Middleware IPs.  Managing IP access control policies is essential for maintaining a secure [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴与你分享 Azure 门户中 Azure Cosmos DB 网络配置选项的更新。此更新引入了 IP 地址列表的拆分，现在显示为两个不同的类别：用户 IP 地址和门户中间件 IP。  管理 IP 访问控制策略对于维护安全至关重要 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MongoDB EF Core Provider: What’s New?】MongoDB EF Core 提供商：有什么新变化？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/mongodb-ef-core-provider-whats-new</link>
      <description>【The latest updates to the MongoDB EF Core Provider brings updates to change tracking, index creation, complex queries, and transactions.】MongoDB EF Core Provider 的最新更新带来了更改跟踪、索引创建、复杂查询和事务的更新。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Evaluating tail call elimination in the face of return address protection, part 2】在返回地址保护的情况下评估尾调用消除，第 2 部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241018-00/?p=110385</link>
      <description>【Rewriting the activation frame.】重写激活帧。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why does adding WS_MINIMIZE­BOX change how my window behaves when the user presses Win+D?】为什么添加 WS_MINIMIZEBOX 会改变用户按下 Win+D 时窗口的行为方式？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241021-00/?p=110393</link>
      <description>【It minimizes your window if it can.】如果可以的话，它会最小化您的窗口。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customer Case Study: How Microsoft streamlined regulatory compliance with GenAI】客户案例研究：Microsoft 如何通过 GenAI 简化监管合规性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-how-microsoft-streamlined-regulatory-compliance-with-genai</link>
      <description>【Customer Case Study: How Microsoft streamlined regulatory compliance with GenAI Today we&amp;#8217;re featuring an external blog from EY featuring Microsoft&amp;#8217;s Semantic Kernel. This case study reveals how Microsoft legal teams are using GenAI to confidently manage regulatory change. Learn more here: How Microsoft uses GenAI for compliance | EY &amp;#8211; Global How can you generate [&amp;hellip;]】客户案例研究：微软如何通过 GenAI 简化监管合规性今天我们将重点介绍 EY 的外部博客，其中介绍了微软的语义内核。本案例研究揭示了 Microsoft 法律团队如何使用 GenAI 自信地管理监管变更。在此处了解更多信息：Microsoft 如何使用 GenAI 来实现合规性 |安永 – 全球您如何生成[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 23:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Make Great Music with Windows on Arm】使用 Windows on Arm 创作美妙的音乐</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/windows-music-dev/making-music-on-windows</link>
      <description>【This week has been amazing, with our musician work really coming together at Qualcomm Snapdragon Summit 2024! There&amp;#8217;s only so much time available in a keynote, so I thought I&amp;#8217;d expand a bit more on the music-related announcements, especially for the new in-box features. Music is all around us. We purposefully listen to music in [&amp;hellip;]】这周真是太棒了，我们的音乐家作品在 2024 年高通 Snapdragon 峰会上真正齐聚一堂！主题演讲的时间有限，所以我想我应该更多地介绍与音乐相关的公告，尤其是新的内置功能。音乐就在我们身边。我们有目的地听音乐[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Windows MIDI Services October 2024 Update】Windows MIDI 服务 2024 年 10 月更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/windows-music-dev/windows-midi-services-oct-2024-update</link>
      <description>【It&amp;#8217;s been a little while since I last posted an update about Windows MIDI Services outside of our Discord Server, but we&amp;#8217;ve been busy! With all the announcements today at Qualcomm&amp;#8217;s Snapdragon Summit, I thought I&amp;#8217;d dive in a bit on where we are with our new MIDI 1.0 and MIDI 2.0 stack on Windows. [&amp;hellip;]】自从我上次在 Discord 服务器之外发布有关 Windows MIDI 服务的更新以来已经有一段时间了，但我们一直很忙！今天在高通 Snapdragon 峰会上发布了所有公告，我想我应该深入了解 Windows 上新的 MIDI 1.0 和 MIDI 2.0 堆栈的进展情况。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 18:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>