<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Semantic Kernel and Copilot Studio Usage Series – Part 1】嘉宾博客：语义内核和副副研究室用法系列 - 第1部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-semantic-kernel-and-copilot-studio-usage-series-part-1</link>
      <description>【Today on the Semantic Kernel blog we&amp;#8217;re excited to welcome a group of guest authors from Microsoft. We&amp;#8217;ll turn it over to Riccardo Chiodaroli, Samar El Housseini, Daniel Lavve and Fabrizio Ruocco to dive into their use cases with Semantic Kernel and Copilot Studio. In today&amp;#8217;s fast-paced digital economy, intelligent automation is no longer optional—it&amp;#8217;s [&amp;hellip;]】今天，在语义内核博客上，我们很高兴欢迎来自Microsoft的一群客座作家。我们将其移交给Riccardo Chiodaroli，Samar El Housseini，Daniel Lavve和Fabrizio Ruocco，以使用语义内核和Copilot Studio潜入他们的用例。在当今快节奏的数字经济中，智能自动化不再是可选的，它是[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 18:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build a Model Context Protocol (MCP) server in C#】在C＃中构建模型上下文协议（MCP）服务器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/build-a-model-context-protocol-mcp-server-in-csharp</link>
      <description>【Learn how to build a Model Context Protocol (MCP) server using the C# SDK to enable seamless communication between AI models and applications.】了解如何使用C＃SDK构建模型上下文协议（MCP）服务器，以启用AI模型和应用程序之间的无缝通信。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Search Capabilities in SQL Server and Azure SQL with Hybrid Search and RRF Re-Ranking】通过混合搜索和RRF重新排名，在SQL Server和Azure SQL中增强搜索功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/enhancing-search-capabilities-in-sql-server-and-azure-sql-with-hybrid-search-and-rrf-re-ranking</link>
      <description>【In today&amp;#8217;s data-driven world, delivering precise and contextually relevant search results is critical. SQL Server and Azure SQL Database now enable this through Hybrid Search—a technique that combines traditional full-text search with modern vector similarity search. This allows developers to build intelligent, AI-powered search experiences directly inside the database engine. Funny enough one of the [&amp;hellip;]】在当今数据驱动的世界中，提供精确和上下文相关的搜索结果至关重要。 SQL Server和Azure SQL数据库现在通过混合搜索启用此功能，该技术将传统的全文搜索与现代矢量相似性搜索相结合。这使开发人员可以直接在数据库引擎内部构建智能的AI驱动搜索体验。有趣的[…]之一</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【On priority inversion in the use of a spinlock to ensure atomic access to a shared_ptr】关于使用Spinlock的优先倒置，以确保原子访问共享_ptr</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250407-00/?p=111054</link>
      <description>【Priority inversion may be rare, but correctness doesn&#39;t care about rarity.】优先倒置可能很少，但是正确性并不关心稀有性。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (March 2025)】VCPKG的新功能（2025年3月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-march-2025</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2025.03.19 registry release, 2025-03-13 tool release, as well as changes to vcpkg documentation throughout March. This release includes two new commands for our continuous integration system PR reviews, minor bugfixes, a new documentation article on authenticating to NuGet feeds, and a [&amp;hellip;]】该博客文章总结了VCPKG软件包管理器的更改，作为2025.03.19注册表版本，2025-03-13工具版本的一部分，以及整个3月的VCPKG文档的更改。该版本包括两个新命令，用于我们的连续集成系统PR评论，次要错误相框，有关Nuget feed验证的新文档文档以及[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Goldilocks zone of software stability】软件稳定性的Goldilocks区域</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250408-00/?p=111057</link>
      <description>【Not too new, not too old.】不太新，不太老。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python Vector Store Connectors update: Faiss, Azure SQL Server and Pinecone】Python Vector Store连接器更新：Faiss，Azure SQL Server和Pinecone</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/python-vector-store-connectors-update-faiss-azure-sql-server-and-pinecone</link>
      <description>【Announcing New Vector Stores: Faiss, SQL Server, and Pinecone We are thrilled to announce the availability of three new Vector Stores and Vector Store Record Collections: Faiss, SQL Server, and Pinecone. These new connectors will enable you to store and retrieve vector data efficiently, making it easier to work with your own data and data [&amp;hellip;]】宣布新的向量商店：Faiss，SQL Server和Pinecone，我们很高兴宣布三家新矢量商店和矢量商店记录集合的可用性：Faiss，SQL Server和Pinecone。这些新连接器将使您能够有效地存储和检索向量数据，从而更容易使用自己的数据和数据[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Dev Box subscriptions and licensing requirements demystified: What You Need and Why】Microsoft Dev Box订阅和许可要求宣传：您需要什么以及为什么</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/microsoft-dev-box-subscriptions-and-licensing-requirements-demystified</link>
      <description>【Thinking of deploying Microsoft Dev Box service but want to understand the licensing and subscription requirements first? Then, you have come to the right place. This blog post breaks it all down—clearly and simply—so you know exactly what you need and why, whether you’re an IT admin, platform engineer, developer, or a decision-maker. Microsoft Dev [&amp;hellip;]】考虑部署Microsoft Dev Box服务，但想首先了解许可和订阅要求？然后，您来了正确的位置。这篇博客文章明显地将其全部弄清楚了，因此您确切地知道您需要什么以及为什么您是IT管理员，平台工程师，开发人员，还是决策者。 Microsoft Dev […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 22:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multi-Process CPU Usage Analysis in Visual Studio】视觉工作室中的多进程CPU使用分析</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/multi-process-cpu-usage-analysis-in-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【Streamlined Performance Insights Across Processes The Visual Studio Profiler&amp;#8217;s CPU Usage tool and Instrumentation tool now supports multi-process analysis, providing a unified view of CPU activity across multiple processes. With performance graphs featuring distinct, color-coded stacked swim lanes for each process, diagnosing and optimizing CPU usage is now more efficient than ever. Tackling Multi-Process Complexity [&amp;hellip;]】简化了跨流程的性能见解，Visual Studio Profiler的CPU使用工具和仪器工具现在支持多过程分析，从而在多个过程中提供了CPU活动的统一视图。通过为每个过程提供独特的颜色编码堆叠游泳车道的性能图，诊断和优化CPU使用情况现在比以往任何时候都更有效。解决多过程复杂性[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【April Patches for Azure DevOps Server and Team Foundation Server】Azure DevOps服务器和团队基础服务器的四月补丁</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/april-patches-for-azure-devops-server-and-team-foundation-server-3</link>
      <description>【Today we are releasing patches that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server, as well as Team Foundation Server 2018.3.2. We strongly encourage and recommend that all customers use the latest, most secure release of Azure DevOps Server. You can download the latest version of the product, Azure DevOps Server 2022.2 from the Azure DevOps [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们发布了影响我们自托管产品Azure DevOps服务器以及Team Foundation Server 2018.3.2的补丁程序。我们强烈鼓励并建议所有客户使用最新，最安全的Azure DevOps服务器。您可以从Azure Devops […]下载最新版本的产品Azure Devops Server 2022.2</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 19:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>