<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I confirm in the Windows debugger that I&#39;m looking at a COMDAT-folded function?】如何在Windows调试器中确认我正在查看Comdat折叠功能？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250725-00/?p=111409</link>
      <description>【Some time ago, we learned about identical COMDAT folding (and also】不久前，我们了解了相同的Comdat折叠（也</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Let’s Learn MCP Series Recap: 8 Languages, 4 Code Bases, Full Resources】让我们学习MCP系列回顾：8种语言，4个代码库，完整资源</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com//lets-learn-mcp-series-recap-8-languages-4-code-bases-full-resources</link>
      <description>【The Model Context Protocol (MCP) has quickly established itself as the go-to standard for seamlessly connecting AI agents with a variety of external tools and services. In just a few months, it has become a prominent topic at developer events and forums, gaining adoption from companies of all sizes. To meet the rapid pace of advancements, we】模型上下文协议（MCP）已迅速确定自己是无缝连接AI代理和各种外部工具和服务的首选标准。在短短几个月内，它已成为开发人员活动和论坛上的一个杰出话题，从各种规模的公司中获得了收养。为了达到进步的快速步伐，我们</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【API design note: Don&#39;t make up multiple names for the same thing】API设计注意：不要为同一件事编写多个名称</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250728-00/?p=111415</link>
      <description>【A recurring problem I encounter when reviewing API proposals is that teams tend not to be precise in their use of terminology. This casualness is inevitable when you work with a feature for a long time and develop notational shortcuts, but the people who are learning your API don&#39;t have the same level of familiarity that you do, and shiftin】我在审查API提案时遇到的反复出现的问题是，在使用术语时，团队往往并不精确。当您长期使用功能并发展符号捷径时，这种休闲性是不可避免的，但是正在学习您的API的人没有与您相同的熟悉程度，而是Shiftin</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Microsoft.PowerShell.PlatyPS 1.0.0】宣布Microsoft.powershell.platyps 1.0.0</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/announcing-platyps-100</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re pleased to announce the general availability (GA) release of Microsoft.PowerShell.PlatyPS v1.0.0. PlatyPS is the tool that Microsoft uses to create the PowerShell content you get from Get】我们很高兴地宣布Microsoft.powershell.platyps v1.0.0的一般可用性（GA）发布。 Platyps是Microsoft用来创建您从GET获得的PowerShell内容的工具</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Developer CLI (azd) - July 2025】Azure开发人员CLI（AZD） -  2025年7月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-developer-cli-azd-july-2025</link>
      <description>【This post shares the details of the latest changes to the Azure Developer CLI (azd) in release 1.17.1 and 1.18.0. We invite you to join our July release discussion on GitHub with questions and comments. This month&#39;s release focuses on enhancing developer experien】这篇文章分享了版本1.17.1和1.18.0中Azure开发人员CLI（AZD）的最新更改的详细信息。我们邀请您加入我们在Github上的7月发布讨论，并提出问题和评论。本月的发布重点是增强开发人员体验</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Container Options: Matching Services to Operational Responsibility】Azure容器选项：将服务与运营责任相匹配</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/azure-container-options-matching-services-to-operational-responsibility</link>
      <description>【Customers are looking to modernize their application on cloud and ask us for guidance on which Azure container services to choose. Should you choose A or B container services or A+B container services? Some choose both (A + B) or use A or B appr】客户希望在云上现代化其应用程序，并向我们询问选择哪种Azure容器服务的指导。您是否应该选择A或B容器服务或A+B容器服务？有些选择同时选择（a + b）或使用A或B ADPER</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 21:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scalable Data Governance &amp; Compliance with UDM】可扩展的数据治理和遵守UDM</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/udm/scalable-data-governance-compliance-with-udm</link>
      <description>【Why Data Governance Matters In today’s data-driven world, governance isn’t just a technical requirement—it’s foundational to successful business operations. Good governance ensures data is not only accurate and compliant but also discoverable and usable at scale. At the heart of this approach lies robust, high-quality meta】为什么数据治理在当今数据驱动的世界中很重要，治理不仅是技术要求，而且是成功的业务运营的基础。良好的治理确保数据不仅准确且合规，而且可以在大规模上发现和可用。这种方法的核心是强大的高质量元</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 20:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Manual Testing to AI-Generated Automation: Our Azure DevOps MCP + Playwright Success Story】从手动测试到AI生成的自动化：我们的Azure Devops MCP +剧作家成功故事</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/from-manual-testing-to-ai-generated-automation-our-azure-devops-mcp-playwright-success-story</link>
      <description>【In today’s fast-paced software development cycles, manual testing often becomes a significant bottleneck. Our team was facing a growing backlog of test cases that required repetitive manual execution—running the entire test suite every sprint. This consumed valuable time that could be better spent on exploratory testing and higher-value】在当今快节奏的软件开发周期中，手动测试通常成为一个重要的瓶颈。我们的团队面临着越来越多的测试案例的积压，这些案例需要重复手动执行，这将使整个测试套件每次冲刺划定。这段耗时的时间可以更好地用于探索性测试和高价值</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 06:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript 5.9 RC】宣布打字稿5.9 RC</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-5-9-rc</link>
      <description>【Today we are excited to announce the Release Candidate (RC) of TypeScript 5.9! To get started using the Release Candidate, you can get it through npm with the following command: npm install -D typescript@rc Let&#39;s take a look at what&#39;s new】今天，我们很高兴宣布打字稿5.9的发行候选人（RC）！要开始使用发布候选者，您可以通过以下命令通过NPM获得：NPM install -d Typescript@rc让我们看一下新的新事物</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Scaling multi-tenant Go applications: Choosing the right database partitioning approach】缩放多租户GO应用程序：选择正确的数据库分区方法</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/scaling-multi-tenant-go-applications-choosing-the-right-database-partitioning-approach</link>
      <description>【Multi-tenant applications face a fundamental challenge: how to efficiently store and query data for tenants of vastly different sizes? Consider the typical scenario where your platform serves both enterprise clients with hundreds of thousands of users, as well as small businesses with just a handful. With traditional database partitioning stra】多租户应用程序面临着一个基本挑战：如何有效地存储和查询大小不同的租户数据？考虑一下您平台为企业客户提供数十万用户的企业客户的典型情况，以及只有少数用户的小型企业。传统数据库分区</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>