<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Python in Visual Studio Code - October 2025 Release】Visual Studio Code 中的 Python - 2025 年 10 月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/python-in-visual-studio-code-october-2025-release</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re excited to announce that the October 2025 release of the Python extensions for Visual Studio Code are now available! This release includes the following announcements: Python Environments extension improvements Enhanced testing】我们很高兴地宣布，2025 年 10 月版的 Visual Studio Code Python 扩展现已推出！此版本包括以下公告： Python 环境扩展改进 增强测试</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The self-assignment principle for Windows Runtime properties: Don&#39;t change behavior based on whether a property has been written to】Windows 运行时属性的自分配原则：不要根据属性是否已写入来更改行为</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251010-00/?p=111673</link>
      <description>【For the past few days, I&#39;ve been investigating the self-assignment principle for Windows Runtime properties: Setting a property to its current value is legal and has no effect. One corollary to this was that】这几天，我一直在研究Windows运行时属性的自分配原理：将属性设置为其当前值是合法的，并且没有任何效果。由此得出的一个推论是</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.25.2-1 and 1.24.8-1 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.25.2-1 和 1.24.8-1 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-25-2-1-and-1-24-8-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new release of the Microsoft build of Go including security fixes is now available for download. For more information about this release and the changes included, see the table below: Microsoft Release Upstream Tag】包含安全修复程序的 Microsoft Go 版本新版本现已可供下载。有关此版本及其所包含更改的更多信息，请参阅下表： Microsoft 版本上游标签</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 01:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Complete Beginner&#39;s Guide to Vibe Coding an App in 5 Minutes】5 分钟内完成 Vibe 应用程序编码初学者指南</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/complete-beginners-guide-to-vibe-coding-an-app-in-5-minutes</link>
      <description>【Picture this: I&#39;m staring at a CSV file containing metrics from 492 episodes of my podcast, Merge Conflict. Years of data—listen counts, retention rates, performance metrics—all sitting there, waiting to tell a story. But I&#39;m not in the mood to spend days building dashboards and wrangling data.】想象一下：我正盯着一个 CSV 文件，其中包含我的播客“合并冲突”的 492 集的指标。多年的数据——收听次数、保留率、绩效指标——全部都放在那里，等待讲述一个故事。但我没有心情花几天时间构建仪表板和整理数据。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【September 2025 (version 1.105)】2025 年 9 月（版本 1.105）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/external-blogs/september-2025-version-1-105</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code September 2025 Release (1.105). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2025 年 9 月版本 (1.105) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【September 2025 (version 1.105)】2025 年 9 月（版本 1.105）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/september-2025-(version-1.105)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code September 2025 Release (1.105). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2025 年 9 月版本 (1.105) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The self-assignment principle for Windows Runtime properties applies to default values】Windows 运行时属性的自分配原则适用于默认值</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251009-00/?p=111664</link>
      <description>【Last time, I introduced the self-assignment principle for Windows Runtime properties: Setting a property to its current value is legal and】上次，我介绍了 Windows 运行时属性的自分配原则：将属性设置为其当前值是合法的，并且</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Working with Git Submodules: Managing Dependencies Across Repositories】使用 Git 子模块：管理跨存储库的依赖关系</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/git-submodules-and-dependencies</link>
      <description>【In complex software projects, it’s common to split functionality across multiple repositories. One common scenario arises when your main project depends on outputs or components developed in another repository that&#39;s also evolving in parallel. Managing this dependency effectively—especially when only a specific part of the secondary reposi】在复杂的软件项目中，将功能划分到多个存储库是很常见的。当您的主项目依赖于另一个并行发展的存储库中开发的输出或组件时，就会出现一种常见情况。有效管理这种依赖关系——尤其是当只有辅助存储库的特定部分时</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Preparing for the .NET 10 GC (DATAS)】准备 .NET 10 GC（数据）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/preparing-for-dotnet-10-gc</link>
      <description>【This article is cross-posted from Maoni&#39;s blog post original Medium article Preparing for the .NET 10 GC by permission. Preparing for the .NET 10 GC In .NET 9 we enabled DATAS by default. But .NET 9 is not an LTS relea】本文经许可交叉发布自 Maoni 的博文原创 Medium 文章《Preparing for the .NET 10 GC》。准备 .NET 10 GC 在 .NET 9 中，我们默认启用 DATAS。但 .NET 9 不是 LTS 版本</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Windows Runtime API design principles around read-write properties: Idempotence and self-assignment】围绕读写属性的 Windows 运行时 API 设计原则：幂等性和自分配</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251008-00/?p=111660</link>
      <description>【Objects in the Windows Runtime can have properties, and those properties could be read-only or read-write. For read-write properties, there are a few general principles. Today we&#39;re going to look at this one: Setting a property to its current value is legal and has no effect.¹ For example: // C# o】Windows 运行时中的对象可以具有属性，并且这些属性可以是只读的或读写的。对于读写属性，有一些一般原则。今天我们来看看这个：将属性设置为其当前值是合法的，并且没有任何效果。 1 例如： // C# o</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>