<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Resolving an ambiguity in the Windows clipboard automated text conversion table】解决 Windows 剪贴板自动文本转换表中的歧义</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251212-05/?p=111862</link>
      <description>【Last time, we encountered a mystery where the synthesis of CF_OEM­TEXT from CF_TEXT did not use Ansi­To­Oem.】上次，我们遇到了一个谜团，从CF_TEXT合成CF_OEMTEXT没有使用AnsiToOem。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 16:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Retirement of Global Personal Access Tokens in Azure DevOps】Azure DevOps 中全局个人访问令牌的停用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/retirement-of-global-personal-access-tokens-in-azure-devops</link>
      <description>【In the new year, we’ll be retiring the Global Personal Access Token (PAT) type in Azure DevOps. Global PATs allow users to authenticate across all accessible organizations. While this can feel convenient, a single credential with broad reach creates a concentrated security risk — especially as a user’s access】新的一年，我们将在 Azure DevOps 中停用全局个人访问令牌 (PAT) 类型。全局 PAT 允许用户在所有可访问的组织中进行身份验证。虽然这感觉很方便，但具有广泛影响力的单一凭证会带来集中的安全风险——尤其是当用户访问时</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 14:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Studying the various locale mismatch scenarios in Windows clipboard text format synthesis】研究Windows剪贴板文本格式合成中的各种区域设置不匹配场景</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251211-37/?p=111858</link>
      <description>【So far, we&#39;ve learned that the conversion between Unicode and the 8-bit ANSI and OEM code pages is performed with the assistance of the CF_LOCALE clipboard format, which itself c】到目前为止，我们已经了解到 Unicode 与 8 位 ANSI 和 OEM 代码页之间的转换是在 CF_LOCALE 剪贴板格式的帮助下执行的，该格式本身就是 c</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:19:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Making Windows Terminal awesome with GitHub Copilot CLI】使用 GitHub Copilot CLI 让 Windows 终端变得更加出色</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/making-windows-terminal-awesome-with-github-copilot-cli</link>
      <description>【As someone who lives and breathes in the command line, I love making my terminal feel like home. Windows Terminal is full of personalization options that really allow for a custom experience. Additionally, I can stay within my terminal for my development with GitHub Copilot with the GitHub Copilot CLI. Let&#39;s walk through how you can trick out】作为一个在命令行中生活和呼吸的人，我喜欢让我的终端感觉像家一样。 Windows Terminal 充满了个性化选项，可以真正实现自定义体验。此外，我可以通过 GitHub Copilot CLI 留在终端中使用 GitHub Copilot 进行开发。让我们来看看如何欺骗</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Aspire Integrations, Batteries Included】Aspire 集成，包含电池</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspire/aspire-integrations-batteries-included</link>
      <description>【Aspire Integrations: Batteries included Modern applications depend on many external services: databases, caches, message brokers, storage layers, observability tools, and sometimes AI systems. Each of these brings its own rules for configuration, connection strings, environment variables, authentication, and deployment. Setting al】Aspire 集成：包含电池现代应用程序依赖于许多外部服务：数据库、缓存、消息代理、存储层、可观察性工具，有时还包括人工智能系统。其中每一个都有自己的配置、连接字符串、环境变量、身份验证和部署规则。设置全部</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB vNext Emulator: Query and Observability Enhancements】Azure Cosmos DB vNext 模拟器：查询和可观察性增强</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-vnext-emulator-query-and-observability-enhancements</link>
      <description>【The Azure Cosmos DB Linux-based vNext emulator (preview) is a local version of the Azure Cosmos DB service that runs as a Docker container on Linux, macOS, and Windows. It provides a cost-effective way to develop and test applications locally without requiring an Azure】基于 Linux 的 Azure Cosmos DB vNext 模拟器（预览版）是 Azure Cosmos DB 服务的本地版本，在 Linux、macOS 和 Windows 上作为 Docker 容器运行。它提供了一种经济高效的方式来在本地开发和测试应用程序，而无需 Azure</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB : Becoming a Search-Native Database】Azure Cosmos DB：成为搜索本机数据库</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-becoming-a-search-native-database</link>
      <description>【For years, “Database” and “Search systems&#34; (think Elastic Search) lived in separate worlds. While both Databases and Search Systems operate in the same domain (storing, indexing and querying data), they prioritized different aspects. OLTP Databases prioritized Structured and Semi-structured data】多年来，“数据库”和“搜索系统”（想想弹性搜索）生活在不同的世界。虽然数据库和搜索系统在同一域中运行（存储、索引和查询数据），但它们优先考虑不同的方面。 OLTP 数据库优先考虑结构化和半结构化数据</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 01:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【General Availability of SharePoint Framework 1.22 - A Major Refresh of the Build &amp; Tooling Experience】SharePoint 框架 1.22 正式发布 - 构建和工具体验的重大更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/general-availability-of-sharepoint-framework-1-22-a-major-refresh-of-the-build-tooling-experience</link>
      <description>【We are excited to announce general availability of the SharePoint Framework (SPFx) 1.22 – with a focus on refreshing the build and toolchain areas. SharePoint Framework is the easiest and the most widely used model to build your enterprise solutions for Microsoft 365 with automatic single s】我们很高兴地宣布 SharePoint Framework (SPFx) 1.22 全面上市 - 重点是更新构建和工具链领域。 SharePoint 框架是使用自动单点构建 Microsoft 365 企业解决方案的最简单且使用最广泛的模型</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【November 2025 (version 1.107)】2025 年 11 月（版本 1.107）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/november-2025-(version-1.107)</link>
      <description>【What&#39;s new in the Visual Studio Code November 2025 Release (1.107). Read the full article】Visual Studio Code 2025 年 11 月版本 (1.107) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【November 2025 (version 1.107)】2025 年 11 月（版本 1.107）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/external-blogs/november-2025-insiders-version-1-107</link>
      <description>【What&#39;s new in the Visual Studio Code November 2025 Release (1.107). Read the full article】Visual Studio Code 2025 年 11 月版本 (1.107) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>