<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Python in Visual Studio Code – May 2025 Release】Visual Studio代码中的Python  -  2025年5月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/python-in-visual-studio-code-may-2025-release</link>
      <description>【The May 2025 release includes updates in the Python Environments extension, a new color picker added by Pylance, branch coverage support, and more!】2025年5月的发布包括在Python环境扩展中的更新，由Pylance添加的新颜色选择器，分支覆盖范围支持等等！</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the General Availability of Managed Identities as Federated Identity Credentials in your Entra apps】在您的ENTRA应用中宣布托管身份作为联合身份证书的一般可用性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/access-cloud-resources-across-tenants-without-secrets-ga</link>
      <description>【Announcing the GA of Managed Identities as Federated Identity Credentials for Microsoft Entra. Enhance security by replacing app secrets with managed identities, simplify setup, and enable seamless cross-tenant access to Entra-protected resources like Azure and Microsoft Graph.】宣布托管身份的GA作为Microsoft Entra的联合身份证书。通过用托管身份替换应用程序秘密，简化设置并启用对ENTRA保护资源（如Azure和Microsoft Graph）启用无缝的跨租户访问来增强安全性。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fabric Mirroring for Azure Cosmos DB: Public Preview Refresh Now Live with New Features】Azure Cosmos DB的面料镜像：公共预览刷新现在具有新功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/fabric-mirroring-for-azure-cosmos-db-public-preview-refresh-now-live-with-new-features</link>
      <description>【We’re thrilled to announce the latest refresh of Fabric Mirroring for Azure Cosmos DB, now available with several powerful new features that enhance your data analytics infrastructure. This update significantly improves the experience, making it easier than ever to replicate your Azure Cosmos DB data into OneLake in Microsoft Fabric—giving you more control and flexibility [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴宣布Azure Cosmos DB的最新织物镜像镜像，现在提供了一些强大的新功能，可增强您的数据分析基础架构。此更新大大改善了体验，使您比以往任何时候都更容易将您的Azure Cosmos DB数据复制到Microsoft Fabric中的OneLake中，从而使您更加控制和灵活性[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【C# 14 – Exploring extension members】C＃14  - 探索扩展成员</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/csharp-exploring-extension-members</link>
      <description>【C# 14 introduces extension members. See how the `extension` syntax offers flexibility for extension authors and continuity for developers using extensions】C＃14介绍扩展成员。查看“扩展”语法如何为扩展作者提供灵活性和使用扩展的开发人员的连续性</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why doesn’t Clipboard History capture rapid changes to clipboard contents?】剪贴板历史记录为什么不捕获剪贴板内容的快速更改？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250508-00/?p=111162</link>
      <description>【Clipboard history operates asynchronously, so you are changing it before it can respond to the changes.】剪贴板历史记录不同步，因此您正在对其进行更改，然后才能响应更改。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Avoid T-SQL anti-patterns with the free T-SQL analysis tool】使用免费的T-SQL分析工具避免使用T-SQL抗模式</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/sql-analysis-dotnet-tool</link>
      <description>【T-SQL Analyzer is a free, open-source, cross platform command line tool for identifying, and reporting the presence of anti-patterns and design issues in SQL Server T-SQL scripts. As a database developer, you can catch any potential bad practices and design problems very early in the project process &amp;#8211; this ensures a frictionless path to deployment [&amp;hellip;]】T-SQL Analyzer是一种免费的开源，跨平台命令行工具，用于识别并报告SQL Server T-SQL脚本中的反平版和设计问题的存在。作为数据库开发人员，您可以在项目过程的早期很早就发现任何潜在的不良实践和设计问题 - 这确保了无摩擦的部署途径[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Developer’s Guide to Build 2025】开发人员的构建指南2025</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/a-developers-guide-to-build-2025</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Build 2025 is just around the corner (May 19-22), and we&amp;#8217;re fired up about all the developer-focused content we&amp;#8217;ve got lined up for you! Whether you&amp;#8217;re a Visual Studio power user, a VS Code fan, all about Azure, looking for the newest in .NET, or just pumped about AI in development, this year&amp;#8217;s Build is [&amp;hellip;]】Microsoft Build 2025即将临近（5月19日至22日），我们对所有以开发人员为中心的内容为您为您准备了！无论您是视觉工作室的电源用户，VS代码迷，所有关于Azure，正在寻找最新的.NET中，还是只是开发AI，今年的构建都是[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Developer CLI (azd) – May 2025】Azure开发人员CLI（AZD） -  2025年5月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-developer-cli-azd-may-2025</link>
      <description>【This post announces the May release of the Azure Developer CLI (`azd`).】这篇文章宣布了Azure开发人员CLI（AZD&#39;）的可能发布。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exchange Web Services code analyzer and usage report】Exchange Web服务代码分析仪和用法报告</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/exchange-web-services-code-analyzer-and-usage-report</link>
      <description>【We are less than 18 months away from the retirement of Exchange Web Services. Start planning your migration from EWS to Microsoft Graph.】我们距交易所网络服务退休不到18个月。开始规划您从EWS到Microsoft Graph的迁移。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integration testing with Dapr and Testcontainers】与DAPR和TestContainers的集成测试</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/external-data-handling-learnings</link>
      <description>【This blog post discusses setting up a Pytest integration test framework for a system using Dapr and Testcontainers. This framework was initially setup for a customer to suit their needs and it has been extracted into a sample project to provide a starting point.】这篇博客文章讨论了使用DAPR和TestContainers为系统设置Pytest集成测试框架。该框架最初是为客户设置的，以适应其需求，并将其提取到示例项目中以提供起点。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>