<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【The case of the image that came out horribly slanted: Negative stride】图像严重倾斜的情况：负步幅</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240906-00/?p=110228</link>
      <description>【It&#39;s all topsy-turvy.】一切都是颠倒的。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.23.1-1 and 1.22.7-1 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.23.1-1 和 1.22.7-1 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-23-1-1-and-1-22-7-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new set of Microsoft Go builds including security fixes is now available for download.】包含安全修复程序的一组新的 Microsoft Go 版本现已可供下载。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 20:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Graph APIs for Teams town hall now generally available】适用于 Teams 市政厅的 Microsoft Graph API 现已全面可用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-graph-apis-for-teams-town-hall-now-generally-available</link>
      <description>【Learn more about the general availability of new Teams town hall APIs and discover what&#39;s new.】详细了解新 Teams 市政厅 API 的一般可用性并发现新功能。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why is F# code so robust and reliable?】为什么 F# 代码如此健壮可靠？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/why-is-fsharp-code-so-robust-and-reliable</link>
      <description>【F# is not just for math and big data, it&#39;s a general purpose language that will greatly reduce the amount of bugs in your code.】F# 不仅仅适用于数学和大数据，它还是一种通用语言，可以大大减少代码中的错误数量。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Askia, an Ipsos company, achieved faster, reproducible builds with vcpkg】Askia（Ipsos 旗下公司）使用 vcpkg 实现了更快、可重复的构建</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/askia-an-ipsos-company-achieved-faster-reproducible-builds-with-vcpkg</link>
      <description>【vcpkg is a free and open-source C/C++ package manager maintained by Microsoft and the C++ community that runs on Windows, macOS, and Linux. Over the years we have heard from companies using vcpkg to manage dependencies at enterprise-scale. In this interview, I spoke to Dimitri Rochette, a lead developer at Askia, an Ipsos company, about [&amp;hellip;]】vcpkg 是由 Microsoft 和 C++ 社区维护的免费开源 C/C++ 包管理器，可在 Windows、macOS 和 Linux 上运行。多年来，我们听到一些公司使用 vcpkg 来管理企业规模的依赖关系。在这次采访中，我与 Ipsos 公司 Askia 的首席开发人员 Dimitri Rochette 谈论了 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 19:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Supercharge C++ Debugging with AI-Generated breakpoint expressions】使用 AI 生成的断点表达式增强 C++ 调试</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/supercharge-c-debugging-with-ai-generated-breakpoint-expressions</link>
      <description>【Have you ever spent hours debugging your C++ code, struggling to set up the right conditional breakpoint or tracepoint? Or wished for a smarter way to obtain detailed runtime information without manually crafting complex expressions? You&amp;#8217;re in luck! With Visual Studio 2022, the latest GitHub Copilot feature now offers AI-generated expressions for both conditional breakpoints [&amp;hellip;]】您是否曾经花费数小时调试 C++ 代码，努力设置正确的条件断点或跟踪点？或者希望有一种更智能的方式来获取详细的运行时信息，而无需手动制作复杂的表达式？你很幸运！在 Visual Studio 2022 中，最新的 GitHub Copilot 功能现在为两个条件断点提供 AI 生成的表达式 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 13:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the Office Add-ins Development Kit for Visual Studio Code (public preview)】宣布推出适用于 Visual Studio Code 的 Office 加载项开发工具包（公共预览版）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/announcing-the-office-add-ins-development-kit-for-visual-studio-code-public-preview</link>
      <description>【The Office Add-ins Development Kit is a new development tool to help you set up your environment, create Office Add-ins, and debug the code with a streamlined developer experience in Visual Studio Code.】Office 加载项开发工具包是一种新的开发工具，可帮助您设置环境、创建 Office 加载项并在 Visual Studio Code 中通过简化的开发人员体验调试代码。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript 5.6】发布 TypeScript 5.6</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-5-6</link>
      <description>【Today we&amp;#8217;re excited to announce the release of TypeScript 5.6! If you&amp;#8217;re not familiar with TypeScript, it&amp;#8217;s a language that builds on top of JavaScript by adding syntax for types. Types describe the shapes we expect of our variables, parameters, and functions, and the TypeScript type-checker can help catch issues like typos, missing properties, and [&amp;hellip;]】今天我们很高兴地宣布 TypeScript 5.6 发布！如果您不熟悉 TypeScript，它是一种通过添加类型语法构建在 JavaScript 之上的语言。类型描述了我们期望的变量、参数和函数的形状，TypeScript 类型检查器可以帮助捕获诸如拼写错误、缺少属性和 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 17:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Earning Agentic (and LangChain) Complexity】赚取代理（和 LangChain）复杂性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/earning-agentic-complexity</link>
      <description>【This post examines the challenges of adopting complex technologies like LangChain and agentic solutions in production environments, emphasizing the importance of understanding the necessity of such complexity. It provides insights on how to evaluate these technologies carefully, manage dependencies, and adhere to best practices for secure and stable AI applications.】这篇文章探讨了在生产环境中采用像 LangChain 这样的复杂技术和代理解决方案所面临的挑战，强调了理解这种复杂性的必要性的重要性。它提供了有关如何仔细评估这些技术、管理依赖关系以及遵守安全稳定人工智能应用程序最佳实践的见解。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub trick to find the commit that deleted a file】GitHub 找到删除文件的提交的技巧</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240909-00/?p=110234</link>
      <description>【Ask for the history of the file.】询问该文件的历史记录。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>