<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【January 2026 Insiders (version 1.109)】2026 年 1 月 Insider（版本 1.109）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/january-2026-insiders-(version-1.109)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code January 2026 Release (1.109). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 1 月版本 (1.109) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build AI Agents with Claude Agent SDK and Microsoft Agent Framework】使用 Claude Agent SDK 和 Microsoft Agent 框架构建 AI 代理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/build-ai-agents-with-claude-agent-sdk-and-microsoft-agent-framework</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Agent Framework now integrates with the Claude Agent SDK, enabling you to build AI agents powered by Claude&#39;s full agentic capabilities. This integration brings together the Agent Framework&#39;s consistent agent abstraction with Claude&#39;s powerful features, including fil】Microsoft Agent Framework 现在与 Claude Agent SDK 集成，使您能够构建由 Claude 完整代理功能支持的 AI 代理。这种集成将代理框架的一致代理抽象与 Claude 的强大功能结合在一起，包括 fil</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why not store the &lt;CODE&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/CODE&gt; reference count as a hidden allocation next to the &lt;CODE&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/CODE&gt;?】为什么不将 &lt;code&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/code&gt; 引用计数存储为 &lt;code&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/code&gt; 旁边的隐藏分配？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260130-00/?p=112025</link>
      <description>【When I described how Safe­Array­Add­Ref keeps its reference count in a side table, commenter Koro Unhallowed wondered】当我描述 SafeArrayAddRef 如何将其引用计数保存在侧表中时，评论者 Koro Unhallowed 表示想知道</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Developer CLI (azd) - January 2026: Configuration &amp; Performance】Azure 开发人员 CLI (azd) - 2026 年 1 月：配置和性能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-developer-cli-azd-january-2026</link>
      <description>【Welcome to the round up of the azd releases in January 2026! This blog post (covers release versions 1.23.0, 1.23.1,】欢迎来到 2026 年 1 月 azd 版本汇总！这篇博文（涵盖发行版本 1.23.0、1.23.1、</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (January 2026)】Azure SDK 版本（2026 年 1 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-january-2026</link>
      <description>【Thank you for your interest in the new Azure SDKs! We release new features, improvements, and bug fixes every month. Subscribe to our Azure SDK Blog RSS Feed to get notified when a new release is available. You can find links to packages, code, and docs on our】感谢您对新的 Azure SDK 的兴趣！我们每月都会发布新功能、改进和错误修复。订阅我们的 Azure SDK 博客 RSS 源，以便在新版本可用时收到通知。您可以在我们的网站上找到包、代码和文档的链接</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 22:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB TV Recap - From Burger to Bots – Agentic Apps with Cosmos DB and LangChain.js | Ep. 111】Azure Cosmos DB TV 回顾 - 从汉堡到机器人 – 使用 Cosmos DB 和 LangChain.js 的代理应用程序 | EP。 111</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-tv-recap-from-burger-to-bots-agentic-apps-with-cosmos-db-and-langchain-js-ep-111</link>
      <description>【In Episode 111 of Azure Cosmos DB TV, host Mark Brown is joined by Yohan Lasorsa to explore how developers can build agent-powered applications using a fully serverless architecture. This episode focuses on a practical, end-to-end exa】在 Azure Cosmos DB TV 第 111 集中，主持人 Mark Brown 与 Yohan Lasorsa 一起探索开发人员如何使用完全无服务器架构构建代理驱动的应用程序。本集重点介绍实用的端到端考试</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I retain access to the data in a &lt;CODE&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/CODE&gt; after my method returns?】在我的方法返回后，如何保留对 &lt;CODE&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/CODE&gt; 中数据的访问权限？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260129-00/?p=112023</link>
      <description>【The original problem our customer had was that the data in a SAFEARRAY disappeared even though they had called Safe­Array­Add­Ref. We learned why this is the case,】我们的客户最初遇到的问题是，即使他们调用了 SafeArrayAddRef，SAFEARRAY 中的数据也消失了。我们了解了为什么会出现这种情况，</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dev Proxy v2.1 with configuration hot reload and stdio proxying】Dev Proxy v2.1 具有配置热重载和 stdio 代理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/dev-proxy-v2-1-with-configuration-hot-reload-and-stdio-proxying</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re excited to announce the release of Dev Proxy v2.1.0! This release brings two major productivity features that developers have been asking for: automatic configuration hot reload and stdio traffic proxying - perfect for testing MCP servers and other stdio-based tools. In this version:】我们很高兴地宣布 Dev Proxy v2.1.0 发布！ 此版本带来了开发人员一直要求的两项主要生产力功能：自动配置热重载和 stdio 流量代理 - 非常适合测试 MCP 服务器和其他基于 stdio 的工具。在此版本中：</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the Microsoft Graph User Configuration API (preview)】Microsoft Graph 用户配置 API 简介（预览版）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/introducing-the-microsoft-graph-user-configuration-api-preview</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce the public preview of the User Configuration API in the Microsoft Graph beta endpoint. The User Configuration API is a new set of endpoints that you can use to create, read, update, and delete user configuration objects in Exchange Online mail folders.  User configuration objects—also】我们很高兴地宣布在 Microsoft Graph beta 端点中推出用户配置 API 的公共预览版。用户配置 API 是一组新的终结点，可用于在 Exchange Online 邮件文件夹中创建、读取、更新和删除用户配置对象。  用户配置对象——还有</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Diagnosing instability in production-scale agent reinforcement learning】诊断生产规模代理强化学习中的不稳定性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/engineering-at-microsoft/diagnosing-instability-in-production-scale-agent-rl</link>
      <description>【On January 28, 2026, Hugging Face announced that they have upstreamed the Post-Training Toolkit into TRL as a first-party integration, making these diagnostics directly usable in production RL and agent post-training pipelines. This enables closed-loop monitoring and control patterns that are increasingly necessary for】2026 年 1 月 28 日，Hugging Face 宣布他们已将训练后工具包作为第一方集成上游到 TRL 中，使这些诊断可直接在生产 RL 和代理训练后管道中使用。这使得闭环监控和控制模式变得越来越必要</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>