<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【May 2025: A look at the latest Microsoft Entra key feature releases, announcements, and updates】2025年5月：查看最新的Microsoft Entra密钥功能发布，公告和更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/eng-connect-feb-25-2</link>
      <description>【Welcome to the May edition of our monthly newsletter, summarizing the latest news and developments in the exciting, ever-evolving world of Microsoft Entra.】欢迎来到我们每月新闻通讯的5月版，总结了令人兴奋的，不断发展的微软Entra世界中的最新消息和发展。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Office Is Modernizing Their App Suite’s UI using Windows App SDK and React Native】Office如何使用Windows App SDK现代化其应用程序套件的UI并进行反应本地</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/react-native/2025-05-09-office-modernize</link>
      <description>【An inside look at how Office has modernized their UI with WinAppSDK and React Native.】内部查看了办公室如何使用Winappsdk进行了现代化的UI现代化，并对本地进行了反应。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I wait for Clipboard History to recognize a clipboard change before I change it again?】在我再次更改之前，如何等待剪贴板历史记录识别剪贴板更改？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250509-00/?p=111169</link>
      <description>【Listen for the change event.】听更改事件。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PIX 2505.09 – Revamped UX, Improved Usability, and Many New Features】PIX 2505.09  - 修改UX，提高可用性和许多新功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pix/pix-2505-09</link>
      <description>【Today we released PIX on Windows version 2505.09, which can be downloaded here. Since our preview announcement at GDC, we have been working hard to deliver the changes we promised and more. Today’s release includes many new improvements to PIX, including big overall changes and changes specific to GPU Captures and Timing Captures. Other improvements, [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们在Windows版本2505.09上发布了PIX，可以在此处下载。自从我们在GDC的预览公告以来，我们一直在努力提供我们承诺的更改以及更多的变化。今天的发布包括对PIX的许多新改进，包括大量的整体变化以及GPU捕获和时机捕获的特定变化。其他改进，[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python in Visual Studio Code – May 2025 Release】Visual Studio代码中的Python  -  2025年5月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/python-in-visual-studio-code-may-2025-release</link>
      <description>【The May 2025 release includes updates in the Python Environments extension, a new color picker added by Pylance, branch coverage support, and more!】2025年5月的发布包括在Python环境扩展中的更新，由Pylance添加的新颜色选择器，分支覆盖范围支持等等！</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 22:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【C# 14 – Exploring extension members】C＃14  - 探索扩展成员</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/csharp-exploring-extension-members</link>
      <description>【C# 14 introduces extension members. See how the `extension` syntax offers flexibility for extension authors and continuity for developers using extensions】C＃14介绍扩展成员。查看“扩展”语法如何为扩展作者提供灵活性和使用扩展的开发人员的连续性</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Claude-Ready Entra ID-Protected MCP Servers with Azure API Management】使用Azure API管理构建Claude准备就绪的ENTRA ID保护的MCP服务器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/claude-ready-secure-mcp-apim</link>
      <description>【With the launch of custom integrations in Claude, developers and enterprises can now extend Claude’s capabilities by connecting their own hosted Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers as native integrations. This capability allows Claude and any of its agents to perform complex tasks by invoking a variety of APIs exposed through MCP servers. Developers might wonder [&amp;hellip;]】随着Claude的自定义集成的启动，开发人员和企业现在可以通过将自己的托管模型上下文协议（MCP）服务器作为本机集成来扩展Claude的功能。该功能使Claude及其任何代理可以通过调用通过MCP服务器暴露的各种API来执行复杂的任务。开发人员可能会想知道[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The State of Coding the Future with Java and AI – May 2025】使用Java和AI编码未来的状态 -  2025年5月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/the-state-of-coding-the-future-with-java-and-ai</link>
      <description>【Software development is changing fast, and Java developers are right in the middle of it &amp;#8211; especially when it comes to using Artificial Intelligence (AI) in their apps. This report brings together feedback from 647 Java professionals to show where things stand and what is possible as Java and AI come together. One of the [&amp;hellip;]】软件开发正在快速变化，Java开发人员正好在其中间 - 尤其是在其应用程序中使用人工智能（AI）时。该报告汇集了647名Java专业人员的反馈，以展示事物的立场以及Java和AI在一起的可能性。中的一个 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Power status, CPU frequency and CPU C-State counters】电源状态，CPU频率和CPU C状态计数器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pix/power-status-cpu-frequency-and-cpu-c-state-counters</link>
      <description>【Starting with the 2505.09 release of PIX on Windows, new metrics have been added to help you optimize your title on battery powered devices such as tablets and Windows handheld gaming devices.  With these counters, you can see whether performance issues in your game can be correlated with power-related events, such as a change in [&amp;hellip;]】从Windows上的2505.09版本的Pix发布开始，已经添加了新的指标，以帮助您在电池电动设备（例如平板电脑和Windows手持式游戏设备）上优化标题。  使用这些计数器，您可以查看游戏中的性能问题是否可以与功率相关的事件相关，例如[…]的变化</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dubious security vulnerability: A program does not run correctly if you run it the wrong way, redux】可疑安全漏洞：如果以错误的方式运行程序，程序将无法正确运行，Redux</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250512-00/?p=111174</link>
      <description>【Trying to make the system run the program automatically.】试图使系统自动运行程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>