<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【A 10x Faster TypeScript】更快的打字稿10倍</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/typescript-native-port</link>
      <description>【Today I&amp;#8217;m excited to announce the next steps we&amp;#8217;re taking to radically improve TypeScript performance. The core value proposition of TypeScript is an excellent developer experience. As your codebase grows, so does the value of TypeScript itself, but in many cases TypeScript has not been able to scale up to the very largest codebases. Developers [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我很高兴宣布我们正在采取的下一步，以从根本上提高打字稿的性能。打字稿的核心价值主张是出色的开发人员体验。随着代码库的增长，打字稿本身的价值也随之增长，但是在许多情况下，Typescript无法扩展到最大的代码库。开发人员[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customer Case Study: INCM transforms legal accessibility with an AI Search Assistant】客户案例研究：INCM通过AI搜索助手改变法律可访问性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-incm-transforms-legal-accessibility-with-an-ai-search-assistant</link>
      <description>【Customer Case Study: INCM transforms legal accessibility with an AI Search Assistant The Imprensa Nacional-Casa da Moeda (INCM) is responsible for managing and publishing Portugal’s Diário da República (Official Gazette of the Republic of Portugal), which includes essential information for understanding laws, regulations, and legal processes. The quantity of information and the complex language used [&amp;hellip;]】客户案例研究：INCM通过AI搜索助理来改变法律访问性。Incrensanacional-casa da Moeda（INCM）负责管理和出版葡萄牙的DiárioDapropública（葡萄牙共和国的官方宪报），其中包括了解法律，法规和法律程序的必要信息。信息数量和所使用的复杂语言[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub Copilot Chat now available in public preview for Eclipse】GitHub Copilot聊天现已在Eclipse的公共预览中可用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/github-copilot-chat-now-available-in-public-preview-for-eclipse</link>
      <description>【Today, GitHub Copilot Chat is available in public preview for Eclipse!  This release follows the initial public preview of GitHub Copilot in Eclipse, which only supported code completions, and is available for all Eclipse users with access to GitHub Copilot.   After installing or updating GitHub Copilot for Eclipse, click on  in the bottom right corner [&amp;hellip;]】今天，Github Copilot聊天可以在Eclipse的公共预览中获得！  该版本遵循Eclipse中GitHub Copilot的首次公开预览，该预览仅支持代码完成，并且可用于所有Eclipse用户，均可访问GitHub Copilot。   安装或更新github副铜进行日食后，单击右下角[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New Boards Hub Update】新董事会中心更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/new-boards-hub-update-spring-2025</link>
      <description>【We&amp;#8217;ve reached a major milestone in the rollout of New Boards Hub this week by making it the default experience for all organizations and users. While many users can still temporarily switch back if they encounter a blocking issue, our telemetry shows that 97% of users are staying on New Boards without reverting. This is [&amp;hellip;]】本周，我们通过为所有组织和用户提供了默认体验，在推出新董事会中心方面达到了一个重要的里程碑。尽管许多用户遇到阻止问题，但仍可以暂时切换，但我们的遥测表明，有97％的用户在不恢复的情况下留在新板上。这是 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GPT-4o Copilot code completion model available now in Visual Studio public preview】GPT-4O Copilot代码完成模型现已在Visual Studio Public Preview中提供</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/gpt-4o-copilot-code-completion-model-available-now-in-visual-studio-public-preview</link>
      <description>【We are excited to announce that the new GPT-4o Copilot code completion model is now available for GitHub Copilot users in Visual Studio starting in 17.14 Preview 2! This new model, based on GPT-4o mini, has undergone additional training on over 275,000 high-quality public repositories across more than 30 popular programming languages. As a result, [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布，现在可以在17.14 Preview 2开始的Visual Studio中的Github Copilot用户使用新的GPT-4O Copilot代码完成模型！这种基于GPT-4O Mini的新模型已经接受了针对30多种流行编程语言的275,000多个高质量公共存储库的额外培训。因此， […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Implementing Chat History for AI Applications Using Azure Cosmos DB Go SDK】使用Azure Cosmos DB GO SDK实施AI应用程序的聊天历史记录</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/implementing-chat-history-for-ai-applications-using-azure-cosmos-db-go-sdk</link>
      <description>【This blog post covers how to build a chat history implementation using Azure Cosmos DB for NoSQL Go SDK and langchaingo. If you are new to the Go SDK, the sample chatbot application presented in the blog serves as a practical introduction, covering basic operations like read, upsert, etc. It also demonstrates using the Azure [&amp;hellip;]】这篇博客文章涵盖了如何使用NoSQL GO SDK和Langchaingo的Azure Cosmos DB构建聊天历史记录实现。如果您是GO SDK的新手，那么博客中介绍的示例聊天机器人应用程序将用作实用介绍，涵盖了Read，Upsert等基本操作。它还使用Azure […]演示了</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Replacing jackson-databind with azure-json and azure-xml】用Azure-Json和Azure-XML代替Jackson-Databind</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/replacing-jackson-databind-with-azure-json-and-azure-xml</link>
      <description>【This blog post explains how azure-json and azure-xml replaced jackson-databind in the Azure SDK for Java.】这篇博客文章解释了Azure-Json和Azure-XML如何在Java的Azure SDK中取代Jackson-Databind。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET and .NET Framework March 2025 servicing releases updates】.NET和.NET框架2025年3月服务发布更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-and-dotnet-framework-march-2025-servicing-updates</link>
      <description>【A recap of the latest servicing updates for .NET and .NET Framework for March 2025.】2025年3月的.NET和.NET框架的最新服务更新的回顾。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【March Patches for Azure DevOps Server】Azure DevOps服务器的三月补丁</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/march-patches-for-azure-devops-server-3</link>
      <description>【Today we are releasing patches that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server. We strongly encourage and recommend that all customers use the latest, most secure release of Azure DevOps Server. You can download the latest version of the product, Azure DevOps Server 2022.2 from the Azure DevOps Server download page. The following versions of [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们正在发布影响我们自托管产品Azure DevOps服务器的补丁。我们强烈鼓励并建议所有客户使用最新，最安全的Azure DevOps服务器。您可以从Azure Devops Server下载页面下载最新版本的产品Azure Devops Server 2022.2。以下版本的[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What an insightful observation, you get to wear “the hat”】多么有见地的观察，你可以戴上“帽子”</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250311-00/?p=110958</link>
      <description>【Maybe not so insightful.】也许不是那么有见地。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>