<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub Copilot app modernization for Java 公共预览版发布】GitHub Copilot app modernization for Java 公共预览版发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java-ch/github-copilot-app-modernization-for-java</link>
      <description>【现代化 Java 应用程序并将其迁移到云端，往往是一个复杂、耗时且碎片化的过程。GitHub Copilot app modernization for Java旨在简化并加速这一迁移过程，助力您顺利迈向云端。 该工具现已在 Visual Studio Code Marketplace 上以单一插件包形式公开预览。GitHub Copilot Java app modernization for Java为 Java 升级与现代化提供了智能、可指导的路径——可自动化重复性任务、提升一致性并降低风险。 六大核心价值 1. 智能问题分析与推荐现代化始于洞察。无论是升级 Java 运行时，还是迁移到 Azure，首要步骤是了解您的代码。该工具可分析项目当前状态并生成计划，结合 Azure Migrate 应用代码评估工具（AppCAT）提供上下文感知的修复建议和可操作的推荐，助您从诊断问题转向实际改造。AppCAT 也可作为独立 CLI 工具使用，详见 AppCAT for Java。 2. 专家驱动的代码转换在生成迁移计划后，GitHub Copilot app modernization for Java利用强大的代码转换引擎，融合专家制定的迁移策略与自动化 Java 升级流程。从 Java 8 升级到 Java 21，或迁移到 Azure 服务平台，Copilot 均可精准地应用结构化变更。 在云端现代化场景中，工具提供预定义的 [&amp;hellip;]】现代化 Java 应用程序并将其迁移到云端，往往是一个复杂、耗时且碎片化的过程。GitHub Copilot app modernization for Java旨在简化并加速这一迁移过程，助力您顺利迈向云端。 该工具现已在 Visual Studio Code Marketplace 上以单一插件包形式公开预览。GitHub Copilot Java app modernization for Java为 Java 升级与现代化提供了智能、可指导的路径——可自动化重复性任务、提升一致性并降低风险。 六大核心价值 1. 智能问题分析与推荐现代化始于洞察。无论是升级 Java 运行时，还是迁移到 Azure，首要步骤是了解您的代码。该工具可分析项目当前状态并生成计划，结合 Azure Migrate 应用代码评估工具（AppCAT）提供上下文感知的修复建议和可操作的推荐，助您从诊断问题转向实际改造。AppCAT 也可作为独立 CLI 工具使用，详见 AppCAT for Java。 2. 专家驱动的代码转换在生成迁移计划后，GitHub Copilot app modernization for Java利用强大的代码转换引擎，融合专家制定的迁移策略与自动化 Java 升级流程。从 Java 8 升级到 Java 21，或迁移到 Azure 服务平台，Copilot 均可精准地应用结构化变更。 在云端现代化场景中，工具提供预定义的 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【One Pipeline to Rule Them All: Ensuring CodeQL Scanning Results and Dependency Scanning Results Go to the Intended Repository】一条统治所有这些的管道：确保CODEQL扫描结果和依赖扫描结果转到预期的存储库</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/one-pipeline-to-rule-them-all-codeql-dependency-scanning</link>
      <description>【&amp;#8220;One Ring to rule them all, One Ring to find them, One Ring to bring them all, and in the darkness bind them.&amp;#8221; – J.R.R. Tolkien, The Lord of the Rings In the world of code scanning and dependency scanning, your pipeline is the One Ring—a single definition that can orchestrate scans across multiple repositories. [&amp;hellip;]】“一个戒指统治它们，一个戒指可以找到它们，一个戒指将它们全部带来，而在黑暗中将它们束缚在一起。” -  J.R.R.托尔金（Tolkien）是《守则扫描和依赖扫描世界》中的指环王，您的管道是一个环，这是一个单一的定义，可以在多个存储库中进行扫描。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure MCP Server – May 2025 Release】Azure MCP服务器 -  2025年5月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-mcp-server-may-2025-release</link>
      <description>【This post discusses the updates to the Azure MCP (Model Context Protocol) Server for Microsoft //build 2025.】这篇文章讨论了Microsoft // build 2025的Azure MCP（模型上下文协议）服务器的更新。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Azure Command Launcher for Java】宣布Java的Azure命令发射器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/announcing-azure-command-launcher-for-java</link>
      <description>【Optimizing JVM Configuration for Azure Deployments Tuning the Java Virtual Machine (JVM) for cloud deployments is notoriously challenging. Over 30% of developers tend to deploy Java workloads with no JVM configuration at all, therefore relying on the default settings of the HotSpot JVM. The default settings in OpenJDK are intentionally conservative, designed to work across [&amp;hellip;]】优化用于Azure部署的JVM配置调整Java虚拟机（JVM）以进行云部署是挑战。超过30％的开发人员倾向于完全没有JVM配置部署Java工作负载，因此依赖于热点JVM的默认设置。 OpenJDK中的默认设置有意保守，旨在跨[…]工作。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET Aspire 9.3 is here and enhanced with GitHub Copilot!】。</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-dotnet-aspire-93</link>
      <description>【.NET Aspire 9.3 is the biggest release of .NET Aspire yet, with the introduction of GitHub Copilot directly into the .NET Aspire Dashboard, updates for integrations, app model enhancements, and more.】。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the Microsoft 365 Agents Toolkit】引入Microsoft 365代理工具包</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/introducing-the-microsoft-365-agents-toolkit</link>
      <description>【Read how the Microsoft 365 Agents Toolkit, an evolution of Microsoft Teams Toolkit, is designed to help developers build agents and apps for Microsoft 365 Copilot, Microsoft Teams, and Microsoft 365.】阅读Microsoft 365代理工具包（Microsoft Teams Toolkit的演变）如何旨在帮助开发人员为Microsoft 365 Copilot，Microsoft Teams和Microsoft 365构建代理和应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announced at Build 2025: Foundry connection for Azure Cosmos DB, Global Secondary Index, full-text search, and more】宣布在2025年的Build：Azure Cosmos DB，全球次要索引，全文搜索等等的铸造厂连接等</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/announced-at-build-2025-foundry-connection-for-azure-cosmos-db-global-secondary-index-full-text-search-and-more</link>
      <description>【The countdown to innovation has begun: Day 1 of Microsoft Build 2025 bought several new announcements, demos, and live coding sessions to in-person and online audiences, showcasing the potential of cloud-native and AI-driven applications. Azure Cosmos DB is at the forefront of this innovation. From powering multi-agent applications and unlocking high-speed analytics to delivering new [&amp;hellip;]】创新的倒计时已经开始：Microsoft Build 2025的第1天购买了几个新公告，演示和实时编码会议，并向面对面和在线观众购买，展示了云本地和AI-Driven驱动的应用程序的潜力。 Azure Cosmos DB处于这项创新的最前沿。从为多代理应用程序供电并解锁高速分析到提供新的[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 23:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure DevOps with GitHub Repositories – Your path to Agentic AI】带有GitHub存储库的Azure Devops  - 您通往代理AI的途径</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/azure-devops-with-github-repositories-your-path-to-agentic-ai</link>
      <description>【GitHub Copilot has evolved beyond a coding assistant in the IDE into an agentic teammate – providing actionable feedback on pull requests, fixing bugs and implementing new features, creating pull requests and responding to feedback, and much more. These new capabilities will transform every aspect of the software development lifecycle, as we are already seeing [&amp;hellip;]】Github Copilot已经发展到IDE中的编码助手超越代理队的成员 - 提供了有关拉的请求，修复错误并实施新功能，创建拉动请求并响应反馈等的可行反馈。这些新功能将改变软件开发生命周期的各个方面，因为我们已经看到[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why does Windows report my processor speed twice, with slightly different values?】Windows为什么要报告我的处理器速度两次，值略有不同？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250520-00/?p=111201</link>
      <description>【One is calculated. The other is self-promotion.】计算一个。另一个是自我促进。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agent mode for every developer】每个开发人员的代理模式</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/agent-mode-for-every-developer</link>
      <description>【At the beginning of April, agent mode rolled out to all users in Visual Studio Code. Since then, we’ve seen and heard how developers are embracing this tool and using it to transform their workflows. Now, just six weeks later, we’re excited to announce that it’s available to all developers using VS Code, Visual Studio, [&amp;hellip;]】在4月初，Agent Mode将Visual Studio代码中的所有用户推出。从那以后，我们看到并听到了开发人员如何拥抱此工具并使用它来改变他们的工作流程。现在，仅仅六周后，我们很高兴地宣布，使用VS代码，Visual Studio，[…]的所有开发人员都可以使用它。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>