<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【November 2025 Insiders (version 1.107)】2025 年 11 月 Insider（版本 1.107）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/november-2025-insiders-(version-1.107)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code November 2025 Release (1.107). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2025 年 11 月版本 (1.107) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSSQL Extension for VS Code: Introducing Edit Data (Public Preview)】VS Code 的 MSSQL 扩展：引入编辑数据（公共预览版）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/vscode-mssql-edit-data</link>
      <description>【Overview Working with table data is an essential part of database development — whether you’re validating behavior, debugging issues, or quickly seeding data. But switching between tools or writing repetitive T-SQL statements can slow down your workflow.】概述 使用表数据是数据库开发的重要组成部分 - 无论您是要验证行为、调试问题还是快速播种数据。但在工具之间切换或编写重复的 T-SQL 语句可能会减慢您的工作流程。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New release cadence and support lifecycle for Microsoft C++ Build Tools】Microsoft C++ 构建工具的新发布节奏和支持生命周期</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/new-release-cadence-and-support-lifecycle-for-msvc-build-tools</link>
      <description>【Starting with Visual Studio 2026, we are introducing a new support lifecycle for the Microsoft C++ (MSVC) Build Tools. We are also updating the MSVC release cadence. As Visual Studio moves to a Modern】从 Visual Studio 2026 开始，我们将为 Microsoft C++ (MSVC) 构建工具引入新的支持生命周期。我们还在更新 MSVC 发布节奏。随着 Visual Studio 转向现代</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio – Built for the Speed of Modern Development】Visual Studio – 专为现代开发速度而打造</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-built-for-the-speed-of-modern-development</link>
      <description>【The release of Visual Studio 2026 two weeks ago marks the next evolution in Microsoft’s 50-year commitment to deliver the tools that developers love and enterprises trust, built to move at the pace of modern development. Software development is moving faster than ever, and Visual Studio is evolving right along with you. Today, we’re ann】两周前发布的 Visual Studio 2026 标志着 Microsoft 50 年来致力于提供开发人员喜爱和企业信任的工具的下一步发展，这些工具旨在跟上现代开发的步伐。软件开发的发展速度比以往任何时候都快，Visual Studio 也在与您一起发展。今天，我们是安</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why does XAML break down when I have an element that is half a billion pixels tall?】当我有一个 5 亿像素高的元素时，为什么 XAML 会崩溃？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251124-00/?p=111811</link>
      <description>【A customer reported that their program encountered rendering problems when they created elements that were a half billion pixels tall, and they wondered why this was happening. A half billion pixels is an awful lot of pixels. At 96 pixels per inch, that gives you an element whose height is over 82 miles (132 km). There is no monitor】一位客户报告说，他们的程序在创建 5 亿像素高的元素时遇到了渲染问题，他们想知道为什么会发生这种情况。五亿像素是一个非常多的像素。如果采用每英寸 96 像素，则元素的高度将超过 82 英里（132 公里）。没有监视器</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SharePoint Site Creation in Microsoft Graph】在 Microsoft Graph 中创建 SharePoint 网站</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/sharepoint-site-creation-in-microsoft-graph</link>
      <description>【The SharePoint team is excited to (finally) bring Site Collection creation to Graph! Starting in Microsoft Graph beta you can now create new site collections! But that’s not all! Creating site collections through older APIs required that your application have Si】SharePoint 团队很高兴（最终）将网站集创建引入 Graph！从 Microsoft Graph Beta 版开始，您现在可以创建新的网站集！但这还不是全部！通过旧版 API 创建网站集要求您的应用程序具有 Si</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing OData .NET (ODL) 9 Preview 3 Release】宣布发布 OData .NET (ODL) 9 预览版 3</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/odata/announcing-odata-net-odl-9-preview-3-release</link>
      <description>【We’re happy to announce that OData .NET (ODL) 9 Preview 3 has been officially released and is available on NuGet: Microsoft.OData.Core 9.0.0 Preview 3】我们很高兴地宣布 OData .NET (ODL) 9 Preview 3 已正式发布并可在 NuGet 上使用：Microsoft.OData.Core 9.0.0 Preview 3</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ignite 2025: A Developer’s Guide to Building Agents for Microsoft 365】Ignite 2025：为 Microsoft 365 构建代理的开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/ignite-2025-a-developers-guide-to-building-agents-for-microsoft-365</link>
      <description>【Ignite 2025 brought many innovations for developers building agents for Microsoft 365. From new capabilities in Declarative Agents and Custom Engine Agents to the introduction of Microsoft Agent 365, the platform now enables organizations to arch】Ignite 2025 为开发人员构建 Microsoft 365 代理带来了许多创新。从声明式代理和自定义引擎代理的新功能到 Microsoft Agent 365 的引入，该平台现在使组织能够构建</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maybe somebody can explain to me how weak references solve the ODR problem】也许有人可以向我解释弱引用如何解决 ODR 问题</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251121-00/?p=111807</link>
      <description>【Some time ago, I proposed Using type aliasing to avoid the ODR problem with conditional compilation. A Reddit thread claimed that &#34;】前段时间，我提出使用类型别名来避免条件编译的 ODR 问题。 Reddit 的一个帖子声称“</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Develop Faster with VS Code for the Web – Azure: Your Browser-Based Dev Environment】使用 VS Code for the Web 加快开发速度 – Azure：基于浏览器的开发环境</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/get-started-with-vs-code-for-the-web</link>
      <description>【Developers can now move from idea to Azure-ready code in minutes with VS Code for the Web – Azure. This browser-based environment removes setup time, reduces friction, and gives you immediate access to pre-configured run】现在，开发人员可以使用 VS Code for the Web – Azure 在几分钟内从想法转变为 Azure 就绪代码。这种基于浏览器的环境消除了设置时间，减少了摩擦，并让您可以立即访问预配置的运行</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>