<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How is the Windows.Foundation.Uri.Domain property different from Host?】Windows.Foundation.Uri.Domain 属性与 Host 有何不同？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240829-00/?p=110192</link>
      <description>【It&#39;s an educated guess.】这是一个有根据的猜测。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft 365 Certification control spotlight: Patch management】Microsoft 365 认证控制焦点：补丁管理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-365-certification-control-spotlight-patch-management</link>
      <description>【Discover how Microsoft 365 Certification validates patching best practices for enterprise-ready apps.】了解 Microsoft 365 认证如何验证企业就绪应用程序的修补最佳实践。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 19:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New GitHub Copilot features in Visual Studio 2022 17.11】Visual Studio 2022 17.11 中的 GitHub Copilot 新功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/new-github-copilot-features-in-visual-studio-2022-17-11</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio 2022 17.11 now brings exciting advancements from GitHub Copilot! This release significantly improves how GitHub Copilot integrates into your development workflow, offering smarter and more intuitive coding assistance. Discover the new GitHub Copilot features in Visual Studio, such as enhanced context understanding,】Visual Studio 2022 17.11 现在带来了来自 GitHub Copilot 的令人兴奋的进步！此版本显着改进了 GitHub Copilot 集成到开发工作流程中的方式，提供更智能、更直观的编码帮助。探索 Visual Studio 中的新 GitHub Copilot 功能，例如增强的上下文理解、</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dev Proxy v0.20 with improved simulating API errors and a new API for building integrations】Dev Proxy v0.20 改进了模拟 API 错误和用于构建集成的新 API</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/dev-proxy-v0-20-with-improved-simulating-api-errors-and-a-new-api-for-building-integrations</link>
      <description>【Discover what&#39;s new in the latest version of Dev Proxy to help you build robust apps connected to APIs.】了解最新版本的 Dev Proxy 中的新增功能，帮助您构建连接到 API 的强大应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 06:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Protecting against Prompt Injection Attacks in Chat Prompts】防范聊天提示中的提示注入攻击</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/protecting-against-prompt-injection-attacks-in-chat-prompts</link>
      <description>【Semantic Kernel allows prompts to be automatically converted to ChatHistory instances. Developers can create prompts which include &amp;lt;message&amp;gt; tags and these will be parsed (using an XML parser) and converted into instances of ChatMessageContent. See mapping of prompt syntax to completion service model for more information.】语义内核允许提示自动转换为 ChatHistory 实例。开发人员可以创建包含 &lt;message&gt; 标签的提示，这些提示将被解析（使用 XML 解析器）并转换为 ChatMessageContent 的实例。有关详细信息，请参阅提示语法到完成服务模型的映射。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 15:53:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【BinaryFormatter removed from .NET 9】BinaryFormatter 从 .NET 9 中删除</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/binaryformatter-removed-from-dotnet-9</link>
      <description>【Starting with .NET 9, we no longer include an implementation of BinaryFormatter in the runtime. This post covers what options you have to move forward.】从 .NET 9 开始，我们不再在运行时中包含 BinaryFormatter 的实现。这篇文章介绍了您必须采取哪些选择才能继续前进。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【We are deprecating earlier versions of Visual Studio for Dynamics 365 for Finance and Operations development】我们将弃用早期版​​本的 Visual Studio for Dynamics 365 用于财务和运营开发</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/we-are-deprecating-earlier-versions-of-visual-studio-for-dynamics-365-for-finance-and-operations-development</link>
      <description>【Abstract Microsoft will no longer be shipping or supporting the Visual Studio extensions supporting development work against Dynamics 365 for Finance and Operations, and for the Power Platform tools, for Visual Studio versions other than Visual Studio 2022. What will change?】摘要 Microsoft 将不再发布或支持 Visual Studio 扩展，这些扩展支持针对 Dynamics 365 for Finance and Operations、Power Platform 工具、Visual Studio 2022 以外的 Visual Studio 版本的开发工作。将会发生什么变化？</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 22:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Vector Support EAP extended to Azure SQL MI】Vector 支持 EAP 扩展到 Azure SQL MI</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/vector-support-eap-extended-to-azure-sql-mi</link>
      <description>【If you are looking forward to build AI-enabled applications on your own data, you&amp;#8217;ll be excited to know that the Early Adopter Preview announced for Azure SQL DB on native vector capabilities is now available also for those who have data stored in Azure SQL Managed Instance!】如果您希望在自己的数据上构建支持 AI 的应用程序，那么您会很高兴知道针对 Azure SQL DB 宣布的基于本机矢量功能的早期采用者预览版现在也可供那些将数据存储在 Azure SQL 中的用户使用托管实例！</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing .NET Aspire 8.2 – Goodbye Components, Hello Integrations!】发布 .NET Aspire 8.2 – 再见组件，你好集成！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-aspire-8-2</link>
      <description>【.NET Aspire 8.2 is here with some nice updates for components... we mean integrations! Learn more about this rename, what it means for you, and what the teams has been adding to testing in .NET Aspire!】.NET Aspire 8.2 在这里对组件进行了一些不错的更新...我们指的是集成！了解有关此重命名的更多信息、它对您意味着什么，以及团队在 .NET Aspire 测试中添加的内容！</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamline your workflow: Embracing Adaptive Cards Templating】简化您的工作流程：采用自适应卡片模板</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/streamline-your-workflow-embracing-adaptive-cards-templating</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to continue our journey with the adaptivecards-templating package, a more robust and streamlined approach to creating Adaptive Cards.】我们很高兴能够继续我们的自适应卡模板包之旅，这是一种更强大、更简化的创建自适应卡的方法。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 15:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>