<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【General Availability for Data API in vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB】基于Vcore的Azure Cosmos DB中数据API的一般可用性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/general-availability-for-data-api-in-vcore-based-azure-cosmos-db-for-mongodb</link>
      <description>【Title: General Availability for Data API in vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB We’re excited to announce the general availability of the Data API for vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB! Overview The Data API is a RESTful HTTPS interface that enables developers to interact with their MongoDB data hosted in vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB [&amp;hellip;]】标题：基于Vcore的Azure Cosmos DB中数据API的一般可用性，我们很高兴宣布MongoDB的基于VCore的Azure Cosmos DB的数据API的一般可用性！概述数据API是一个恢复的HTTPS接口，使开发人员能够与基于VCore的Azure Cosmos DB中托管的MongODB数据进行交互[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Prepare your Office Add-in for the European Accessibility Act (EAA)】为《欧洲可访问性法》（EAA）准备办公室加载项</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/prepare-your-office-add-in-for-the-european-accessibility-act</link>
      <description>【Starting June 28, 2025, the European Accessibility Act (EAA) takes effect, requiring all digital products and services offered to EU customers to meet comprehensive accessibility standards. If you&#39;re developing Office Add-ins, this may impact you. This blog explains what you need to know to ensure your Office Add-ins are compliant.】从2025年6月28日开始，《欧洲可及性法》（EAA）生效，要求提供给欧盟客户的所有数字产品和服务以符合全面的可访问性标准。如果您正在开发办公室加载项，这可能会影响您。该博客解释了您需要知道的知识，以确保您的办公室加载项合规。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB with DiskANN Part 4: Stable Vector Search Recall with Streaming Data】Azure Cosmos DB，带DISKANN第4部分：稳定的矢量搜索召回与流数据</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-with-diskann-part-4-stable-vector-search-recall-with-streaming-data</link>
      <description>【Vector search with Azure Cosmos DB  In Part 1 and Part 2 of this series, we explored vector search with Azure Cosmos DB and best practices for scaling it to 1 billion vector datasets while maintaining low query latency. In Part 3, we saw how we can create efficient sharded DiskANN indices for multi-tenant apps.  [&amp;hellip;]】在本系列的第1部分和第2部分中，使用Azure Cosmos DB进行矢量搜索，我们通过Azure Cosmos DB探索了矢量搜索，以及将其扩展到10亿个矢量数据集的最佳实践，同时保持低查询延迟。在第3部分中，我们看到了如何为多租户应用程序创建高效的碎片迪斯坎索引。  […]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Nested App Authentication: Now generally available across Microsoft 365】嵌套应用程序身份验证：现在通常在Microsoft 365上找到</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/nested-app-authentication-now-generally-available-across-microsoft-365</link>
      <description>【Get started with Nested App Authentication, a modern protocol for simplifying authentication for Personal Tab Teams apps that run across Microsoft 365.】开始使用Nested App Authentication，这是一种现代协议，用于简化Microsoft 365运行的个人选项卡团队的身份验证。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.24.3-1 and 1.23.9-1 Microsoft builds now available】GO 1.24.3-1和1.23.9-1 Microsoft现在可用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-24-3-1-and-1-23-9-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new release of the Microsoft build of Go including security fixes is now available for download.】现在可以下载Microsoft Go Build的新版本。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Efficiently and Elegantly Modeling Embeddings in Azure SQL and SQL Server】在Azure SQL和SQL Server中有效，优雅地建模嵌入</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/efficiently-and-elegantly-modeling-embeddings-in-azure-sql-and-sql-server</link>
      <description>【Storing and querying text embeddings in a database it might seem challenging, but with the right schema design, it&amp;#8217;s not only possible, it&amp;#8217;s powerful. Whether you’re building AI-powered search, semantic filtering, or recommendation features, embeddings, and thus vectors, are now a first-class data type. So how do you model them well inside a database like [&amp;hellip;]】存储和查询数据库中的文本嵌入方式似乎具有挑战性，但是有了正确的模式设计，它不仅有可能强大。无论您是构建AI驱动的搜索，语义过滤还是推荐功能，嵌入以及矢量现在都是一流的数据类型。因此，您如何在[…]之类的数据库中对其进行良好的建模。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why we built our startup in C#】为什么我们在C＃中构建了初创企业</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/why-we-built-our-startup-in-csharp</link>
      <description>【Tracebit built their B2B SaaS security product using C#.】TraceBit使用C＃构建了其B2B SaaS安全产品。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fedora Linux is now an official WSL distro】Fedora Linux现在是官方WSL发行版</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/fedora-linux-is-now-an-official-wsl-distro</link>
      <description>【We’re pleased to announce that one of the latest additions to the list of official WSL distros is Fedora Linux! The Fedora Project has taken advantage of WSL’s new tar-based architecture to produce WSL images beginning with Fedora 42. Try it out To install it, run wsl –-install FedoraLinux-42and then launch it with wsl –d [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布，官方WSL发行版列表中的最新添加是Fedora Linux！ Fedora Project已利用WSL的新基于TAR的体系结构来生产以Fedora 42开头的WSL图像。尝试安装它，运行WSL  - 安装Fedoralinux-42，然后使用WSL –D […]启动它。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Developer CLI (azd) – May 2025】Azure开发人员CLI（AZD） -  2025年5月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-developer-cli-azd-may-2025</link>
      <description>【This post announces the May release of the Azure Developer CLI (`azd`).】这篇文章宣布了Azure开发人员CLI（AZD&#39;）的可能发布。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 17:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What were the MS-DOS programs that the moricons.dll icons were intended for?】Moricons.dll图标的意图是什么MS-DOS程序？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250507-00/?p=111157</link>
      <description>【Tallying them up.】将它们付诸实践。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>