<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Cost and Performance Improvements with Azure Cosmos DB’s Binary Encoding】宣布通过 Azure Cosmos DB 的二进制编码实现成本和性能改进</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/announcing-cost-and-performance-improvements-with-azure-cosmos-dbs-binary-encoding</link>
      <description>【We are excited to announce a significant enhancement to Azure Cosmos DB, bringing substantial cost savings and performance improvements to our users. The new binary encoding feature is now available for new containers and will soon be available for existing ones. What is Binary Encoding? Binary encoding converts JSON or other text-based data formats into [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布对 Azure Cosmos DB 进行重大增强，为我们的用户带来大量成本节省和性能改进。新的二进制编码功能现已可用于新容器，并且很快将可用于现有容器。什么是二进制编码？二进制编码将 JSON 或其他基于文本的数据格式转换为 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Common annotated security keys】常见的带注释的安全密钥</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/engineering-at-microsoft/common-annotated-security-keys</link>
      <description>【In April 2021, GitHub announced changes to their security token format that significantly enhanced security. The improvement leveraged two straightforward techniques: a fixed signature in the generated token and a checksum &amp;#8211; both of which are highly effective in eliminating false positives (noise) and false negatives (missed findings). Microsoft also implements these techniques widely in [&amp;hellip;]】2021 年 4 月，GitHub 宣布更改其安全令牌格式，显着增强了安全性。该改进利用了两种简单的技术：生成的令牌中的固定签名和校验和——这两种技术在消除误报（噪声）和漏报（遗漏发现）方面非常有效。微软还在[...]中广泛实施了这些技术</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 18:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the GA of Dynamic Scaling (Per Region and Per Partition Autoscale)】宣布动态扩展正式发布（按区域和按分区自动缩放）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/announcing-the-ga-of-dynamic-scaling-per-region-and-per-partition-autoscale</link>
      <description>【We are excited to announce the GA of Azure Cosmos DB dynamic scaling – among multiple new features (Binary Encoding, Reserved Capacity) released recently to make your Azure Cosmos DB workloads even more cost efficient. Dynamic scaling is an enhancement to autoscale which provides cost optimization for nonuniform workloads. In the earlier version of autoscale, [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布 Azure Cosmos DB 动态扩展正式发布，其中包括最近发布的多项新功能（二进制编码、预留容量），可让您的 Azure Cosmos DB 工作负载更具成本效益。动态扩展是自动扩展的增强功能，可为非均匀工作负载提供成本优化。在早期版本的自动缩放中，[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Sep 2024: A look at the latest Microsoft Entra key feature releases, announcements, and updates】2024 年 9 月：查看最新的 Microsoft Entra 关键功能版本、公告和更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/eng-connect-sep-24</link>
      <description>【An overview of the latest updates in Microsoft Entra for Sep 2024. Discover how these new capabilities can be integrated into your projects for optimal performance and security.】Microsoft Entra 2024 年 9 月最新更新概述。了解如何将这些新功能集成到您的项目中，以获得最佳性能和安全性。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft 365 Certification control spotlight: Secure software development and deployment】Microsoft 365 认证控制焦点：安全软件开发和部署</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-365-certification-control-spotlight-secure-software-development-and-deployment</link>
      <description>【Explore how Microsoft 365 Certification validates secure software development and deployment best practices.】探索 Microsoft 365 认证如何验证安全软件开发和部署最佳实践。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting started with testing and .NET Aspire】测试和 .NET Aspire 入门</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/getting-started-with-testing-and-dotnet-aspire</link>
      <description>【Learn how to improve your software development process with automated testing in .NET Aspire. This post covers the basics of getting started, writing tests for distributed applications, and ensuring your services run smoothly.】了解如何通过 .NET Aspire 中的自动化测试改进软件开发流程。这篇文章涵盖了入门、为分布式应用程序编写测试以及确保服务顺利运行的基础知识。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Security Update: Changes to URI Expiry Time in Azure Notification Hubs】安全更新：Azure 通知中心中 URI 过期时间的更改</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-notification-hubs/security-update-changes-to-uri-expiry-time-in-azure-notification-hubs</link>
      <description>【As part of our ongoing efforts to enhance the security of Azure Notification Hubs, we are making an important change to the expiry time of the generated URIs. Starting from October 2024, the expiry time of PnsErrorDetailsUri will be reduced from 10 days to 5 days. This means that the PnsErrorDetailsUri returned will now be [&amp;hellip;]】作为我们增强 Azure 通知中心安全性的持续努力的一部分，我们正在对生成的 URI 的到期时间进行重要更改。从2024年10月开始，PnsErrorDetailsUri的过期时间将从10天减少到5天。这意味着返回的 PnsErrorDetailsUri 现在将是 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Organize Your Breakpoints like a pro】像专业人士一样组织您的断点</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/organize-your-breakpoints-like-a-pro</link>
      <description>【Do you feel overwhelmed by the sheer number of breakpoints in your Visual Studio project? Wish you could categorize and toggle them on and off with ease? The new breakpoint group feature in Visual Studio 2022 is here to transform your debugging experience. Breakpoint groups allow you to create custom collections of breakpoints and apply [&amp;hellip;]】您是否对 Visual Studio 项目中断点的数量感到不知所措？希望您可以轻松地对它们进行分类并打开和关闭它们？ Visual Studio 2022 中的新断点组功能将改变您的调试体验。断点组允许您创建自定义断点集合并应用[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 10:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating AI into Business Processes with the Process Framework】通过流程框架将人工智能集成到业务流程中</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/integrating-ai-into-business-processes-with-the-process-framework</link>
      <description>【As organizations look to enhance efficiency and decision-making, the integration of AI into business processes has become increasingly important. The new Process Framework for Microsoft Semantic Kernel empowers developers to seamlessly embed AI into their workflows, providing a structured approach to optimizing daily operations. Not sure what a business process is? A Process is a structured sequence [&amp;hellip;]】随着组织寻求提高效率和决策能力，将人工智能集成到业务流程中变得越来越重要。 Microsoft Semantic Kernel 的新流程框架使开发人员能够将 AI 无缝嵌入到他们的工作流程中，从而提供优化日常运营的结构化方法。不确定什么是业务流程？流程是一个结构化序列[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Another example of the Windows Runtime interop pattern: Using the UserConsentVerifier from a Win32 program】Windows 运行时互操作模式的另一个示例：使用 Win32 程序中的 UserConsentVerifier</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240925-00/?p=110312</link>
      <description>【Following the standard pattern.】遵循标准模式。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>