<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【ASP.NET Core on .NET Framework servicing release advisory: ASP.NET Core 2.3】ASP.NET核心在.NET框架服务释放咨询：ASP.NET Core 2.3</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/servicing-release-advisory-aspnetcore-23</link>
      <description>【ASP.NET Core 2.1 has been reshipped as ASP.NET Core 2.3 to help users on the unsupported ASP.NET Core 2.2 move to a supported version.】ASP.NET Core 2.1已作为ASP.NET Core 2.3重新研究，以帮助用户在未支持的ASP.NET Core 2.2上移动到受支持的版本。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Azure OpenAI Chat Completion with data source and Function Calling】使用数据源和功能调用的Azure OpenAI聊天完成</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/using-azure-openai-chat-completion-with-data-source-and-function-calling</link>
      <description>【Azure OpenAI Chat Completion with data source provides powerful capabilities for integrating conversational AI into applications. However, using a data source and function calling in a single request is not supported yet. When both features are enabled, function calling is ignored, and only the data source is used. This presents a challenge when retrieving information, [&amp;hellip;]】Azure OpenAI聊天完成数据源为将对话AI集成到应用程序中提供了强大的功能。但是，在单个请求中使用数据源和调用函数尚不支持。启用两个功能后，忽略了函数调用，并且仅使用数据源。这在检索信息时提出了一个挑战，[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 01:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【On exactly when XAML bindings are evaluated if an element is not yet loaded】如果尚未加载元素，则准确评估XAML绑定</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250205-00/?p=110840</link>
      <description>【It depends on which abstraction you prefer.】这取决于您喜欢哪种抽象。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Azure OpenAI Realtime API Support in JavaScript】在JavaScript中引入Azure Openai实时API支持</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/introducing-azure-openai-realtime-api-support-in-javascript</link>
      <description>【Introducing the new Realtime API support in the OpenAI JavaScript library, enabling developers to create highly interactive and responsive applications by instantly sending and receiving messages from Azure OpenAI models.】在OpenAI JavaScript库中引入新的实时API支持，使开发人员能够通过立即从Azure OpenAI模型发送和接收消息来创建高度交互式和响应式应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 05:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.23.6-1 and 1.22.12-1 Microsoft builds now available】GO 1.23.6-1和1.22.12-1 Microsoft现在可用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-23-6-1-and-1-22-12-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new set of Microsoft Go builds including security fixes is now available for download.】现在可以下载一组新的Microsoft GO构建，包括安全修复程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Turning AI Prompts into Playing Cards: A Platform Engineering Experiment】将AI提示变成扑克牌：平台工程实验</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/turning-ai-prompts-into-playing-cards-a-platform-engineering-experiment</link>
      <description>【The inspiration for this project came from my desire to leverage AI to create a tangible product that you can hold, touch, and share.  Cardmaker showcases the capabilities of modern AI as a tool to help its user craft a custom card deck.  But that&amp;#8217;s not all.  It also provides a unique and tangible product [&amp;hellip;]】这个项目的灵感来自于我希望利用AI创建您可以持有，触摸和分享的有形产品。  卡机制造商展示了现代AI作为帮助其用户制作自定义卡甲板的工具。  但这不是全部。  它还提供了独特而有形的产品[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 03:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Windows Terminal Preview 1.23 Release】Windows Terminal预览1.23版本</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/windows-terminal-preview-1-23-release</link>
      <description>【Happy New Year everyone! Here is our first Windows Terminal Preview release of the year! In this release, we focused on porting many of our beloved settings to the Settings UI. We also have several bug fixes and accessibility updates as well. We are also updating Windows Terminal stable to version 1.22 which will include [&amp;hellip;]】大家新年快乐！这是我们本年度的第一个Windows Terminal预览发布！在此版本中，我们专注于将许多心爱的设置移植到设置UI上。我们也有几个错误修复和可访问性更新。我们还将更新Windows Terminal稳定为1.22版，其中包括[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing: Windows MIDI Services Customer Preview 1!】宣布：Windows Midi服务客户预览1！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/windows-music-dev/announcing-windows-midi-services-customer-preview-1</link>
      <description>【Today, we&amp;#8217;re releasing the latest version of Windows MIDI Services to the Windows Insider Canary Channel, fully enabled for anyone to evaluate. We recommend this for technical users (as with any Canary release) and not for production use because we will have bugs. You can learn more about the Insider release here. The Windows Insider [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们将向Windows Insider Canary Channel发布最新版本的Windows Midi服务，以供任何人进行评估。我们建议技术用户（与任何加那利释放一样），而不是用于生产使用的情况，因为我们会有错误。您可以在此处了解有关内部版本的更多信息。 Windows Insider […]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Let your Copilot Declarative Agent think deep with DeepSeek-R1】来宾博客：让您的副copilot代理人用DeepSeek-R1思考</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-let-your-copilot-declarative-agent-think-deep-with-deepseek-r1</link>
      <description>【Today we&amp;#8217;d like to feature a guest author on our Semantic Kernel blog, Mahmoud Hassan, a Microsoft Valuable Professional (MVP) focused on AI. We&amp;#8217;ll turn it over to him to dive into his work below. &amp;nbsp; In recent days, there has been significant attention in the AI community regarding DeepSeek-R1 and its capabilities. Many people [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们想在我们的语义内核博客Mahmoud Hassan上介绍一位客座作者，Mahmoud Hassan是一位专注于AI的Microsoft Prodial Professional（MVP）。我们将其交给他以深入研究他的工作。   最近几天，AI社区在DeepSeek-R1及其功能方面受到了极大的关注。许多人[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 20:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Use Azure Cosmos DB as a Docker container in CI/CD pipelines】在CI/CD管道中使用Azure Cosmos DB作为Docker容器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/use-azure-cosmos-db-as-a-docker-container-in-ci-cd-pipelines</link>
      <description>【There are lot of benefits to using Docker containers in CI/CD pipelines, especially for stateful systems like databases. For example, when you run integration tests, each CI job can start the database in an isolated container with a clean state, preventing conflicts between tests. This results in a testing environment that is reliable, consistent, and [&amp;hellip;]】在CI/CD管道中使用Docker容器有很多好处，尤其是对于数据库等状态系统。例如，当您运行集成测试时，每个CI作业都可以在具有干净状态的孤立容器中启动数据库，从而防止测试之间的冲突。这导致了可靠，一致且[…]的测试环境</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>