<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【February 2026 Insiders (version 1.110)】2026 年 2 月 Insider（版本 1.110）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/february-2026-insiders-(version-1.110)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code February 2026 Release (1.110). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 2 月版本 (1.110) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【DPO Fine-Tuning Using Microsoft Foundry SDK】使用 Microsoft Foundry SDK 进行 DPO 微调</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/dpo-fine-tuning-using-microsoft-foundry-sdk</link>
      <description>【In the rapidly evolving landscape of large language models (LLMs), achieving precise control over model behavior while maintaining quality has become a critical challenge. While models like GPT-4 demonstrate impressive capabilities, ensuring their outputs align with human preferences—whether for safety, helpfulness, or style—requires sophi】在快速发展的大型语言模型 (LLM) 领域，在保持质量的同时实现对模型行为的精确控制已成为一项关键挑战。虽然像 GPT-4 这样的模型展示了令人印象深刻的功能，但确保它们的输出符合人类偏好（无论是安全性、有用性还是风格）需要复杂的设计</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 23:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.26.0-1 Microsoft build now available】Go 1.26.0-1 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-26-0-1-microsoft-build-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new release of the Microsoft build of Go is now available for download. For more information about this release and the changes included, see the table below: Microsoft Release Upstream Tag】Microsoft 版本的 Go 新版本现已可供下载。有关此版本及其所包含更改的更多信息，请参阅下表： Microsoft 版本上游标签</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I distinguish between the numeric keypad 0 and the top-row 0 in the &lt;CODE&gt;WM_&lt;WBR&gt;CHAR&lt;/CODE&gt; message?】如何区分 &lt;CODE&gt;WM_&lt;WBR&gt;CHAR&lt;/CODE&gt; 消息中的数字键盘 0 和顶行 0？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260213-00/?p=112062</link>
      <description>【Last time, we looked at how to distinguish the numeric keypad 0 and the top-row 0 in the WM_KEY­DOWN message. We may as well look at th】上次我们研究了如何区分 WM_KEYDOWN 消息中的数字键盘 0 和顶行 0。我们不妨看看</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft at DevNexus 2026: Practical AI for Real-World Java Development】Microsoft 在 DevNexus 2026 上：用于现实世界 Java 开发的实用 AI</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/microsoft-at-devnexus-2026-practical-ai-for-real-world-java-development</link>
      <description>【Java developers face a tough trifecta: keeping mission-critical systems running, modernizing legacy apps, and weaving AI into real engineering workflows, all without increasing risk. At DevNexus 2026, the Microsoft Java team is tackling these challenges head-on. 】Java 开发人员面临着严峻的三重挑战：保持关键任务系统运行、对遗留应用程序进行现代化改造以及将人工智能融入到实际的工程工作流程中，所有这些都不会增加风险。在 DevNexus 2026 上，Microsoft Java 团队正在正面应对这些挑战。 </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Handling Legacy User Settings in SharePoint Framework】处理 SharePoint 框架中的旧用户设置</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/handling-legacy-user-settings-in-sharepoint-framework</link>
      <description>【Introduction The SharePoint Framework (SPFx) has undergone some important changes in how it handles Entra ID app registration and security models. Here you can find additional details about what w】简介 SharePoint 框架 (SPFx) 在处理 Entra ID 应用程序注册和安全模型的方式方面发生了一些重要变化。在这里您可以找到有关 w 的更多详细信息</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Intelligent Apps with SQL: Join the SQL + AI Datathon】使用 SQL 构建智能应用程序：加入 SQL + AI Datathon</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/build-intelligent-apps-with-sql-join-the-sql-ai-datathon</link>
      <description>【T】时间</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I distinguish between the numeric keypad 0 and the top-row 0 in the &lt;CODE&gt;WM_&lt;WBR&gt;KEY­DOWN&lt;/CODE&gt; message?】如何区分 &lt;CODE&gt;WM_&lt;WBR&gt;KEYDOWN&lt;/CODE&gt; 消息中的数字键盘 0 和顶行 0？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260212-00/?p=112059</link>
      <description>【A customer wanted to know how to distinguish between the numeric keypad 0 and the top-row 0 in the WM_KEY­DOWN message. And while we&#39;re at it, let&#39;s also distinguish between the numeric keypad 0 and the Ins key. We start with this table of what you get in the WM_KEY­DOWN message w】客户想知道如何区分WM_KEYDOWN消息中的数字键盘0和顶行0。在我们讨论这个问题的同时，我们还要区分数字键盘 0 和 Ins 键。我们从这张表开始，列出了您在 WM_KEYDOWN 消息中得到的内容</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How we built the Microsoft Learn MCP Server】我们如何构建 Microsoft Learn MCP 服务器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/engineering-at-microsoft/how-we-built-the-microsoft-learn-mcp-server</link>
      <description>【When we launched the Microsoft Learn Model Context Protocol (MCP) Server in June 2025, our goal was simple: make it effortless for AI agents to use trusted, up-to-date Microsoft Learn documentation. GitHub Copilot and other agents are increasingly comm】当我们于 2025 年 6 月推出 Microsoft Learn 模型上下文协议 (MCP) 服务器时，我们的目标很简单：让 AI 代理轻松使用值得信赖的最新 Microsoft Learn 文档。 GitHub Copilot 和其他代理越来越多地交流</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript 6.0 Beta】宣布推出 TypeScript 6.0 Beta</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-6-0-beta</link>
      <description>【Today we are announcing the beta release of TypeScript 6.0! To get started using the beta, you can get it through npm with the following command: npm install -D typescript@beta TypeScript 6.0 is a unique release in that we intend f】今天我们宣布 TypeScript 6.0 测试版发布！要开始使用 Beta 版，您可以使用以下命令通过 npm 获取它： npm install -D typescript@beta TypeScript 6.0 是一个独特的版本，我们打算</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>