<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (July 2024)】Azure SDK 版本（2024 年 7 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-july-2024</link>
      <description>【The Azure SDKs release every month. This post includes the month&#39;s highlights and release notes.】Azure SDK 每月发布一次。这篇文章包括本月的亮点和发行说明。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 19:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What can I do if IMlangConvertCharset is unable to convert from code page 28591 directly to UTF-8?】如果 IMlangConvertCharset 无法从代码页 28591 直接转换为 UTF-8，我该怎么办？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240726-00/?p=110048</link>
      <description>【You can do the conversion in two steps using things you already have.】您可以使用已有的东西分两步进行转换。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSVC Backend Updates in Visual Studio 2022 version 17.10】Visual Studio 2022 版本 17.10 中的 MSVC 后端更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/msvc-backend-updates-in-visual-studio-2022-version-17-10</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio 2022 17.10 brings new optimizations, intrinsics, features, and improvements to the MSVC backend. Check out the highlights below: Performance improvements and additional functionality for all architectures: Improved SLP vectorizer. Now it runs on more functions, recognizes more operations, and may choose to use larger vector widths if allowed by the appropriate /arch flag.】Visual Studio 2022 17.10 为 MSVC 后端带来了新的优化、内在函数、功能和改进。查看以下亮点： 所有架构的性能改进和附加功能：改进的 SLP 矢量器。现在，它可以运行更多函数，识别更多操作，并且如果适当的 /arch 标志允许，可以选择使用更大的向量宽度。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 19:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Sign VSIX packages with Sign CLI】使用 Sign CLI 签署 VSIX 包</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/sign-vsix-packages-with-sign-cli</link>
      <description>【You can now leverage Sign CLI for a more secure, modern way to sign your Visual Studio extensions. Signing your VSIX packages improves security, prevents tampering, and builds trust with your users. This integration makes it easier and more convenient to sign your packages than ever before!】现在，您可以利用 Sign CLI 以更安全、更现代的方式来签署 Visual Studio 扩展。对 VSIX 包进行签名可以提高安全性、防止篡改并与用户建立信任。这种集成使您比以往任何时候都更轻松、更方便地签署您的包裹！</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Easily Create Bindings for .NET MAUI with Native Library Interop】使用本机库互操作轻松创建 .NET MAUI 的绑定</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/native-library-interop-dotnet-maui</link>
      <description>【Learn how to get started creating bindings with Native Library Interop by following this example binding native Chart libraries in a .NET MAUI application.】通过遵循在 .NET MAUI 应用程序中绑定本机图表库的示例，了解如何开始使用本机库互操作创建绑定。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrated Hybrid Support in the Azure Quantum Development Kit】Azure Quantum 开发套件中的集成混合支持</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/qsharp/integrated-hybrid-support-in-the-azure-quantum-development-kit</link>
      <description>【Some quantum computers can do more than execute a static sequence of gates. The most advanced ones can perform mid-circuit measurements, conditionally execute gates, perform real-time classical computations and re-use qubits. If you want to experiment with these state-of-the-art capabilities, we have good news for you.】一些量子计算机不仅仅可以执行静态门序列。最先进的可以执行中间电路测量、有条件地执行门、执行实时经典计算和重用量子位。如果您想尝试这些最先进的功能，我们有好消息给您。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 17:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Entra External ID: Secure, scalable external identity management for your apps and resources】Microsoft Entra 外部 ID：为您的应用程序和资源提供安全、可扩展的外部身份管理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/external-identity-solutions</link>
      <description>【Unlock the potential of secure and efficient identity management with Microsoft Entra External ID. Focusing on two key scenarios, we show how External ID simplifies the process of managing external identities, including business partners, consumers, and customers. Dive in to discover how you can streamline identity management with straightforward, customizable solutions that cater to diverse end-user segments.】使用 Microsoft Entra 外部 ID 释放安全、高效的身份管理的潜力。我们重点关注两个关键场景，展示外部 ID 如何简化管理外部身份（包括业务合作伙伴、消费者和客户）的流程。深入了解如何通过简单、可定制的解决方案来简化身份管理，以满足不同的最终用户群体。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【LLM Prompt Injection Considerations With Tool Use】法学硕士即时注入工具使用注意事项</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/llm-prompt-injection-considerations-for-tool-use</link>
      <description>【This post discusses a pattern to prevent a class of prompt injection attacks in LLM-based solutions. It emphasizes the importance of building strong foundational patterns to mitigate risks and avoid potential pitfalls. By implementing this pattern, teams can enhance the security of their tool-based solutions.】这篇文章讨论了一种在基于 LLM 的解决方案中防止一类即时注入攻击的模式。它强调了建立强大的基础模式以减轻风险和避免潜在陷阱的重要性。通过实施此模式，团队可以增强基于工具的解决方案的安全性。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript 5.6 Beta】宣布推出 TypeScript 5.6 Beta</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-5-6-beta</link>
      <description>【Today we are excited to announce the availability of TypeScript 5.6 Beta. To get started using the beta, you can get it through NuGet, or through npm with the following command: npm install -D typescript@beta Here&amp;#8217;s a quick list of what&amp;#8217;s new in TypeScript 5.6!】今天，我们很高兴地宣布 TypeScript 5.6 Beta 推出。要开始使用 Beta 版，您可以通过 NuGet 或通过 npm 使用以下命令获取它： npm install -D typescript@beta 以下是 TypeScript 5.6 中新增功能的快速列表！</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 14:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why don’t Windows Imaging Component pixel format GUIDs continue their nice pattern?】为什么 Windows 成像组件像素格式 GUID 不继续其良好的模式？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240729-00/?p=110054</link>
      <description>【Patterns are predictable, which is not always a good thing.】模式是可预测的，这并不总是一件好事。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>