<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript 5.9】宣布打字稿5.9</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-5-9</link>
      <description>【Today we are excited to announce the release of TypeScript 5.9! If you&#39;re not familiar with TypeScript, it&#39;s a language that builds on JavaScript by adding syntax for types. With types, TypeScript makes it possible to check your code to avoid bugs ahead of time. The TypeScript type-checker does all this, and is also the foundation of grea】今天，我们很高兴宣布发行Typescript 5.9！如果您不熟悉打字稿，则是一种通过添加类型的语法在JavaScript上构建的语言。使用类型，TypeScript使您可以检查您的代码，以避免提前错误。 Typescript类型检查器完成了所有这些工作，也是Grea的基础</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 16:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What&#39;s new in Azure AI Foundry | July 2025】Azure AI Foundry中的新功能| 2025年7月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/whats-new-in-azure-ai-foundry-july-2025</link>
      <description>【TL;DR Deep Research Agent (Public Preview): Automate complex, multi-step web research with OpenAI’s o3-deep-research model, now available in Azure AI Foundry Agent Service. GPT-image-1 model: Adds input fidelity controls and partial image streaming for advanced image editing and generation.】TL; DRED Deep Research Agent（公共预览）：与OpenAI的O3深研究模型自动化，多步网络研究，现已在Azure AI Foundry代理服务中获得。 GPT-Image-1模型：为高级图像编辑和生成添加输入保真控制和部分图像流。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automate your open-source dependency scanning with Advanced Security】使用高级安全性自动化开源依赖性扫描</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/automate-your-open-source-dependency-scanning-with-advanced-security</link>
      <description>【Any experiences that require additional setup is cumbersome, especially when there are multiple people needed. In GitHub Advanced Security for Azure DevOps, we&#39;re working to make it easier to enable features and scale out enablement across your enterprise. You can now automatically inject the dependency scanning task into a】任何需要额外设置的经验都很麻烦，尤其是在需要多个人的情况下。在GitHub的Azure DevOps Advanced Security中，我们正在努力使启用功能并扩展启用企业的功能变得更加容易。您现在可以自动将依赖项扫描任务注入</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 17:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I read more than 4GB of data from a file in a single call to &lt;CODE&gt;Read­File&lt;/CODE&gt;?】如何在单个调用中读取&lt;code&gt; readfile &lt;/code&gt;的文件中的文件超过4GB的数据？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250804-00/?p=111432</link>
      <description>【The nNumber­Of­Bytes­To­Read parameter to Read­File is a 32-bit unsigned integer, which limits the number of bytes that could be read at once to 4GB. What if you need to read more than 4GB? The Read­File function cannot read more than 4GB of data at a time. At the time the function was or】读取文件的nnumberofbytestoread参数是一个32位的无符号整数，它限制了可以立即读取到4GB的字节数。如果您需要阅读超过4GB怎么办？读取文件函数一次不能读取超过4GB的数据。当时该功能是或</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The new Dependabot NuGet updater: 65% faster with native .NET】新的Disperabot Nuget Updater：使用本机.NET快65％</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/the-new-dependabot-nuget-updater</link>
      <description>【If you&#39;ve ever waited impatiently for Dependabot to update your .NET dependencies, or worse, watched it fail with cryptic errors, we have some great news. Over the past year, the Dependabot team has worked on a refactor of the NuGet updater, and the results are impressive. From hybrid to native The previous NuGet updater use】如果您曾经不耐烦地等待Disperabot更新您的.NET依赖项，或者更糟糕的是，请注意它失败了，我们会有一些好消息。在过去的一年中，Displabot团队一直致力于Nuget Updater的重构，结果令人印象深刻。从混合到本地</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dynamically Update C++ syntax using Next Edit Suggestions】使用下一个编辑建议动态更新C ++语法</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/dynamically-update-c-syntax-using-next-edit-suggestions</link>
      <description>【When working in a C++ repo, you often are maintaining and updating existing code just as often as you are writing new code. However, updating code in C++ can often require navigating to several different locations in a file to ensure consistency, which can disrupt your logical workflow. For example, changing a data member’s access level typi】在C ++仓库中工作时，您通常会像编写新代码一样频繁地维护和更新现有代码。但是，C ++中的更新代码通常需要导航到文件中的几个不同位置以确保一致性，这可能会破坏您的逻辑工作流程。例如，更改数据成员的访问级别典型</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:36:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A consequence of the weird &lt;CODE&gt;wReserved&lt;/CODE&gt; value at the start of the &lt;CODE&gt;DECIMAL&lt;/CODE&gt; structure】在&lt;code&gt; DECIMAL &lt;/code&gt;结构开始时，怪异&lt;code&gt; wresvered &lt;/code&gt;值的结果</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250731-00/?p=111423</link>
      <description>【Not too long ago, I explained why why there is a weird wReserved value at the start of the DECIMAL structure. Markus Grohs pointed out】不久前，我解释了为什么在十进制结构开始时有一个奇怪的变形值。马库斯·格罗斯（Markus Grohs）指出</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Two related questions about keeping track of PIDs of IPC clients】有关跟踪IPC客户pid的两个相关问题</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250801-00/?p=111427</link>
      <description>【A customer was writing a program that was intended to run in the background and was looking for recommendations on how to store its PID so that other programs can find it and start communicating with the background process. Another customer was writing a provider program that will have multiple clients connect to it. They want the p】客户正在编写一个旨在在后台运行的程序，并正在寻找有关如何存储其PID的建议，以便其他程序可以找到它并开始与后台过程进行通信。另一个客户是编写一个提供商计划，该计划将使多个客户连接到它。他们想要P</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Updated .NET and JDBC Drivers with Native Vector Data Support for High-Performance AI Workload】更新具有本机向量数据支持的.NET和JDBC驱动程序，以实现高性能AI工作负载</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/updated-net-and-jdbc-drivers-with-native-vector-data-support-for-high-performance-ai-workload</link>
      <description>【We’ve just released major updates to our data access libraries, bringing native support for vector data to both the .NET and JDBC ecosystems, unlocking significant performance gains for AI and machine learning workloads. Microsoft.Data.SqlClient 6.1.0 With the new SqlVector class, you can now handle vector data in bin】我们刚刚发布了对数据访问库的重大更新，为.NET和JDBC生态系统带来了对矢量数据的本机支持，从而为AI和机器学习工作负载提供了显着的性能增长。 Microsoft.data.sqlclient 6.1.0带有新的SQLVector类，您现在可以在bin中处理矢量数据</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Join us at Azure Dev Summit 2025】加入我们的Azure Dev Summit 2025</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com//join-us-at-azure-dev-summit-2025</link>
      <description>【The success of AI-powered apps and agents hinges not only on cutting edge models and AI platforms, but on the developers who are chartered with designing innovative services that are secure, scalable, and grounded in the right knowledge. The inaugural Azure Dev Summit on October 13-16, 2025】AI驱动的应用程序和代理商的成功不仅取决于最前沿的模型和AI平台，还取决于开发人员，这些开发人员却涉及设计安全，可扩展和基于正确知识的创新服务。 2025年10月13日至16日举行的首届Azure Dev峰会</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>