<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Cosmos DB Embeddings Generator Sample】Cosmos DB 嵌入生成器示例</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/embeddings-generator-sample</link>
      <description>【Ever since our first preview announcement for vector indexing and support for DiskANN and then again when we announced the GA for these features, customers have been asking us to make it easier to generate Azure OpenAI embeddings on their data in Azure Cosmos DB. So we did just that and created the Azure Cosmos [&amp;hellip;]】自从我们首次发布矢量索引和对 DiskANN 支持的预览版以来，以及当我们再次宣布这些功能的 GA 时，客户一直要求我们更轻松地在 Azure Cosmos DB 中的数据上生成 Azure OpenAI 嵌入。所以我们就这么做了并创建了 Azure Cosmos [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 02:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Join the Conversation: Call for Proposals for Azure Cosmos DB Conf 2025!】加入对话：征集 Azure Cosmos DB Conf 2025 提案！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/join-the-conversation-call-for-proposals-for-azure-cosmos-db-conf-2025</link>
      <description>【Are you passionate about Azure Cosmos DB? Do you have insights, experiences, or innovations that the developer community would love to hear? Now is your chance to shine at the Azure Cosmos DB Conference 2025 – a free, virtual developer event co-organized by Microsoft and the vibrant Azure Cosmos DB community. Mark your calendar for [&amp;hellip;]】您对 Azure Cosmos DB 充满热情吗？您是否有开发者社区希望听到的见解、经验或创新？现在，您有机会在 2025 年 Azure Cosmos DB 大会上大放异彩，这是由 Microsoft 和充满活力的 Azure Cosmos DB 社区共同举办的免费虚拟开发者活动。在您的日历上标记[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 15:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Understanding Semantic Kernel AI Connectors】了解语义内核 AI 连接器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/understanding-semantic-kernel-ai-connectors</link>
      <description>【AI Connectors in Semantic Kernel are components that facilitate communication between the Kernel&amp;#8217;s core functionalities and various AI services. They abstract the intricate details of service-specific protocols, allowing developers to seamlessly interact with AI services for tasks like text generation, chat interactions, and more. &amp;nbsp; Using AI Connectors in Semantic Kernel Developers utilize AI connectors [&amp;hellip;]】语义内核中的 AI 连接器是促进内核核心功能与各种 AI 服务之间通信的组件。它们抽象了特定于服务的协议的复杂细节，使开发人员能够与 AI 服务无缝交互，以完成文本生成、聊天交互等任务。   在语义内核中使用 AI 连接器开发人员利用 AI 连接器 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A simplified overview of ways to add or update elements in a std::map】在 std::map 中添加或更新元素的方法的简化概述</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250113-00/?p=110757</link>
      <description>【And using it to find missing opportunities.】并用它来寻找错过的机会。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Powerful Devs Conference + Hack Together 2025】宣布 Powerful Devs Conference + Hack Together 2025</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/announcing-powerful-devs-conference-and-hack-together-2025</link>
      <description>【We are excited to invite you to participate in this year’s Powerful Devs Conference + Hackathon, commencing on February 12, 2025. The conference will be followed by a two-week Hack Together, ending on February 28, 2025. Join us to unleash your creativity and build innovation solutions!】我们很高兴邀请您参加今年的 Powerful Devs Conference + Hackathon，将于 2025 年 2 月 12 日开始。会议结束后将举办为期两周的 Hack Together，将于 2025 年 2 月 28 日结束。加入我们，释放您的创造力并构建创新解决方案！</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 14:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why does inadvertently passing a std::string instead of a char const* to a variadic function crash on x86-32 but not x86-64?】为什么无意中将 std::string 而不是 char const* 传递给可变参数函数会在 x86-32 上崩溃，但在 x86-64 上不会崩溃？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250110-00/?p=110744</link>
      <description>【Looking at the calling convention and the small string optimization.】查看调用约定和小字符串优化。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhanced Change Signature in C++】C++ 中的增强更改签名</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/enhanced-change-signature-in-c</link>
      <description>【Change Signature allows you to modify a function&amp;#8217;s parameters, including reordering, adding, removing, or altering them across various locations. Previously, the Change Signature feature in Visual Studio involved multiple clicks and nested pop-up windows. In Visual Studio 2022 version 17.12, we&amp;#8217;ve reduced the number of clicks and eliminated these nested steps to streamline the process. [&amp;hellip;]】更改签名允许您修改函数的参数，包括在不同位置重新排序、添加、删除或更改它们。以前，Visual Studio 中的更改签名功能涉及多次单击和嵌套弹出窗口。在 Visual Studio 2022 版本 17.12 中，我们减少了点击次数并消除了这些嵌套步骤以简化流程。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 13:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microspeak: The walk-on topic】Microspeak：走心话题</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250114-00/?p=110762</link>
      <description>【Just walk on in with your topic.】继续你的主题。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET and .NET Framework January 2025 servicing releases updates】.NET 和 .NET Framework 2025 年 1 月服务版本更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/net-and-net-framework-january-2025-servicing-releases-updates</link>
      <description>【Welcome to our combined .NET servicing updates for January 2025. Let&amp;#8217;s get into the latest release of .NET &amp;amp; .NET Framework, here is a quick overview of what&amp;#8217;s new in these releases: Security Improvements .NET updates .NET Framework updates Security improvements &amp;nbsp; This month you will find several CVEs that have been fixed this month: [&amp;hellip;]】欢迎使用 2025 年 1 月的合并 .NET 服务更新。让我们了解最新版本的 .NET 和 .NET Framework，以下是这些版本中新增功能的快速概述： 安全改进 .NET 更新 .NET Framework 更新 安全改进 这本月您会发现本月已修复的几个 CVE：[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 21:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Join us at VS Live! 2025 Las Vegas】加入我们的 VS Live！ 2025 年拉斯维加斯</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/vs-live-2025-las-vegas</link>
      <description>【Join Your Favorite Speakers at VS Live! Las Vegas With the new year here, many developers are looking for the best ways to stay ahead in a rapidly evolving tech landscape. That’s why Visual Studio Live! Las Vegas, March 10-14, 2025, is a must-attend event! Stay ahead of the curve with the latest enhancements in [&amp;hellip;]】与您最喜欢的演讲者一起参加 VS Live！拉斯维加斯 随着新的一年的到来，许多开发人员正在寻找在快速发展的技术领域保持领先地位的最佳方法。这就是 Visual Studio Live! 的原因！ 2025 年 3 月 10 日至 14 日，拉斯维加斯，不容错过的活动！利用 [...] 的最新增强功能保持领先地位</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>