<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure AI Foundry MCP Server May 2025 Update: Adding Models, Knowledge &amp; Evaluation】Azure AI Foundry MCP服务器2025年5月更新：添加模型，知识和评估</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/azure-ai-foundry-mcp-server-may-2025</link>
      <description>【Major expansion of Azure AI Foundry MCP Server with new Models, Knowledge Management, and Evaluation capabilities joining the existing Agent Services, enabling developers to interact with Azure AI through natural language.】Azure AI Foundry MCP服务器的主要扩展具有新的模型，知识管理和评估功能，可加入现有代理服务，使开发人员能够通过自然语言与Azure AI进行交互。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing General Availability of JavaScript SDK v4 for Azure Cosmos DB】宣布JavaScript SDK V4的一般可用性用于Azure Cosmos DB</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/announcing-general-availability-of-javascript-sdk-v4-for-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to launch version 4 of the Azure Cosmos DB JavaScript SDK! This update delivers major improvements that make it easier and faster to build high-performance apps with the Azure Cosmos DB for NoSQL API. Version 4 is available now and targets Node.js v18 and above, introducing a host of new capabilities, including: Improved [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴启动Azure Cosmos DB JavaScript SDK的版本4！此更新提供了重大改进，使使用NOSQL API的Azure Cosmos DB构建高性能应用程序变得更加容易，更快。版本4现在可用，目标是Node.js V18及以上，引入了许多新功能，包括：改进[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 22:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What was origin of the code name Redpill for Windows 8 feature lockout?】Windows 8功能锁定的代码名称redpill的来源是什么？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250527-00/?p=111220</link>
      <description>【Pretty obvious, actually.】实际上很明显。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure DevOps with GitHub Repositories – Your path to Agentic AI】带有GitHub存储库的Azure Devops  - 您通往代理AI的途径</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-with-github-repositories-your-path-to-agentic-ai</link>
      <description>【GitHub Copilot has evolved beyond a coding assistant in the IDE into an agentic teammate – providing actionable feedback on pull requests, fixing bugs and implementing new features, creating pull requests and responding to feedback, and much more. These new capabilities will transform every aspect of the software development lifecycle, as we are already seeing [&amp;hellip;]】Github Copilot已经发展到IDE中的编码助手超越代理队的成员 - 提供了有关拉的请求，修复错误并实施新功能，创建拉动请求并响应反馈等的可行反馈。这些新功能将改变软件开发生命周期的各个方面，因为我们已经看到[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 19:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Circuit Breaker Policy Fine-tuning Best Practice】断路器政策微调最佳实践</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/circuit-breaker-policy-finetuning-best-practice</link>
      <description>【Summary of some best practice and insights about circuit breaker resilience policy fine-tuning.】关于断路器弹性政策微调的一些最佳实践和见解的摘要。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why does Enum­Process­Modules report no modules on a process that was created suspended?】为什么EnumProcessModules在创建的过程中没有报告任何模块？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250526-00/?p=111218</link>
      <description>【There are no modules yet because you didn&#39;t give them a chance to load.】还没有模块，因为您没有给他们加载的机会。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Address Sanitizer Updates for Visual Studio 2022 Version 17.14】Visual Studio 2022版本17.14的地址消毒剂更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/address-sanitizer-updates-for-visual-studio-2022-17-14</link>
      <description>【Introduction It has been an exciting few months for the Address Sanitizer (ASan) since our last update. In addition to our continuous focus on quality and correctness, our internal “dogfooding” (i.e. internal adoption) effort has reached several important milestones. In this update, I want to go over some of the quality improvements since Visual Studio [&amp;hellip;]】引言自上次更新以来，对于地址消毒剂（ASAN）来说，这是一个令人兴奋的几个月。除了我们不断关注质量和正确性外，我们的内部“狗食”（即内部采用）的工作达到了几个重要的里程碑。在此更新中，我想介绍视觉工作室[…]以来的一些质量改进。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 20:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing New Tools and Features in the Responses API in Azure AI Foundry】在Azure AI Foundry中的响应API中引入新工具和功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/introducing-new-tools-and-features-in-the-responses-api-in-azure-ai-foundry</link>
      <description>【With the introduction of the Responses API, Microsoft is enabling a new standard for AI development within the Azure ecosystem. Originally launched by OpenAI and now natively supported in Azure AI Foundry, the Responses API combines the simplicity of the Chat Completions API with the advanced tool-calling capabilities of the Assistants API. It offers a [&amp;hellip;]】随着响应API的引入，Microsoft为Azure生态系统中的AI开发提供了新的标准。 API最初由OpenAI推出，现在由Azure AI铸造厂提供了本地支持，API将聊天完成API的简单性与助手API的高级工具称呼功能结合在一起。它提供了[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【VisualStudio.Extensibility: Editor classification and updates to user prompt】visualStudio.textensible：编辑器分类和更新到用户提示</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visualstudio-extensibility-editor-classification-and-updates-to-user-prompt</link>
      <description>【We continue to invest in the VisualStudio.Extensibility SDK to allow users like you to create extensions that run faster and smoother than ever before! VisualStudio.Extensibility helps you build extensions that run outside the main Visual Studio IDE process for improved performance, reliability, and installation without restarting Visual Studio. Additional benefits include a sleek and intuitive [&amp;hellip;]】我们继续投资于VisualStudio.stensensibility SDK，以允许像您这样的用户创建比以往更快，更光滑的扩展！ Extensensible。可帮助您构建在主要Visual Studio IDE过程之外运行的扩展，以提高性能，可靠性和安装，而无需重新启动Visual Studio。其他好处包括时尚直觉[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Semantic Kernel: Multi-agent Orchestration】语义内核：多代理编排</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/semantic-kernel-multi-agent-orchestration</link>
      <description>【The field of AI is rapidly evolving, and the need for more sophisticated, collaborative, and flexible agent-based systems is growing. With this in mind, Semantic Kernel introduces a new multi-agent orchestration framework that enables developers to build, manage, and scale complex agent workflows with ease. This post explores the new orchestration patterns, their capabilities, and [&amp;hellip;]】人工智能领域正在迅速发展，需要基于更复杂，协作和灵活的基于代理的系统的需求正在增长。考虑到这一点，语义内核引入了一个新的多代理编排框架，该框架使开发人员可以轻松地构建，管理和扩展复杂的代理工作流程。这篇文章探讨了新的编排模式，它们的能力和[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>