<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Failures Happen in Cloud, but how Azure Cosmos DB keeps your Applications Online】云中经常发生故障，但 Azure Cosmos DB 如何使应用程序保持在线</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/failures-happen-in-cloud-but-how-azure-cosmos-db-keeps-your-applications-online</link>
      <description>【The only thing that’s constant in distributed systems is failures. No cloud platform is immune to failures — from regional outages and transient network blips to human errors or hardware faults. What defines resiliency &amp;amp; reliability isn’t the absence of failure, but how systems anticipate, isolate, and recover from them. Here is a】分布式系统中唯一不变的就是失败。没有一个云平台能够免受故障的影响——从区域性中断和短暂的网络故障到人为错误或硬件故障。弹性和可靠性的定义不是没有故障，而是系统如何预测、隔离故障并从中恢复。这是一个</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the azd extension to configure GitHub Copilot coding agent integration with Azure】引入 azd 扩展来配置 GitHub Copilot 编码代理与 Azure 的集成</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-developer-cli-copilot-coding-agent-config</link>
      <description>【This new azd extension makes it easy to use the GitHub Copilot coding agent with Azure Want Copilot to help you build apps in the cloud? This tool does all the boring setup work for you. Instead of spending hours figuring out permissions and security, you can get Copilot coding agent connected to your cloud resources i】这个新的 azd 扩展使您可以轻松地将 GitHub Copilot 编码代理与 Azure 结合使用 想要 Copilot 来帮助您在云中构建应用程序吗？该工具可以为您完成所有无聊的设置工作。您可以让 Copilot 编码代理连接到您的云资源，而无需花费数小时来确定权限和安全性。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Upgrading C++ Projects to Visual Studio 2026】将 C++ 项目升级到 Visual Studio 2026</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/upgrading-c-projects-to-visual-studio-2026</link>
      <description>【With Visual Studio 2026 version 18.0 getting closer to General Availability (GA), we want to share with you how you can upgrade your projects from your current versions of Visual Studio and the Microsoft C++ (MSVC) Build Tools to the latest versions.】随着 Visual Studio 2026 版本 18.0 距离正式发布 (GA) 越来越近，我们希望与您分享如何将项目从当前版本的 Visual Studio 和 Microsoft C++ (MSVC) 生成工具升级到最新版本。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Trying to build a XAML tree in code throws a &#34;No installed components were detected&#34; exception】尝试在代码中构建 XAML 树会引发“未检测到已安装的组件”异常</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251030-00/?p=111746</link>
      <description>【You might, for some reason, be building some XAML in code rather than markup. Starting with this XAML: &amp;lt;!-- XAML markup --&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Grid&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Grid.ColumnDefinitions&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ColumnDefinition Width=&#34;Auto&#34; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;ColumnDefinition Width=&#34;Auto&#34; /&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/Grid.ColumnDefinitions&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/Grid&amp;gt;】由于某种原因，您可能会在代码中而不是标记中构建一些 XAML。从此 XAML 开始： &lt;!-- XAML 标记 --&gt; &lt;Grid&gt; &lt;Grid.ColumnDefinitions&gt; &lt;ColumnDefinition Width=&#34;Auto&#34; /&gt; &lt;ColumnDefinition Width=&#34;Auto&#34; /&gt; &lt;/Grid.ColumnDefinitions&gt; &lt;/Grid&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SharePoint Framework (SPFx) roadmap update – October 2025】SharePoint 框架 (SPFx) 路线图更新 – 2025 年 10 月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/sharepoint-framework-spfx-roadmap-update-october-2025</link>
      <description>【We continue to be humbled by the incredible momentum of SharePoint Framework (SPFx) and the growth it is driving with our customers and partners. There are tens of millions of users across the world using custom SPFx solutions on a daily basis in Microsoft 365 – built by our customers and pa】SharePoint 框架 (SPFx) 令人难以置信的势头及其与我们的客户和合作伙伴共同推动的增长让我们继续感到谦卑。全球有数千万用户每天在 Microsoft 365 中使用自定义 SPFx 解决方案 – 由我们的客户和合作伙伴构建</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio October Update – new models, memories, planning, and more】Visual Studio 十月更新 – 新模型、记忆、规划等</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-october-update</link>
      <description>【The October 2025 update for Visual Studio 2022 (v17.14) is now available. In this month, we are bringing you improvements to model choices, agentic flows, and chat thread management. 】Visual Studio 2022 (v17.14) 的 2025 年 10 月更新现已推出。本月，我们将为您带来模型选择、代理流程和聊天线程管理方面的改进。 </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Dev Proxy v1.3 with exporting to HAR, LLM usage tracking, and enhanced permissions analysis】Dev Proxy v1.3，具有导出到 HAR、LLM 使用情况跟踪和增强的权限分析功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/dev-proxy-v1-3-with-exporting-to-har-llm-usage-tracking-and-enhanced-permissions-analysis</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re thrilled to announce the release of Dev Proxy v1.3.0! This update introduces two powerful new plugins: HAR file generation for universal debugging and LLM usage tracking for cost optimization, along with enhanced permissions analysis and improved OpenAPI spec generation for complex testing scenarios. In this version: New】我们很高兴地宣布 Dev Proxy v1.3.0 发布！此更新引入了两个强大的新插件：用于通用调试的 HAR 文件生成和用于成本优化的 LLM 使用情况跟踪，以及用于复杂测试场景的增强的权限分析和改进的 OpenAPI 规范生成。在此版本中：新</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java OpenJDK October 2025 Patch &amp; Security Update】Java OpenJDK 2025 年 10 月补丁和安全更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/java-openjdk-oct-2025-patch-security-update</link>
      <description>【Hello Java customers! We are happy to announce the latest July 2025 patch &amp;amp; security update release for the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK. Download and install the binaries today. OpenJDK 25.0.1 OpenJDK 21.0.9 OpenJDK 17.0.17 OpenJDK 11.0.29】Java 客户您好！我们很高兴地宣布 Microsoft Build of OpenJDK 的最新 2025 年 7 月补丁和安全更新版本。立即下载并安装二进制文件。 OpenJDK 25.0.1 OpenJDK 21.0.9 OpenJDK 17.0.17 OpenJDK 11.0.29</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Migrating from IDCRL authentication to modern authentication in SharePoint】在 SharePoint 中从 IDCRL 身份验证迁移到新式身份验证</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/migrating-from-idcrl-authentication-to-modern-authentication-in-sharepoint</link>
      <description>【In the next few months, Microsoft will be removing the legacy authentication protocol known as IDCRL (Identity Client Run Time Library) in SharePoint and force calls to rely on OpenID connect and OAuth Protocols. Since 2018, regular sign-in for services such as OneDrive and SharePoint has always relied on the more secure OpenID Connect and OAu】在接下来的几个月中，Microsoft 将删除 SharePoint 中名为 IDCRL（身份客户端运行时库）的旧身份验证协议，并强制调用依赖 OpenID 连接和 OAuth 协议。自2018年以来，OneDrive和SharePoint等服务的定期登录始终依赖于更安全的OpenID Connect和OAu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New GitHub Copilot capabilities for C++ developers: Upgrade MSVC, improve build performance, and refactor C++ code】面向 C++ 开发人员的新 GitHub Copilot 功能：升级 MSVC、提高构建性能并重构 C++ 代码</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/new-github-copilot-capabilities-for-c-developers-upgrade-msvc-improve-build-performance-and-refactor-c-code</link>
      <description>【[alert type=&#34;important&#34;]GitHub Copilot app modernization for C++, GitHub Copilot build performance for Windows, and C++ code editing tools for GitHub Copilot will be available soon in Private Preview. Join the waitlist for Private Preview today.[/alert] Yesterday at GitHub Universe, Gi】[alert type=&#34;important&#34;]适用于 C++ 的 GitHub Copilot 应用程序现代化、适用于 Windows 的 GitHub Copilot 构建性能以及适用于 GitHub Copilot 的 C++ 代码编辑工具即将在私人预览版中提供。今天加入私人预览的候补名单。[/alert] 昨天在 GitHub Universe，Gi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>