<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Copilot for Xcode Adds Support for Anthropic Claude Sonnet 4 and Opus 4】Xcode的Copilot增加了对人类Claude Sonnet 4和Opus 4的支持</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xcode/copilot-for-xcode-adds-support-for-claude-sonnet-4-and-opus-4</link>
      <description>【GitHub Copilot for Xcode now supports Anthropic Claude Sonnet 4 and Claude Opus 4, bringing more powerful AI assistance to your Swift, Objective-C, and Apple platform development.  】Xcode的GitHub Copilot现在支持人类的Claude Sonnet 4和Claude Opus 4，为您的Swift，Objective-C和Apple Platform Platform开发提供了更强大的AI帮助。  </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 02:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the Azure Storage Connector for PyTorch】引入Pytorch的Azure存储连接器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/introducing-the-azure-storage-connector-for-pytorch</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re excited to introduce the Azure Storage Connector for PyTorch (azstoragetorch), a new library that brings seamless, performance-optimized integration between Azure Storage and PyTorch. The library makes it easy to access and store data in Azure Blob Storage directly within your training workflows. What is PyTorch?】我们很高兴地介绍了Pytorch（Azstoragetorch）的Azure存储连接器，这是一个新的库，它在Azure Storage和Pytorch之间带来了无缝，性能优化的集成。该库使直接在培训工作流程中的Azure Blob存储中访问和存储数据。什么是Pytorch？</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Anthropic Claude Sonnet 4 and Opus 4 Now Available in GitHub Copilot for JetBrains and Eclipse】拟人化的克劳德十四行诗4和opus 4现在在Github副铜中可用于喷气式和日食</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/anthropic-claude-sonnet-4-and-opus-4-support</link>
      <description>【Anthropic Claude Sonnet 4 and Claude Opus 4 are now available in GitHub Copilot Chat for JetBrains IDEs and Eclipse. Model Availability✨】现在可以在Github Copilot聊天中为喷气式和Eclipse提供拟人的Claude Sonnet 4和Claude Opus 4。模型可用性✨</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 05:57:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Electronic Arts standardized C++ builds across Windows and Linux with Visual Studio Build Tools】电子艺术如何使用Visual Studio构建工具在Windows和Linux跨Windows和Linux上建造</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/how-electronic-arts-standardized-c-builds-across-windows-and-linux-with-visual-studio-build-tools</link>
      <description>【At Electronic Arts (EA), the Frostbite Enginering Workflows team has thousands of developers who work on powerful game engines behind popular games.  EA has relied on Visual Studio for years due to several features such as IntelliSense, Build Insights, and the overall debugging experience and eagerly use newer integrations such as GitHub Copi】在电子艺术（EA），Frostbite Enginering Workfrows团队拥有成千上万的开发人员，他们在流行游戏背后的强大游戏引擎工作。  由于诸如Intellisense，Build Insights和整体调试体验，并热切使用较新的集成（例如GitHub Copi），EA一直依靠Visual Studio多年来依靠Visual Studio。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 12:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why do I get errors about some weird symbol called ?main@@YAHP$01E$AAV?$Array@PE$AAVString@Platform..., part 2】为什么我会遇到一些怪异符号的错误？main @@ yahp $ 01e $ aav？$ array@pe $ aavstring@platform ...，第2部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250626-00/?p=111314</link>
      <description>【We are investigating why a project is getting an error about a weird C++/CX symbol, and we thought we had figured it out, but our a】我们正在调查为什么一个项目对怪异的C ++/CX符号遇到错误，我们认为我们已经弄清楚了，但是我们的A</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing MSSQL MCP Server (Preview)】介绍MSSQL MCP服务器（预览）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/introducing-mssql-mcp-server</link>
      <description>【The next leap in data interaction isn&#39;t just about efficient processing; it&#39;s about intuitive and meaningful conversation with your own data. For years, the true power of SQL Server databases has been locked behind complex query languages and specialized tools, accessible primarily to developers and database adm】数据交互的下一个飞跃不仅仅是有效的处理。 这是关于与您自己的数据的直观和有意义的对话。多年来，SQL Server数据库的真正功能一直锁定在复杂的查询语言和专业工具后面，主要可用于开发人员和数据库ADM</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 20:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft 365 Copilot APIs: Unlocking enterprise knowledge for AI with the Retrieval API — Now in Public Preview】Microsoft 365 Copilot API：通过检索API解锁AI的企业知识 - 现在在公共预览中</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-365-copilot-apis-unlocking-enterprise-knowledge-for-ai-with-the-retrieval-api</link>
      <description>【At Build 2025, we introduced the Microsoft 365 Copilot APIs. Developers now have an extensibility layer that empowers them to create intelligent, AI-driven experiences deeply integrated with the Microsoft 365 ecosystem. These API】在Build 2025，我们引入了Microsoft 365 Copilot API。现在，开发人员拥有一个可扩展的层，可以使他们能够创建与Microsoft 365生态系统深入整合的智能AI驱动体验。这些API</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Model Context Protocol Support (preview) in Azure AI Foundry Agent Service】在Azure AI铸造代理服务中宣布模型上下文协议支持（预览）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/announcing-model-context-protocol-support-preview-in-azure-ai-foundry-agent-service</link>
      <description>【Generative-AI agents only become useful when they can do things—query systems of record, trigger workflows, or look up specialized knowledge. Until now that meant hand-rolling Azure Functions, managing OpenAPI specs, or writing custom pl】生成型代理只有在能够做事时才会变得有用 - 记录的Query Systems，触发工作流或查找专业知识。到目前为止</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 22:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why do I get errors or warnings about some weird symbol called ?main@@YAHP$01E$AAV?$Array@PE$AAVString@Platform..., part 3】为什么我会收到有关称为怪异符号的错误或警告？main @@ yahp $ 01e $ aav？$ array@pe $ aavstring@platform ...，第3部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250627-00/?p=111316</link>
      <description>【We have been investigating why a project is getting an error about a weird C++/CX symbol, and we tracked it down to three things:】我们一直在调查为什么一个项目对怪异的C ++/CX符号遇到错误，然后我们将其跟踪到三件事：</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Simpler XAML in .NET MAUI 10】更简单的XAML在.NET MAUI 10</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/simpler-xaml-in-dotnet-maui-10</link>
      <description>【Building UI in .NET MAUI with XAML continues to be the most popular approach. It&#39;s easy to see the nesting structure of your UI, works for most use cases with hot reload, and it supports powerful state flow with data binding. One of the downsides is how verbose it can become. Every page requires you to declare the namespaces for any types used】用XAML在.NET MAUI中构建UI仍然是最受欢迎的方法。它很容易看到UI的嵌套结构，适用于大多数带有热装加载的用例，并且用数据绑定支持强大的状态流。缺点之一是它可以变成详细的。每个页面都要求您声明使用的任何类型的名称空间</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>