<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【February 2026 Insiders (version 1.110)】2026 年 2 月 Insider（版本 1.110）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/february-2026-insiders-(version-1.110)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code February 2026 Release (1.110). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 2 月版本 (1.110) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Light up Multiple Databases with a Single API with Data API builder&#39;s multi-source configuration】通过数据 API 构建器的多源配置，通过单个 API 点亮多个数据库</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/multi-source-data-api-builder</link>
      <description>【Data API builder (DAB) supports multi-source configurations Data API builder (DAB) connects to your database with a safe REST or GraphQL endpoint. But DAB is not limited to just one database. Using a multi-source configuration, you can connect to more than one database simultaneously. Learn more about Data A】数据 API 构建器 (DAB) 支持多源配置 数据 API 构建器 (DAB) 使用安全的 REST 或 GraphQL 端点连接到您的数据库。但 DAB 并不仅限于一种数据库。使用多源配置，您可以同时连接到多个数据库。了解有关数据 A 的更多信息</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The 2026/2027 Seattle Symphony subscription season at a glance】2026/2027 西雅图交响乐团订阅季一览</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260220-01/?p=112076</link>
      <description>【For two decades, I&#39;ve】二十年来，我</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customizing the ways the dialog manager dismisses itself: Detecting the ESC key, first (failed) attempt】自定义对话框管理器自行关闭的方式：检测 ESC 键，第一次（失败）尝试</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260220-00/?p=112074</link>
      <description>【Suppose you want to distinguish between dismissing a dialog by pressing ESC and dismissing a dialog by clicking the Close button. One suggestion I saw was to call Get­Async­Key­State(VK_ESCAPE) to check whether the ESC is down. In general, any time you see Get­Async­Key­St】假设您想要区分通过按 ESC 关闭对话框和通过单击“关闭”按钮关闭对话框。我看到的一个建议是调用 GetAsyncKeyState(VK_ESCAPE) 来检查 ESC 是否已关闭。一般来说，任何时候您看到 GetAsyncKeySt</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using Codes to Increase Adherence to Prompts】使用代码来提高对提示的遵守程度</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/using-codes-to-increase-adherence-to-prompts</link>
      <description>【Introduction: The Problem Agentic systems have some discretion in the parameters they send to tooling, but there are cases, such as experimentation, when you need 100% adherence to a set of parameters. In practice, this tension exists because modern LLM-based agents are optimized for semantic correctness and helpfulness, not for s】简介：问题代理系统在发送给工具的参数方面有一定的自由裁量权，但在某些情况下，例如实验，您需要 100% 遵守一组参数。在实践中，这种张力的存在是因为现代基于 LLM 的代理针对语义正确性和有用性进行了优化，而不是针对s</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Migrate your Semantic Kernel and AutoGen projects to Microsoft Agent Framework Release Candidate】将您的语义内核和 AutoGen 项目迁移到 Microsoft Agent Framework 候选版本</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/migrate-your-semantic-kernel-and-autogen-projects-to-microsoft-agent-framework-release-candidate</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re thrilled to announce that Microsoft Agent Framework has reached Release Candidate status for both .NET and】我们很高兴地宣布 Microsoft Agent Framework 已达到 .NET 和 .NET 的候选版本状态</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Agent Framework Reaches Release Candidate】Microsoft Agent 框架发布候选版本</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/microsoft-agent-framework-reaches-release-candidate</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re happy to announce that Microsoft Agent Framework is now in Release Candidate status for both .NET and Python. Release Candidate is an important milestone on the road to General Availability — it means the A】我们很高兴地宣布，Microsoft Agent Framework 现在处于 .NET 和 Python 的候选版本状态。候选版本是通用化道路上的一个重要里程碑——它意味着 A</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 05:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Custom Agents in Visual Studio: Built in and Build-Your-Own agents】Visual Studio 中的自定义代理：内置和构建您自己的代理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/custom-agents-in-visual-studio-built-in-and-build-your-own-agents</link>
      <description>【Agents in Visual Studio now go beyond a single general-purpose assistant. We&#39;re shipping a set of curated preset agents that tap into deep IDE capabilities; debugging, profiling, testing alongside a framework for building your own custom agents tailored to how your team works. Built in agents Each preset agent is designed around a s】Visual Studio 中的代理现在不再是单一的通用助手。我们正在提供一组精心设计的预设代理，可利用深度 IDE 功能；调试、分析、测试以及框架，用于构建适合您团队工作方式的自定义代理。内置代理 每个预设代理都是围绕一个 s 设计的</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 21:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【C++ symbol context and CMake build configuration awareness for GitHub Copilot in VS Code】VS Code 中 GitHub Copilot 的 C++ 符号上下文和 CMake 构建配置感知</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/c-symbol-context-and-cmake-build-configuration-awareness-for-github-copilot-in-vs-code</link>
      <description>【C++ code navigation and build system tooling play an important role in the developer inner-loop. Code navigation tooling provides a precise, semantic understanding of your codebase, while build system tooling helps you express build configurations and variants for reproducible builds. In the VS Code ecosystem, these powerful capabilities are a】C++ 代码导航和构建系统工具在开发人员内循环中发挥着重要作用。代码导航工具提供对代码库的精确语义理解，而构建系统工具可帮助您表达可重现构建的构建配置和变体。在 VS Code 生态系统中，这些强大的功能是</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:13:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring the signals the dialog manager uses for dismissing a dialog】探索对话框管理器用于关闭对话框的信号</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260219-00/?p=112072</link>
      <description>【There are a few different built-in ways to close a dialog box in the classic Windows dialog manager. Let&#39;s run them down. First, there&#39;s hitting the ESC key. The ESC key, as with all keyboard navigation, is handled by the Is­Dialog­Message function. Assuming that the dialog control with f】在经典的 Windows 对话框管理器中，有几种不同的内置方法可以关闭对话框。让我们把他们打倒吧。首先，按下 ESC 键。与所有键盘导航一样，ESC 键由 IsDialogMessage 函数处理。假设对话框控件带有f</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>