<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Reducing personal access token (PAT) usage across Azure DevOps】减少 Azure DevOps 中的个人访问令牌 (PAT) 使用量</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/reducing-pat-usage-across-azure-devops</link>
      <description>【In the new year, we’ll be making moves towards strengthening Microsoft and our customers&amp;#8217; security posture in regards to the usage and creation of personal access tokens (PATs). If you’ve been following this blog, you may have noticed we’ve been distancing away from PATs as the recommended authentication method for Azure DevOps APIs by offering [&amp;hellip;]】在新的一年里，我们将采取措施加强 Microsoft 和客户在使用和创建个人访问令牌 (PAT) 方面的安全状况。如果您一直在关注此博客，您可能已经注意到，我们已经通过提供 [...] 来远离将 PAT 作为 Azure DevOps API 的推荐身份验证方法。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 19:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Emergency power resets on Lenovo, HP, Dell, and Acer laptops】Lenovo、HP、Dell 和 Acer 笔记本电脑的紧急电源重置</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250107-00/?p=110719</link>
      <description>【Looking for the magic button.】寻找神奇的按钮。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【azd CDN changing January 2025】azd CDN 将于 2025 年 1 月发生变化</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azd-cdn-changing-january-2025</link>
      <description>【This blog post makes customers aware of a critical Content Delivery Network (CDN) change for azd (the Azure Developer CLI) because the CDN provider is changing from Edgio to Azure Front Door.】此博文让客户了解 azd（Azure 开发人员 CLI）的关键内容交付网络 (CDN) 更改，因为 CDN 提供商正在从 Edgio 更改为 Azure Front Door。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 22:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【VS Code Java中的JavaC支持发布！】VS Code Java中的JavaC支持发布！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java-ch/visual-studio-code-java-javc</link>
      <description>【大家新年好！我们很高兴宣布，Visual Studio Code Java、JDT 和 JDT-LS 现已部分支持使用 Javac 作为底层编译器。这项支持是红帽和微软经过近一年合作的成果。 此更改旨在确保对最新 Java 特性的及时支持，并使 VS Code 上的 Java 语言支持与常见构建工具（如 Maven、Gradle）更加一致。许多用户希望获得更无缝的开箱即用开发体验，我们相信引入 Javac 是实现这一目标的重要第一步。 用户可以从基于 Javac 的工具中获得以下好处： 更符合 Java 规范的编译器正确性 在 VS Code 和 Eclipse 中更快地支持新 Java 版本 减少 JDT 和 JDT-LS 团队的维护负担 更轻松地测试预览功能和尚未发布的 Java 版本 请注意，基于 Javac 的 JDT 是 ECJ 编译器的另一选项，并非要完全替代 ECJ。目前，VS Code Java 中的基于 Javac 的支持默认处于关闭状态，可以通过以下方式启用： [&amp;hellip;]】大家新年好！我们很高兴宣布，Visual Studio Code Java、JDT 和 JDT-LS 现已部分支持使用 Javac 作为底层编译器。这项支持是红帽和微软经过近一年合作的成果。 此更改旨在确保对最新 Java 特性的及时支持，并使 VS Code 上的 Java 语言支持与常见构建工具（如 Maven、Gradle）更加一致。许多用户希望获得更无缝的开箱即用开发体验，我们相信引入 Javac 是实现这一目标的重要第一步。 用户可以从基于 Javac 的工具中获得以下好处： 更符合 Java 规范的编译器正确性 在 VS Code 和 Eclipse 中更快地支持新 Java 版本 减少 JDT 和 JDT-LS 团队的维护负担 更轻松地测试预览功能和尚未发布的 Java 版本 请注意，基于 Javac 的 JDT 是 ECJ 编译器的另一选项，并非要完全替代 ECJ。目前，VS Code Java 中的基于 Javac 的支持默认处于关闭状态，可以通过以下方式启用： […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 08:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (December 2024)】vcpkg 的新增功能（2024 年 12 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-december-2024</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2024.12.16 registry release, 2024-12-09 tool release, as well as changes to vcpkg documentation throughout December. This release includes a command line option to force vcpkg to use classic mode even if a manifest file is found along with bug fixes. Some [&amp;hellip;]】本博文总结了作为 2024.12.16 注册表版本、2024-12-09 工具版本一部分的 vcpkg 包管理器的更改，以及整个 12 月份对 vcpkg 文档的更改。此版本包含一个命令行选项，用于强制 vcpkg 使用经典模式，即使发现了清单文件并修复了错误。一些 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 18:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Gesellschaft zur Stärkung der Verben: The German Society for the Irregularization of Verbs】动词强化学会：德国动词不规则化学会</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250107-01/?p=110724</link>
      <description>【Stand strong and proud.】坚强而自豪。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Benchmarking with Visual Studio Profiler】使用 Visual Studio Profiler 进行基准测试</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/benchmarking-with-visual-studio-profiler</link>
      <description>【In Visual Studio 17.13 Preview we have released our updated BenchmarkDotNet diagnosers, allowing you to use more of the tools in the performance profiler to analyze benchmarks. With this change it is super quick to dig into CPU usage and allocations of benchmarks making the measure, change, measure cycle quick and efficient. Benchmarking a real [&amp;hellip;]】在 Visual Studio 17.13 预览版中，我们发布了更新的 BenchmarkDotNet 诊断程序，允许您使用性能分析器中的更多工具来分析基准。通过此更改，可以非常快速地深入了解 CPU 使用情况和基准分配，从而使测量、更改、测量周期快速高效。基准测试真实的[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 13:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enabling Neural Rendering in DirectX: Cooperative Vector Support Coming Soon】在 DirectX 中启用神经渲染：协作矢量支持即将推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/directx/enabling-neural-rendering-in-directx-cooperative-vector-support-coming-soon</link>
      <description>【Neural Rendering: A New Paradigm in 3D Graphics Programming In the constantly advancing landscape of 3D graphics, neural rendering technology represents a significant evolution. Neural rendering broadly defines the suite of techniques that leverage AI/ML to dramatically transform traditional graphics pipelines. These new methods promise to push the boundaries of what’s possible in real-time graphics. [&amp;hellip;]】神经渲染：3D 图形编程的新范式 在不断发展的 3D 图形领域，神经渲染技术代表了重大发展。神经渲染广泛地定义了一套利用 AI/ML 来显着改变传统图形管道的技术。这些新方法有望突破实时图形的可能性界限。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 04:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET Aspire Quick Tip – Managing Container &amp; Data Lifetime】.NET Aspire 快速提示 – 管理容器和数据生命周期</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-aspire-container-lifetime</link>
      <description>【.NET Aspire 9 adds new control over the lifetime of containers on your local developer environment. Let&#39;s look at how to manage them with the new APIs!】.NET Aspire 9 添加了对本地开发人员环境中容器生命周期的新控制。让我们看看如何使用新的 API 来管理它们！</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Important Update: blog migration to quantum.microsoft.com】重要更新：博客迁移到Quantum.microsoft.com</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/qsharp/important-update-blog-migration-to-quantum-microsoft-com</link>
      <description>【We are excited to announce that the Q# blog will be migrating to a new home at Azure Quantum in Feb 2025. This move will allow us to provide you with a more integrated and enhanced experience, featuring the latest updates and resources in the world of quantum computing. Stay tuned for more details and [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布，Q# 博客将于 2025 年 2 月迁移到 Azure Quantum 的新家。此举将使我们能够为您提供更加集成和增强的体验，其中包括世界各地的最新更新和资源。量子计算。请继续关注更多详细信息和 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 21:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>