<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft and LangChain4j: A Partnership for Secure, Enterprise-Grade Java AI Applications】Microsoft和Langchain4J：安全的企业级Java AI应用程序的合作伙伴关系</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/microsoft-and-langchain4j-a-partnership-for-secure-enterprise-grade-java-ai-applications</link>
      <description>【】</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Command GitHub&#39;s Coding Agent from VS Code】命令GitHub的编码代理来自VS代码</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/command-github&#39;s-coding-agent-from-vs-code</link>
      <description>【VS Code&#39;s integration with GitHub Copilot Coding Agent allows you to delegate tasks to the agent and let it handle them in the background. Read the full article】VS代码与GitHub Copilot编码代理的集成使您可以将任务委托给代理，并让其在后台处理它们。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build reliable Go applications: Configuring Azure Cosmos DB Go SDK for real-world scenarios】构建可靠的GO应用程序：为真实情况配置Azure Cosmos DB GO SDK</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/build-reliable-go-applications-configuring-azure-cosmos-db-go-sdk-for-real-world-scenarios</link>
      <description>【When building applications that interact with databases, developers frequently encounter scenarios where default SDK configurations don&#39;t align with their specific operational requirements. They need to customize SDK behavior to address real-world challenges like network instability, performance bottlenecks, debugging complexity, monitoring re】当构建与数据库互动的应用程序时，开发人员经常遇到默认SDK配置与其特定操作要求不符的方案。他们需要自定义SDK行为，以应对现实世界中的挑战，例如网络不稳定性，性能瓶颈，调试复杂性，监视RE</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Updates to Warning Suppressions in Microsoft C++ Code Analysis】Microsoft C ++代码分析中警告抑制的更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/updates-to-warning-suppressions-in-microsoft-c-code-analysis</link>
      <description>【Microsoft C++ Code Analysis is a powerful static analysis tool integrated into Visual Studio that helps you identify and fix potential issues in your C++ code. Large projects require effective management of analysis warnings to maintain code quality and you sometimes need to suppress warnings, but must do so in a clear and auditable way.】Microsoft C ++代码分析是一种集成到Visual Studio中的功能强大的静态分析工具，可帮助您识别和修复C ++代码中的潜在问题。大型项目需要有效管理分析警告以维持代码质量，有时您需要抑制警告，但必须以清晰可视化的方式进行警告。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The case of the invalid instruction exception on an instruction that should never have executed】无效的指令例外情况是无法执行的指令</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250718-00/?p=111390</link>
      <description>【The image processing folks added specialized AVX2 versions of their code, but found that it was crashing with an illegal instruction exception. The code went something like this: void SwizzleAVX2(uint32_t* source, uint32_t* destination, uint32_t count) { ⟦ do stuff using AVX-only instructions ⟧ ⟦ such as _mm256_cv】图像处理人员添加了其代码的专门AVX2版本，但发现它正在崩溃，但具有非法指令例外。代码进行了类似的操作：void swizzleavx2（uint32_t* source，uint32_t* destinate，uint32_t count）{⟦使用AVX仅使用AVX-仅使用AVX-for Avx-mmm256_cv做事</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【If the Window Runtime PropertyValue is for boxing non-inspectables, why is there a PropertyValue.CreateInspectable?】如果窗口运行时属性值用于拳击非检查物，为什么有属性值。</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250717-00/?p=111388</link>
      <description>【The Windows Runtime provides a class named Property­Value which is a helper class for boxing non-inspectables. &#34;Boxing&#34; means taking a value type and wrapping inside an object so it can be used as an object type, and in the Windows Runtime, &#34;objects&#34; are represented by the IInspectable interface. There are】Windows Runtime提供了一个名为PropertyValue的类，该类是用于拳击非观察物的助手类。 “拳击”是指在对象中使用值类型并包裹在对象中，因此可以用作对象类型，在Windows运行时，“对象”由Iinspoctable接口表示。有</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Model Promotion with dstoolkit-mlops-v2】DstoolKit-Mlops-V2的AI模型促进</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/ai-model-promotion-with-dstoolkit-v2</link>
      <description>【Introduction In a recent engagement, our team of Data Scientists and Software Engineers, developed a series of custom AI models to meet our customer&#39;s specific use case. While doing so, consideration was given to how best to allow Data Scientists the freedom to quickly experiment and iterate on model development, while also incorpora】在最近的参与度中，我们的数据科学家和软件工程师团队开发了一系列自定义AI模型，以满足客户的特定用例。在这样做的同时，考虑了如何最好地允许数据科学家快速实验和迭代模型开发的自由，同时也将</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Fundamental Failure-Mode Theorem: Systems lie about their proper functioning】基本故障模式定理：系统谎称其适当的功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250716-00/?p=111383</link>
      <description>【I have on occasion referred to Le Chatelier&#39;s Principle for complex systems, as presented by John Gall in the book Systemantics: &#34;Every complex system r】我有时会提到约翰·盖尔（John Gall）在《系统主义者》一书中提出的《复杂系统的原理》：“每个复杂系统r r</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bring your own agents into Microsoft 365 Copilot】将自己的代理商带入Microsoft 365 Copilot</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/bring-your-own-agents-into-microsoft-365-copilot</link>
      <description>【Custom Engine Agents now generally available—build and integrate your own AI into the flow of work Microsoft 365 Copilot is redefining how people interact with AI—embedding it directly into the flow of work as the intuitive, natural interface for agents: the ‘UI for AI’ As Copilot becomes the interface for】自定义发动机代理现在通常可用 - 建立并将自己的AI集成到Microsoft 365 Copilot的工作流程中，正在重新定义人们与AI的互动方式 - 将其直接插入工作流中，作为代理的直观，自然界面：“ ui for AI”作为副cop的copilot成为copilot的界面。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【10 Microsoft MCP Servers to Accelerate Your Development Workflow】10 Microsoft MCP服务器加速您的开发工作流程</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com//10-microsoft-mcp-servers-to-accelerate-your-development-workflow</link>
      <description>【We&#39;ve been talking a lot about the Model Context Protocol (MCP) lately, including recent blog posts and sessions at Microsoft Build. In this post, I&#39;d like to share some top tips for how you can use MCP servers we&#39;ve been building to improve yo】最近，我们一直在谈论模型上下文协议（MCP），包括Microsoft Build的最新博客文章和会议。在这篇文章中，我想分享一些您如何使用我们一直在建造的MCP服务器来改善您的主要技巧</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>