<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Boost your Azure Cosmos DB Efficiency with Azure Advisor Insights】使用 Azure Advisor Insights 提高 Azure Cosmos DB 效率</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/boost-your-azure-cosmos-db-efficiency-with-azure-advisor-insights</link>
      <description>【Azure Cosmos DB is】Azure Cosmos DB 是</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Streamlined Setup, Stronger Guardrails for Microsoft Dev Box】简化的设置，为 Microsoft Dev Box 提供更强大的保护</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/streamlined-setup-stronger-guardrails-for-microsoft-dev-box</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to introduce a new capability that simplifies Dev Box setup—enabling platform engineers and project admins to specify images and SKUs directly when configuring Dev Box pools, without needing to create Dev Box definitions at the Dev Cent】我们很高兴推出一项简化 Dev Box 设置的新功能，使平台工程师和项目管理员能够在配置 Dev Box 池时直接指定映像和 SKU，而无需在开发中心创建 Dev Box 定义</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using RAII to remedy a defect where not all code paths performed required exit actions, follow-up】使用 RAII 修复并非所有代码路径都执行所需退出操作的缺陷，后续</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251017-00/?p=111698</link>
      <description>【Last time, we looked at a way to use the RAII design pattern (Resource Acquisition Is Initialization) to ensure that a function eventually got called on all code paths】上次，我们研究了一种使用 RAII 设计模式（资源获取即初始化）来确保最终在所有代码路径上调用函数的方法</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exciting new capabilities and enhancements for M365 Developer Program - October 2025】M365 开发者计划令人兴奋的新功能和增强功能 - 2025 年 10 月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/exciting-new-capabilities-and-enhancements-for-m365-developer-program-october-2025</link>
      <description>【The Microsoft 365 Developer Program has long been a great resource for developers building solutions on the Microsoft 365 platform. Today, we’re thrilled to share some exciting updates that make onboarding easier, environments more ca】Microsoft 365 开发人员计划长期以来一直是在 Microsoft 365 平台上构建解决方案的开发人员的重要资源。今天，我们很高兴与大家分享一些令人兴奋的更新，这些更新使入门更容易、环境更轻松</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【NASA&#39;s Harmonized Landsat and Sentinel-2 (HLS) Data Now Available on Microsoft&#39;s Planetary Computer】NASA 的统一 Landsat 和 Sentinel-2 (HLS) 数据现已在 Microsoft 行星计算机上提供</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azuregov/nasa-hls-on-mpc</link>
      <description>【NASA’s vast archive of Earth observation data has long been a cornerstone for scientific discovery, environmental monitoring, and global sustainability efforts. Now, Microsoft has made it even easier for researchers, developers, and decision-makers to access and utilize this critical resource. Through a collaboration with NASA, the H】NASA 庞大的地球观测数据档案长期以来一直是科学发现、环境监测和全球可持续发展努力的基石。现在，Microsoft 使研究人员、开发人员和决策者能够更轻松地访问和利用这一关键资源。通过与 NASA 的合作，H</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using RAII to remedy a defect where not all code paths performed required exit actions】使用 RAII 来修复并非所有代码路径都执行所需退出操作的缺陷</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251016-00/?p=111691</link>
      <description>【A team asked me to review their pull request that fixed a bug that was caused by failing to perform some required action along all code paths. Here&#39;s a simplified sketch: void MySpecialFeature::OnButtonClick() { try { auto file = PickFile(); if (!file) { DismissUI(); return;】一个团队要求我审查他们的拉取请求，该请求修复了由于未能在所有代码路径上执行某些所需操作而导致的错误。这是一个简化的草图： void MySpecialFeature::OnButtonClick() { try { auto file = PickFile(); if (!file) { DismissUI();返回;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Managing secrets on Azure KeyVault with a Tagging strategy to perform automations】使用标记策略管理 Azure KeyVault 上的机密以执行自动化</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/managing-azure-keyvault-secrets-with-tagging-strategy</link>
      <description>【Introduction While Azure managed identities are the preferred authentication method to avoid storing secrets, organizations still need effective strategies for managing existing secrets in Azure KeyVault. For the purpose of managing secrets in KeyVault, there is a need to: Detail in plain language what the purpose of】简介 虽然 Azure 托管标识是避免存储机密的首选身份验证方法，但组织仍然需要有效的策略来管理 Azure KeyVault 中的现有机密。为了管理 KeyVault 中的机密，需要： 用通俗易懂的语言详细说明其目的是什么</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PowerToys 0.95 is here: new Light Switch utility, faster Command Palette, and Peek with Spacebar】PowerToys 0.95 现已推出：新的灯光开关实用程序、更快的命令面板以及带空格键的 Peek</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/powertoys-0-95-is-here-new-light-switch-utility-faster-command-palette-and-peek-with-spacebar</link>
      <description>【】</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 23:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Easily connect AI workloads to Azure Blob Storage with adlfs】使用 adlfs 轻松将 AI 工作负载连接到 Azure Blob 存储</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/easily-connect-ai-workloads-to-azure-blob-storage-with-adlfs</link>
      <description>【Easily connect AI workloads to Azure Blob Storage with adlfs We&#39;re excited to announce the newest release of adlfs—a unified Pythonic file system interface to Azure Blob Storage and Azure Data Lake Storage. Microsoft works closely with the】使用 adlfs 轻松将 AI 工作负载连接到 Azure Blob 存储 我们很高兴地宣布推出最新版本的 adlfs - Azure Blob 存储和 Azure Data Lake Storage 的统一 Pythonic 文件系统接口。 Microsoft 与</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why can you increment a reference count with relaxed semantics, but you have to decrement with release semantics?】为什么可以使用宽松语义来增加引用计数，但必须使用发布语义来减少引用计数？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251015-00/?p=111686</link>
      <description>【When managing reference counts, there is an asymmetry between incrementing and decrementing: Incrementing the reference count can use relaxed semantics, but decrementing requires release semantics (and destroying requires acquire semantics). The asymmetry may strike you as odd, but maybe it shouldn&#39;t. After all, it&#39;s not surprising】在管理引用计数时，递增和递减之间存在不对称性：递增引用计数可以使用宽松语义，但递减需要释放语义（而销毁需要获取语义）。这种不对称性可能会让您觉得奇怪，但也许不应该。毕竟这并不奇怪</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>