<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【January 2026 Insiders (version 1.109)】2026 年 1 月 Insider（版本 1.109）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/january-2026-insiders-(version-1.109)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code January 2026 Release (1.109). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 1 月版本 (1.109) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing GPT-5.2 Availability in Azure for U.S. Government Secret and Top Secret Clouds】宣布 Azure 中适用于美国政府机密和绝密云的 GPT-5.2</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azuregov/advancing-ai-capabilities-in-azure-for-u-s-government-secret-and-top-secret-clouds</link>
      <description>【Today, we are excited to announce that GPT-5.2, Azure OpenAI’s newest frontier reasoning model, is available in Microsoft Azure for U.S. Government Secret and Top Secret cloud environments. This release marks another significant milestone in our mission to b】今天，我们很高兴地宣布，Azure OpenAI 的最新前沿推理模型 GPT-5.2 已在 Microsoft Azure 中用于美国政府机密和绝密云环境。此版本标志着我们使命的另一个重要里程碑</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When programs assume that the system will never change, episode 4: Stealing strings】当程序假设系统永远不会改变时，第 4 集：窃取字符串</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260115-00/?p=111988</link>
      <description>【A customer had a program that automated a workflow, and one of the steps was to run a console program that came with Windows, and that console program printed a confirmation prompt &#34;Are you sure (Y/N)?&#34;. They wanted to programmatically say Yes, but since the customer had employees around the world, they couldn&#39;t hard code the lette】一位客户有一个自动化工作流程的程序，其中一个步骤是运行 Windows 附带的控制台程序，该控制台程序打印一条确认提示“您确定 (Y/N) 吗？”。他们想以编程方式说“是”，但由于客户在世界各地都有员工，他们无法对字母进行硬编码</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Microsoft Entra PowerShell v1.2.0】宣布推出 Microsoft Entra PowerShell v1.2.0</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/entrapowershell/announcing-microsoft-entra-powershell-v1-2-0</link>
      <description>【We are excited to introduce Microsoft Entra PowerShell v1.2.0, a major update that delivers full support for Agent Identity Blueprints, expanded application configuration capabilities, and modernized invitation APIs aligned with Microsoft Graph】我们很高兴推出 Microsoft Entra PowerShell v1.2.0，这是一项重大更新，提供对代理身份蓝图的全面支持、扩展的应用程序配置功能以及与 Microsoft Graph 一致的现代化邀请 API</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Copilot Memories】副驾驶回忆</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/copilot-memories</link>
      <description>【Are you wasting time reviewing code for nits on code standards, project preferences, or important contribution guidelines?】您是否在浪费时间审查代码以了解代码标准、项目偏好或重要的贡献指南？</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB Conf 2026 — Call for Proposals Is Now Open】Azure Cosmos DB Conf 2026 — 提案征集现已开放</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-conf-2026-call-for-proposals-is-open</link>
      <description>【Every production system has a story behind it. The scaling limit you didn’】每个生产系统背后都有一个故事。你没有的缩放限制</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building docfind: Fast Client-Side Search with Rust and WebAssembly】构建 docfind：使用 Rust 和 WebAssembly 进行快速客户端搜索</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/external-blogs/building-docfind-fast-client-side-search-with-rust-and-webassembly</link>
      <description>【How we built docfind, a high-performance client-side search engine using Rust and WebAssembly, and how GitHub Copilot accelerated development. Read the full article】我们如何使用 Rust 和 WebAssembly 构建 docfind（一个高性能客户端搜索引擎），以及 GitHub Copilot 如何加速开发。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building docfind: Fast Client-Side Search with Rust and WebAssembly】构建 docfind：使用 Rust 和 WebAssembly 进行快速客户端搜索</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/building-docfind:-fast-client-side-search-with-rust-and-webassembly</link>
      <description>【How we built docfind, a high-performance client-side search engine using Rust and WebAssembly, and how GitHub Copilot accelerated development. Read the full article】我们如何使用 Rust 和 WebAssembly 构建 docfind（一个高性能客户端搜索引擎），以及 GitHub Copilot 如何加速开发。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Copilot Studio Extension for Visual Studio Code Is Now Generally Available】适用于 Visual Studio Code 的 Copilot Studio 扩展现已全面推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/copilot-studio-extension-for-visual-studio-code-is-now-generally-available</link>
      <description>【If you build agents with the Copilot Studio extension for Visual Studio Code, you already know the fastest way to iterate is to treat your agent like software: version it, review changes, and promote it through environments with confidence. Today, the Microsoft Copilot Studio extension fo】如果您使用 Visual Studio Code 的 Copilot Studio 扩展构建代理，您已经知道最快的迭代方法是将代理视为软件：对其进行版本控制、审查更改并自信地在环境中推广它。今天，Microsoft Copilot Studio 扩展适用于</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:04:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Agent Academy: Operative】宣布特工学院：特工</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/announcing-agent-academy-operative</link>
      <description>【Earlier this year, we launched Agent Academy: Recruit, a foundational learning path designed to help makers and developers get started with building agents in Copilot Studio. The response exceeded our expectations. Since launch, thousands of learners have worked through the Recruit】今年早些时候，我们推出了 Agent Academy：Recruit，这是一个基础学习路径，旨在帮助创客和开发人员开始在 Copilot Studio 中构建代理。反响超出了我们的预期。自推出以来，已有数千名学员通过 Recruit 进行了工作</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>