<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【November 2025 Insiders (version 1.107)】2025 年 11 月 Insider（版本 1.107）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/november-2025-insiders-(version-1.107)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code November 2025 Release (1.107). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2025 年 11 月版本 (1.107) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Message-only windows are for messaging, not as a convenient victim for hosting UI】仅消息窗口用于消息传递，而不是作为托管 UI 的方便牺牲品</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251127-00/?p=111817</link>
      <description>【A customer wanted to show a dialog box, but they didn&#39;t want it to be attached to any of their existing windows because it was a general dialog that applied to all of their windows. So they had a great idea: Their program already had a message-only window, so they figured, &#34;Hey, I already have this garbage window I can use as the owner of s】客户想要显示一个对话框，但他们不希望将其附加到任何现有窗口，因为这是一个适用于所有窗口的通用对话框。所以他们有了一个好主意：他们的程序已经有了一个仅显示消息的窗口，所以他们想，“嘿，我已经有了这个垃圾窗口，我可以将其用作 s 的所有者</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visualizing GitHub Audit Log in Microsoft Defender】在 Microsoft Defender 中可视化 GitHub 审核日志</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/visualizing-github-audit-log-in-microsoft-defender</link>
      <description>【[alert type=&#34;tip&#34; heading=&#34;Tips&#34;]In today’s rapidly evolving DevSecOps landscape, the need for real-time v】[alert type=&#34;tip&#34; header=&#34;Tips&#34;]在当今快速发展的 DevSecOps 环境中，需要实时监控</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 07:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET Day on Agentic Modernization Coming Soon】.NET 代理现代化日即将到来</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-day-on-agentic-modernization-coming-soon</link>
      <description>【Join us on December 9, 2025 between 9AM-1PM Pacific for .NET Day of Agentic Modernization! This is a free, one-day virtual event focused on the latest tooling, techniques, and guidance for modernizing your .NET applications. Whether you&#39;re upgrading legacy code, preparing for cloud workloads,】请于 2025 年 12 月 9 日上午 9 点至下午 1 点（太平洋时间）参加 .NET Agentic 现代化日！这是一个免费的、为期一天的虚拟活动，重点关注用于实现 .NET 应用程序现代化的最新工具、技术和指南。无论您是升级遗留代码、为云工作负载做准备，</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【At what point in the Windows development cycle is it too late to change the text of a translatable string?】在 Windows 开发周期的哪个阶段更改可翻译字符串的文本为时已晚？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251126-00/?p=111815</link>
      <description>【Back in 2009, I noted that the &#34;Prevent windows from being automatically arranged when moved to the edge of the screen&#34; check box is a dreaded】早在 2009 年，我就注意到“移动到屏幕边缘时防止窗口自动排列”复选框是一个可怕的选项</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing OData Model Builder 3.0.0 Preview 1 Release】宣布推出 OData Model Builder 3.0.0 预览版 1</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/odata/announcing-odata-model-builder-3-0-0-preview-1-release</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re excited to announce that OData Model Builder 3.0.0 Preview 1 has been officially released and is available on NuGet: Microsoft.OData.ModelBuilder 3.0.0 Preview 1 This is a major release that brings the libr】我们很高兴地宣布，OData Model Builder 3.0.0 Preview 1 已正式发布，并可在 NuGet 上使用： Microsoft.OData.ModelBuilder 3.0.0 Preview 1 这是一个主要版本，带来了 libr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 08:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (November 2025)】Azure SDK 版本（2025 年 11 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-november-2025</link>
      <description>【Thank you for your interest in the new Azure SDKs! We release new features, improvements, and bug fixes every month. Subscribe to our Azure SDK Blog RSS Feed to get notified when a new release is available. You can find links to packages, code, and docs on our】感谢您对新的 Azure SDK 的兴趣！我们每月都会发布新功能、改进和错误修复。订阅我们的 Azure SDK 博客 RSS 源，以便在新版本可用时收到通知。您可以在我们的网站上找到包、代码和文档的链接</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Manage Containers the Easy Way: Copilot + VS Code】轻松管理容器：Copilot + VS Code</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/manage-containers-the-easy-way-copilot-vs-code</link>
      <description>【Managing containers can be one of the most repetitive parts of modern development. Between remembering CLI commands, switching contexts, and digging through logs, it’s easy to lose focus on the actual code you’re building. The latest release of the VS Code Container Tools extension changes that by putting Copilot directly】管理容器可能是现代开发中最重复的部分之一。在记住 CLI 命令、切换上下文和挖掘日志之间，很容易失去对正在构建的实际代码的关注。最新版本的 VS Code 容器工具扩展改变了这一点，直接将 Copilot</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 22:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Celebrating Community Contributions in Aspire 13】庆祝 Aspire 13 中的社区贡献</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspire/thanksgiving-contributions</link>
      <description>【Aspire 13.0 marks a major milestone, not just for the product, but for the vibrant community that helped shape it. This release includes meaningful contributions from community members across features, integrations, tooling, and documentation. We wanted to highlight some standout PRs from this release as a way to say thanks, and hopefully i】Aspire 13.0 标志着一个重要的里程碑，不仅对于该产品而言，而且对于帮助塑造该产品的充满活力的社区而言也是如此。此版本包含社区成员在功能、集成、工具和文档方面做出的有意义的贡献。我们想重点介绍此版本中的一些出色的 PR，以表示感谢，希望我能</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Memory in Foundry Agent Service】在 Foundry Agent 服务中引入内存</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/introducing-memory-in-foundry-agent-service</link>
      <description>【Give your agents the power to remember  Imagine your agent never asks the same question twice. Until now, most agents hav】赋予您的客服人员记住的能力想象一下，您的客服人员永远不会问同一个问题两次。到目前为止，大多数代理商都已</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>