<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Git tooling updates in Visual Studio 17.12】Visual Studio 17.12 中的 Git 工具更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/git-tooling-updates-in-visual-studio-17-12</link>
      <description>【We are thrilled to announce the latest updates to Git tooling in Visual Studio, designed to enhance your development experience and streamline your workflow. These new features are in direct response to user feedback, ensuring that you have the tools you need to be more productive and efficient. For the full list, check out the [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布 Visual Studio 中的 Git 工具的最新更新，旨在增强您的开发体验并简化您的工作流程。这些新功能直接响应用户反馈，确保您拥有提高生产力和效率所需的工具。有关完整列表，请查看 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 15:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PowerShell 7.5 RC-1 is now available】PowerShell 7.5 RC-1 现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/powershell-7-5-rc-1-is-now-available</link>
      <description>【Availability of PowerShell 7.5 RC1】PowerShell 7.5 RC1 的可用性</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 15:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhance Your .NET Developer Productivity with GitHub Copilot】使用 GitHub Copilot 提高 .NET 开发人员的工作效率</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/enhance-your-dotnet-developer-productivity-with-github-copilot</link>
      <description>【Learn how to get started with GitHub Copilot for .NET development for AI assisted development in Visual Studio and Visual Studio Code】了解如何开始使用 GitHub Copilot 进行 .NET 开发，以在 Visual Studio 和 Visual Studio Code 中进行 AI 辅助开发</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Software is a team sport: Building the future of software development together】软件是一项团队运动：共同构建软件开发的未来</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com//building-the-future-of-software-development-together</link>
      <description>【At Microsoft, we strive to build the world’s most beloved developer tools and services. Our vision is to empower every developer to transform their concepts into reality, from idea to code to cloud, at lightning speed. The Visual Studio family, Azure, GitHub, and GitHub Copilot empower developers around the world to do just that. Since [&amp;hellip;]】在 Microsoft，我们致力于打造世界上最受欢迎的开发人员工具和服务。我们的愿景是让每个开发人员能够以闪电般的速度将他们的概念转化为现实，从想法到代码到云。 Visual Studio 系列、Azure、GitHub 和 GitHub Copilot 使世界各地的开发人员能够做到这一点。自从 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the General Availability of Managed DevOps Pools (MDP) for Azure DevOps】宣布面向 Azure DevOps 的托管 DevOps 池 (MDP) 全面推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/managed-devops-pools-ga</link>
      <description>【We are thrilled to announce that Managed DevOps Pools for Azure DevOps is now generally available! This milestone marks a significant advancement in our mission to improve developer productivity in the CI/CD loop, reduce your cloud bill for ES infra and to reduce the toil associated with creating and maintaining custom CI/CD infrastructure for your [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布，Azure DevOps 的托管 DevOps 池现已全面推出！这一里程碑标志着我们的使命取得了重大进展，即提高 CI/CD 循环中的开发人员生产力，减少 ES 基础设施的云费用，并减少与为您的 [...] 创建和维护自定义 CI/CD 基础设施相关的工作量。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft’s Agentic Frameworks: AutoGen and Semantic Kernel】微软的代理框架：AutoGen 和语义内核</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/autogen/microsofts-agentic-frameworks-autogen-and-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Microsoft’s agentic AI frameworks, Semantic Kernel and AutoGen are deeply collaborating to provide the best-in-class agentic developer experience. With Semantic Kernel’s enterprise ready AI capabilities, customers can already use and get support for building agent applications and, moving forward, we’ll align the multi-agent runtime in AutoGen (called autogen-core) with Semantic Kernel, allowing customers to create [&amp;hellip;]】Microsoft 的代理 AI 框架、Semantic Kernel 和 AutoGen 正在深入合作，以提供一流的代理开发人员体验。借助 Semantic Kernel 的企业级 AI 功能，客户已经可以使用并获得构建代理应用程序的支持，并且，展望未来，我们将把 AutoGen 中的多代理运行时（称为 autogen-core）与 Semantic Kernel 保持一致，从而允许客户创建 [ ……]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 15:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customer Case Study: Fujitsu Kozuchi AI Agent Powered by Semantic Kernel】客户案例研究：由语义内核提供支持的 Fujitsu Kozuchi AI Agent</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-fujitsu-kozuchi-ai-agent-powered-by-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Customer Case Study: Fujitsu Kozuchi AI Agent Powered by Semantic Kernel Japanese multinational Fujitsu, a pioneer of information and communications technology, has been transforming industries since 1935. With a workforce of 124,000 dedicated professionals across 50 countries, Fujitsu’s mission is to “make the world more sustainable by building trust in society through innovation.” After introducing [&amp;hellip;]】客户案例研究：由语义内核提供支持的 Fujitsu Kozuchi AI Agent 日本跨国公司富士通是信息和通信技术的先驱，自 1935 年以来一直在改变行业。富士通在 50 个国家/地区拥有 124,000 名敬业的专业人员，其使命是“创造世界”通过创新建立社会信任，从而实现可持续发展。”介绍后[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 20:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Allow users to talk and listen to your chatbot using Semantic Kernel Python】允许用户使用语义内核 Python 与您的聊天机器人交谈和聆听</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/allow-users-to-talk-and-listen-to-your-chatbot-using-semantic-kernel-python</link>
      <description>【Until now, Semantic Kernel Python only allowed for the development of text-based AI applications. However, this is no longer the case, as we have expanded its capabilities to include audio as one of the supported modalities. In this article, I will provide a detailed, step-by-step guide on how to create a chatbot that can both [&amp;hellip;]】到目前为止，语义内核 Python 只允许开发基于文本的人工智能应用程序。然而，情况已不再是这样，因为我们已经扩展了其功能，将音频作为支持的模式之一。在本文中，我将提供详细的分步指南，介绍如何创建一个聊天机器人，该机器人可以 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 16:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The operations for reading and writing single elements for C++ standard library maps】C++标准库映射的单个元素读写操作</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241118-00/?p=110535</link>
      <description>【Breaking down the options.】分解选项。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customer Case Study: Zipp by Sticos – Powered by Semantic Kernel】客户案例研究：Sticos 的 Zipp – 由 Semantic Kernel 提供支持</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-zipp-by-sticos-powered-by-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Today we&amp;#8217;re featuring Sticos on our Semantic Kernel blog to highlight their customer journey with AI and Semantic Kernel. Who is Sticos Company focused on helping Norwegian businesses, communes, accountants, and auditors understand regulations since 1983 Sticos covers the market from Rv9 in Trondheim Sticos is a part of Visma company since 2021, with 127 [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们在 Semantic Kernel 博客上重点介绍 Sticos，以重点介绍他们使用 AI 和 Semantic Kernel 的客户旅程。 Sticos 公司是谁，自 1983 年以来一直致力于帮助挪威企业、公社、会计师和审计师了解法规 Sticos 从特隆赫姆的 Rv9 开始覆盖市场 Sticos 自 2021 年起成为 Visma 公司的一部分，拥有 127 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 01:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>