<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Windows MIDI Services and the 10-MIDI driver limit】Windows MIDI 服务和 10-MIDI 驱动程序限制</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/windows-music-dev/windows-midi-services-and-the-10-midi-driver-limit</link>
      <description>【The USB MIDI 1.0 specification was released in the late 90s around the same time that PCs were starting to move from rectangular beige boxes to things like fake-silvered bulbous plastic shapes. At this point, some of the code in Windows to support USB MIDI 1.0 has become intergenerational – it&#39;s certainly older than my teenagers here at h】USB MIDI 1.0 规范于 20 世纪 90 年代末发布，大约在同一时间，个人电脑开始从矩形米色盒子转向假银色球状塑料形状。此时，Windows 中支持 USB MIDI 1.0 的一些代码已经成为代际代码——它肯定比我在 h 的十几岁孩子还要老。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 22:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.25.4-2 and 1.24.10-1 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.25.4-2 和 1.24.10-1 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-25-4-2-and-1-24-10-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new release of the Microsoft build of Go is now available for download. For more information about this release and the changes included, see the table below: Microsoft Release Upstream Tag】Microsoft 版本的 Go 新版本现已可供下载。有关此版本及其所包含更改的更多信息，请参阅下表： Microsoft 版本上游标签</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【IntelePeer supercharges its agentic AI platform with Azure Cosmos DB】IntelePeer 使用 Azure Cosmos DB 增强其代理 AI 平台</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/intelepeer-supercharges-its-agentic-ai-platform-with-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【Reducing latency by 50% and scaling intelligent CX for SMBs This article was co-authored by Sergey Galchenko, Chief Technology Officer, IntelePeer, and Subhash Ramamoorthi, Director, IntelePeer AI Hub. Don’t miss: Discover how IntelePeer enhances agent intelligence and powers their multi-agent】将延迟减少 50% 并扩展中小型企业的智能 CX 本文由 IntelePeer 首席技术官 Sergey Galchenko 和 IntelePeer AI Hub 总监 Subhash Ramamoorthi 共同撰写。不要错过：了解 IntelePeer 如何增强代理智能并为其多代理提供支持</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Non-recursively deleting a binary tree in constant space: Restructuring the tree】在常量空间中非递归删除二叉树：重构树</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251107-00/?p=111774</link>
      <description>【We&#39;ve been looking at non-recursive algorithms for deleting the nodes of a binary tree. The previous algorithm performed a postorder traversal, cleverly repurposing】我们一直在研究用于删除二叉树节点的非递归算法。之前的算法执行了后序遍历，巧妙地重新利用</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Patterns for Building a Scalable Multi-Agent System】构建可扩展的多代理系统的模式</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/multi-agent-systems-at-scale</link>
      <description>【Introduction LLMs are enabling a new generation of multi-agent systems that tackle complex, multi-step tasks. Moving from prototype to production is hard—especially when orchestrating dozens or hundreds of specialized agents. Commercial viability depends on intentional design, scalability, latency control, and predictable outcomes.】简介 法学硕士正在支持新一代多智能体系统，以解决复杂的多步骤任务。从原型转向生产是很困难的，尤其是在协调数十或数百个专业代理时。商业可行性取决于有意的设计、可扩展性、延迟控制和可预测的结果。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Inside Visual Studio: Improving Open-Source Workflows with vcpkg】Visual Studio 内部：使用 vcpkg 改进开源工作流程</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/inside-visual-studio-improving-open-source-workflows-with-vcpkg</link>
      <description>【vcpkg, an open-source C/C++ package manager maintained by Microsoft, is increasingly recognized as a leading dependency management solution. As an enterprise-grade tool, it enables organizations to streamline library imports, reduce duplication, and support flexible, reproducible builds acros】vcpkg 是 Microsoft 维护的开源 C/C++ 包管理器，越来越被认为是领先的依赖管理解决方案。作为企业级工具，它使组织能够简化库导入、减少重复并支持灵活、可重复的构建 acros</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 23:34:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Real-Time Analytics to AI: Your Azure Cosmos DB &amp; DocumentDB Agenda for Microsoft Ignite 2025】从实时分析到 AI：Microsoft Ignite 2025 年 Azure Cosmos DB 和 DocumentDB 议程</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmosdb-documentdb-agenda-microsoft-ignite-2025</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Ignite 2025 is your opportunity to explore how Azure Cosmos DB, Cosmos DB in Microsoft Fabric, and DocumentDB power the next ge】Microsoft Ignite 2025 为您提供了探索 Azure Cosmos DB、Microsoft Fabric 中的 Cosmos DB 和 DocumentDB 如何为下一代提供动力的机会</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Troubleshooting recent MIDI issues in Windows 11 (and Windows 10)】解决 Windows 11（和 Windows 10）中最近的 MIDI 问题</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/windows-music-dev/troubleshooting-recent-midi-issues-in-windows-11</link>
      <description>【If you are on Windows 11 (or Windows 10 for the UAD issue) and recently had either of these two issues, please read on: You use a Universal Audio (UAD) device and found that all or most of your MIDI devices are no longer recognized in your DAW in Windows 11 or Windows 10 You have a new MIDI 2.0 (UMP Data Format – mo】如果您使用的是 Windows 11（或针对 UAD 问题的 Windows 10）并且最近遇到了这两个问题中的任何一个，请继续阅读：您使用通用音频 (UAD) 设备，发现所有或大部分 MIDI 设备在 Windows 11 或 Windows 10 中的 DAW 中不再被识别您有一个新的 MIDI 2.0（UMP 数据格式 – mo）</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Non-recursively deleting a binary tree in constant space: Synthesizing the parent pointer】非递归删除常量空间中的二叉树：合成父指针</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251106-00/?p=111771</link>
      <description>【Last time, we looked at a way to delete a binary tree non-recursively, assuming that we had parent pointers. But nodes in a classical binary tree does not remember t】上次，我们研究了一种非递归删除二叉树的方法，假设我们有父指针。但经典二叉树中的节点不记得 t</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Open Source AI Editor: Second Milestone】开源人工智能编辑器：第二个里程碑</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/open-source-ai-editor:-second-milestone</link>
      <description>【Ghost text suggestions are now open source as part of the Copilot Chat extension - the second milestone in making VS Code an open source AI editor. Read the full article】Ghost 文本建议现已开源，作为 Copilot Chat 扩展的一部分 - 这是使 VS Code 成为开源 AI 编辑器的第二个里程碑。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>