<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How we ended up rewriting NuGet Restore in .NET 9】我们如何最终在.NET 9中重写Nuget还原</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/rewriting-nuget-restore-in-dotnet-9</link>
      <description>【Learn about the journey that led to a full rewrite of the NuGet Restore algorithm in .NET 9, achieving break-through scale and performance.】了解导致Nuget Restore算法在.NET 9中的全面改写的旅程，从而实现了突破性的规模和性能。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET 10 Preview 3 is now available!】.NET 10预览3现在可用！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-10-preview-3</link>
      <description>【Find out about the new features in .NET 10 Preview 3 across the .NET runtime, SDK, libraries, ASP.NET Core, Blazor, C#, .NET MAUI, and more!】在.NET 10预览3中查找.NET运行时，SDK，库，ASP.NET Core，Blazor，C＃，.Net Maui等！</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET and .NET Framework April 2025 servicing releases updates】.NET和.NET框架2025年4月服务发布更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-and-dotnet-framework-april-2025-servicing-updates</link>
      <description>【A recap of the latest servicing updates for .NET and .NET Framework for April 2025.】2025年4月的.NET和.NET框架的最新服务更新的回顾。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 19:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Function overloading is more flexible (and more convenient) than template function specialization】与模板功能专业化相比，功能超载更灵活（更方便）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250410-00/?p=111063</link>
      <description>【You can change more things in an overload.】您可以在超负荷中更改更多内容。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Hybrid Search with Semantic Kernel for .NET】使用.NET的语义内核宣布混合搜索</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/announcing-hybrid-search-with-semantic-kernel-for-net</link>
      <description>【Today we’re thrilled to announce support for Hybrid search with Semantic Kernel Vector Stores for .NET. What is Hybrid Search? Hybrid search performs two parallel searches on a vector database.  The union of the results of these two searches are then returned to callers with a combined rank, based on the rankings from each of [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们很高兴宣布与.NET的语义内核矢量商店对混合搜索的支持。什么是混合搜索？混合搜索在矢量数据库上执行两个并行搜索。  然后，这两个搜索结果的结合基于[…]的每个排名，并将其汇总给呼叫者。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 19:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET Aspire 9.2 is Now Available with New Ways to Deploy】.NET ASPIRE 9.2现在可以提供新的部署方式</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-aspire-92-is-now-available-with-new-ways-to-deploy</link>
      <description>【.NET Aspire 9.2 is now available with cool new dashboard features and introducing the publishers feature】.NET ASPIRE 9.2现在可以提供凉爽的新仪表板功能并介绍发布者功能</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft 365 Certification control spotlight: Privacy】Microsoft 365认证控制聚光灯：隐私</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-365-certification-control-spotlight-privacy</link>
      <description>【Discover how Microsoft 365 Certification ensures ISVs use the latest privacy and personally identifiable information (PII) management controls to protect customer data.】查找Microsoft 365认证如何确保ISV使用最新的隐私和个人身份信息（PII）管理控件来保护客户数据。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting insights from changes to items in Azure Cosmos DB just got easier!】从变更到Azure Cosmos DB中的项目中获得见解变得更加容易！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/getting-insights-from-changes-to-items-in-azure-cosmos-db-just-got-easier</link>
      <description>【Azure Cosmos DB’s change feed provides a view of changes to data in your container. This enables patterns like event sourcing, auditing and synchronizing downstream systems. Change feed can be read in real time or on demand, giving you the most flexibility for processing and reprocessing changes. Change feed is available in two modes, latest [&amp;hellip;]】Azure Cosmos DB的更改fef提供了对容器中数据的更改的视图。这可以实现诸如事件采购，审核和同步下游系统之类的模式。更改供稿可以实时或按需阅读，从而为您提供处理和再处理更改的最灵活性。更改供稿有两种模式可用，最新的[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft at PyTexas 2025: Join Us for a Celebration of Python and Innovation】Microsoft在Pytexas 2025：加入我们，庆祝Python和创新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/pytexas-2025</link>
      <description>【Microsoft is thrilled to announce our participation in PyTexas 2025, taking place this year in the vibrant city of Austin, Texas! At this year’s event, Microsoft is proud to contribute to the community’s growth and excitement by hosting a booth and delivering an engaging talk.】微软很高兴宣布我们参加今年在充满活力的德克萨斯州奥斯汀市举行的Pytexas 2025！在今年的活动中，微软很自豪地通过举办展位并发表引人入胜的演讲来为社区的成长和兴奋做出贡献。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 17:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to build Multi-agent AI Apps using Microsoft Azure】如何使用Microsoft Azure构建多代理AI应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/how-to-build-multi-agent-ai-apps-using-microsoft-azure</link>
      <description>【Understanding Multi-Agent Workflow Automation  At its core, a multi-agent architecture is like a team of specialized experts working together on complex tasks. Instead of having a single AI agent trying to handle everything, multiple AI agents—each with specific roles and capabilities—collaborate to achieve common goals. Think of it as the difference between having one person [&amp;hellip;]】了解多代理工作流程自动化的核心，一个多代理体系结构就像一个专家团队，共同从事复杂的任务。与其让单个AI代理商试图处理所有事物，不如说是具有特定角色和能力的多个AI代理，以实现共同的目标。将其视为一个人[…]之间的区别</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 23:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>