<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Moving to TLS 1.2 for Azure Cosmos DB: Ensuring Secure Connections】搬到Azure Cosmos DB的TLS 1.2：确保安全连接</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/moving-to-tls-1-2-for-azure-cosmos-db-ensuring-secure-connections</link>
      <description>【Security and reliability are at the core of modern cloud applications. To strengthen data protection and align with industry best practices, we encourage all Azure Cosmos DB customers to transition to TLS 1.2. This post explains why this change is important, how to make the transition, and the benefits it brings to your applications. Why [&amp;hellip;]】安全性和可靠性是现代云应用程序的核心。为了加强数据保护并与行业最佳实践保持一致，我们鼓励所有Azure Cosmos DB客户过渡到TLS 1.2。这篇文章解释了为什么这种变化很重要，如何进行过渡以及它给您的应用程序带来的好处。为什么 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio Code CMake Tools Extension 1.20 Release: Introducing Built-In CMake Language Services】Visual Studio代码CMAKE工具扩展1.20版本：引入内置CMAKE语言服务</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/visual-studio-code-cmake-tools-extension-1-20-release-introducing-built-in-cmake-language-services</link>
      <description>【The February release of CMake Tools in VS Code is now available. With this release, we have some new updates to the extension to improve CMake integrations with the extension’s support. Some updates include the built-in support for CMake Language services, addressing our most highly-upvoted issues in the CMake Tools extension, and CMake presets v9 [&amp;hellip;]】VS代码中CMAKE工具的2月发布现已可用。通过此版本，我们对扩展程序有一些新的更新，以通过扩展的支持来改善CMAKE集成。一些更新包括对CMAKE语言服务的内置支持，解决了我们在CMAKE工具扩展中最高度投资的问题，以及CMAKE PRESETS PRESETS V9 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【C++/WinRT implementation inheritance: Notes on winrt::implements, part 2】C ++/WINRT实现继承：Winrt :: insterments上的注释，第2部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250220-00/?p=110893</link>
      <description>【Untangling unwrap_implements_t.】解开unwrap_implements_t。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Instrumenting Apache Spark Structured Streaming jobs using OpenTelemetry】仪器使用OpenTelemetry的Apache火花结构化流媒体作业</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/spark_job_otel</link>
      <description>【Apache spark monitoring using OpenTelemetry】使用OpenTelemetry的Apache Spark监视</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Revolutionizing AI Workflows: Multi-Agent Group Chat with Copilot Agent Plugins in Microsoft Semantic Kernel】来宾博客：革新AI工作流程：Microsoft语义内核中与Copilot Agent插件的多代理小组聊天</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-revolutionizing-ai-workflows-multi-agent-group-chat-with-copilot-agent-plugins-in-microsoft-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Revolutionizing AI Workflows: Multi-Agent Group Chat with Copilot Agent Plugins in Microsoft Semantic Kernel  Copilot Agent Plugins (CAPs) are revolutionizing how developers interact with Microsoft 365 data. By transforming natural language into seamless CRUD actions using Microsoft Graph and Semantic Kernel, CAPs enable the creation of intelligent, AI-driven solutions. This sample demonstrates a multi-agent group [&amp;hellip;]】革命性的AI工作流程：Microsoft语义内核副代理插件（CAPS）中与Copilot代理插件的多代理组聊天正在彻底改变开发人员与Microsoft 365数据的交互方式。通过使用Microsoft Graph和语义内核将自然语言转换为无缝的CRUD动作，Caps可以创建智能，AI驱动的解决方案。该样本展示了一个多代理组[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visualize ROI of your GitHub Copilot Usage, Deploy it!】可视化您的github副用法的ROI，部署它！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/visualize-roi-of-your-github-copilot-usage-deploy-it</link>
      <description>【Deployment: Let&amp;#8217;s do it! All operations are performed in the VM Prerequisites everything is on-premises and free (except VM) The only thing you need is: a VM Memory: 16G is recommended Operating system: Ubuntu 22.04 (recommended, other operating systems have no difference except Docker installation) Port: 3000 port needs to be released for Grafana to use, and 22 port [&amp;hellip;]】部署：让我们做！所有操作均在VM先决条件中执行所有操作，所有操作都是本地的，并且免费（VM除外）您需要的是：VM内存：建议使用16G的操作系统：Ubuntu 22.04（推荐其他操作系统没有差异，除Docker安装外， ）端口：需要释放3000个端口才能使用Grafana，还有22个端口[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking More Power: Tool Calling in GitHub Copilot for Visual Studio】解锁更多功能：在GitHub Copilot中为Visual Studio打电话的工具</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/function-calling-is-now-enabled-in-github-copilot</link>
      <description>【Have you ever been frustrated when Copilot doesn’t understand you? While it can’t read your mind, we’ve been working hard to make your coding experience smoother. Previously, Copilot in Visual Studio could look at files in your repository, but you needed to specify the context of your code manually. We understand this wasn’t the most [&amp;hellip;]】当副驾驶不了解您时，您是否曾经感到沮丧？虽然无法读懂您的想法，但我们一直在努力使您的编码体验更加顺畅。以前，Visual Studio中的Copilot可以查看存储库中的文件，但是您需要手动指定代码的上下文。我们知道这不是最[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET MAUI Performance Features in .NET 9】.NET MAUI性能功能.NET 9</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-9-performance-improvements-in-dotnet-maui</link>
      <description>【Optimize .NET MAUI application size and startup times with trimming and NativeAOT. Learn about `dotnet-trace` and `dotnet-gcdump` for measuring performance.】使用修剪和纳塔维亚特优化.NET MAUI应用程序大小和启动时间。了解“ dotnet-trace”和`dotnet-gcdump“以测量性能。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automating Developer Environments with Microsoft Dev Box and Teams Customizations Part 2】使用Microsoft Dev Box和团队自定义第2部分自动化开发人员环境</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/automating-developer-environments-with-microsoft-dev-box-and-teams-customizations-part-2</link>
      <description>【Developers today typically work on multiple projects simultaneously, with each project requiring different tools and configuration requirements. Being able to have a dedicated environment explicitly configured to that project unlocks enhanced developer productivity and reduces outside noise, allowing developers to focus just on the work they are doing. This also extends to developers who may [&amp;hellip;]】今天，开发人员通常同时从事多个项目，每个项目都需要不同的工具和配置要求。能够明确配置为该项目的专用环境可以解锁增强的开发人员生产力并降低外部噪音，从而使开发人员只专注于他们正在做的工作。这也扩展到可能[…]的开发人员</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visualize ROI of your GitHub Copilot Usage, How it works!】可视化您的github副用法的ROI，其工作原理！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/visualize-roi-of-your-github-copilot-usage-how-it-works</link>
      <description>【Architecture: How it works! The Copilot Usage Advanced Dashboard offers a comprehensive suite of features designed to revolutionize how organizations track and analyze their Copilot usage. At its core, the solution leverages Elasticsearch for persistent data storage, breaking free from the traditional 28-day limitation and enabling analysis across extended time periods, from months to years. [&amp;hellip;]】建筑：它的工作方式！ Copilot使用Advanced Dashboard提供了一套全面的功能，旨在彻底改变组织如何跟踪和分析其Copilot使用情况。该解决方案以此为核心，利用Elasticsearch进行持续的数据存储，摆脱了从传统的28天限制，并从几个月到几年之间跨越长时间的分析实现了分析。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>