<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Watch Live: Visual Studio Toolbox at VS LIVE! Redmond 2025】观看直播：Vs Visio Studio Toolbox in VS Live！ Redmond 2025</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/watch-live-visual-studio-toolbox-at-vs-live-redmond-2025</link>
      <description>【Join Robert Green and Leslie Richardson for a full day of live sessions, demos, and interviews. Live from Microsoft HQ – Stream Tuesday’s Sessions with Visual Studio Toolbox! On Tuesday, August 5, join us for a special edition of Visual Studio Toolbox Live—broadcast f】加入罗伯特·格林（Robert Green）和莱斯利·理查森（Leslie Richardson），进行一整天的现场会议，演示和访谈。来自Microsoft HQ  - 流媒体工作室工具箱的流媒体周二会议！ 8月5日，星期二，加入我们，进行特别版的Visual Studio Toolbox Live -Broadcast f</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 15:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft build of Go 1.25 crypto backend changes】Microsoft构建GO 1.25加密后端更改</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/microsoft-go-defaults-to-system-crypto</link>
      <description>【Starting in Go 1.25, the Microsoft build of Go will default to using system-provided cryptography: OpenSSL on Linux and CNG on Windows. The systemcrypto GOEXPERIMENT will be enabled by default and picks the supported backend for the target platform.】从GO 1.25开始，GO的Microsoft构建将默认为使用System提供的密码学：Linux上的OpenSSL和Windows上的CNG。默认情况下将启用SystemCrypto Gosperiment，并为目标平台选择支持的后端。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Aspire 9.4 is here with a CLI and interactive dashboard features】Aspire 9.4在这里具有CLI和互动仪表板功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-aspire-9-4</link>
      <description>【Today, we released .NET Aspire 9.4, our biggest release ever, bringing new integrations, interactive dashboard-based inputs, and a standalone, native AOT command line tool for creating and running Aspirified apps. We also published our first roadmap last week, which outl】今天，我们发布了.NET ASPIRE 9.4，这是我们有史以来最大的发行版，带来了新的集成，基于交互式仪表板的输入以及一个独立的本机AOT命令行工具，用于创建和运行Applesified应用程序。上周我们还发布了第一张路线图，</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why is there a window with no name blocking Windows shutdown?】为什么没有一个没有名称阻止窗口关闭的窗口？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250729-00/?p=111417</link>
      <description>【If you try to shut down Windows, and there&#39;s a program that is not allowing the shutdown to proceed, then the Blocked Shutdown Resolver (BSDR) shows a list of windows that includes the one that is processing the shutdown notification, as well as】如果您尝试关闭Windows，并且有一个程序不允许关闭进行，则阻止的关闭解析器（BSDR）显示一个窗口的列表，其中包括正在处理关闭通知的一个窗口</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing General Availability of UNISTR function and ANSI SQL || Operator in Azure SQL】宣布UNISTR功能的一般可用性和ANSI SQL || Azure SQL的操作员</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/announcing-general-availability-of-unistr-function-and-ansi-sql-operator-in-azure-sql</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce the General Availability (GA) of two long-standing capabilities that address critical needs for SQL developers and enterprise customers in Azure SQL Database and Azure SQL Managed Instance, configured with the】我们很高兴地宣布，在Azure SQL数据库和Azure SQL托管实例中，解决了两个长期存在能力的一般可用性（GA），以解决SQL开发人员和企业客户的关键需求，并配置</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 15:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【In C++/WinRT, how can I await multiple coroutines and capture the results?, part 0】在C ++/Winrt中，我该如何等待多个共核并捕获结果？，第0部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250730-00/?p=111421</link>
      <description>【A while ago, I investigated ways of awaiting multiple C++/WinRT corotuines and capturing the results. I started with winrt::when_all(), but really I co】不久前，我研究了等待多个C ++/Winrt Corotuines并捕获结果的方法。我从winrt :: wher_all（）开始，但真的我合作</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (July 2025)】Azure SDK发布（2025年7月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-july-2025</link>
      <description>【Thank you for your interest in the new Azure SDKs! We release new features, improvements, and bug fixes every month. Subscribe to our Azure SDK Blog RSS Feed to get notified when a new release is available. You can find links to packages, code, and docs on our】感谢您对新的Azure SDK的关注！我们每月发布新功能，改进和错误修复。订阅我们的Azure SDK博客RSS feed，以便在有新版本时通知。您可以在我们的包装，代码和文档中找到链接</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Full-Stack App with React and Aspire: A Step-by-Step Guide】构建一个具有React和Aspire的全栈应用程序：逐步指南</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/new-aspire-app-with-react</link>
      <description>【In this post we will build we will build a TODO app from start to finish using Aspire and React. We will do this using the CLI and C# Dev Kit. The todo items will be stored in a SQLite database. The React front-end will use a Web API to handle all the interactions with the data. I&#39;m going to be showing this with the dotnet CLI, Aspire CLI a】在这篇文章中，我们将构建我们将使用Aspire和反应构建一个TODO应用程序。我们将使用CLI和C＃DEV套件来执行此操作。 TODO项目将存储在SQLite数据库中。 React前端将使用Web API处理与数据的所有交互。我将与dotnet CLI，Aspire Cli A一起展示这一点</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Plan Validation in Copilot Studio Kit】在Copilot Studio套件中引入计划验证</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/plan-validation-cat-kit</link>
      <description>【Ever wonder why your agent&#39;s answers can be right but for the wrong reasons? Let&#39;s dive into why that matters, with a brief foray into epistemology (bear with me!) Knowledge: More Than Just Right Answers Imagine asking someone the time, and they confidently reply, “2:30 PM.” They&#39;re correct—but what if their watch】有没有想过为什么您的经纪人的答案是正确的，但是出于错误的原因？让我们深入了解为什么这很重要，并短暂地涉足认识论（与我同在！）知识：不仅仅是正确的答案，想象一下问某人的时间，他们自信地回答：“下午2:30。”他们是正确的 - 但是如果他们的手表</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 10:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub Copilot for Xcode: Introducing Copilot Vision, Custom Instructions, Locale-Aware Responses, and More】Xcode的GitHub Copilot：介绍副本视觉，自定义说明，环境感知响应等等</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/xcode/github-copilot-for-xcode-introducing-copilot-vision-and-more</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to introduce updates to GitHub Copilot for Xcode, bringing new ways to interact with AI and streamline your development workflow. With Copilot Vision, you can upload and chat with images—like screenshots and UI designs—directly in Xcode. We’ve also introduced global】我们很高兴向Github Copilot介绍Xcode的更新，从而带来了与AI互动并简化开发工作流程的新方法。使用Copilot Vision，您可以在Xcode中直接上传和与图像（例如屏幕截图和UI设计）上传和聊天。我们还介绍了全球</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 03:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>