<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio 2022 v17.13 is Now Available!】Visual Studio 2022 V17.13现在可用！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-2022-v17-13-is-now-available</link>
      <description>【We&amp;#8217;re excited to announce the availability of Visual Studio 2022 v17.13. This update focuses on stability and security, along with continuous improvements for all developers using Visual Studio. Based on your feature requests, several new tools and enhancements have been added to this release. This update includes improvements for developers, such as advanced debugging capabilities, [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴宣布Visual Studio 2022 V17.13的可用性。此更新着重于稳定性和安全性，以及使用Visual Studio的所有开发人员的持续改进。根据您的功能请求，此版本已添加了几种新工具和增强功能。此更新包括开发人员的改进，例如高级调试功能，[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【February Patches for Azure DevOps Server】Azure DevOps服务器的2月补丁</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/february-patches-for-azure-devops-server-4</link>
      <description>【Today we are releasing patches that impact our self-hosted product, Azure DevOps Server. We strongly encourage and recommend that all customers use the latest, most secure release of Azure DevOps Server. You can download the latest version of the product, Azure DevOps Server 2022.2 from the Azure DevOps Server download page. The following version of [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们正在发布影响我们自托管产品Azure DevOps服务器的补丁。我们强烈鼓励并建议所有客户使用最新，最安全的Azure DevOps服务器。您可以从Azure Devops Server下载页面下载最新版本的产品Azure Devops Server 2022.2。以下版本的[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 19:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET and .NET Framework February 2025 servicing releases updates】.NET和.NET框架2025年2月Servicing Releases更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-and-dotnet-framework-february-2025-servicing-updates</link>
      <description>【A recap of the latest servicing updates for .NET and .NET Framework for February 2025.】2025年2月的.NET和.NET框架的最新服务更新的回顾。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【C# Dev Kit Updates: .NET Aspire, Hot Reload, and More!】C＃开发套件更新：.net Aspire，热重载等等！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/csharp-on-visual-studio-code-just-got-better-with-enhancements-to-csharp-dev-kit</link>
      <description>【Exploring the latest features and enhancements in the C# Dev Kit for VS Code including .NET Aspire orchestration support, new hot reload features, enhanced debugging capabilities, and more!】探索C＃DEV套件中的最新功能和增强功能，包括.NET ASPIRE编排支持，新的热重加载功能，增强的调试功能等等！</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the end of support for Node.js 18.x in the Azure SDK for JavaScript】宣布javaScript的Azure SDK中对Node.js 18.x的支持结束</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/announcing-the-end-of-support-for-node-js-18-x-in-the-azure-sdk-for-javascript</link>
      <description>【After July 10, 2025, the Azure SDK for JavaScript will no longer support Node.js 18.x. Upgrade to an Active Node.js Long Term Support (LTS) version to stay secure and up-to-date.】2025年7月10日之后，JavaScript的Azure SDK将不再支持Node.js 18.x.升级到Active Node.js长期支持（LTS）版本，以保持安全和最新。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 22:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bells and whistles: Building with Microsoft Copilot Studio】钟声和口哨：与Microsoft Copilot Studio建造</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/bells-whistles-building-with-microsoft-copilot-studio</link>
      <description>【In this series, we showcase the different capabilities of building agents with Copilot Studio, which includes building, testing, deploying, analyzing, security and data loss prevention policy.】在本系列中，我们通过Copilot Studio展示了建筑代理的不同功能，其中包括建筑，测试，部署，分析，安全性和数据损失预防政策。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A Powerful, Open-Source MongoDB GUI for Everyone】每个人都有强大的开源MongoDB GUI</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/a-powerful-open-source-mongodb-gui-for-everyone</link>
      <description>【Introduction Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB provides robust support through its Request Units (RU) model and vCore-based architecture, enabling flexible and scalable options for various workloads. We are now on a mission to deliver the ultimate developer experience. To achieve this, we have integrated Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB support into the Azure Databases VS [&amp;hellip;]】简介MongoDB的Azure Cosmos DB通过其请求单元（RU）模型和基于VCORE的架构提供了强大的支持，从而为各种工作负载提供了灵活且可扩展的选项。现在，我们的使命是提供最终的开发人员体验。为了实现这一目标，我们将Azure Cosmos DB集成了以MongoDB支持到Azure数据库与[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSVC Compiler Updates in Visual Studio 2022 version 17.13】Visual Studio 2022版本17.13中的MSVC编译器更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/msvc-compiler-updates-in-visual-studio-2022-version-17-13</link>
      <description>【Introduction For this update, we have changed things up a little bit. We now have more distinct buckets of fixes/implemented features. This is to help guide readers who care about specific features to more easily see how the compiler front-end team is making progress on the things you care about. 17.12 notes for reference. C++23 [&amp;hellip;]】简介此更新，我们对事情进行了一些更改。现在，我们拥有更多不同的修复/实现功能。这是为了帮助指导读者关心特定功能，以更轻松地了解编译器前端团队如何在您关心的事情上取得进展。 17.12注释供参考。 C ++ 23 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 19:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Step-by-Step Guide to Building a Portfolio Manager: A Multi-Agent System with Microsoft Semantic Kernel and Azure OpenAI】来宾博客：建立投资组合经理的分步指南：具有Microsoft语义内核和Azure OpenAI的多代理系统</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-step-by-step-guide-to-building-a-portfolio-manager-a-multi-agent-system-with-microsoft-semantic-kernel-and-azure-openai</link>
      <description>【Today the Semantic Kernel team is excited to welcome back a guest author, Akshay Kokane to share his recent Medium article using Semantic Kernel and Azure OpenAI, showcasing a step-by-step guide to building a Portfolio Manager. We’ll turn it over to him to dive into his work below. In my previous blog, we went over [&amp;hellip;]】今天，语义内核团队很高兴欢迎一位客座作家Akshay Kokane使用语义内核和Azure Openai分享他最近的媒介文章，并展示了建立投资组合经理的逐步指南。我们将其交给他以深入研究他的工作。在我以前的博客中，我们浏览了[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 23:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New for C++ Developers in Visual Studio 2022 17.13】Visual Studio中的C ++开发人员的新功能2022 17.13</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-for-c-developers-in-visual-studio-2022-17-13</link>
      <description>【We are happy to announce that Visual Studio 2022 version 17.13 is now generally available! This post summarizes the new features you can find in this release for C++. You can download Visual Studio 2022 from the Visual Studio downloads page or upgrade your existing installation by following the Update Visual Studio Learn page. Standard Library and Compiler [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布，Visual Studio 2022版本17.13现在通常可用！这篇文章总结了您可以在此版本中找到C ++的新功能。您可以从“ Visual Studio下载页面”页面下载Visual Studio 2022，也可以按照“更新Visual Studio Learn Learn”页面升级现有安装。标准图书馆和编译器[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>