<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub Models and .NET: Building Generative AI apps for engineers】GitHub 模型和 .NET：为工程师构建生成式 AI 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/using-github-models-and-dotnet-to-build-generative-ai-apps</link>
      <description>【In this post, you&#39;ll learn how to use AI models on GitHub.】在本文中，您将学习如何使用 GitHub 上的 AI 模型。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing large payloads in Fluid Framework】优化 Fluid Framework 中的大型有效负载</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/optimizing-large-payloads-in-fluid-framework</link>
      <description>【Learn about three Fluid Framework features which can be used to work around large payload scenarios: Grouped Batching, Batch Compression, and Compressed Batch Chunking.】了解可用于解决大负载场景的三个 Fluid Framework 功能：分组批处理、批量压缩和压缩批量分块。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET 9 Release Candidate 1 is now available!】.NET 9 候选版本 1 现已推出！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-9-release-candidate-1-is-now-available</link>
      <description>【Try out the latest features in .NET 9 Release Candidate 1 across the .NET SDK, libraries, ASP.NET Core, SignalR, .NET MAUI, and more!】跨 .NET SDK、库、ASP.NET Core、SignalR、.NET MAUI 等尝试 .NET 9 Release Candidate 1 中的最新功能！</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fix C++ warnings and errors with Copilot: Introducing AI-Assisted Code Fixes in Visual Studio】使用 Copilot 修复 C++ 警告和错误：在 Visual Studio 中引入 AI 辅助代码修复</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/fix-c-warnings-and-errors-with-copilot-introducing-ai-assisted-code-fixes-in-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【Stuck on an unfamiliar build error? Want to resolve your code errors quickly? Copilot is now integrated into Visual Studio error workflows to assist you with understanding and resolving C++ errors and warnings. To access this new feature, you will need an active Copilot subscription and the latest 17.11 GA version of Visual Studio. How [&amp;hellip;]】遇到不熟悉的构建错误？想要快速解决代码错误吗？ Copilot 现已集成到 Visual Studio 错误工作流程中，以帮助您理解和解决 C++ 错误和警告。要访问此新功能，您需要有效的 Copilot 订阅和最新的 17.11 GA 版本的 Visual Studio。如何 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The case of the string being copied from a mysterious pointer to invalid memory, revisited】重新审视字符串从神秘指针复制到无效内存的情况</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240911-00/?p=110247</link>
      <description>【Reflections on an older topic.】对一个较旧主题的思考。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.23.1-2 and 1.22.7-2 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.23.1-2 和 1.22.7-2 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-23-1-2-and-1-22-7-2-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new set of Microsoft Go builds is now available for download.】一组新的 Microsoft Go 版本现已可供下载。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Azure AI Inference Connector for Azure AI Studio Models】推出适用于 Azure AI Studio 模型的 Azure AI 推理连接器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/introducing-azure-ai-inference-connector-for-azure-ai-studio-models</link>
      <description>【Introduction  With the latest launch of the Azure AI Inference SDK for Azure AI Studio Models Catalog, we are happy to announce that we have also made available our dedicated Azure AI Inference Semantic Kernel Connector.  This connector is specially designed on top of the published Azure AI Inference SDK and is targeted to allow [&amp;hellip;]】简介 随着最新推出适用于 Azure AI Studio 模型目录的 Azure AI 推理 SDK，我们很高兴地宣布，我们还推出了专用的 Azure AI 推理语义内核连接器。  该连接器是在已发布的 Azure AI 推理 SDK 之上专门设计的，旨在允许 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 16:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Search scoping helps you find what you’re looking for】搜索范围可帮助您找到所需内容</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/search-scoping-helps-you-find-what-youre-looking-for</link>
      <description>【If you&amp;#8217;re working on a large and complex solution, you might find yourself overwhelmed by the number of results when you use code search in Visual Studio. You might be looking for a specific class, method, or variable, but end up scrolling through pages of irrelevant matches. Wouldn&amp;#8217;t it be nice if you could narrow [&amp;hellip;]】如果您正在开发大型且复杂的解决方案，那么当您在 Visual Studio 中使用代码搜索时，您可能会发现自己对结果数量感到不知所措。您可能正在寻找特定的类、方法或变量，但最终会滚动浏览不相关匹配的页面。如果你能缩小范围，那不是很好吗？</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EAP for Vector Support Refresh – Introducing Vector type】用于矢量支持刷新的 EAP – 引入矢量类型</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/eap-for-vector-support-refresh-introducing-vector-type</link>
      <description>【Not even 6 months ago we started the Early Adopter Preview vector data support in Azure SQL, and we got great feedback and a lot of enthusiasm about the feature. Developers are excited to be able to easily build AI-enabled solution using an enterprise ready, secure, scalable and proven platform like Azure SQL, without the [&amp;hellip;]】不到 6 个月前，我们就开始在 Azure SQL 中提供早期采用者预览版矢量数据支持，我们得到了很好的反馈以及对该功能的极大热情。开发人员很高兴能够使用 Azure SQL 等企业就绪、安全、可扩展且经过验证的平台轻松构建支持 AI 的解决方案，而无需 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:56:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Modernize your UWP app with preview UWP support for .NET 9 and Native AOT】通过对 .NET 9 和本机 AOT 的预览 UWP 支持实现 UWP 应用现代化</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ifdef-windows/preview-uwp-support-for-dotnet-9-native-aot</link>
      <description>【We’re introducing the initial preview UWP (Universal Windows Platform) support for .NET 9, providing a path for existing UWP developers to modernize their apps with the latest .NET and Native AOT. Are you a UWP app developer considering migrating to Windows App SDK and WinUI 3? Or wanting to leverage the latest releases of .NET [&amp;hellip;]】我们推出了对 .NET 9 的初始预览版 UWP（通用 Windows 平台）支持，为现有 UWP 开发人员提供了一条利用最新的 .NET 和本机 AOT 对其应用进行现代化改造的途径。您是考虑迁移到 Windows App SDK 和 WinUI 3 的 UWP 应用开发人员吗？或者想要利用最新版本的 .NET [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 15:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>