<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Customer Case Study: Suntory and Reliability in AI with Semantic Kernel】客户案例研究：三得利与语义内核人工智能可靠性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-suntory-and-reliability-in-ai-with-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Suntory Global Spirits is the spirits division of Suntory Holdings, a multinational beverage and food company based in Japan. Suntory is renowned for its high-quality alcoholic beverages, including premium Japanese whisky, gin, vodka, and other spirits. We&amp;#8217;ll turn it over to Urko Benito from Suntory to dive into their AI journey with Semantic Kernel.  The [&amp;hellip;]】三得利全球烈酒是三得利控股公司的烈酒部门，三得利控股是一家总部位于日本的跨国饮料和食品公司。三得利以其高品质酒精饮料而闻名，包括优质日本威士忌、杜松子酒、伏特加和其他烈酒。我们将把它交给来自三得利 (Suntory) 的 Urko Benito，深入探讨他们与 Semantic Kernel 的人工智能之旅。  这 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 18:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fix Code with GitHub Copilot】使用 GitHub Copilot 修复代码</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/fix-code-with-github-copilot</link>
      <description>【Looking to resolve code issues quickly? The new GitHub Copilot feature integrated into the lightbulb and error list in Visual Studio 2022 offers a valuable solution for developers. Whether you&amp;#8217;re working in C# or C++, this feature will help you understand and address problems in your codebase more efficiently. The integration of GitHub Copilot into [&amp;hellip;]】希望快速解决代码问题？集成到 Visual Studio 2022 中的灯泡和错误列表中的新 GitHub Copilot 功能为开发人员提供了有价值的解决方案。无论您使用 C# 还是 C++，此功能都将帮助您更有效地理解和解决代码库中的问题。将 GitHub Copilot 集成到 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Solving the puzzle of trying to put an object into a std::optional】解决尝试将对象放入 std::Optional 的难题</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241114-00/?p=110521</link>
      <description>【How do I set a value? Let me count the ways.】我如何设置一个值？让我数一下方法。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Filtered change notifications in Microsoft Graph callRecords API are now available】Microsoft Graph callRecords API 中的筛选更改通知现已可用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/filtered-change-notifications-in-microsoft-graph-callrecords-api-are-now-available</link>
      <description>【We are pleased to announce that you can now optionally filter change notifications for the callRecord GraphAPI by participant Entra Object IDs.】我们很高兴地宣布，您现在可以选择按参与者 Entra 对象 ID 过滤 callRecord GraphAPI 的更改通知。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 17:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Calling methods is easier and faster with C# 13 params collections】使用 C# 13 参数集合调用方法更加轻松快捷</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/csharp13-calling-methods-is-easier-and-faster</link>
      <description>【Let&#39;s take a look at C# 13&#39;s new params collections that make methods easier to use and allow new optimizations.】让我们看一下 C# 13 的新参数集合，它们使方法更易于使用并允许新的优化。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New Microsoft Graph callRecords API capabilities in GCCH and DoD】GCCH 和 DoD 中的新 Microsoft Graph callRecords API 功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/new-microsoft-graph-callrecords-api-capabilities-in-gcch-and-dod</link>
      <description>【Read about the new capabilities for the Microsoft Graph callRecords API coming to GCCH and DOD environments in December.】了解 12 月份将在 GCCH 和 DOD 环境中推出的 Microsoft Graph callRecords API 的新功能。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating an Azure OpenAI app with Python using External ID authentication】使用外部 ID 身份验证通过 Python 创建 Azure OpenAI 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/azure-openai-app-with-python-and-external-id</link>
      <description>【Learn how to securely integrate Azure’s OpenAI services with External ID authentication, using Python, Azure CLI, and Bicep templates. This guide walks you through setting up a secure AI-driven application with streamlined access management on Azure.】了解如何使用 Python、Azure CLI 和 Bicep 模板将 Azure 的 OpenAI 服务与外部 ID 身份验证安全集成。本指南将引导你在 Azure 上设置具有简化访问管理的安全 AI 驱动应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Developer CLI (azd) – November 2024】Azure 开发人员 CLI (azd) – 2024 年 11 月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-developer-cli-azd-november-2024</link>
      <description>【This post announces the November release of the Azure Developer CLI (`azd`).】本文宣布 11 月份发布 Azure 开发人员 CLI (`azd`)。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 22:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Nullable Reference Types in F# 9】F# 9 中的可为空引用类型</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/nullable-reference-types-in-fsharp-9</link>
      <description>【Read about latest F# 9 feature, Nullable Reference Types】了解最新的 F# 9 功能：可空引用类型</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the .NET Aspire Community Toolkit】.NET Aspire 社区工具包简介</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-the-dotnet-aspire-community-toolkit</link>
      <description>【Learn about the .NET Aspire Community Toolkit, a collection of tools and libraries that help you build with .NET Aspire.】了解 .NET Aspire 社区工具包，它是帮助您使用 .NET Aspire 进行构建的工具和库的集合。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>