<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【January 2026 Insiders (version 1.109)】2026 年 1 月 Insider（版本 1.109）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/january-2026-insiders-(version-1.109)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code January 2026 Release (1.109). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 1 月版本 (1.109) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Now in Public Preview: GitHub Copilot build performance for Windows】现已推出公共预览版：Windows 的 GitHub Copilot 构建性能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/now-in-public-preview-github-copilot-build-performance-for-windows</link>
      <description>【Last year, we launched our new GitHub Copilot build performance capabilities in Private Preview. With help from our fantastic C++ community, we gathered insights and addressed key feedback. We’re happy to share that GitHub Copilot build performance for Windows is now in Public Preview. Today, all C++ developers can try out the new capabiliti】去年，我们在私人预览版中推出了新的 GitHub Copilot 构建性能功能。在我们出色的 C++ 社区的帮助下，我们收集了见解并解决了关键反馈。我们很高兴与大家分享，适用于 Windows 的 GitHub Copilot 构建性能现已推出公共预览版。今天，所有 C++ 开发人员都可以尝试新功能</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【On the proper usage of a custom Win32 dialog class】浅谈自定义Win32对话框类的正确使用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260121-00/?p=112002</link>
      <description>【Some time ago, I discussed custom dialog classes. You can specify that a dialog template use your custom dialog class by putting the custom class&#39;s name in the CLASS statement of the dialog template. A c】前段时间，我讨论了自定义对话框类。您可以通过将自定义类的名称放入对话框模板的 CLASS 语句中来指定对话框模板使用您的自定义对话框类。交流</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Context-Driven Development: Agent Skills for Microsoft Foundry and Azure】上下文驱动开发：Microsoft Foundry 和 Azure 的代理技能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/context-driven-development-agent-skills-for-microsoft-foundry-and-azure</link>
      <description>【Code will be generated, not written. Working with 100+ companies, I have seen this firsthand: most enterprise workloads taking dependencies on AI SDKs are usually net-new microservices. Hardly anyone has Windows-scale codebases for their new AI features. This is modular, greenfield work. Perfect for coding agents. The catch? Out-of-the-box】代码将被生成，而不是被编写。我与 100 多家公司合作，亲眼目睹了这一点：大多数依赖 AI SDK 的企业工作负载通常是全新的微服务。几乎没有人拥有用于新 AI 功能的 Windows 规模代码库。这是模块化的、全新的工作。非常适合编码代理。收获是什么？开箱即用</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Azure Performance Diagnostics Tool for Java: Automated Java Performance Analysis in Kubernetes via Azure SRE Agent】推出适用于 Java 的 Azure 性能诊断工具：通过 Azure SRE 代理在 Kubernetes 中进行自动化 Java 性能分析</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/introducing-azure-performance-diagnostics-tool-for-java-automated-java-performance-analysis-in-kubernetes-via-azure-sre-agent</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re excited to announce that the Azure Performance Diagnostics Tool for Java is now available for preview as part of the Azure SRE Agent platform, bringing intelligent, automated Java performance diagnoses. Currently supporting Java workloads deployed to Azure Kubernetes S】我们很高兴地宣布，适用于 Java 的 Azure 性能诊断工具现在可以作为 Azure SRE 代理平台的一部分进行预览，从而带来智能、自动化的 Java 性能诊断。目前支持部署到 Azure Kubernetes S 的 Java 工作负载</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 22:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PIX 2601.15 - new Intel plugin, many buffer viewer improvements, and more】PIX 2601.15 - 新的 Intel 插件、许多缓冲区查看器改进等等</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pix/pix-2601-15</link>
      <description>【Today we released PIX version 2601.15, which can be downloaded here. This release includes everything in the previous 2509.25 release, plus: A new Intel plugin with many new featu】今天我们发布了 PIX 版本 2601.15，可以在这里下载。此版本包含之前 2509.25 版本中的所有内容，此外还有： 具有许多新功能的新 Intel 插件</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.25.6-1 and 1.24.12-1 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.25.6-1 和 1.24.12-1 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-25-6-1-and-1-24-12-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new release of the Microsoft build of Go including security fixes is now available for download. For more information about this release and the changes included, see the table below: Microsoft Release Upstream Tag】包含安全修复程序的 Microsoft Go 版本新版本现已可供下载。有关此版本及其所包含更改的更多信息，请参阅下表： Microsoft 版本上游标签</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microspeak: On fire, putting out fires】Microspeak：着火了，灭火</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260120-00/?p=111998</link>
      <description>【Remember, Microspeak is not necessarily jargon exclusive to Microsoft, but it&#39;s jargon that you need to know if you work at Microsoft. When something has gone horribly wrong and requires immediate attention, one way to describe it is to say that it is on fire. The obvious metaphor here is that the situation is so severe that】请记住，Microspeak 不一定是 Microsoft 专有的术语，但它是您在 Microsoft 工作时需要了解的术语。当某件事发生严重错误并需要立即关注时，描述它的一种方法是说它着火了。这里明显的隐喻是，形势如此严峻，以至于</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PowerToys 0.97 is here: a big Command Palette update and a new mouse utility】PowerToys 0.97 现已推出：命令面板大更新和新的鼠标实用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/powertoys-0-97-is-here-a-big-command-palette-update-and-a-new-mouse-utility</link>
      <description>【】</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Boards additional field filters (private preview)】Azure Boards 附加字段筛选器（私人预览版）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-boards-additional-field-filters-private-preview</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce a limited private preview that introduces the ability to add additional fields as filters on both the backlog and Kanban boards. This feature has been a long-standing request from the developer com】我们很高兴地宣布推出有限的私人预览版，该预览版引入了在待办事项列表和看板板上添加其他字段作为过滤器的功能。此功能是开发者委员会长期以来的要求</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>