<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【January 2026 Insiders (version 1.109)】2026 年 1 月 Insider（版本 1.109）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/january-2026-insiders-(version-1.109)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code January 2026 Release (1.109). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 1 月版本 (1.109) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub Copilot app modernization for C++ is now in Public Preview】C++ 的 GitHub Copilot 应用程序现代化现已推出公共预览版</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/github-copilot-app-modernization-cpp-public-preview</link>
      <description>【With the launch of Visual Studio 2026, we announced a Private Preview of GitHub Copilot app modernization for C++, which reduces the cost of adopting the】随着 Visual Studio 2026 的推出，我们宣布了针对 C++ 的 GitHub Copilot 应用现代化的私人预览版，这降低了采用</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build AI Agents with GitHub Copilot SDK and Microsoft Agent Framework】使用 GitHub Copilot SDK 和 Microsoft Agent 框架构建 AI 代理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/build-ai-agents-with-github-copilot-sdk-and-microsoft-agent-framework</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Agent Framework now integrates with the GitHub Copilot SDK, enabling you to build AI agents powered by GitHub Copilot. This integration brings together the Agent Framework&#39;s consistent agent abstraction with GitHub Copilot&#39;s capabilities, including function calling, streaming respon】Microsoft Agent Framework 现在与 GitHub Copilot SDK 集成，使您能够构建由 GitHub Copilot 提供支持的 AI 代理。这种集成将代理框架的一致代理抽象与 GitHub Copilot 的功能结合在一起，包括函数调用、流响应</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio January Update — Enhanced Editor Experience】Visual Studio 1 月更新 — 增强编辑器体验</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-january-update-enhanced-editor-experience</link>
      <description>【】</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio Code CMake Tools 1.22: Target bookmarks and better CTest output】Visual Studio Code CMake 工具 1.22：目标书签和更好的 CTest 输出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/visual-studio-code-cmake-tools-1-22-target-bookmarks-and-better-ctest-output</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re excited to announce the latest 1.22 release of the CMake Tools extension for Visual Studio Code. This update brings a host of new additions, including project outline updates for filtering and bookmarking CMake targets in large CMake projects and expa】我们很高兴地宣布推出适用于 Visual Studio Code 的 CMake 工具扩展的最新 1.22 版本。此更新带来了许多新功能，包括项目大纲更新，用于在大型 CMake 项目和扩展中过滤和添加 CMake 目标书签。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A digression on the design and implementation of &lt;CODE&gt;Safe­Array­Add­Ref&lt;/CODE&gt; and extending APIs in general】离题一下 &lt;CODE&gt;SafeArrayAddRef&lt;/CODE&gt; 的设计和实现以及一般的 API 扩展</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260127-00/?p=112018</link>
      <description>【Last time, we learned about the difference between Safe­Array­Access­Data and Safe­Array­Add­Ref. I noted that Safe­Arra】上次，我们了解了 SafeArrayAccessData 和 SafeArrayAddRef 之间的区别。我注意到 SafeArra</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Budget Bytes: Build Powerful AI Apps for Under $25】介绍 Budget Bytes：以低于 25 美元的价格构建强大的 AI 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/introducing-budget-bytes</link>
      <description>【When developers hear &#34;cloud&#34; and &#34;AI,&#34; their first thought is often about cost. &#34;How much will this cost me to learn? Can I build something meaningful without racking up a surprise bill?&#34; &amp;nbsp;】当开发人员听到“云”和“人工智能”时，他们首先想到的往往是成本。 “我要花多少钱来学习？我可以在不增加意外账单的情况下构建一些有意义的东西吗？”  </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 22:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Join Microsoft at NDC London 2026 - Let’s Build the Future of .NET Together】与 Microsoft 一起参加 2026 年伦敦 NDC - 让我们一起构建 .NET 的未来</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/join-us-at-ndc-london-2026</link>
      <description>【NDC London is here, with pre-conference workshops running January 26–27 and the main conference running January 28–30. If you&#39;re a .NET or Azure developer, this is the place to be. Whether you want to sharpen your cloud-native skills, get hands-on with AI-powered development, learn from Microsoft engineers, or simply connect with people wh】NDC 伦敦在这里举行，会前研讨会将于 1 月 26 日至 27 日举行，主会议于 1 月 28 日至 30 日举行。如果您是 .NET 或 Azure 开发人员，那么这里就是您该去的地方。无论您是想提高云原生技能、亲身体验人工智能驱动的开发、向 Microsoft 工程师学习，还是只是与需要帮助的人建立联系</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the Evals for Agent Interop starter kit】介绍 Evals for Agent Interop 入门套件</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/introducing-the-evals-for-agent-interop-starter-kit</link>
      <description>【As enterprise customers roll out and govern AI agents through Agent 365, they have been asking for pre canned evals they can run out of the box. They want transparent, reproducible evaluations that reflect their own work in realistic environments, including interoperability, how agents con】随着企业客户通过 Agent 365 推出和管理 AI 代理，他们一直在要求可以开箱即用的预装评估。他们想要透明的、可重复的评估来反映他们自己在现实环境中的工作，包括互操作性、代理如何控制</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What&#39;s the difference between &lt;CODE&gt;Safe­Array­Access­Data&lt;/CODE&gt; and &lt;CODE&gt;Safe­Array­Add­Ref&lt;/CODE&gt;?】&lt;code&gt;SafeArrayAccessData&lt;/code&gt; 和 &lt;code&gt;SafeArrayAddRef&lt;/code&gt; 之间有什么区别？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260126-00/?p=112016</link>
      <description>【Once upon a time, there was SAFEARRAY, the representation of an array used by IDispatch and intended for use as a common mechanism for interchange of data between native code and scripting languages such as Visual Basic. You used the Safe­Array­Create function to create one, and a variety of other fu】曾几何时，有 SAFEARRAY，它是 IDispatch 使用的数组表示形式，旨在用作本机代码和脚本语言（例如 Visual Basic）之间交换数据的通用机制。您使用 SafeArrayCreate 函数创建了一个，以及其他各种 fu</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>