<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【New T-SQL AI Features are now in Public Preview for Azure SQL and SQL database in Microsoft Fabric】Microsoft Fabric 中的 Azure SQL 和 SQL 数据库的新 T-SQL AI 功能现已推出公共预览版</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/ai-functions-public-preview-azure-sql</link>
      <description>【At the start of this year, we released a new set of T-SQL AI features for embedding your relational data for AI applications. Today, we have brought those features to Azure SQL and SQL database in Microsoft Fabric. This post will help you get started usi】今年年初，我们发布了一组新的 T-SQL AI 功能，用于嵌入 AI 应用程序的关系数据。今天，我们将这些功能引入了 Microsoft Fabric 中的 Azure SQL 和 SQL 数据库。这篇文章将帮助您开始使用</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 21:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A step-by-step guide to modernizing .NET applications with GitHub Copilot agent mode】使用 GitHub Copilot 代理模式实现 .NET 应用程序现代化的分步指南</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/modernizing-dotnet-with-github-copilot-agent-mode</link>
      <description>【Upgrading an old .NET app doesn’t have to mean chasing broken builds and cryptic errors. Yet for many developers, a simple version bump turns into hours of dependency conflicts and manual fixes. Modernization isn’t just about staying current. Older frameworks can introduce security risks, slow performance, and block cloud adoptio】升级旧的 .NET 应用程序并不一定意味着要追寻损坏的构建和神秘的错误。然而对于许多开发人员来说，一个简单的版本升级就会变成数小时的依赖冲突和手动修复。现代化不仅仅是保持与时俱进。较旧的框架可能会带来安全风险、性能下降和块云采用</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure DevOps and GitHub Repositories — Next Steps in the Path to Agentic AI】Azure DevOps 和 GitHub 存储库 — 迈向代理 AI 的后续步骤</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-devops-and-github-repositories-next-steps-in-the-path-to-agentic-ai</link>
      <description>【In May, we talked about the evolution of GitHub Copilot from a coding assistant into an AI powered peer programmer. Since then, GitHub has taken a major step forward - becoming an open platform for agentic devel】五月份，我们讨论了 GitHub Copilot 从编码助手到人工智能驱动的同行程序员的演变。自此，GitHub向前迈出了一大步——成为代理开发的开放平台</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the Microsoft Teams SDK (Formerly the Teams AI Library)】宣布推出 Microsoft Teams SDK（以前称为 Teams AI 库）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/announcing-the-updated-teams-ai-library-and-mcp-support</link>
      <description>【[alert type=&#34;important&#34; heading=&#34;UPDATE November 17: We&#39;re excited to announce that the Teams AI Library is now called the Microsoft Teams SDK.&#34;]The Teams SDK, now generally available in C# and JavaScript and in public preview for Python, remains a developer’s one-stop-shop to build anything, including conversational agents, for Micros】[alert type =“important”heading =“11 月 17 日更新：我们很高兴地宣布 Teams AI 库现在称为 Microsoft Teams SDK。”]Teams SDK 目前已在 C# 和 JavaScript 版本中普遍提供，并在 Python 中提供公共预览版，仍然是开发人员为 Micros 构建任何内容（包括对话代理）的一站式商店</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Spend Less Time Upgrading, More Time Coding in Visual Studio 2026】在 Visual Studio 2026 中花更少的时间升级，更多的时间编码</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/spend-less-time-upgrading-more-time-coding-in-visual-studio-2026</link>
      <description>【In the past, moving to the next major version of Visual Studio could take hours, sometimes days, to recreate your dev environment the way you like it. Visual Studio 2026 makes it easier than ever to stay current with the latest productivity features, performance improvements, and security fixes all without disrupting your flow. With the new Vi】过去，迁移到 Visual Studio 的下一个主要版本可能需要数小时甚至数天的时间才能按照您喜欢的方式重新创建开发环境。 Visual Studio 2026 让您比以往更轻松地掌握最新的生产力功能、性能改进和安全修复，而无需中断您的流程。有了新的 Vi</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Innovation to Enterprise Trust with Microsoft Agent 365】使用 Microsoft Agent 365 从创新到企业信任</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/from-innovation-to-enterprise-trust-with-microsoft-agent-365</link>
      <description>【The bridge between agent innovation and enterprise readiness  While teams can build an agent in just a few days, deployin】代理创新和企业准备就绪之间的桥梁虽然团队可以在短短几天内构建代理，但部署</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSSQL Extension for VS Code: GitHub Copilot Chat GA and New Public Previews for Edit Data, Data-tier Application, and more】VS Code 的 MSSQL 扩展：GitHub Copilot Chat GA 和用于编辑数据、数据层应用程序等的新公共预览版</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/vscode-mssql-copilot-ga-edit-data</link>
      <description>【The MSSQL Extension for VS Code continues to evolve, delivering features that make SQL development more integrated, more consistent, and more developer-friendly. In version v1.37.0, we’re announcing the Public Preview of Edit Data,】VS Code 的 MSSQL 扩展不断发展，提供的功能使 SQL 开发更加集成、更加一致且对开发人员更加友好。在 v1.37.0 版本中，我们宣布推出编辑数据的公共预览版，</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Major New Agentic Capabilities for GitHub Copilot in JetBrains and Eclipse】在 JetBrains 和 Eclipse 中引入 GitHub Copilot 的主要新代理功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/new-agentic-capabilities-for-github-copilot-in-jetbrains-and-eclipse</link>
      <description>【GitHub Copilot is taking a major step forward with expanded, deeply integrated support for JetBrains and Eclipse — bringing a new generation of agentic, intelligent capabilities directly into your favorite Java IDEs. This release strengthens Copilot’s cross-IDE experience, unifies agentic workflows, and unlocks m】GitHub Copilot 向前迈出了一大步，扩展了对 JetBrains 和 Eclipse 的深度集成支持，将新一代的代理智能功能直接引入您最喜欢的 Java IDE 中。此版本增强了 Copilot 的跨 IDE 体验，统一了代理工作流程，并解锁了更多功能</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Public preview of vector indexing in Azure SQL DB, Azure SQL MI, and SQL database in Microsoft Fabric】Azure SQL DB、Azure SQL MI 和 Microsoft Fabric 中的 SQL 数据库中的矢量索引的公开预览版</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/public-preview-of-vector-indexing-in-azure-sql-db-azure-sql-mi-and-sql-database-in-microsoft-fabric</link>
      <description>【We are happy to share that DiskANN vector indexing is now in public preview across Azure SQL Database, Azure SQL Managed Instance, and SQL database in Microsoft Fabric. DiskANN is a cutting-edge algorithm for efficient vector similarity search, making it ideal for powering recommendation systems】我们很高兴与大家分享，DiskANN 矢量索引现已在 Azure SQL 数据库、Azure SQL 托管实例和 Microsoft Fabric 中的 SQL 数据库中提供公共预览版。 DiskANN 是一种用于高效向量相似性搜索的尖端算法，非常适合为推荐系统提供动力</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB Extension for VS Code Now Generally Available】适用于 VS Code 的 Azure Cosmos DB 扩展现已正式推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-extension-for-vs-code-now-generally-available</link>
      <description>【We’re thrilled to announce the general availability (GA) of the Azure Cosmos DB extension for Visual Studio Code! This powerful extension brings enterprise-grade database management directly into your development environment, making it easi】我们很高兴地宣布适用于 Visual Studio Code 的 Azure Cosmos DB 扩展全面可用 (GA)！这个强大的扩展将企业级数据库管理直接带入您的开发环境，使其变得轻松</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>