<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET 9 Release Candidate 2 is now available!】.NET 9 候选版本 2 现已推出！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-9-rc-2</link>
      <description>【Try out the latest features in .NET 9 Release Candidate 2 across the .NET SDK, libraries, runtime, ASP.NET Core, SignalR, .NET MAUI, and more!】尝试 .NET 9 Release Candidate 2 中跨 .NET SDK、库、运行时、ASP.NET Core、SignalR、.NET MAUI 等的最新功能！</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (September 2024)】vcpkg 的新增功能（2024 年 9 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-september-2024</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2024.09.23 and 2024.09.30 releases, 2024-09-18 and 2024-09-30 tool releases, as well as changes to vcpkg documentation throughout September. This month’s release includes some minor changes and bug fixes, 18 new ports, and 319 updates to existing ports. When updating vcpkg, we [&amp;hellip;]】本博文总结了 2024.09.23 和 2024.09.30 版本、2024-09-18 和 2024-09-30 工具版本中对 vcpkg 包管理器的更改，以及整个 9 月份对 vcpkg 文档的更改。本月的版本包括一些细微的更改和错误修复、18 个新端口以及对现有端口的 319 个更新。更新 vcpkg 时，我们 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 01:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing RBAC Authentication and more for the Azure Cosmos DB Integrated Cache】介绍 Azure Cosmos DB 集成缓存的 RBAC 身份验证及更多功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/introducing-rbac-authentication-and-more-for-the-azure-cosmos-db-integrated-cache</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce new features for the Azure Cosmos DB integrated cache! The integrated cache is built into the dedicated gateway, and now there’s new ways to authenticate your requests. Security is top of mind for many organizations, and you can now use Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) with Microsoft Entra ID to authenticate to [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布 Azure Cosmos DB 集成缓存的新功能！集成缓存内置于专用网关中，现在有新的方法来验证您的请求。对于许多组织来说，安全性是首要考虑因素，您现在可以使用基于角色的访问控制 (RBAC) 和 Microsoft Entra ID 来进行身份验证 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Data Explorer: Custom Columns, Filter History, and Query Views Explained】增强数据资源管理器：自定义列、过滤器历史记录和查询视图说明</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/data-explorer-custom-columns-filter-history-and-query-views-explained</link>
      <description>【Managing large amounts of data is exciting. As a dataset grows in complexity and size, finding efficient ways to sort and analyze this info becomes more important. Azure Cosmos DB Data Explorer is a tool to query, review, and manage your data.  We’ve heard from your feedback in our NPS survey that there’s a need [&amp;hellip;]】管理大量数据是令人兴奋的。随着数据集的复杂性和规模的增加，找到有效的方法来排序和分析这些信息变得更加重要。 Azure Cosmos DB 数据资源管理器是一个用于查询、查看和管理数据的工具。  我们从您在 NPS 调查中的反馈中得知，有必要 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Meet the Winners | Microsoft Developers Azure AI &amp; Azure Cosmos DB Learning Hackathon】认识获奖者 | Microsoft 开发人员 Azure AI 和 Azure Cosmos DB 学习黑客马拉松</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/meet-the-winners-microsoft-developers-azure-ai-azure-cosmos-db-learning-hackathon</link>
      <description>【Azure Cosmos DB powers some of the world’s most popular intelligent apps like ChatGPT. In a recent hackathon, Over 9,500 developers engaged with Azure Cosmos DB and Azure AI services, making it one of the most popular on Devpost, ranking in the top 0.2% of all Devpost hackathons.  Participants explored AI fundamentals and built their [&amp;hellip;]】Azure Cosmos DB 为 ChatGPT 等一些世界上最受欢迎的智能应用程序提供支持。在最近的一次黑客马拉松中，超过 9,500 名开发人员参与了 Azure Cosmos DB 和 Azure AI 服务，使其成为 Devpost 上最受欢迎的黑客马拉松之一，在所有 Devpost 黑客马拉松中排名前 0.2%。  参与者探索了人工智能基础知识并构建了他们的[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Debug Queries More Efficiently with the Improved Error Messaging in Azure Cosmos DB Data Explorer】使用 Azure Cosmos DB 数据资源管理器中改进的错误消息传递更有效地调试查询</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/improved-error-messaging-in-azure-cosmos-db-data-explorer</link>
      <description>【Azure Cosmos DB Data Explorer is a web-based tool available in the Azure Portal that allows you to manage data, as well as track and fix issues with your queries. In this blog post, we will focus on some of the new features in data explorer that improve the error messaging in the query editor, [&amp;hellip;]】Azure Cosmos DB 数据资源管理器是 Azure 门户中提供的基于 Web 的工具，可让你管理数据以及跟踪和修复查询问题。在这篇博文中，我们将重点关注数据浏览器中的一些新功能，这些功能可改进查询编辑器中的错误消息传递，[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Easier localization with the new resource (.resx) manager】使用新资源 (.resx) 管理器更轻松地进行本地化</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/easier-localization-with-the-new-resource-resx-manager</link>
      <description>【If you&amp;#8217;re developing applications that target multiple languages and cultures, you probably know how challenging it can be to manage the resources for each localization. You need to keep track of all the strings, images, icons, and other assets that are specific to each culture, and make sure they are consistent and up to date [&amp;hellip;]】如果您正在开发针对多种语言和文化的应用程序，您可能知道管理每种本地化的资源是多么具有挑战性。您需要跟踪每种文化特有的所有字符串、图像、图标和其他资产，并确保它们一致且是最新的 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 15:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【If threads are created without a message queue, why can I post to them immediately upon creation?】如果创建线程时没有消息队列，为什么我可以在创建后立即向它们发送消息？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241009-00/?p=110354</link>
      <description>【Check who is doing the posting.】检查谁在发帖。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Utilize Multiple Monitors for Microsoft Dev Box with the Windows App】通过 Windows 应用程序利用 Microsoft Dev Box 的多个显示器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/utilize-multiple-monitors-for-microsoft-dev-box-with-the-windows-app</link>
      <description>【Do you use cloud-based developer environments like Microsoft Dev Box? Do you use multiple monitors in your setup? Did you know there a new app in Windows that will give you a great experience with multiple monitors and Microsoft Dev Box? Take a look at this video showing configuring multiple monitor setup with the Windows [&amp;hellip;]】您是否使用基于云的开发人员环境（例如 Microsoft Dev Box）？您的设置中是否使用多个显示器？您是否知道 Windows 中有一款新应用程序可以为您提供多显示器和 Microsoft Dev Box 的出色体验？观看此视频，该视频展示了使用 Windows 配置多显示器设置 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript 5.7 Beta】宣布推出 TypeScript 5.7 Beta</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-5-7-beta</link>
      <description>【Today we are announcing the availability of TypeScript 5.7 Beta. To get started using the beta, you can get it through npm with the following command: npm install -D typescript@beta Let&amp;#8217;s take a look at what&amp;#8217;s new in TypeScript 5.7! Checks for Never-Initialized Variables For a long time, TypeScript has been able to catch issues [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们宣布推出 TypeScript 5.7 Beta。要开始使用 Beta 版，您可以使用以下命令通过 npm 获取它： npm install -D typescript@beta 让我们来看看 TypeScript 5.7 中的新增功能！检查从未初始化的变量很长一段时间以来，TypeScript 一直能够捕获问题 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>