<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing SharePoint Framework 1.20 with updates on building enterprise extensibility within Microsoft 365】发布 SharePoint 框架 1.20，其中包含有关在 Microsoft 365 中构建企业可扩展性的更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/announcing-sharepoint-framework-1-20-with-updates-on-building-enterprise-extensibility-within-microsoft-365</link>
      <description>【We are excited to announce general availability for the SharePoint Framework 1.20. This time focus is primarily on the Microsoft Viva platform capabilities.】我们很高兴地宣布 SharePoint Framework 1.20 全面上市。这次的重点主要是 Microsoft Viva 平台功能。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft 365 Certification control spotlight: Secure software development and deployment】Microsoft 365 认证控制焦点：安全软件开发和部署</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-365-certification-control-spotlight-secure-software-development-and-deployment</link>
      <description>【Explore how Microsoft 365 Certification validates secure software development and deployment best practices.】探索 Microsoft 365 认证如何验证安全软件开发和部署最佳实践。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 14:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting started with testing and .NET Aspire】测试和 .NET Aspire 入门</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/getting-started-with-testing-and-dotnet-aspire</link>
      <description>【Learn how to improve your software development process with automated testing in .NET Aspire. This post covers the basics of getting started, writing tests for distributed applications, and ensuring your services run smoothly.】了解如何通过 .NET Aspire 中的自动化测试改进软件开发流程。这篇文章涵盖了入门、为分布式应用程序编写测试以及确保服务顺利运行的基础知识。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating a React TODO app in Visual Studio 2022】在 Visual Studio 2022 中创建 React TODO 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/creating-a-react-todo-app-in-visual-studio-2022</link>
      <description>【In this tutorial we will create a React front-end, with JavaScript, of a TODO web app using a Visual Studio 2022. To get started install Visual Studio with the Node.js development workload. This will include the JavaScript/TypeScript (JSTS) projects and the associated support. The code for this app can be found at sayedihashimi/todojswebapp (github.com). Create [&amp;hellip;]】在本教程中，我们将使用 Visual Studio 2022 创建一个带有 JavaScript 的 TODO Web 应用程序的 React 前端。要开始安装带有 Node.js 开发工作负载的 Visual Studio。这将包括 JavaScript/TypeScript (JSTS) 项目和相关支持。该应用程序的代码可以在 sayedihashimi/todojswebapp (github.com) 中找到。创造 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【If you’re going to specify the LVS_SORTASCENDING or LVS_SORTDESCENDING style, you had better be telling the truth】如果你要指定 LVS_SORTASCENDING 或 LVS_SORTDESCENDING 风格，你最好说实话</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240926-00/?p=110316</link>
      <description>【Because the listview control uses it to optimize searching.】因为listview控件就是用它来优化搜索的。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using JSON Schema for Structured Output in Python for OpenAI Models】在 OpenAI 模型的 Python 中使用 JSON 架构进行结构化输出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/using-json-schema-for-structured-output-in-python-for-openai-models</link>
      <description>【In working with AI applications, ensuring that the output generated by a language model is structured and follows a consistent format is critical—especially when handling complex tasks like solving math problems. A powerful way to achieve this is through the use of JSON Schema, which allows the AI model to produce outputs that align with [&amp;hellip;]】在使用人工智能应用程序时，确保语言模型生成的输出是结构化的并遵循一致的格式至关重要，尤其是在处理解决数学问题等复杂任务时。实现这一目标的一个强大方法是使用 JSON Schema，它允许 AI 模型生成与 [...] 一致的输出。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 17:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build a chatbot on your own data in 1 hour with Azure SQL, Langchain and Chainlit】使用 Azure SQL、Langchain 和 Chainlit 在 1 小时内根据您自己的数据构建聊天机器人</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/build-a-chatbot-on-your-own-data-in-1-hour-with-azure-sql-langchain-and-chainlit</link>
      <description>【Chatbots are the hot topic lately, and now you can create them easily by downloading solutions like OpenWebUI, connect it to Ollama or any OpenAI compatible API, choose your favorite language model, and then run it. It just takes a few minutes and it&amp;#8217;s done. But building chatbots is not enough, you most likely want [&amp;hellip;]】聊天机器人是最近的热门话题，现在您可以通过下载 OpenWebUI 等解决方案轻松创建它们，将其连接到 Ollama 或任何 OpenAI 兼容的 API，选择您最喜欢的语言模型，然后运行它。只需几分钟就可以完成。但构建聊天机器人还不够，您很可能想要 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.23.1-3 and 1.22.7-3 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.23.1-3 和 1.22.7-3 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-23-1-3-and-1-22-7-3-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new set of Microsoft Go builds is now available for download.】一组新的 Microsoft Go 版本现已可供下载。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 18:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Common annotated security keys】常见的带注释的安全密钥</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/engineering-at-microsoft/common-annotated-security-keys</link>
      <description>【In April 2021, GitHub announced changes to their security token format that significantly enhanced security. The improvement leveraged two straightforward techniques: a fixed signature in the generated token and a checksum &amp;#8211; both of which are highly effective in eliminating false positives (noise) and false negatives (missed findings). Microsoft also implements these techniques widely in [&amp;hellip;]】2021 年 4 月，GitHub 宣布更改其安全令牌格式，显着增强了安全性。该改进利用了两种简单的技术：生成的令牌中的固定签名和校验和——这两种技术在消除误报（噪声）和漏报（遗漏发现）方面非常有效。微软还在[...]中广泛实施了这些技术</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 18:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tailored Code Completions for C++ Developers: Fine-tuned models are now in limited public beta for GitHub Copilot Enterprise】为 C++ 开发人员量身定制的代码完成：微调模型现已进入 GitHub Copilot Enterprise 的有限公开测试版</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/tailored-code-completions-for-c-developers-fine-tuned-models-are-now-in-limited-public-beta-for-github-copilot-enterprise</link>
      <description>【GitHub recently announced that custom models are available for GitHub Copilot Enterprise users in limited public beta. Custom models are fine-tuned on your organization’s proprietary codebases and coding practices to provide more contextually relevant and consistent inline suggestions. How It Works: Security and Privacy in Custom Models The data used to train your organization’s custom [&amp;hellip;]】GitHub 最近宣布，在有限的公开测试版中，自定义模型可供 GitHub Copilot Enterprise 用户使用。自定义模型根据您组织的专有代码库和编码实践进行微调，以提供更上下文相关且一致的内联建议。它是如何工作的：自定义模型中的安全性和隐私用于培训组织的自定义模型的数据[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>