<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Preparing Your .NET MAUI Apps for Google Play&#39;s 16 KB Page Size Requirement】为Google Play的16 KB页面尺寸要求准备.NET MAUI应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/maui-google-play-16-kb-page-size-support</link>
      <description>【If you&#39;re a .NET MAUI developer publishing apps to Google Play, there&#39;s an important requirement coming your way. Starting November 1st, 2025, Google Play will require all new apps and updates targeting Android 15+ to support 16 KB page sizes on 64-bit devices. What is the 16 KB Page Size Requirement? Androi】如果您是Google Play的.NET MAUI开发人员发布应用程序，那么您的方式就会有一个重要的要求。从2025年11月1日开始，Google Play将需要所有针对Android 15+的更新，以支持64位设备上的16 KB页面尺寸。 16 KB页面大小的要求是什么？ Androi</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why didn&#39;t Windows 95 setup install a miniature Windows 95 so that it could be written as a 32-bit program?】为什么Windows 95设置不安装微型Windows 95，以便可以将其写入32位程序？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250926-00/?p=111629</link>
      <description>【I noted some time ago that Windows 95 Setup was actually three programs running under three different operating systems. The first part was an MS-DOS program, which was used if you installed Windows 9】我一段时间以前指出，Windows 95设置实际上是在三个不同的操作系统下运行的三个程序。第一部分是MS-DOS程序，如果您安装了Windows 9</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Simplifying Resource Management in mssql-python through Context Manager】通过上下文管理器简化MSSQL-Python中的资源管理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/simplifying-resource-management-in-mssql-python-through-context-manager</link>
      <description>【Reviewed by: Sumit Sarabhai】评论者：Sumit Sarabhai</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking MCP in JetBrains: How Copilot Uses Sampling, Prompts, Resources, and Elicitation】解锁Jetbrains：Copilot如何使用采样，提示，资源和启发</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/unlocking-mcp-in-jetbrains-how-copilot-uses-sampling-prompts-resources-and-elicitation</link>
      <description>【With the enhanced capability of the MCP on JetBrains, you can now bring prompts, resources, and even interac】随着MCP在喷气桥上的功能增强，您现在可以带来提示，资源，甚至可以携带Interac</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PIX 2509.25 - support for new D3D features and devices, and misc bug fixes】PIX 2509.25-支持新的D3D功能和设备，以及MISC错误修复</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pix/pix-2509-25</link>
      <description>【Today we released PIX version 2509.25, which can be downloaded here. This release includes everything in the previous 2507.11 release, plus: A compatibility fix to make PIX work on Windows 11 24H2 or 25H2 with K】今天，我们发布了PIX版本2509.25，可以在此处下载。此版本包括上一版中的所有内容，以及：使pix在Windows 11 24H2或25H2上使用k的兼容性修复</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Aspire 9.5】宣布Aspire 9.5</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-aspire-95</link>
      <description>【Aspire 9.5 is here with exciting new features and improvements that enhance the developer experience for building distributed applications. For the complete list of changes and technical details, visit the official Aspire 9.5 release notes. Let&#39;s】Aspire 9.5在这里具有令人兴奋的新功能和改进，可增强开发人员用于构建分布式应用程序的体验。有关更改和技术细节的完整列表，请访问官方Aspire 9.5发行说明。让我们</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agility SDK 1.618: Advanced Shader Delivery and 1.716 out of preview】敏捷SDK 1.618：高级着色器交付和1.716的预览</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/directx/agility-sdk-1-618</link>
      <description>【We are pleased to announce the retail release of AgilitySDK 1.618, available on Agility SDK Downloads today! This release promotes our 1.716 features out of preview and also】我们很高兴地宣布，Agilitysdk 1.618的零售发布，今天可在Agility SDK下载上使用！此版本促进了我们的1.716功能，从预览中提取</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing WinUI Gallery 2.7】宣布Winui Gallery 2.7</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ifdef-windows/announcing-winui-gallery-2-7</link>
      <description>【&amp;nbs】＆nbs</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data API builder 1.6: Flexible Logging for Every Developer】数据API构建器1.6：每个开发人员的灵活记录</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/data-api-builder-16-logging</link>
      <description>【Previously, developers were limited to the default log levels and filters hardcoded into DAB. With release 1.6, you can now configure filters and levels for logs emitted by the engine. This release also adds new sinks. In addition to Application Insights and OpenTelemetry publishing, Data API builder now suppo】以前，开发人员仅限于默认日志级别，并将过滤器用于DAB。使用Release 1.6，您现在可以为发动机发射的日志配置过滤器和级别。此版本还增加了新的水槽。除了应用程序见解和OpenTelemetry Publishing外，数据API构建器现在可以支持</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Samples note: Use comments to describe what code does, not what you wish the code would do】示例注意：使用注释来描述代码的作用，而不是您希望代码会做什么</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250925-00/?p=111627</link>
      <description>【Windows API design is samples-driven. This means that when a team proposes an API, we want them to demonstrate how to use that API with a sample code fragment. We do this so that we can evaluate the ergonomics of the API and see】Windows API设计是样品驱动的。这意味着，当团队提出API时，我们希望他们演示如何使用示例代码片段使用该API。我们这样做，以便我们可以评估API的人体工程学并看到</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>