<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【The symbolism of the magnifying glass is not universal】放大镜的象征不是通用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250603-00/?p=111240</link>
      <description>【Just making things bigger?】只是使事情变大？</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Extension Manager updates in Visual Studio】Visual Studio中的扩展管理器更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/extension-manager-updates-in-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【The latest updates in Visual Studio 2022 introduced features specifically designed to improve how you manage extensions. These updates offer tools that help you automate processes, provide detailed controls for configuration, and enhance the user interface to streamline your development workflows. Seamless auto updates Visual Studio now automatically triggers updates whenever you open the Extension [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio 2022中的最新更新引入了专门设计的功能，以改善您管理扩展的方式。这些更新提供的工具可帮助您自动化流程，为配置提供详细的控件，并增强用户界面以简化开发工作流程。无缝自动更新Visual Studio现在每当打开扩展名时会自动触发更新[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing Conversational Agents with Azure AI Language Conversational Language Understanding and Custom Question Answering】用Azure AI语言对话语言理解和自定义问题回答增强对话代理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/enhancing-conversational-agents-with-azure-ai-language-conversational-language-understanding-and-custom-question-answering</link>
      <description>【As we focus our work on empowering the agent design experience, a list of the new features in the we published earlier this week, including the intent triage agent and the exact question-answering agent, utilizing Conversational language understanding (CLU) and Custom question answering (CQA). We’re excited to share new enhancements to the customization experiences in CLU and CQA [&amp;hellip;]】当我们将工作重点放在授权代理设计经验上时，我们本周早些时候发布的新功能列表，包括Intent Triage Agent和确切的问题撤职代理，利用对话性语言理解（CLU）和自定义问题答案（CQA）。我们很高兴分享CLU和CQA的定制体验的新增强功能[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 22:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (May 2025)】Azure SDK版本（2025年5月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-may-2025</link>
      <description>【Azure SDK releases every month. In this post, you&#39;ll find this month&#39;s highlights and release notes.】Azure SDK每月发布。在这篇文章中，您会发现本月的亮点和发行说明。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using AI Foundry with .NET MAUI】将AI Foundry与.net Maui一起使用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/using-ai-foundry-with-dotnet-maui</link>
      <description>【Using AI Foundry with .NET MAUI brings the power of LLMs to mobile and desktop applications.】使用带有.NET MAUI的AI Foundry将LLM的功能带入移动和桌面应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Stating the obvious about debugging an invalid parameter error when freeing memory】说明在释放内存时调试无效参数错误的明显</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250602-00/?p=111236</link>
      <description>【Writing it down for posterity.】将其写下来以进行后代。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub Secret Protection and GitHub Code Security for Azure DevOps】GitHub秘密保护和Azure DevOps的GitHub代码安全性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/github-secret-protection-and-github-code-security-for-azure-devops</link>
      <description>【Following the changes to GitHub Advanced Security on GitHub, we&amp;#8217;re launching the standalone security products of GitHub Secret Protection and GitHub Code Security for Azure DevOps today. You can bring the protection of Advanced Security to your enterprise with the flexibility to enable the right level of protection for your repositories. GitHub Secret Protection for [&amp;hellip;]】在GITHUB上对GitHub Advanced Security进行了更改后，我们正在为Azure DevOps推出GitHub Secret Protection和GitHub Code Security的独立安全产品。您可以将高级安全保护的保护带入您的企业，以便灵活地为您的存储库提供适当的保护级别。 Github的秘密保护[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【D3D12 Cooperative Vector】D3D12合作矢量</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/directx/cooperative-vector</link>
      <description>【Welcome to the preview release for Cooperative Vector support in D3D12.  This exposes powerful new hardware acceleration for vector and matrix operations, enabling developers to efficiently drive neural rendering techniques directly from individual shader threads in real-time graphics pipelines. In research and in industry, machine learning based approaches have made their way to mainstream, replacing/augmenting [&amp;hellip;]】欢迎来到D3D12中合作向量支持的预览发布。  这将为向量和矩阵操作公开强大的新硬件加速度，使开发人员能够在实时图形管道中直接从单个着色器线程中直接从单个着色器线程中驱动神经渲染技术。在研究和行业中，基于机器学习的方法已成为主流，取代/增强[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Cloud Academy: Unlock Your Azure Skills and Accelerate Your Career】云学院：解锁您的Azure技能并加速您的职业生涯</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/cloud-academy-benefit-for-visual-studio-subscribers</link>
      <description>【When we launched the Cloud Academy benefit for Visual Studio Professional and Enterprise subscribers back in March 2025, our goal was simple: give you the hands-on, practical learning experience you need to confidently master Azure and cloud technologies — without spending a dime beyond your subscription. Why? Because in today’s fast-changing tech world, knowing theory [&amp;hellip;]】当我们在2025年3月推出Visual Studio专业人士和企业订阅者的Cloud Academy福利时，我们的目标很简单：为您提供动手实践，实用的学习经验，您需要确信掌握Azure和Cloud Technologies，而无需花费贵重的订阅。为什么？因为在当今快速变化的技术世界中，了解理论[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A story of collaborating agents: chatting with your database the right way】一个合作代理人的故事：以正确的方式与您的数据库聊天</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/a-story-of-collaborating-agents-chatting-with-your-database-the-right-way</link>
      <description>【Today, more and more customers are embracing AI with one clear goal in mind: they want to chat with their data. And by &amp;#8220;data,&amp;#8221; they mean all of it:  structured tables, unstructured documents, images, audio, and more. This demand has given rise to hybrid approaches that blend semantic understanding with precise data retrieval. But here’s [&amp;hellip;]】如今，越来越多的客户正在考虑一个明确的目标：他们想与数据聊天。通过“数据”，它们的意思是所有：结构化表，非结构化文档，图像，音频等。这种需求引起了混合方法，将语义理解与精确的数据检索融为一体。但这是[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>