<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Running RAG with ONNX Runtime GenAI for On-Prem Windows】使用onnx运行时genai运行抹布，用于本地窗口</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/running-rag-onnxruntime-genai</link>
      <description>【Exploring how to efficiently run a RAG pipeline with structured language models (SLMs) and guardrails on Windows, achieving inference under 5 seconds with ONNX Runtime GenAI.】探索如何使用结构化语言模型（SLM）和Windows上的护栏有效运行RAG管道，并使用ONNX Runtime Genai在5秒钟内进行推理。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Rapidly prototype with gpt-image-1 from Azure OpenAI Service in the Images Playground in Azure AI Foundry】Azure AI Foundry的图像操场上的Azure Openai服务中的GPT-Image-1快速原型</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/images-playground-may-2025</link>
      <description>【Introducing the next-gen images playground in Azure AI Foundry, a high-fidelity UX sandbox for developers to rapidly prototype with state-of-the-art image generation models like gpt-image-1 from Azure OpenAI Service 1. This playground enables real-time experimentation, prompt optimization, and integration with developer tools like VS Code, accelerating the &#34;Build-Measure-Learn&#34; development loop and enhancing productivity.】Introducing the next-gen images playground in Azure AI Foundry, a high-fidelity UX sandbox for developers to rapidly prototype with state-of-the-art image generation models like gpt-image-1 from Azure OpenAI Service 1. This playground enables real-time experimentation, prompt optimization, and integration with developer tools like VS Code, accelerating the &#34;Build-Measure-Learn&#34; development loop and enhancing productivity.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Azure DevOps ID Token Refresh and Terraform Task Version 5】介绍Azure Devops ID令牌刷新和Terraform任务版本5</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/introducing-azure-devops-id-token-refresh-and-terraform-task-version-5</link>
      <description>【We are excited to share some recent updates that improve the experience of using Workload identity federation (OpenID Connect) with Azure DevOps and Terraform on Microsoft Azure. Many working parts have come together to make this possible and we&amp;#8217;ll share those here. We are also very pleased to announce version 5 of the Microsoft DevLabs [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴分享一些最近的更新，以改善使用Azure DevOps和Microsoft Azure上的Azure DevOps和Terraform的工作量身份联合会（OpenID Connect）的经验。许多工作部件都聚集在一起，使这一切成为可能，我们将在这里分享。我们也很高兴宣布Microsoft DevLabs的第5版[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 08:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using C++ type aliasing to avoid the ODR problem with conditional compilation, part 1】使用C ++类型混叠来避免有条件汇编的ODR问题，第1部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250501-00/?p=111134</link>
      <description>【Still one definition, but two types.】仍然是一个定义，但两种类型。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using type aliasing to avoid the ODR problem with conditional compilation, part 2】使用类型混叠来避免有条件汇编的ODR问题，第2部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250502-00/?p=111140</link>
      <description>【Ensuring that you pick a side.】确保您选择一侧。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Modernizing Project Files with AI: A Success Story from the .NET Team】使用AI：.NET团队的成功案例现代化项目文件</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/modernizing-project-files-with-ai-a-success-story-from-the-dotnet-team</link>
      <description>【At Microsoft, we are constantly exploring innovative ways to enhance our workflows, improve productivity, and ensure we have a secure supply chain that uses modern tools. One of our recent initiatives was to rebuild the .NET Framework build system by leveraging AI to automate the process. Here’s the story of how we successfully achieved this [&amp;hellip;]】在微软，我们一直在探索创新的方法来增强我们的工作流程，提高生产率并确保我们拥有使用现代工具的安全供应链。我们最近的举措之一是通过利用AI自动化流程来重建.NET框架构建系统。这是我们如何成功实现这一目标的故事[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【There’s a Linux File Explorer built into Visual Studio!?!】Visual Studio中内置有Linux文件资源管理器！？！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/theres-a-linux-file-explorer-built-into-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【The Remote File Explorer in Visual Studio provides developers with a convenient way to browse, view, and edit files on remote machines—directly from within the IDE. It&amp;#8217;s a powerful tool for managing remote environments without leaving your development workflow. Scott Hanselman published a new YouTube video to his channel, taking us on the journey of [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio中的远程文件资源管理器为开发人员提供了一种方便的方式，可以从IDE内部直接浏览，查看和编辑文件。它是管理远程环境而不离开开发工作流程的强大工具。斯科特·汉塞尔曼（Scott Hanselman）向他的频道发布了一个新的YouTube视频，带我们进行了[…]的旅程。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure AI Foundry extension for Visual Studio Code April 2025 Update】视觉工作室代码2025年4月更新的视觉工作室代码的Azure AI Foundry扩展</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/azure-ai-foundry-extension-for-visual-studio-code-april-2025-update</link>
      <description>【Azure AI Foundry extension for Visual Studio Code April 2025 Update Azure AI Foundry is a trusted platform for designing, customizing, and managing AI applications, with a portal that enables secure data integration, model customization, and enterprise-grade governance. Earlier this month, we announced the public preview of the Azure AI Foundry extension. And today, the [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio代码的Azure AI Foundry扩展2025年4月更新Azure AI Foundry是一个可信赖的平台，用于设计，自定义和管理AI应用程序，并借助一个门户，该门户可启用安全的数据集成，模型自定义和企业级治理。本月初，我们宣布了Azure AI铸造扩展的公开预览。今天，[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Orchestrating AI Agents with Semantic Kernel Plugins: A Technical Deep Dive】来宾博客：使用语义内核插件协调AI代理：技术深入潜水</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-orchestrating-ai-agents-with-semantic-kernel-plugins-a-technical-deep-dive</link>
      <description>【Today we&amp;#8217;re excited to welcome Jarre Nejatyab as a guest blog to highlight a technical deep dive on orchestrating AI Agents with Semantic Kernel Plugins. In the rapidly evolving world of Large Language Models (LLMs), orchestrating specialized AI agents has become crucial for building sophisticated cognitive architectures capable of complex reasoning and task execution. While [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们很高兴欢迎Jarre Nejatyab作为来宾博客，以突出有关使用语义内核插件协调AI代理的技术深入研究。在大型语言模型（LLM）迅速发展的世界中，精心策划专业的AI代理对于建立能够复杂的推理和任务执行的复杂认知体系结构变得至关重要。尽管 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 21:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (April 2025)】VCPKG的新功能（2025年4月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-april-2025</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2025.04.09 registry release, 2025-03-22, 2025-04-01, and 2025-04-07 tool releases, as well as changes to vcpkg documentation throughout April. This release contains bug fixes, a new documentation article on offline usage of vcpkg, and other minor improvements. Arm64 Linux users of vcpkg [&amp;hellip;]】这篇博客文章总结了VCPKG软件包管理器的更改，作为2025.04.09注册表版本的一部分，即2025-03-22、2025-04-01和2025-04-07工具发行，以及整个4月VCPKG文档的更改。该版本包含错误修复程序，有关VCPKG离线使用情况的新文档文档以及其他较小的改进。 VCPKG的ARM64 Linux用户[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 21:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>