<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Making Visual Studio a bit more visual】让 Visual Studio 更加直观</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/making-visual-studio-a-bit-more-visual</link>
      <description>【Any web, desktop, or mobile developer works with images often. You reference them from C#, HTML, XAML, CSS, C++, VB, TypeScript, and even in code comments. Some images are local, and some exist online or on network shares, while others only exist as base64 encoded strings.】任何 Web、桌面或移动开发人员都经常使用图像。您可以从 C#、HTML、XAML、CSS、C++、VB、TypeScript 甚至代码注释中引用它们。有些图像是本地的，有些存在于在线或网络共享上，而其他图像仅作为 base64 编码字符串存在。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Fluid Relay: Leveraging Azure Blob Storage to scale Git】Azure Fluid Relay：利用 Azure Blob 存储来扩展 Git</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/azure-fluid-relay-leveraging-azure-blob-storage-to-scale-git</link>
      <description>【Learn how to leverage Git as a storage mechanism behind the globally available Azure Fluid Relay (AFR) service.】了解如何利用 Git 作为全球可用的 Azure Fluid Relay (AFR) 服务背后的存储机制。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 15:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET 9 Preview 6 is now available!】.NET 9 预览版 6 现已推出！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-9-preview-6</link>
      <description>【Try out the latest features in .NET 9 Preview 6 across the .NET runtime, SDK, libraries, ASP.NET Core, Blazor, and more!】跨 .NET 运行时、SDK、库、ASP.NET Core、Blazor 等尝试 .NET 9 Preview 6 中的最新功能！</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating an already-completed asynchronous activity in C++/WinRT, part 7】在 C++/WinRT 中创建已完成的异步活动，第 7 部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240717-00/?p=109975</link>
      <description>【Implementing the contract directly.】直接履行合同。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building a Safer Future – How NuGet is Tackling Software Supply Chain Threats】构建更安全的未来 - NuGet 如何应对软件供应链威胁</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/nuget/building-a-safer-future-how-nuget-is-tackling-software-supply-chain-threats</link>
      <description>【Despite significant technological progress in addressing complex security threats, the key to preventing the next attack lies in adhering to fundamental security principles. It&amp;#8217;s essential to ensure the software ecosystem is secure, focusing on protecting .NET developers who design, build, and maintain the critical software we all use.】尽管在解决复杂的安全威胁方面取得了重大的技术进步，但防止下一次攻击的关键在于坚持基本的安全原则。确保软件生态系统的安全至关重要，重点是保护设计、构建和维护我们都使用的关键软件的 .NET 开发人员。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Get Hands-On with Visual Studio and Azure: Live at Microsoft HQ this August!】亲身体验 Visual Studio 和 Azure：今年 8 月在 Microsoft 总部现场直播！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-live-2024-microsoft-hq</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio LIVE! Microsoft HQ 2024 August 5-9 | Microsoft Conference Center, Redmond, WA There’s still time to register, join us, get your questions answered, and bring back a wealth of knowledge and excitement to your teams! We’re close to selling out for next month’s conference,】视觉工作室上线！ Microsoft 总部 2024 年 8 月 5 日至 9 日 |华盛顿州雷德蒙德 Microsoft 会议中心 现在还有时间注册、加入我们、解答您的问题并为您的团队带回丰富的知识和兴奋！下个月的会议门票即将售完，</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Model as a Service (MaaS) Available for Semantic Kernel】可用于语义内核的模型即服务 (MaaS)</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/model-as-a-service-maas-available-for-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Hello! We are delighted to make an announcement regarding the availability of Azure AI Inference within Semantic Kernel (Python). This latest AI connector empowers you to experiment with a broader range of models hosted on Azure within your applications. &amp;nbsp; The Sample Application: Evaluating LLMs Here is the location of the full sample.】你好！我们很高兴地宣布有关语义内核 (Python) 中 Azure AI 推理的可用性。这个最新的 AI 连接器使您能够在应用程序中试验 Azure 上托管的更广泛的模型。   示例应用程序：评估法学硕士 这里是完整示例的位置。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【NuGetAudit 2.0: Elevating Security and Trust in Package Management】NuGetAudit 2.0：提升包管理的安全性和信任度</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/nuget/nugetaudit-2-0-elevating-security-and-trust-in-package-management</link>
      <description>【Introduction In November 2023 (NuGet 6.8, Visual Studio 17.8, .NET SDK 8.0.100), we released NuGet Audit. NuGet Audit provides warnings during restore when a package with a known vulnerability is used by a project. More information about NuGet Audit, including detailed configuration options can be found on our learn website.】简介 2023 年 11 月（NuGet 6.8、Visual Studio 17.8、.NET SDK 8.0.100），我们发布了 NuGet Audit。当项目使用具有已知漏洞的包时，NuGet Audit 会在还原期间提供警告。有关 NuGet Audit 的更多信息（包括详细的配置选项）可以在我们的学习网站上找到。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating an already-completed asynchronous activity in C++/WinRT, part 6】在 C++/WinRT 中创建已完成的异步活动，第 6 部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240716-00/?p=109973</link>
      <description>【Let the conversion do the talking.】让转换来说话。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building React Native for Windows Apps from a Mac】从 Mac 构建 React Native for Windows 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/react-native/2024-07-18-running-rnw-from-a-mac-md</link>
      <description>【Owning a Windows PC is not a requirement to build and ship Windows experiences. In this blog post, I&#39;ll walk through my investigation of how to develop React Native for Windows applications from a Mac.】拥有 Windows PC 并不是构建和交付 Windows 体验的必要条件。在这篇博文中，我将逐步研究如何从 Mac 开发适用于 Windows 应用程序的 React Native。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>