<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Roadmap for AI in Visual Studio (September)】Visual Studio的AI路线图（9月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/roadmap-for-ai-in-visual-studio-september</link>
      <description>【Today, we’re excited to share our public roadmap, which outlines the next steps in evolving Visual Studio with AI-powered agentic experiences. With every month, we aim to deliver smarter, faster, and more intuitive tools that enhance your coding experience. Disclaimer: The items outlined here represent ongoing work for the month. They】今天，我们很高兴分享我们的公共路线图，该路线图概述了通过AI驱动的代理体验发展视觉工作室的下一步。我们每个月都打算提供更智能，更快，更直观的工具，以增强您的编码体验。免责声明：此处概述的项目代表了当月正在进行的工作。他们</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EFCore.Visualizer - View Entity Framework Core query plan inside Visual Studio】efcore.visualizer-查看“实体框架核心查询计划”</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/ef-core-visualizer-view-entity-framework-core-query-plan-inside-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【This is a guest blog from Giorgi Dalakishvili, the developer of EFCore.Visualizer. Entity Framework Core is a powerful, feature-rich ORM powering many of today&#39;s applications. W】这是efcore.visualizer的开发商Giorgi Dalakishvili的来宾博客。 Entity Framework Core是一个功能强大的功能丰富的ORM，可为当今许多应用程序提供动力。 w</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thoughts on creating a tracking pointer class, part 13: Restoring the strong exception guarantee】关于创建跟踪指针类的想法，第13部分：恢复强大的异常保证</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250827-00/?p=111518</link>
      <description>【Last time, we created a tracking pointer class based on std::shared_ptr. We found a problem with the move-assignment operator: It didn&#39;t satisfy the str】上次，我们创建了一个基于std :: shared_ptr的跟踪指针类。我们发现了移动管理操作员的问题：它不满足STR</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Encoding Changes for Template Arguments in Semantic Kernel】在语义内核中编码模板参数的更改</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/encoding-changes-for-template-arguments-in-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【In previous versions of the Semantic Kernel, the encoding of template arguments was performed automatically if the argument type was a string. The encoding was not applied for custom types, anonymous types, or collections. With the latest changes, we&#39;ve introduced stricter rules: if automatic encoding is enabled (the default be】在语义内核的先前版本中，如果参数类型是字符串，则会自动执行模板参数的编码。该编码不适用于自定义类型，匿名类型或集合。有了最新的更改，我们引入了更严格的规则：如果启用了自动编码（默认为</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 05:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Authentication Changes in Semantic Kernel Python】Azure身份验证语义内核Python的变化</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/azure-authentication-changes-in-semantic-kernel-python</link>
      <description>【In previous versions of the Semantic Kernel Python, the default fallback authentication mechanism for Azure services like AzureChatCompletion was DefaultAzureCredential from the Azure Identity library. This provided a convenient way to authenticate without explicitly passing credentials, especially during development.】在先前版本的语义内核Python中，AzurechatCompletion（例如AzureChatCompletion）的默认后备身份验证机制是Azure Identity库中的DefaultazureCrecrecreCrecretential。这提供了一种方便的方法来验证而无需明确传递凭据，尤其是在开发过程中。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 05:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Visual Studio August Update is here - smarter AI, better debugging, and more control】Visual Studio 8月更新在这里 - 更聪明的AI，更好的调试和更多控制</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/the-visual-studio-august-update-is-here-smarter-ai-better-debugging-and-more-control</link>
      <description>【The August 2025 update for Visual Studio 2022 (v17.14) is now available, and it’s all about helping developers stay focused, productive, and in control. Whether you&#39;re building games, tuning performance, or exploring AI, this release brings meaningful improvements that make everyday development smoother and smarter.】2025年8月的Visual Studio 2022更新（V17.14）现已上市，这一切都涉及帮助开发人员保持专注，富有成效和控制。无论您是构建游戏，调整性能还是探索AI，此版本都会带来有意义的改进，使日常开发变得更加顺畅，更聪明。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Windows Terminal Preview 1.24 Release】Windows Terminal Preview 1.24版本</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/commandline/windows-terminal-preview-1-24-release</link>
      <description>【We’re back with another Terminal release for you! This development cycle, we focused on overall quality of life improvements and bug fixes. We are also updating Windows Terminal stable to version 1.23, which will include all of the features from】我们将为您提供另一个终端版本！在开发周期，我们专注于整体生活质量改善和错误修复。我们还将更新Windows终端稳定为1.23版，其中包括来自</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thoughts on creating a tracking pointer class, part 12: A shared tracking pointer】关于创建跟踪指针类的想法，第12部分：共享跟踪指针</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250826-00/?p=111506</link>
      <description>【The tracking pointer designs we&#39;ve been using so far have had O(n) complexity on move, where n is the number of outstanding tracking pointers. But we can reduce this to O(1) by the classic technique of introducing another level of indirection. What we can do is give every trackable object】到目前为止，我们一直使用的跟踪指针设计在移动中具有O（n）的复杂性，其中N是出色的跟踪指针的数量。但是，我们可以通过引入另一个间接级别的经典技术将其简化为O（1）。我们能做的就是给每个可追踪的对象</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【VS Code Dev Days – Join an event near you to learn about AI-assisted development】VS代码开发日 - 参加您附近的活动，了解AI辅助开发</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/vs-code-dev-days-–-join-an-event-near-you-to-learn-about-ai-assisted-development</link>
      <description>【Join a VS Code Dev Days event to learn about GitHub Copilot in VS Code Read the full article】加入VS代码开发日活动，以了解有关GitHub Copilot在VS代码中阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Secure Your Connections with Entra ID Support in the DocumentDB VS Code Extension】在文档DB VS代码扩展中使用ENTRA ID支持保护您的连接</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/secure-your-connections-with-entra-id-support-in-the-documentdb-vs-code-extension</link>
      <description>【Today, we&#39;re thrilled to announce a major update to the DocumentDB for VS Code extension that will make life easier for enterprise developers. With】今天，我们很高兴地宣布对VS代码扩展的文档DB进行重大更新，这将使企业开发人员的生活更轻松。和</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 22:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>