<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhance Pull Request Reviews with In-Depth Feedback】通过深入的反馈来增强拉的请求评论</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/enhance-pull-request-reviews-with-in-depth-feedback</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio 2022 has taken the pull request experience to the next level by making reviews interactive. We previously enabled viewing your pull request comments inline in your working files. Now, the latest update empowers you to add comments directly within the IDE, streamlining the review process. Now, pull request reviewers can conduct deep reviews [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio 2022通过使评论互动将拉力请求体验提升到了一个新的水平。我们先前启用了您的工作文件中的“拉动请求”注释。现在，最新的更新使您可以直接在IDE中添加注释，从而简化审核过程。现在，拉请请求审稿人可以进行深入的评论[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【C++ Dynamic Debugging: Full Debuggability for Optimized Builds】C ++动态调试：优化构建的完整调试性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/cpp-dynamic-debugging-full-debuggability-for-optimized-builds</link>
      <description>【Over the past 5 years, we’ve had many incredible opportunities to engage with game developers. From AAA studios to indie developers, the passion for slashing iteration times is significant. Amidst all the fantastic feedback we&amp;#8217;ve received for Visual Studio, one sentiment has rung loud and clear: a desire to debug optimized C++ code without sacrificing [&amp;hellip;]】在过去的5年中，我们有许多与游戏开发人员互动的机会。从AAA工作室到独立开发人员，对削减迭代时代的热情非常重要。在我们为Visual Studio收到的所有奇妙反馈中，一个情绪大声而清晰：渴望调试优化的C ++代码而无需牺牲[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Hidden Risks of Docker Build Time Arguments and How to Secure Your Secrets】Docker的隐藏风险建立时间论点以及如何确保您的秘密</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/hidden-risks-of-docker-build-time-arguments-and-how-to-secure-your-secrets</link>
      <description>【This post discusses the security risks of using Docker build-time arguments to pass secrets, and suggests alternative methods for handling secrets securely.】这篇文章讨论了使用Docker Build Time参数通过秘密的安全风险，并建议使用安全处理秘密的替代方法。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enforcement of license checks for PSTN Bot calls】执行PSTN机器人通话的许可证检查</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/enforcement-of-license-checks-for-pstn-bot-calls</link>
      <description>【As part of Microsoft’s feature parity with Teams Phone extensibility, we’re announcing the enforcement of Phone System license checks for Bot-initiated transfers to Teams users. This current gap in our systems will be addressed in June 2025.  Microsoft Teams requires that Teams users behind applications such as queue applications require a phone system license and [&amp;hellip;]】作为Microsoft与Teams Phone Extresibility的功能均等的一部分，我们宣布执行电话系统许可证检查机器人发射的转移到团队用户。我们系统中当前的差距将于2025年6月解决。微软团队要求将用户在诸如队列应用程序等应用程序之后的用户需要电话系统许可和[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 15:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft 365 Certification control spotlight: Data at rest】Microsoft 365认证控制聚光灯：静止数据</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-365-certification-control-spotlight-data-at-rest</link>
      <description>【Read how Microsoft 365 Certification ensures compliance for data at rest.】阅读Microsoft 365认证如何确保静止数据的合规性。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 15:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing Developer Tools with Authentication Brokers】使用身份验证经纪人确保开发人员工具</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com//securing-developer-tools-with-authentication-brokers</link>
      <description>【If you’ve used any applications that required connecting your personal Microsoft or Entra ID account, you’re probably familiar with the typical “authentication dance” – you see a browser window pop up, you enter your credentials, then you can close the browser, and the application is magically authenticated. The next application you launch does the same [&amp;hellip;]】如果您使用了任何需要连接个人Microsoft或Entra ID帐户的应用程序，那么您可能熟悉典型的“身份验证舞蹈”  - 您会看到浏览器窗口弹出，输入凭据，然后您可以关闭浏览器，并且该应用程序具有神奇的认证。您启动的下一个应用程序执行相同的[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What could cause a memory corruption bug to disappear in safe mode?】是什么可能导致内存腐败错误在安全模式下消失？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250320-00/?p=110981</link>
      <description>【A simplified execution environment means fewer things that you can stumble over.】简化的执行环境意味着您可以偶然发现的事情更少。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing DirectX Raytracing 1.2, PIX, Neural Rendering and more at GDC 2025!】在GDC 2025宣布DirectX RayTracing 1.2，Pix，Neural渲染等等！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/directx/announcing-directx-raytracing-1-2-pix-neural-rendering-and-more-at-gdc-2025</link>
      <description>【Today in the DirectX State of the Union at GDC 2025, we proudly showcased the next evolution in graphics with the announcement of DirectX Raytracing (DXR) 1.2. This update promises groundbreaking performance improvements and breathtaking visual fidelity, marking another milestone in our mission to deliver immersive, realistic experiences to gamers everywhere. We also brought developers [&amp;hellip;]】今天，在GDC 2025年的DirectX州，我们自豪地展示了DirectX RayTracing（DXR）1.2的下一个图形发展。此更新有望提高开创性的性能和令人叹为观止的视觉保真度，这标志着我们的任务中的另一个里程碑，向各地的游戏玩家提供了沉浸式，现实的体验。我们还带来了开发人员[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 21:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSTest 3.8: Top 10 features to supercharge your .NET tests!】MSTST 3.8：增强.NET测试的前10个功能！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/mstest-3-8-highlights</link>
      <description>【MSTest 3.8 is here! It&#39;s built on your feedback and packed with powerful new features to simplify and smooth your testing experience.】Mstest 3.8在这里！它建立在您的反馈基础上，并包含强大的新功能，以简化和平滑您的测试体验。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Dev Box roadmap update】Microsoft Dev Box路线图更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/microsoft-dev-box-roadmap-updates</link>
      <description>【What features and enhancements are planned for Microsoft Dev Box Microsoft Dev Box continues to evolve, providing a secure, scalable, and ready-to-code cloud-based development environment. Over the next few months, significant improvements will focus on three key areas: Ready-to-code environments: Faster setup, enhanced debugging, and GitHub Copilot integration to streamline developer workflows. Developers will benefit [&amp;hellip;]】Microsoft Dev Box Microsoft Dev Box计划的功能和增强功能将继续发展，提供了一个安全，可扩展且基于代码的基于云的开发环境。在接下来的几个月中，重大改进将集中在三个关键领域：即编码环境：更快的设置，增强的调试以及Github Copilot集成以简化开发人员工作流程。开发人员将受益[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 16:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>