<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Graph Toolkit retirement】Microsoft Graph Toolkit退休</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-graph-toolkit-retirement</link>
      <description>【We are announcing the deprecation of the Microsoft Graph Toolkit (MGT). The retirement period begins September 1st, 2025 with full retirement planned for August 28th, 2026. Why we’re retiri】我们宣布Microsoft Graph Toolkit（MGT）的弃用。退休期开始于2025年9月1日，计划于2026年8月28日全额退休。为什么我们要退休</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 20:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Graph CLI retirement】Microsoft Graph CLI退休</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-graph-cli-retirement</link>
      <description>【We are announcing the retirement of the Microsoft Graph command-line interface (CLI). The Microsoft Graph CLI has served as a powerful tool for developers and IT professionals to interact with Microsoft Graph through simple terminal commands—enabling automation, scripting, and streamli】我们宣布退休Microsoft Graph命令行接口（CLI）。 Microsoft Graph CLI已成为开发人员和IT专业人员通过简单终端命令与Microsoft Graph互动的强大工具 - 以实现自动化，脚本和shartli</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using SQL Server&#39;s new AI features and Python to create a T-SQL assistant】使用SQL Server的新AI功能和Python创建T-SQL助手</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/using-sql-servers-new-ai-features-and-python-to-create-a-t-sql-assistant</link>
      <description>【[alert type=&#34;important&#34; heading=&#34;Guest Post&#34;]Rodrigo Ribeiro Gomes, Head of Innovation at Power Tuning, has been leveraging the new AI features in SQL Server engine to simplify the lives of DBAs and developers. He generously shared his experience with us: thank you, Rodrigo![/alert] I recently created a】[Alert Type =“重要” heading =“来宾帖子”] Power Tuning创新负责人Rodrigo Ribeiro Gomes一直利用SQL Server Engine中的新AI功能来简化DBAS和开发人员的生活。他慷慨地与我们分享了自己的经历：谢谢，Rodrigo！[/ALERT]我最近创建了一个</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thoughts on creating a tracking pointer class, part 15: A custom shared pointer】关于创建跟踪指针类的想法，第15部分：自定义共享指针</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250829-00/?p=111526</link>
      <description>【Last time, we made our trackable object implementation&#39;s constructors and assignment operations non-throwing, although it came at a cost of making】上次，我们使可跟踪的对象实现的构造函数和任务操作不付诸实施，尽管它是以制造成本的代价</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Getting Started with the Aspire CLI】Aspire CLI入门</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/getting-started-with-the-aspire-cli</link>
      <description>【The Aspire CLI is a powerful, cross-platform tool designed to streamline the development, management, and deployment of application systems. Whether you’re building a simple website or an enterprise-scale distributed application with microservices and queues and databases, the Aspire CLI offers an interactive-first experience to help you cre】Aspire CLI是一种功能强大的跨平台工具，旨在简化应用程序系统的开发，管理和部署。无论您是构建一个简单的网站还是使用微服务和队列和数据库的企业规模的分布式应用程序，Aspire CLI都会提供交互式优先的体验，以帮助您CRE</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Awesome Copilot MCP Server】宣布很棒的Copilot MCP服务器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/announcing-awesome-copilot-mcp-server</link>
      <description>【Today, we&#39;re excited to announce the Awesome Copilot MCP Server - a simple way to search those customizations and save them directly to your repository from the MCP server. In early July, we announced the community-driven Awesome GitHub Co】今天，我们很高兴地宣布Awesome Copilot MCP服务器 - 一种搜索这些自定义并将其直接从MCP服务器保存到存储库的简单方法。 7月初，我们宣布了社区驱动的很棒的Github Co</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thoughts on creating a tracking pointer class, part 14: Nonthrowing moves with the shared tracking pointer】关于创建跟踪指针类的想法，第14部分：通过共享跟踪指针进行的非预设动作</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250828-00/?p=111524</link>
      <description>【So far, we&#39;ve been working on an alternate design for tracking pointers, but we found that it had the unfortunate property of having potentially-throwing constructors and m】到目前为止，我们一直在为跟踪指针进行替代设计，但我们发现它具有不幸的属性，即具有潜在的构造函数和M</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Roadmap for AI in Visual Studio (September)】Visual Studio的AI路线图（9月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/roadmap-for-ai-in-visual-studio-september</link>
      <description>【Today, we’re excited to share our public roadmap, which outlines the next steps in evolving Visual Studio with AI-powered agentic experiences. With every month, we aim to deliver smarter, faster, and more intuitive tools that enhance your coding experience. Disclaimer: The items outlined here represent ongoing work for the month. They】今天，我们很高兴分享我们的公共路线图，该路线图概述了通过AI驱动的代理体验发展视觉工作室的下一步。我们每个月都打算提供更智能，更快，更直观的工具，以增强您的编码体验。免责声明：此处概述的项目代表了当月正在进行的工作。他们</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【EFCore.Visualizer - View Entity Framework Core query plan inside Visual Studio】efcore.visualizer-查看“实体框架核心查询计划”</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/ef-core-visualizer-view-entity-framework-core-query-plan-inside-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【This is a guest blog from Giorgi Dalakishvili, the developer of EFCore.Visualizer. Entity Framework Core is a powerful, feature-rich ORM powering many of today&#39;s applications. W】这是efcore.visualizer的开发商Giorgi Dalakishvili的来宾博客。 Entity Framework Core是一个功能强大的功能丰富的ORM，可为当今许多应用程序提供动力。 w</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thoughts on creating a tracking pointer class, part 13: Restoring the strong exception guarantee】关于创建跟踪指针类的想法，第13部分：恢复强大的异常保证</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250827-00/?p=111518</link>
      <description>【Last time, we created a tracking pointer class based on std::shared_ptr. We found a problem with the move-assignment operator: It didn&#39;t satisfy the str】上次，我们创建了一个基于std :: shared_ptr的跟踪指针类。我们发现了移动管理操作员的问题：它不满足STR</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>