<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing OData .NET (ODL) 9 Preview 3 Release】宣布发布 OData .NET (ODL) 9 预览版 3</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/odata/announcing-odata-net-odl-9-preview-3-release</link>
      <description>【We’re happy to announce that OData .NET (ODL) 9 Preview 3 has been officially released and is available on NuGet: Microsoft.OData.Core 9.0.0 Preview 3】我们很高兴地宣布 OData .NET (ODL) 9 Preview 3 已正式发布并可在 NuGet 上使用：Microsoft.OData.Core 9.0.0 Preview 3</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ignite 2025: A Developer’s Guide to Building Agents for Microsoft 365】Ignite 2025：为 Microsoft 365 构建代理的开发人员指南</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/ignite-2025-a-developers-guide-to-building-agents-for-microsoft-365</link>
      <description>【Ignite 2025 brought many innovations for developers building agents for Microsoft 365. From new capabilities in Declarative Agents and Custom Engine Agents to the introduction of Microsoft Agent 365, the platform now enables organizations to arch】Ignite 2025 为开发人员构建 Microsoft 365 代理带来了许多创新。从声明式代理和自定义引擎代理的新功能到 Microsoft Agent 365 的引入，该平台现在使组织能够构建</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Maybe somebody can explain to me how weak references solve the ODR problem】也许有人可以向我解释弱引用如何解决 ODR 问题</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251121-00/?p=111807</link>
      <description>【Some time ago, I proposed Using type aliasing to avoid the ODR problem with conditional compilation. A Reddit thread claimed that &#34;】前段时间，我提出使用类型别名来避免条件编译的 ODR 问题。 Reddit 的一个帖子声称“</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reinventing how .NET Builds and Ships (Again)】（再次）重塑 .NET 的构建和发布方式</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/reinventing-how-dotnet-builds-and-ships-again</link>
      <description>【After I wrote my last post on how .NET builds and ships, I was cautiously optimistic that I wouldn&#39;t be writing another one. Or at least not another one about how we build and ship. That problem was done and dusted. .NET had done it! We&#39;d struck a】在写完关于 .NET 如何构建和发布的上一篇文章后，我对自己不会再写一篇持谨慎乐观的态度。或者至少不是关于我们如何构建和运输的另一篇文章。这个问题已经解决并尘埃落定了。 .NET 做到了！我们击中了一个</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft 365 Copilot APIs: What’s New and What’s Next】Microsoft 365 Copilot API：新增功能和下一步发展</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-365-copilot-apis-whats-new-and-whats-next</link>
      <description>【At Build 2025, we introduced the Microsoft 365 Copilot APIs to help developers bring grounded AI into their solutions without rebuilding indexes or compromising security. The response has been encouraging, and your fee】在 Build 2025 上，我们推出了 Microsoft 365 Copilot API，以帮助开发人员将基础 AI 引入其解决方案，而无需重建索引或损害安全性。反响令人鼓舞，您的费用</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Develop Faster with VS Code for the Web – Azure: Your Browser-Based Dev Environment】使用 VS Code for the Web 加快开发速度 – Azure：基于浏览器的开发环境</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/get-started-with-vs-code-for-the-web</link>
      <description>【Developers can now move from idea to Azure-ready code in minutes with VS Code for the Web – Azure. This browser-based environment removes setup time, reduces friction, and gives you immediate access to pre-configured run】现在，开发人员可以使用 VS Code for the Web – Azure 在几分钟内从想法转变为 Azure 就绪代码。这种基于浏览器的环境消除了设置时间，减少了摩擦，并让您可以立即访问预配置的运行</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Complexity to Simplicity: Intelligent JVM Optimizations on Azure】从复杂到简单：Azure 上的智能 JVM 优化</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/from-complexity-to-simplicity-intelligent-jvm-optimizations-on-azure</link>
      <description>【Introduction As cloud-native architectures scale across thousands of containers and virtual machines, Java performance tuning has become more distributed, complex, and error-prone than ever. As highlighted in our public preview announcement, traditional JVM optimization relied on ex】简介 随着云原生架构扩展到数千个容器和虚拟机，Java 性能调优变得比以往更加分布式、复杂且容易出错。正如我们的公开预览版公告中所强调的那样，传统的 JVM 优化依赖于 ex</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the Public Preview of Azure Command Launcher for Java】宣布推出适用于 Java 的 Azure 命令启动器的公共预览版</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/announcing-the-public-preview-of-azure-command-launcher-for-java</link>
      <description>【Today we are announcing the Public Preview of the Azure Command Launcher for Java, a new tool that helps developers, SREs, and infrastructure teams standardize and automate JVM configuration on Azure. The goal is to simplify tuning practices and reduce resource waste across Java workloads.】今天，我们宣布推出适用于 Java 的 Azure 命令启动器的公共预览版，这是一款新工具，可帮助开发人员、SRE 和基础架构团队在 Azure 上标准化和自动化 JVM 配置。目标是简化调优实践并减少 Java 工作负载的资源浪费。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Foundry Local comes to Android—plus on-device speech, on-prem support, and a simpler SDK】Foundry Local 登陆 Android，加上设备上语音、本地支持和更简单的 SDK</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/foundry-local-comes-to-android</link>
      <description>【Today, we’re introducing a powerful new way to bring AI directly to your mobile apps: Foundry Local on Android. Starting now, you can build Android applications that run AI on-device—no cloud round trips required. Sign up for the gated preview here: https://aka.m】今天，我们推出了一种将 AI 直接引入您的移动应用的强大新方法：Android 上的 Foundry Local。从现在开始，您可以构建在设备上运行 AI 的 Android 应用程序，无需云往返。在此处注册门禁预览：https://aka.m</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure DevOps to GitHub migration Playbook: Unlocking Agentic DevOps】Azure DevOps 到 GitHub 迁移手册：解锁 Agentic DevOps</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/azure-devops-to-github-migration-playbook-unlocking-agentic-devops</link>
      <description>【Azure DevOps or GitHub Enterprise ? Today, in the Microsoft ecosystem, two Software Development Lifecycle management platforms coexist: - Azure DevOps is designed from the ground up for enterprise with advanced planning features through Azure Boards, build and release automation with Azure Pipelines, and a unique】Azure DevOps 还是 GitHub Enterprise？如今，在 Microsoft 生态系统中，两个软件开发生命周期管理平台共存： - Azure DevOps 是为企业从头开始设计的，通过 Azure Boards 提供高级规划功能，使用 Azure Pipelines 构建和发布自动化，以及独特的</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 11:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>