<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【MSVC Backend Updates in Visual Studio 2022 version 17.10】Visual Studio 2022 版本 17.10 中的 MSVC 后端更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/msvc-backend-updates-in-visual-studio-2022-version-17-10</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio 2022 17.10 brings new optimizations, intrinsics, features, and improvements to the MSVC backend. Check out the highlights below: Performance improvements and additional functionality for all architectures: Improved SLP vectorizer. Now it runs on more functions, recognizes more operations, and may choose to use larger vector widths if allowed by the appropriate /arch flag.】Visual Studio 2022 17.10 为 MSVC 后端带来了新的优化、内在函数、功能和改进。查看以下亮点： 所有架构的性能改进和附加功能：改进的 SLP 矢量器。现在，它可以运行更多函数，识别更多操作，并且如果适当的 /arch 标志允许，可以选择使用更大的向量宽度。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 19:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Support for Azure.AI.OpenAI and OpenAI v2 is coming】对 Azure.AI.OpenAI 和 OpenAI v2 的支持即将推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/support-for-azure-ai-openai-and-openai-v2-is-coming</link>
      <description>【Microsoft announced the official OpenAI library for .NET at the Build 2024 conference. This new SDK ensures that .NET developers have parity with other programming language libraries when accessing Azure OpenAI models. This means the new SDK will be able to support the latest OpenAI features and models as soon as they come out,】微软在 Build 2024 大会上宣布了适用于 .NET 的官方 OpenAI 库。这个新的 SDK 可确保 .NET 开发人员在访问 Azure OpenAI 模型时与其他编程语言库具有同等地位。这意味着新的SDK一经推出就能够支持最新的OpenAI功能和模型，</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 08:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (July 2024)】Azure SDK 版本（2024 年 7 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-july-2024</link>
      <description>【The Azure SDKs release every month. This post includes the month&#39;s highlights and release notes.】Azure SDK 每月发布一次。这篇文章包括本月的亮点和发行说明。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 19:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【There is no mystery over who wrote the Blue Screen of Death, despite what some may want you to believe】尽管有些人可能想让你相信，谁创造了蓝屏死机，这并不神秘</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240730-00/?p=110062</link>
      <description>【No real contradictions in anybody&#39;s story.】任何人的故事中都没有真正的矛盾。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s coming next? Summer / Fall roadmap for Semantic Kernel】接下来会发生什么？语义内核夏季/秋季路线图</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/whats-coming-next-summer-fall-roadmap-for-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【It feels like yesterday when we went live with v1.0+ of all our SDKs (Python, Java, and C#) at Microsoft Build. Since then, the Semantic Kernel team has been hard at work making Semantic Kernel even better. Now that we&amp;#8217;ve made some progress,】当我们在 Microsoft Build 上发布所有 SDK（Python、Java 和 C#）的 v1.0+ 时，感觉就像昨天一样。从那时起，Semantic Kernel 团队一直在努力使 Semantic Kernel 变得更好。现在我们已经取得了一些进展</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing #help in F# Interactive】增强 F# Interactive 中的 #help</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/enhancing-help-in-fsi</link>
      <description>【The &#39;#help&#39; directive in F# Interactive can now quickly access documentation instantly within the REPL.】F# Interactive 中的“#help”指令现在可以在 REPL 中立即快速访问文档。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing a new Learn module: Create a copilot to help promote your podcast】宣布推出新的学习模块：创建副驾驶以帮助推广您的播客</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/create-a-copilot-to-help-promote-your-podcast</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Learn has always been a way to learn new skills and concepts and discover the power of Microsoft products with step-by-step guidance. Recently, there has been an increase of learn paths and modules that throw you further into the deep end allowing you to develop new skills by building an end-to-end solution or project.】Microsoft Learn 始终是学习新技能和概念并通过分步指导发现 Microsoft 产品功能的一种方式。最近，学习路径和模块的增加使您进一步深入，使您可以通过构建端到端解决方案或项目来开发新技能。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 10:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python in Visual Studio Code – August 2024 Release】Visual Studio Code 中的 Python – 2024 年 8 月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/python-in-visual-studio-code-august-2024-release</link>
      <description>【The August 2024 release of the Python and Jupyter extensions for Visual Studio Code are now available. This month&#39;s updates include improved Python discovery using python environment tools, inline variable values with the python debugger, and improvements to the VS Code native REPL. Keep reading to learn more!】2024 年 8 月发布的 Visual Studio Code 的 Python 和 Jupyter 扩展现已推出。本月的更新包括使用 python 环境工具改进 Python 发现、使用 python 调试器内联变量值以及对 VS Code 本机 REPL 的改进。继续阅读以了解更多信息！</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 20:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to compress out interior padding in a std::pair and why you don’t want to】如何压缩 std::pair 中的内部填充以及为什么你不想这样做</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240731-00/?p=110069</link>
      <description>【Context-sensitive layout means you get a different structure each time you use it.】上下文相关布局意味着每次使用它时都会得到不同的结构。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transforming Fleet Operations with vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB Geospatial Capabilities】使用基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB 地理空间功能转变车队运营</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/transforming-fleet-operations-with-vcore-based-azure-cosmos-db-for-mongodb-geospatial-capabilities</link>
      <description>【Efficient fleet management is essential for industries that rely on transportation, such as logistics, delivery services, and public transportation. vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB supports enabling developers to create sophisticated geo-enabled applications with ease. Organizations can streamline fleet operations, monitor vehicle locations in real-time,】高效的车队管理对于依赖运输的行业（例如物流、送货服务和公共交通）至关重要。基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB 支持开发人员轻松创建复杂的地理应用程序。组织可以简化车队运营、实时监控车辆位置、</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>