<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Building Multi-Agent Solutions with Semantic Kernel and A2A Protocol】来宾博客：使用语义内核和A2A协议构建多代理解决方案</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-building-multi-agent-solutions-with-semantic-kernel-and-a2a-protocol</link>
      <description>【In the rapidly evolving landscape of AI application development, the ability to orchestrate multiple intelligent agents has become crucial for building sophisticated, enterprise-grade solutions. While individual AI agents excel at specific tasks, complex business scenarios often require coordination between specialized agents running on differ】在AI应用程序开发的快速发展的景观中，协调多种智能代理的能力对于建立复杂的企业级解决方案至关重要。虽然单个AI代理在特定任务上表现出色，但复杂的业务场景通常需要在奔跑的专用代理之间进行协调</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 08:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integration testing for Go applications using Testcontainers and containerized databases】使用TestContainers和容器化数据库为GO应用程序进行集成测试</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/integration-testing-for-go-applications-using-testcontainers-and-containerized-databases</link>
      <description>【Integration testing has always presented a fundamental challenge: how do you test your application against real dependencies without the complexity of managing external services? Traditional approaches often involve either mocking dependencies (which can miss integration issues) or maintaining separate test environments (which can be expensive】集成测试始终提出了一个基本挑战：您如何在不管理外部服务的复杂性的情况下测试针对真实依赖的应用程序？传统方法通常涉及嘲笑依赖项（可能会错过集成问题）或保持单独的测试环境（这可能很昂贵）</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Developer CLI: From Dev to Prod with One Click】Azure开发人员CLI：从开发人员到prod一键</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/azure-developer-cli-from-dev-to-prod-with-one-click</link>
      <description>【This post walks through how to implement a &#34;build once, deploy everywhere&#34; pattern using Azure Developer CLI (azd) that provisions environment-specific infrastructure and promotes applications from dev to prod with t】这篇文章介绍了如何使用Azure Developer CLI（AZD）实施“构建一次，在任何地方部署”模式，该模式可以提供特定于环境的基础架构，并促进与T Dev一起使用T Dev的应用程序</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What happens if C++/WinRT is unable to resume execution on a dispatcher thread?】如果C ++/WinRT无法在调度程序线程上恢复执行情况会怎样？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250721-00/?p=111396</link>
      <description>【The C++/WinRT library provides the winrt::resume_foreground() function for resuming a coroutine on the foreground thread of a dispatcher. It supports three types of dispatchers: Windows.UI.Core.CoreDispatcher, Windows.System.DispatcherQueue, Micros】C ++/WinRT库提供了WinRT :: insume_foreground（）函数，用于在调度程序的前景线上恢复coroutine。它支持三种类型的调度程序：windows.ui.core.coredispatcher，windows.system.dispatcherqueue，micros</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Model Promotion with dstoolkit-mlops-v2】DstoolKit-Mlops-V2的AI模型促进</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/ai-model-promotion-with-dstoolkit-v2</link>
      <description>【Introduction In a recent engagement, our team of Data Scientists and Software Engineers, developed a series of custom AI models to meet our customer&#39;s specific use case. While doing so, consideration was given to how best to allow Data Scientists the freedom to quickly experiment and iterate on model development, while also incorpora】在最近的参与度中，我们的数据科学家和软件工程师团队开发了一系列自定义AI模型，以满足客户的特定用例。在这样做的同时，考虑了如何最好地允许数据科学家快速实验和迭代模型开发的自由，同时也将</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Ask Mode vs Agent Mode - Choosing the Right Copilot Experience for .NET】询问模式与代理模式 - 选择.net的合适的副本体验</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/ask-mode-vs-agent-mode</link>
      <description>【As a .NET developer, productivity and problem-solving are at the heart of your workflow. GitHub Copilot Chat offers two powerful modes, Ask Mode and Agent Mode, that can dramatically accelerate your development, but knowing when to use each is essential to getting the most out of this tool. In this post, we’ll break down the differences,】作为.NET开发人员，生产力和解决问题是您工作流程的核心。 Github Copilot聊天提供了两个强大的模式，即询问模式和代理模式，它们可以极大地加速您的开发，但是知道何时使用每个模式，对于充分利用了该工具至关重要。在这篇文章中，我们将分解差异，</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java OpenJDK July 2025 Patch &amp; Security Update】Java OpenJDK 2025年7月补丁和安全更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/java-openjdk-july-2025-patch-security-update</link>
      <description>【Hello Java customers! We are happy to announce the latest July 2025 patch &amp;amp; security update release for the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK. Download and install the binaries today. OpenJDK 21.0.8 OpenJDK 17.0.16 OpenJDK 11.0.28 Check our】您好Java客户！我们很高兴宣布2025年7月的最新补丁程序和安全更新版本，用于OpenJDK的Microsoft Build。立即下载并安装二进制文件。 OpenJDK 21.0.8 OpenJDK 17.0.16 OpenJDK 11.0.28检查我们</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio Code CMake Tools Extension 1.21 Release: Multi-root improvements, CMake Presets v10, and more…】Visual Studio代码CMAKE工具扩展1.21版本：多根改进，CMAKE PRESTES V10等等…</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/visual-studio-code-cmake-tools-extension-1-21-release-multi-root-improvements-cmake-presets-v10-and-more</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce the latest 1.21 release of the CMake Tools extension for Visual Studio Code. This update brings a host of new updates, including addressing one of our top-voted issues for multi-root improvements and adding】我们很高兴宣布最新的1.21版本的CMAKE工具扩展名用于Visual Studio Code。此更新带来了许多新的更新，包括解决我们最重要的问题之一，以进行多个重点改进和添加</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 12:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The case of the invalid instruction exception on an instruction that should never have executed】无效的指令例外情况是无法执行的指令</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250718-00/?p=111390</link>
      <description>【The image processing folks added specialized AVX2 versions of their code, but found that it was crashing with an illegal instruction exception. The code went something like this: void SwizzleAVX2(uint32_t* source, uint32_t* destination, uint32_t count) { ⟦ do stuff using AVX-only instructions ⟧ ⟦ such as _mm256_cv】图像处理人员添加了其代码的专门AVX2版本，但发现它正在崩溃，但具有非法指令例外。代码进行了类似的操作：void swizzleavx2（uint32_t* source，uint32_t* destinate，uint32_t count）{⟦使用AVX仅使用AVX-仅使用AVX-for Avx-mmm256_cv做事</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Smarter with the Microsoft 365 Agents Toolkit MCP Server】使用Microsoft 365代理工具包MCP服务器构建更聪明的人</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/build-smarter-with-the-microsoft-365-agents-toolkit-mcp-server</link>
      <description>【As AI agents become central to how we build and interact with modern productivity apps, developers need tools that are flexible, standard-based, and deeply integrated with AI. That’s where the Microsoft 365 Agents Toolkit MCP Server】随着AI代理人成为我们如何与现代生产力应用程序构建和互动的核心，开发人员需要灵活，基于标准并与AI深入集成的工具。这就是Themicrosoft 365代理工具包MCP服务器的地方</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>