<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Updates to Warning Suppressions in Microsoft C++ Code Analysis】Microsoft C ++代码分析中警告抑制的更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/updates-to-warning-suppressions-in-microsoft-c-code-analysis</link>
      <description>【Microsoft C++ Code Analysis is a powerful static analysis tool integrated into Visual Studio that helps you identify and fix potential issues in your C++ code. Large projects require effective management of analysis warnings to maintain code quality and you sometimes need to suppress warnings, but must do so in a clear and auditable way.】Microsoft C ++代码分析是一种集成到Visual Studio中的功能强大的静态分析工具，可帮助您识别和修复C ++代码中的潜在问题。大型项目需要有效管理分析警告以维持代码质量，有时您需要抑制警告，但必须以清晰可视化的方式进行警告。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Extension concerns when replacing the OS disk】更换OS磁盘时的扩展问题</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-vm-runtime/extension-concerns-when-replacing-the-os-disk</link>
      <description>【One confusing area regarding extensions on Azure VMs is - what happens when the OS disk is swapped out? Well, in that case the extensions will run again. Is this the desired behavior? Well, we don&#39;t know. There are many types of extensions. Some handle monitoring and security, so those you&#39;ll probably want to keep. Some install applications】关于Azure VM的扩展的一个令人困惑的区域是 - 当OS磁盘被换掉时会发生什么？好吧，在这种情况下，扩展将再次运行。这是所需的行为吗？好吧，我们不知道。扩展有多种类型。有些人处理监视和安全性，因此您可能要保留这些监视。一些安装应用程序</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 17:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft and LangChain4j: A Partnership for Secure, Enterprise-Grade Java AI Applications】Microsoft和Langchain4J：安全的企业级Java AI应用程序的合作伙伴关系</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/microsoft-and-langchain4j-a-partnership-for-secure-enterprise-grade-java-ai-applications</link>
      <description>【】</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The Fundamental Failure-Mode Theorem: Systems lie about their proper functioning】基本故障模式定理：系统谎称其适当的功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250716-00/?p=111383</link>
      <description>【I have on occasion referred to Le Chatelier&#39;s Principle for complex systems, as presented by John Gall in the book Systemantics: &#34;Every complex system r】我有时会提到约翰·盖尔（John Gall）在《系统主义者》一书中提出的《复杂系统的原理》：“每个复杂系统r r</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【10 Microsoft MCP Servers to Accelerate Your Development Workflow】10 Microsoft MCP服务器加速您的开发工作流程</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com//10-microsoft-mcp-servers-to-accelerate-your-development-workflow</link>
      <description>【We&#39;ve been talking a lot about the Model Context Protocol (MCP) lately, including recent blog posts and sessions at Microsoft Build. In this post, I&#39;d like to share some top tips for how you can use MCP servers we&#39;ve been building to improve yo】最近，我们一直在谈论模型上下文协议（MCP），包括Microsoft Build的最新博客文章和会议。在这篇文章中，我想分享一些您如何使用我们一直在建造的MCP服务器来改善您的主要技巧</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 19:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Power Platform API and SDKs: From UX-First to API-First】电源平台API和SDK：从UX-First到API-First</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/power-platform-api-and-sdks-from-ux-first-to-api-first</link>
      <description>【Historically, Power Platform has empowered administrators through the Power Platform Admin Center (PPAC). This UX-first experience offered a seamless, intuitive interface for managing environments, automating everyday tasks, and discovering new capabilities within the platform. Today, we’re taking a bold step forward. We’re tran】从历史上看，Power Platform通过Power Platform Admin Center（PPAC）授权管理员。这种UX优先的体验提供了一个无缝，直观的界面，用于管理环境，自动化日常任务以及在平台内发现新功能。今天，我们迈出了大胆的一步。我们是Tran</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 17:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building Your First MCP Server with .NET and Publishing to NuGet】使用.NET构建您的第一台MCP服务器并发布到Nuget</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/mcp-server-dotnet-nuget-quickstart</link>
      <description>【Want to extend AI assistants with custom capabilities? In this post, we&#39;ll show you how to build a Model Context Protocol (MCP) server using .NET 10 and publish it to NuGet — making your AI tools discoverable and reusable by the entire .NET community. We&#39;ll also show you some new features we&#39;ve added to .NET 10 and NuGet to support this, and】是否想通过自定义功能扩展AI助手？在这篇文章中，我们将向您展示如何使用.NET 10构建模型上下文协议（MCP）服务器并将其发布给Nuget，这使您的AI工具可在整个.NET社区中发现和重复使用。我们还将向您展示一些我们添加到.NET 10和Nuget的新功能以支持此功能，并且</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Bring your own agents into Microsoft 365 Copilot】将自己的代理商带入Microsoft 365 Copilot</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/bring-your-own-agents-into-microsoft-365-copilot</link>
      <description>【Custom Engine Agents now generally available—build and integrate your own AI into the flow of work Microsoft 365 Copilot is redefining how people interact with AI—embedding it directly into the flow of work as the intuitive, natural interface for agents: the ‘UI for AI’ As Copilot becomes the interface for】自定义发动机代理现在通常可用 - 建立并将自己的AI集成到Microsoft 365 Copilot的工作流程中，正在重新定义人们与AI的互动方式 - 将其直接插入工作流中，作为代理的直观，自然界面：“ ui for AI”作为副cop的copilot成为copilot的界面。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Perhaps not a recommended usage for an emergency power outlet】也许不是建议使用紧急电源插座</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250715-00/?p=111381</link>
      <description>【It is not uncommon for Microsoft employees who are aficionados of arcade video games to set up a unit in free play mode in a public space for anyone to play. For example, the Habitrail in the Building 16-18 complex】对于街机视频游戏的狂热者来说，Microsoft员工在公共场所以免费游戏模式设置单元供任何人玩游戏并不少见。例如，大楼16-18综合大楼的栖息地</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET 10 Preview 6 is now available!】.NET 10预览6现在可用！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-10-preview-6</link>
      <description>【Today, we are excited to announce the sixth preview release of .NET 10 with enhancements across the .NET Runtime, SDK, libraries, C#, ASP.NET Core, Blazor, .NET MAUI, and more. Check out the full release notes linked below and get started today. [cta-button align=&#34;center&#34; text=&#34;Download .NET 10 Preview 6&#34; url=&#34;https://get.d】今天，我们很高兴宣布.NET 10的第六次预览版本，并在.NET运行时，SDK，Libraries，C＃，ASP.NET Core，Blazor，.Net Maui等增强功能。查看下面链接的完整发行说明，并立即开始。 [cta button align =“中心” text =“下载.net 10预览6” url =“ https：//get.d</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>