<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【January 2026 Insiders (version 1.109)】2026 年 1 月 Insider（版本 1.109）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/january-2026-insiders-(version-1.109)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code January 2026 Release (1.109). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 1 月版本 (1.109) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What&#39;s new with Azure Repos?】Azure Repos 有哪些新功能？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/whats-new-with-azure-repos</link>
      <description>【We thought it was a good time to check in and highlight some of the work happening in Azure Repos. In this post, we’ve covered several recent improvements, along with a preview of features that are coming soon. To stay up to date, be sure to visit the】我们认为现在是检查并重点介绍 Azure Repos 中发生的一些工作的好时机。在这篇文章中，我们介绍了最近的几项改进，以及即将推出的功能预览。要了解最新信息，请务必访问</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I get the tab index number from a dialog box control?】如何从对话框控件中获取选项卡索引号？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260116-00/?p=111991</link>
      <description>【A customer wanted to retrieve the TabIndex of a dialog box control. They were able to get its class name and】客户想要检索对话框控件的 TabIndex。他们能够得到它的类名并且</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Part 1: Building Your First Serverless HTTP API on Azure with Azure Functions &amp; FastAPI】第 1 部分：使用 Azure Functions 和 FastAPI 在 Azure 上构建第一个无服务器 HTTP API</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/building-your-first-serverless-http-api-on-azure-with-azure-functions-fastapi</link>
      <description>【Introduction  This post is Part 1 of the series Serverless Application Development with Azure Functions and Az】简介 本文是使用 Azure Functions 和 Az 进行无服务器应用程序开发系列的第 1 部分</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Evaluate Small Language Model Function Calling using the Azure AI Evaluation SDK】使用 Azure AI 评估 SDK 评估小语言模型函数调用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/slm-function-calling-with-azure-ai-evaluation-sdk</link>
      <description>【Introduction In recent years, Small Language Models (SLMs) have become increasingly important. SLMs are language models with far fewer parameters and use significantly fewer resources than their Large Language Model (LLM) counterparts, while still achieving comparable performance in specific tasks. SLMs are ideal for environments wh】简介 近年来，小语言模型（SLM）变得越来越重要。 SLM 是参数少得多的语言模型，比大型语言模型 (LLM) 模型使用的资源少得多，同时在特定任务中仍能实现相当的性能。 SLM 非常适合以下环境：</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing GPT-5.2 Availability in Azure for U.S. Government Secret and Top Secret Clouds】宣布 Azure 中适用于美国政府机密和绝密云的 GPT-5.2</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azuregov/advancing-ai-capabilities-in-azure-for-u-s-government-secret-and-top-secret-clouds</link>
      <description>【Today, we are excited to announce that GPT-5.2, Azure OpenAI’s newest frontier reasoning model, is available in Microsoft Azure for U.S. Government Secret and Top Secret cloud environments. This release marks another significant milestone in our mission to b】今天，我们很高兴地宣布，Azure OpenAI 的最新前沿推理模型 GPT-5.2 已在 Microsoft Azure 中用于美国政府机密和绝密云环境。此版本标志着我们使命的另一个重要里程碑</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When programs assume that the system will never change, episode 4: Stealing strings】当程序假设系统永远不会改变时，第 4 集：窃取字符串</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260115-00/?p=111988</link>
      <description>【A customer had a program that automated a workflow, and one of the steps was to run a console program that came with Windows, and that console program printed a confirmation prompt &#34;Are you sure (Y/N)?&#34;. They wanted to programmatically say Yes, but since the customer had employees around the world, they couldn&#39;t hard code the lette】一位客户有一个自动化工作流程的程序，其中一个步骤是运行 Windows 附带的控制台程序，该控制台程序打印一条确认提示“您确定 (Y/N) 吗？”。他们想以编程方式说“是”，但由于客户在世界各地都有员工，他们无法对字母进行硬编码</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Microsoft Entra PowerShell v1.2.0】宣布推出 Microsoft Entra PowerShell v1.2.0</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/entrapowershell/announcing-microsoft-entra-powershell-v1-2-0</link>
      <description>【We are excited to introduce Microsoft Entra PowerShell v1.2.0, a major update that delivers full support for Agent Identity Blueprints, expanded application configuration capabilities, and modernized invitation APIs aligned with Microsoft Graph】我们很高兴推出 Microsoft Entra PowerShell v1.2.0，这是一项重大更新，提供对代理身份蓝图的全面支持、扩展的应用程序配置功能以及与 Microsoft Graph 一致的现代化邀请 API</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Copilot Memories】副驾驶回忆</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/copilot-memories</link>
      <description>【Are you wasting time reviewing code for nits on code standards, project preferences, or important contribution guidelines?】您是否在浪费时间审查代码以了解代码标准、项目偏好或重要的贡献指南？</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB Conf 2026 — Call for Proposals Is Now Open】Azure Cosmos DB Conf 2026 — 提案征集现已开放</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-conf-2026-call-for-proposals-is-open</link>
      <description>【Every production system has a story behind it. The scaling limit you didn’】每个生产系统背后都有一个故事。你没有的缩放限制</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>