<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData with Qdrant and Azure AI Search】使用 Qdrant 和 Azure AI 搜索探索 Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/vector-data-qdrant-ai-search-dotnet</link>
      <description>【Discover how to use Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData to implement semantic search using Qdrant and Azure AI Search】了解如何使用 Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData 通过 Qdrant 和 Azure AI 搜索实现语义搜索</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Refresh your Find results】刷新您的查找结果</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/refresh-your-find-results</link>
      <description>【Are you tired of having to repeatedly launch the Find window in Visual Studio to update your search results? Whether you&amp;#8217;ve just refactored some code or pulled recent changes, having to redo a search to get updated results is no longer necessary. With the new refresh option, you can now update your Find results without [&amp;hellip;]】您是否厌倦了必须在 Visual Studio 中重复启动“查找”窗口来更新搜索结果？无论您刚刚重构了一些代码还是提取了最近的更改，都不再需要重新搜索来获取更新的结果。使用新的刷新选项，您现在可以更新查找结果，而无需 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET Conf 2024 Recap – Celebrating .NET 9, AI, Community, &amp; More】.NET Conf 2024 回顾 – 庆祝 .NET 9、AI、社区等</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-conf-2024-recap</link>
      <description>【.NET Conf 2024 is over, but you can catch up with all the announcement and fun with video recordings, slides, demos, and more.】.NET Conf 2024 已经结束，但您可以通过视频录制、幻灯片、演示等了解所有公告和乐趣。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transforming Language into Code: Building and Evaluating a Robotic Code Generation Copilot】将语言转换为代码：构建和评估机器人代码生成副驾驶</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/code-generation-evaluation</link>
      <description>【This blog post explores the development and evaluation of an AI assistant that converts natural language into robotic code.】这篇博文探讨了将自然语言转换为机器人代码的人工智能助手的开发和评估。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why do we have header files &lt;pshpackN.h&gt; and &lt;poppack.h&gt; instead of just issuing the pragma directly?】为什么我们有头文件 &lt;pshpackN.h&gt; 和 &lt;poppack.h&gt; 而不是直接发出 pragma？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241216-00/?p=110645</link>
      <description>【Because the pragma may not work everywhere.】因为该编译指示可能并非在所有地方都有效。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microspeak terms that didn’t take hold: airspace, synthetics, and AOI】未流行的 Microspeak 术语：空域、合成物和 AOI</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241217-00/?p=110647</link>
      <description>【Sometimes they don&#39;t stick.】有时它们不粘。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Embedding models and dimensions: optimizing the performance to resource-usage ratio】嵌入模型和维度：优化性能与资源利用率</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/embedding-models-and-dimensions-optimizing-the-performance-resource-usage-ratio</link>
      <description>【Since the release of vector preview, we&amp;#8217;ve been working with many customers that are building AI solution on Azure SQL and SQL Server and one of the most common questions is how to support high-dimensional data, for example more than 2000 dimensions per vector. In fact, at the moment, the vector type supports &amp;#8220;only&amp;#8221; up [&amp;hellip;]】自矢量预览版发布以来，我们一直在与许多在 Azure SQL 和 SQL Server 上构建 AI 解决方案的客户合作，最常见的问题之一是如何支持高维数据，例如每个矢量超过 2000 个维度。事实上，目前，向量类型“仅”支持 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 16:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PIX 2412.12 – Texture/Buffer/Visualizer improvements, Work Graph Shader Debugging, and many Timing Capture improvements】PIX 2412.12 – 纹理/缓冲区/可视化器改进、工作图着色器调试以及许多时序捕获改进</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pix/pix-2412-12</link>
      <description>【Today we released PIX on Windows version 2412.12, which can be downloaded here. This release includes several new improvements to GPU Captures and Timing Captures, including: GPU Captures: Custom Buffer/Texture/Mesh Visualizer Improvements Work Graph Shader Debugging (preview) VRS Shading Rate Visualizer Many bug fixes + smaller improvements Timing Captures: New Comparison Layout Range Details “v2” [&amp;hellip;]】今天我们发布了 Windows 版本的 PIX 2412.12，可以在此处下载。此版本包括对 GPU 捕获和时序捕获的多项新改进，包括： GPU 捕获：自定义缓冲区/纹理/网格可视化工具改进 工作图着色器调试（预览） VRS 着色率可视化工具 许多错误修复 + 较小的改进 时序捕获：新的比较布局范围详细信息“v2”[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 19:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Create internal GitHub repos for your team】为您的团队创建内部 GitHub 存储库</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/create-internal-github-repos-for-your-team</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio 2022 now includes support for creating internal repositories for GitHub organizations. This feature allows developers to work within their GitHub organization&amp;#8217;s guidelines within the Visual Studio environment more effectively. Managing repositories involves configuring varying levels of visibility and permissions. Visual Studio 2022’s new feature aims to smooth this process by providing support for [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio 2022 现在支持为 GitHub 组织创建内部存储库。此功能允许开发人员在 Visual Studio 环境中更有效地按照 GitHub 组织的指南进行工作。管理存储库涉及配置不同级别的可见性和权限。 Visual Studio 2022 的新功能旨在通过提供对 [...] 的支持来平滑这一过程。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SQL ❤️ Python!】Azure SQL ❤️ Python！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/azure-sql-loves-python</link>
      <description>【I recently presented at Python Day 2024 on Langchain integration. I created a slide deck that I believe can be useful beyond just the session, so I wanted to share it here for everyone&amp;#8217;s benefit. The deck covers the most common topics for a Python developer: Is there a free version of SQL Server or [&amp;hellip;]】我最近在 2024 年 Python Day 上发表了有关 Langchain 集成的演讲。我创建了一个幻灯片，我相信它除了会议之外还有用，所以我想在这里分享它，以造福于每个人。该套牌涵盖了 Python 开发人员最常见的主题：是否有 SQL Server 的免费版本或 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 22:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>