<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Everyone is talkin’ bout vibes】每个人都在说话的共鸣</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/everyone-is-talkin-bout-vibes</link>
      <description>【Leading up to Microsoft Ignite, I wanted to pressure-test something the community keeps talking about: vibe coding. It’s a style of AI-assisted development where you describe outcomes in natural language and your assistant does most of the scaffolding, refacto】在Microsoft Ignite之后，我想对社区一直在谈论的事情进行压力测试：Vibe编码。这是一种AI辅助发展的风格，您可以描述自然语言的结果，而您的助手进行了大部分的脚手架，重新处理</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking GPT-5’s Freeform Tool Calling: A New Era of Seamless Integration】解锁GPT-5的Freeform工具呼叫：无缝集成的新时代</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/unlocking-gpt-5s-freeform-tool-calling-a-new-era-of-seamless-integration</link>
      <description>【GPT-5 models are now available in Azure AI Foundry via Azure OpenAI. Designed for advanced reasoning and generation. One of the core capabilities of the model is tool calling, which enables it to interact with external systems by generating an】GPT-5型号现在可以通过Azure Openai在Azure AI铸造厂中获得。专为高级推理和发电而设计。该模型的核心功能之一是工具调用，它使其能够通过生成一个与外部系统进行交互</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thoughts on creating a tracking pointer class, part 10: Proper conversion】关于创建跟踪指针类的想法，第10部分：正确的转换</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250822-00/?p=111494</link>
      <description>【Last time, we added the ability to convert tracking pointers to non-const objects into tracking pointers to const objects, but we noted that there&#39;s a problem. The problem is that】上次，我们添加了将跟踪指针转换为非const对象的能力，以跟踪指针到const对象，但我们注意到存在问题。问题是</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【OData .NET (ODL) 9 Preview Release】ODATA .NET（ODL）9预览版本</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/odata/odata-net-9-preview-release</link>
      <description>【We’re happy to announce that OData .NET (ODL) 9 Preview 2 has been officially released and is available on NuGet: Microsoft.OData.Core 9.0.0 Preview 2】我们很高兴地宣布ODATA .NET（ODL）9预览2已正式发布，可在Nuget上发布：Microsoft.odata.core 9.0.0 Preview 2</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 09:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Create embeddings in SQL Server 2025 RC0 with a local ONNX model on Windows】在Windows上使用本地ONNX模型在SQL Server 2025 RC0中创建嵌入式</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/create-embeddings-in-sql-server-2025-rc0-with-a-local-onnx-model-on-windows</link>
      <description>【With the release of SQL Server 2025 RC0, we have enabled the ability to use a local ONNX model on th】随着SQL Server 2025 RC0的发布，我们启用了在TH上使用本地onnx模型的能力</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 01:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhance your CLI testing workflow with the new dotnet test】通过新的dotnet测试增强CLI测试工作流程</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-test-with-mtp</link>
      <description>【The dotnet test command is part of the .NET CLI and is used to run tests in a given solution. It supports multiple test frameworks, including MSTest, xUnit, NUnit and TUnit. The command recognizes two main test platforms: VSTest and Microsoft.Testing.Platform】dotnet test命令是.NET CLI的一部分，用于在给定解决方案中运行测试。它支持多个测试框架，包括Mstest，Xunit，Nunit和Tunit。该命令识别两个主要测试平台：vstest and Microsoft.testing.platform</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Better Control over Your Copilot Code Suggestions】更好地控制您的Copilot代码建议</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/better-control-over-your-copilot-code-suggestions</link>
      <description>【Copilot code completions and suggestions in the editor speed you up in your daily programming and coding activities, at every keystroke. They help you finish the line you&#39;re typing or anticipate your next edit, making your workflow smoother and faster. At the same time, editor is where you focus and put in the deep work. Based on your feedback】副本代码的完成和编辑中的建议在每日钥匙中都会加快您的日常编程和编码活动的速度。它们可以帮助您完成您要键入或预期下一个编辑的线路，从而使您的工作流程更加顺畅，更快。同时，编辑是您专注于深入工作的地方。根据您的反馈</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSSQL Extension for VS Code: Schema Compare, Schema Designer, Local SQL Server Container GA】VS代码的MSSQL扩展名：架构比较，架构设计器，本地SQL Server Container GA</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/vscode-mssql-schema-container</link>
      <description>【The MSSQL Extension for VS Code continues to evolve, delivering features that make SQL development more visual, more consistent, and more developer-friendly. In version v1.35.0, we’re announcing the General Availability (GA) of】VS代码的MSSQL扩展名继续发展，提供了使SQL开发更具视觉，更一致和更友好的功能。在版本v1.35.0中，我们宣布了一般可用性（GA）</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Thoughts on creating a tracking pointer class, part 9: Conversion】关于创建跟踪指针类的想法，第9部分：转换</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250821-00/?p=111492</link>
      <description>【Last time, we added the ability to create tracking pointers from const objects. But we discovered that you could not convert a tracking_ptr&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; to a tra】上次，我们添加了从const对象创建跟踪指针的能力。但是我们发现您无法将tracking_ptr &lt;t&gt;转换为tra</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Designing Multi-Agent Intelligence】设计多代理智能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/designing-multi-agent-intelligence</link>
      <description>【Written by: Maggie Liu, Thiago Rotta, Vinicius Souza, James Tooles, &amp;amp;】撰写者：Maggie Liu，Thiago Rotta，Vinicius Souza，James Tooles，＆</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>