<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I choose a different C++ constructor at runtime?】如何在运行时选择其他C ++构造函数？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250306-00/?p=110942</link>
      <description>【Make somebody else do it, and then use copy elision.】让别人这样做，然后使用复制elision。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multi Root Workspaces in Visual Studio Code】Visual Studio代码中的多根工作区</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/multi_root_workspaces_in_visual_studio_code</link>
      <description>【How to manage multiple independent python projects, with different dependencies, inside Visual Studio Code.】如何在Visual Studio代码内部管理具有不同依赖关系的多个独立的Python项目。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET AI Template Now Available in Preview】.NET AI模板现已在预览中可用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/announcing-dotnet-ai-template-preview1</link>
      <description>【Announcing the first preview of the .NET AI Template, for Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, and the .NET CLI. Get started building amazing AI apps with .NET.】宣布为Visual Studio，Visual Studio Code和.NET CLI宣布.NET AI模板的第一个预览。开始使用.NET构建惊人的AI应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How Microsoft Copilot scales to millions of users with Azure Cosmos DB】Microsoft Copilot如何使用Azure Cosmos DB缩放数百万用户</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/how-microsoft-copilot-scales-to-millions-of-users-with-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【This article is guest authored by Youssef Moussaoui, member of the technical staff, Microsoft Copilot. As part of the team developing Microsoft Copilot, we’re constantly looking for ways to improve the application and keep our millions of users engaged. With this in mind, we recently evaluated the structure of our backend and began looking for [&amp;hellip;]】本文是由Microsoft Copilot的技术人员成员Youssef Moussaoui撰写的来宾。作为开发Microsoft Copilot的团队的一部分，我们一直在寻找改善应用程序并保持数百万用户参与的方法。考虑到这一点，我们最近评估了后端的结构，并开始寻找[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 17:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Effortlessly Integrate xAI’s Grok with Semantic Kernel】轻松地将Xai的grok与语义内核整合在一起</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/integrate-sk-with-xai-grok-easily</link>
      <description>【For Semantic Kernel users, integrating xAI&amp;#8217;s Grok API using the OpenAI connector is a breeze thanks to its compatibility with OpenAI&amp;#8217;s API format. This tutorial focuses on setting up Grok in your Semantic Kernel projects with minimal fuss, using C# and Python examples. Why Grok? Grok, built by xAI, is a powerful AI model, offers [&amp;hellip;]】对于语义内核用户，由于其与OpenAI的API格式的兼容性，使用OpenAI连接器集成XAI的Grok API变得轻而易举。本教程的重点是使用C＃和Python示例在您的语义内核项目中设置Grok。为什么要格罗克？由XAI建造的Grok是一种强大的AI模型，提供[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 15:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Guidelines Support Library v4.2.0】宣布指南支持库v4.2.0</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/announcing-guidelines-support-library-v4-2-0</link>
      <description>【Version 4.2.0 of Microsoft&#39;s Guidelines Support Library brings performance improvements, safety features, modern compiler support.】微软指南支持库的4.2.0版带来了性能改进，安全功能，现代编译器支持。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSSQL Extension for VS Code: What’s new and what’s next】VS代码的MSSQL扩展：什么是新事物和下一步</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/mssql-vs-code-whats-new-next</link>
      <description>【The MSSQL Extension for VS Code continues to evolve, bringing powerful new features and enhancements that make SQL development more seamless and efficient. In this update, we’re excited to share the latest improvements in v1.29.0 and give you a sneak peek at what’s coming next in our open roadmap. This extension is designed for developers [&amp;hellip;]】VS代码的MSSQL扩展不断发展，带来了强大的新功能和增强功能，使SQL开发更加无缝和高效。在此更新中，我们很高兴分享v1.29.0中的最新改进，并为您提供开放路线图中的下一步情况。此扩展是为开发人员设计的[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Talk to your agents! Introducing the Realtime API’s in Semantic Kernel!】与您的代理商交谈！在语义内核中介绍实时API！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/talk-to-your-agents-introducing-the-realtime-apis-in-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Introducing Realtime Agents in Semantic Kernel for Python! With release 1.23.0 of the Python version of Semantic Kernel we are introducing a new set of clients for interacting with the realtime multi-modal API&amp;#8217;s of OpenAI and Azure OpenAI. They provide a abstracted approach to connecting to those services, adding your tools and running apps that [&amp;hellip;]】在python的语义内核中介绍实时代理！随着Python版本的语义内核版本1.23.0，我们正在介绍一组新的客户端，以与OpenAI和Azure Openai的实时多模式API进行交互。他们提供了一种抽象的方法来连接到这些服务，添加您的工具和运行应用程序[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 21:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AutoGen and Semantic Kernel, Part 2】Autogen和语义内核，第2部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/semantic-kernel-and-autogen-part-2</link>
      <description>【Following on from our blog post a couple months ago: Microsoft’s Agentic AI Frameworks: AutoGen and Semantic Kernel, Microsoft’s agentic AI story is evolving at a steady pace. Both Azure AI Foundry’s Semantic Kernel and AI Frontier’s AutoGen are designed to empower developers to build advanced multi-agent systems. The AI Frontier’s team is charging ahead [&amp;hellip;]】在几个月前我们的博客文章之后：Microsoft的代理AI框架：Autogen和Sminantic内核，Microsoft的代理AI故事正在以稳定的速度发展。 Azure AI Foundry的语义内核和AI Frontier的Autogen都旨在增强开发人员的能力，以构建先进的多代理系统。 AI Frontier的团队正在向前冲锋[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 17:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python in Visual Studio Code – March 2025 Release】Visual Studio代码中的Python  -  2025年3月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/python-in-visual-studio-code-march-2025-release</link>
      <description>【The March 2025 release of the Python and Jupyter extensions for Visual Studio Code are now available. This month&#39;s updates include improvements to shell integration, a new setting to change auto test discovery file patterns, inline values shown on hover, and more!】2025年3月的Python和Jupyter扩展名的版本现已提供。本月的更新包括改进Shell集成，一种新的设置，以更改自动测试发现文件模式，悬停在悬停的内联值等等！</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 19:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>