<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Hello HybridCache! Streamlining Cache Management for ASP.NET Core Applications】您好Hybridcache！简化用于ASP.NET核心应用程序的高速缓存管理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/hybrid-cache-is-now-ga</link>
      <description>【HybridCache is now GA, use today】Hybridcache现在是GA，今天使用</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Make more sense of multithreaded debugging】更有意义地多线程调试</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/make-more-sense-of-multithreaded-debugging</link>
      <description>【Debugging complex programs often feels like navigating a labyrinth of threads and stack traces. The challenge of understanding thread behaviors and tracing issues can be daunting, leading to longer development times and increased frustration. But now, there&amp;#8217;s a solution that simplifies this process—introducing AI-powered thread summaries in Parallel Stacks Window with Visual Studio. To address [&amp;hellip;]】调试复杂程序通常感觉就像导航迷宫的线程和堆栈痕迹。理解线程行为和追踪问题的挑战可能是令人生畏的，导致了更长的发展时间并增加了挫败感。但是现在，有一个解决方案简化了此过程 - 使用Visual Studio在并行堆栈窗口中引入了AI驱动的线程摘要。解决[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customer Case Story: Creating a Semantic Kernel Agent for Automated GitHub Code Reviews】客户案例故事：为自动化GitHub代码评论创建语义内核代理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-story-creating-a-semantic-kernel-agent-for-automated-github-code-reviews</link>
      <description>【Today I want to welcome a guest author to our Semantic Kernel blog, Rasmus Wulff Jensen, to cover how he&amp;#8217;s created a Semantic Kernel agent for automated GitHub code review. We&amp;#8217;ll turn it over to Rasmus to dive in. Introduction If you work in software development, you know that Code reviews are an essential part [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我想欢迎一位来宾作者进入我们的语义内核博客Rasmus Wulff Jensen，以介绍他如何为自动化GitHub代码评论创建语义内核代理。我们将其移交给Rasmus进行潜水。简介您在软件开发中工作，您知道代码评论是必不可少的部分[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 22:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Microsoft Desired State Configuration v3.0.0】宣布Microsoft所需状态配置v3.0.0</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/announcing-dsc-v3</link>
      <description>【This post announces the release of Microsoft Desired State Configuration v3.0.0. We discuss the features and benefits of DSC and how it differs from PowerShell DSC.】这篇文章宣布了Microsoft所需状态配置v3.0.0的发布。我们讨论了DSC的特征和好处，以及它与PowerShell DSC的不同之处。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What are the thread safety requirements of HSTRING and BSTR?】HSTRING和BSTR的线程安全要求是什么？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250312-00/?p=110960</link>
      <description>【They do not have thread affinity.】他们没有线程亲和力。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Effortless Scaling: Autoscale goes GA on vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB】轻松缩放：AutoScale在基于Vcore的Azure Cosmos DB上进行GA</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/effortless-scaling-autoscale-goes-ga-on-vcore-based-azure-cosmos-db-for-mongodb</link>
      <description>【We’re thrilled to announce that Autoscale is now generally available (GA) for vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB! Say goodbye to manual scaling and overprovisioning—Autoscale dynamically adjusts your database capacity in real time, ensuring peak performance exactly when you need it. Instant scaling? Check. Cost savings? Absolutely. Predictable pricing? You got it. Unlike traditional managed [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布，AutoScale现在通常可用于MongoDB的基于Vcore的Azure Cosmos DB（GA）！告别手动缩放和过度配置 -  Autoscale会实时动态调整您的数据库容量，从而确保在需要时准确确定峰值性能。即时缩放？查看。节省成本？绝对地。可预测的定价？你明白了。与传统管理不同[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New Python Driver for SQL Server and Azure SQL!】SQL Server和Azure SQL的新python驱动程序！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/mssql-python-for-sqlserver-alpha-release</link>
      <description>【We’re thrilled to announce the alpha release of our new open-source Python driver for Microsoft SQL Server and the Azure SQL family, now available on GitHub at mssql-python.】我们很高兴宣布Alpha发布我们的新开源Python driver for Microsoft SQL Server和Azure SQL家族，该驱动程序现已在MSSQL-Python的GitHub上找到。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Get started with Microsoft Desired State Configuration v3.0.0】开始使用Microsoft所需状态配置v3.0.0</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/get-started-with-dsc-v3</link>
      <description>【This post show you how to install DSC v3.0.0 and get started using the **dsc** command.】这篇文章向您展示了如何安装DSC v3.0.0并开始使用** dsc **命令开始。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 17:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Authoring Enhancements in Microsoft Desired State Configuration v3.0.0】Microsoft所需状态配置v3.0.0中的创作增强功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/enhanced-authoring-with-dsc-v3</link>
      <description>【This is the third post in a multi-part series about the new release of DSC. Microsoft Desired State Configuration (DSC) v3.0.0 provides powerful feature that enhance the authoring experience. Shell completion Schema-based validation Support for modern DSLs like Azure Bicep DSC command completer The completer command returns a shell script that, when executed, registers completions [&amp;hellip;]】这是有关DSC新版本的多部分系列中的第三篇文章。 Microsoft所需的状态配置（DSC）v3.0.0提供了增强创作体验的功能强大的功能。基于shell架构模式的验证支持对现代DSL（例如Azure BICEP DSC命令完成器）命令命令返回一个shell脚本，执行后，该脚本登记完成[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 18:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s new in Microsoft Dev Box】Microsoft Dev Box中的新功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/whats-new-in-microsoft-dev-box</link>
      <description>【This post covers the latest features and enhancements in Microsoft Dev Box. These updates introduce advanced customization capabilities, improved security, performance optimizations, and better developer experience to make Dev Box even more efficient. Last update: 03/12/2025 In this post: Config-as-workflow improvements Enhanced user provided customizations Developer onboarding &amp;amp; experience Streamlined and flexible onboarding for enterprises [&amp;hellip;]】这篇文章涵盖了Microsoft Dev Box中的最新功能和增强功能。这些更新介绍了高级自定义功能，提高安全性，性能优化以及更好的开发人员体验，以使开发框更加有效。上次更新：本文中的03/12/2025：config-as-workflow改进增强用户为企业提供了自定义开发人员入职和体验的精简和灵活的企业登机工作[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>