<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【TypeScript 7 native preview in Visual Studio 2026】TypeScript 7 Visual Studio中的本机预览2026</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/typescript-7-native-preview-in-visual-studio-2026</link>
      <description>【In March of this year Anders Hejlsberg announced TypeScript 7 native preview and in May Daniel posted Announcing TypeScript Native Previews. Visual Studio 2026 Insiders n】今年3月，安德斯·赫尔斯伯格（Anders Hejlsberg）宣布了Typescript 7本地预览，丹尼尔（Daniel）发布了宣布打字稿本机预览的宣布。 Visual Studio 2026内部人员n</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microspeak: Convicted】微言：被定罪</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250930-00/?p=111639</link>
      <description>【When you do something with conviction, you do so with full confidence that you are correct. But what is the verb that means &#34;To be fully confident that one is correct&#34;? At Microsoft, it is often backformed into the verb convict (stress on second syllable). This backformation typically happens in speech,】当您有信念做某事时，您会完全相信自己是正确的。但是，“完全有信心一个正确的动词”是什么意思？在微软，通常会将其反面到动词定罪中（第二个音节上的压力）。这种反映通常发生在语音中，</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio September Update - profiler agent, app modernization, and more】Visual Studio 9月更新 -  Profiler代理，应用现代化等等</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-september-update</link>
      <description>【The September 2025 update for Visual Studio 2022 (v17.14) is now available. In this month, we are bringing you a fully integrated and game-changing agentic AI experience, from code generation to modernization, profiling, and code reviews.  】Visual Studio 2022（V17.14）的2025年9月更新现已可用。在本月，我们将为您带来完全集成和改变游戏的代理AI体验，从代码生成到现代化，分析和代码评论。  </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft’s OpenJDK builds now ready for Java 25】Microsoft的OpenJDK现在可以为Java 25构建</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/microsofts-openjdk-builds-now-ready-for-java-25</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce that the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK binaries are now available for Java 25. As always, our builds aim to provide a high-quality, production-ready build of OpenJDK, with binaries tested across plat】我们很高兴地宣布，Microsoft的OpenJDK二进制文件现在可用于Java 25。与往常一样，我们的构建旨在提供高质量的，可准备的OpenJDK，并在Plat上测试了二进制文件</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Data API builder 1.6: Advanced Behaviors with Special HTTP Headers】数据API构建器1.6：具有特殊HTTP标头的高级行为</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/data-api-builder-16-http-headers</link>
      <description>【Data API builder (DAB) provides REST and GraphQL endpoints over SQL Server, Azure Cosmos DB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, and SQL Data Warehouse. REST endpoints support several HTTP headers that let you control how requests behave. These headers give you precision over updates, caching, and discovering new resources.】数据API构建器（DAB）通过SQL Server，Azure Cosmos DB，PostgreSQL，MySQL和SQL数据仓库提供REST和GRAPHQL端点。 REST端点支持几个HTTP标头，可让您控制请求的行为方式。这些标题为您提供了更新，缓存和发现新资源的精确度。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fixing Overload Resolution For Parameter Arrays in C++/CLI】修复C ++/CLI中参数阵列的过载分辨率</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/fixing-overload-resolution-for-parameter-arrays-in-c-cli</link>
      <description>【Introduction In the below discussion, .NET Framework refers to the older version of the Microsoft Common Language Runtime, also known as &#34;Desktop Framework&#34; (versions 4.0 through 4.8.x) while .NET  refers t】引言在以下讨论中，.NET框架是指Microsoft通用语言运行时的旧版本，也称为“桌面框架”（版本4.0至4.8.x版本），而.NET则是指t</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I enumerate the overflow icons in the Notification Area without showing them?】如果不显示通知区域，我如何列举通知区域中的溢出图标？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250929-00/?p=111637</link>
      <description>【Some time ago, I demonstrated enumerating notification icons via UI Automation. Part of the exercise was enumerating the icons in the overflow area. This was done by finding the button that expands the over】不久前，我通过UI自动化表明了列举通知图标。练习的一部分是列举溢流区域中的图标。这是通过找到扩展超过的按钮来完成的</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Preparing Your .NET MAUI Apps for Google Play&#39;s 16 KB Page Size Requirement】为Google Play的16 KB页面尺寸要求准备.NET MAUI应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/maui-google-play-16-kb-page-size-support</link>
      <description>【If you&#39;re a .NET MAUI developer publishing apps to Google Play, there&#39;s an important requirement coming your way. Starting November 1st, 2025, Google Play will require all new apps and updates targeting Android 15+ to support 16 KB page sizes on 64-bit devices. What is the 16 KB Page Size Requirement? Androi】如果您是Google Play的.NET MAUI开发人员发布应用程序，那么您的方式就会有一个重要的要求。从2025年11月1日开始，Google Play将需要所有针对Android 15+的更新，以支持64位设备上的16 KB页面尺寸。 16 KB页面大小的要求是什么？ Androi</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why didn&#39;t Windows 95 setup install a miniature Windows 95 so that it could be written as a 32-bit program?】为什么Windows 95设置不安装微型Windows 95，以便可以将其写入32位程序？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250926-00/?p=111629</link>
      <description>【I noted some time ago that Windows 95 Setup was actually three programs running under three different operating systems. The first part was an MS-DOS program, which was used if you installed Windows 9】我一段时间以前指出，Windows 95设置实际上是在三个不同的操作系统下运行的三个程序。第一部分是MS-DOS程序，如果您安装了Windows 9</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Simplifying Resource Management in mssql-python through Context Manager】通过上下文管理器简化MSSQL-Python中的资源管理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/simplifying-resource-management-in-mssql-python-through-context-manager</link>
      <description>【Reviewed by: Sumit Sarabhai】评论者：Sumit Sarabhai</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 09:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>