<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Build a Streamlit application with Fabric SQL Database】使用Fabric SQL数据库构建简化应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/build-a-streamlit-application-with-fabric-sql-database</link>
      <description>【Building an application allows you to operationalize the data you have in Microsoft Fabric, such that it can be consumed by stakeholders in your organization to generate business insights.  Streamlit is easy to use to build simple applications without needing to know front-end application frameworks like Flask, Django etc. It makes it easier to prototype [&amp;hellip;]】构建应用程序可以使您可以在Microsoft Fabric中运行您的数据，从而可以由组织中的利益相关者消费以生成业务见解。  简化很容易用于构建简单的应用程序，而无需了解烧瓶，django等前端应用程序框架。它使原型更容易[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 19:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Embracing Zero Trust: Never Trust, Always Verify】拥抱零信任：永远不要信任，始终验证</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azuregov/embracing-zero-trust-never-trust-always-verify</link>
      <description>【Microsoft&amp;#8217;s 2024 Digital Defense Report found that between July 2023 and July 2024, Microsoft customers faced an astounding 600 million attacks daily from both cybercriminals and nation-state actors. space In this high-risk and rapidly evolving environment, individuals and organizations must not only strengthen digital defenses at every level but also foster a deep and enduring [&amp;hellip;]】微软的2024年数字防御报告发现，在2023年7月至2024年7月之间，微软客户每天都面临着6亿次攻击，网络犯罪分子和民族国家参与者都面临着6亿次攻击。在这个高风险和迅速发展的环境中，个人和组织不仅必须在各个层面上加强数字防御，还必须促进深刻而持久的境地[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Boost your GitHub productivity with our new multi-account support!】通过我们的新多学院支持提高您的GitHub生产率！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/boost-your-github-productivity-with-our-new-multi-account-support</link>
      <description>【Managing your GitHub identity in Visual Studio 2022 just got easier! Our latest update overhauls the GitHub account management experience and improves how you work with multiple accounts, especially for GitHub Copilot and version control scenarios. In this post, we&amp;#8217;ll detail how these changes will make your GitHub workflow smoother, from the moment you start [&amp;hellip;]】在Visual Studio 2022中管理您的GitHub身份只是变得更加容易了！我们的最新更新大修了GitHub帐户管理经验，并改善了您与多个帐户的合作方式，尤其是对于Github Copilot和版本控制方案。在这篇文章中，我们将详细说明这些更改将如何使您的github工作流程更加顺畅，从您开始[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the General Availability of OpenID Connect external identity provider support for Microsoft Entra External ID】宣布OpenID Connect的一般可用性外部身份提供商对Microsoft Entra外部ID的支持</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/openid-connect-external-identity-provider-support-ga</link>
      <description>【Discover the new OpenID Connect identity provider support in Microsoft Entra External ID, now generally available. Simplify user sign-in and partner integrations, and improve conversion rates and user satisfaction by federating with external identity providers like Okta, Amazon, Auth0, and Azure AD B2C.】在Microsoft Entra外部ID中发现新的OpenID Connect Identity提供商支持，现在通常可用。简化用户登录和合作伙伴集成，并通过与Okta，Amazon，Auth0和Azure AD B2C等外部身份提供商联合来提高转换率和用户满意度。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Upcoming Updates for Azure Pipelines Agents Images】Azure Pipelines代理图像的即将到来的更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/upcoming-updates-for-azure-pipelines-agents-images</link>
      <description>【To ensure our hosted agents in Azure Pipelines are operating in the most secure and up-to-date environments, we continuously update the supported images and phase out older ones. In October 2024, we announced support for Ubuntu-24.04. Soon, we plan to update the ubuntu-latest image to map to Ubuntu-24.04. Additionally, MacOS 15 Sequoia and Windows 2025 [&amp;hellip;]】为了确保我们在最安全和最新的环境中运行的Azure管道中的托管代理，我们不断更新受支持的图像并逐步逐步淘汰较旧的图像。 2024年10月，我们宣布支持Ubuntu-24.04。很快，我们计划更新Ubuntu-latt的图像以将其映射到Ubuntu-24.04。此外，MacOS 15红杉和Windows 2025 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Self-Serve Restoration in Microsoft Dev Box】Microsoft Dev Box中的自助恢复</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/self-serve-restoration-in-microsoft-dev-box</link>
      <description>【Developers grapple with the anxiety of potential data loss due to unforeseen issues, such as accidental deletions, system failures, or even corrupt files. The Dev Box team is addressing this concern with the self-service restoration feature for the Dev Box, designed to put you back in control. This functionality streamlines recovery by allowing direct restorations [&amp;hellip;]】开发人员努力应对因无法预料的问题而引起的潜在数据丢失的焦虑，例如意外删除，系统故障甚至损坏的文件。开发框团队正在使用开发框的自助恢复功能来解决这个问题，该功能旨在使您重新控制。该功能通过允许直接修复来简化恢复[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 04:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET 10 Preview 2 is now available!】.NET 10预览2现在可用！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-10-preview-2</link>
      <description>【Find out about the new features in .NET 10 Preview 2 across the .NET runtime, SDK, libraries, ASP.NET Core, Blazor, C#, .NET MAUI, and more!】在.NET 10 Preview 2中查找.NET运行时，SDK，Libraries，ASP.NET Core，Blazor，C＃，.Net Maui等等中的新功能！</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing ABAP Support in GitHub Copilot for Eclipse】在Eclipse的Github Copilot中引入ABAP支持</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/introducing-abap-support-in-github-copilot-for-eclipse</link>
      <description>【The latest release of GitHub Copilot for Eclipse now includes support for ABAP! This update builds on the recent release of code completion and chat integration, offering a robust toolset for developers working within the SAP environment. ABAP remains a critical language in the enterprise space, powering a wide range of business applications, and its [&amp;hellip;]】Eclipse的Github Copilot的最新版本现在包括对ABAP的支持！此更新基于最近发布的代码完成和聊天集成，为在SAP环境中工作的开发人员提供了强大的工具集。 ABAP在企业领域仍然是一种关键语言，为广泛的业务应用程序提供动力，及其[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 03:13:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why didn’t Windows 95 setup use a miniature version of Windows 95 as its fallback GUI?】为什么Windows 95设置不使用Windows 95的微型版本作为后备GUI？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250318-00/?p=110975</link>
      <description>【Avoiding an interim GUI environment.】避免临时GUI环境。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimizing Build Times with Build Insights: How Activision Cut Call of Duty’s Build Time by 50%】通过构建见解优化构建时间：Activision如何将《使命召唤》的构建时间缩短50％</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/optimizing-build-times-with-build-insights-how-activision-cut-call-of-dutys-build-time-by-50</link>
      <description>【Slow build times are a major headache for developers, especially in large, complex C++ codebases like game engines. Every minute spent waiting on a build is time that could be used to refine features, resolve issues, or push development forward. Activision faced this challenge with Call of Duty: Modern Warfare II, where prolonged build times [&amp;hellip;]】缓慢的构建时间是开发人员的主要头痛，尤其是在大型，复杂的C ++代码库中，例如游戏引擎。等待构建的每一分钟都是可以用来完善功能，解决问题或推动发展向前发展的时间。 Activision通过《使命召唤：现代战争II》面临着这一挑战，在那里长时间的构建时间[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>