<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Why do I observe reads from a memory-mapped file when writing large blocks?】为什么在写入大块时会观察到内存映射文件的读取？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241107-00/?p=110486</link>
      <description>【The CPU doesn&#39;t see the entire write at once.】CPU 不会立即看到整个写入。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How do I declare an operator overload for my Windows Runtime class?】如何为我的 Windows 运行时类声明运算符重载？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241106-00/?p=110478</link>
      <description>【That&#39;s not something expressible in the Windows Runtime.】这不是 Windows 运行时中可以表达的内容。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to subscribe for GitHub copilot business without GitHub Enterprise: A Step-by-Step Guide】如何在没有 GitHub Enterprise 的情况下订阅 GitHub copilot 业务：分步指南</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/how-to-subscribe-for-github-copilot-business-without-github-enterprise</link>
      <description>【Did you know that now you can subscribe to GitHub Copilot Business without GitHub Enterprise (GHE), which means you can get GitHub Copilot Business as a standalone capability, while having the normal GitHub Enterprise features (repositories, actions, etc.) disabled. This post is a screenshot-based step-by-step guide on how to configure a new GitHub Copilot Business [&amp;hellip;]】您是否知道，现在您可以在没有 GitHub Enterprise (GHE) 的情况下订阅 GitHub Copilot Business，这意味着您可以将 GitHub Copilot Business 作为独立功能获得，同时禁用正常的 GitHub Enterprise 功能（存储库、操作等）。这篇文章是一个基于屏幕截图的分步指南，介绍如何配置新的 GitHub Copilot Business [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 16:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Get Ready for .NET Conf 2024!】为 .NET Conf 2024 做好准备！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/get-ready-for-dotnet-conf-2024</link>
      <description>【The biggest .NET event of the year is almost here, its all free, all online, and you&#39;re invited!】年度最大的 .NET 活动即将到来，全部免费，全部在线，诚邀您！</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【RAG with SQL Vector Store: A Low-Code/No-Code Approach using Azure Logic Apps】带有 SQL 矢量存储的 RAG：使用 Azure 逻辑应用的低代码/无代码方法</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/sql-vector-store-data-ingestion-and-retrieval-using-azure-logic-apps</link>
      <description>【Data is at the heart of every AI application, and efficient data ingestion is critical for success. With over 1,400 enterprise connectors, Logic Apps offers unmatched access to a diverse range of systems, applications, and databases, whether hosted in the cloud or on-premises. These connectors give businesses the flexibility to keep their data where it [&amp;hellip;]】数据是每个人工智能应用程序的核心，高效的数据摄取对于成功至关重要。凭借 1,400 多个企业连接器，逻辑应用提供对各种系统、应用程序和数据库的无与伦比的访问，无论托管在云中还是本地。这些连接器使企业能够灵活地将数据保存在适当的位置[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 05:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exciting Announcement: Public Preview of Native Vector Support in Azure SQL Database!】激动人心的公告：Azure SQL 数据库中原生矢量支持的公开预览版！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/exciting-announcement-public-preview-of-native-vector-support-in-azure-sql-database</link>
      <description>【Public Preview of Native Vector Support in Azure SQL Database We are excited to share that the dedicated vector data type in Azure SQL Database, which was previously available through the Early Adopter Preview, is now transitioning to Public Preview! As of today, the Vector data type and its associated functions are accessible to everyone, [&amp;hellip;]】Azure SQL 数据库中本机矢量支持的公共预览版 我们很高兴地与大家分享，Azure SQL 数据库中的专用矢量数据类型（之前通过早期采用者预览版提供）现在正在过渡到公共预览版！截至今天，每个人都可以访问 Vector 数据类型及其相关函数，[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.23.3-1 and 1.22.9-1 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.23.3-1 和 1.22.9-1 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-23-3-1-and-1-22-9-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new set of Microsoft Go builds is now available for download.】一组新的 Microsoft Go 版本现已可供下载。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 23:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (October 2024)】vcpkg 的新增功能（2024 年 10 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-october-2024</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2024.10.21 registry release, 2024-10-18 tool release, as well as changes to vcpkg documentation throughout October. This release adds support for Azure universal packages as a binary caching provider and other minor improvements. CppCon Talk on Managing C++ Dependencies I also gave [&amp;hellip;]】本博客文章总结了作为 2024.10.21 注册表版本、2024-10-18 工具版本一部分的 vcpkg 包管理器的更改，以及整个 10 月份对 vcpkg 文档的更改。此版本添加了对 Azure 通用包作为二进制缓存提供程序的支持以及其他细微改进。我还发表了关于管理 C++ 依赖关系的 CppCon 演讲 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 06:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing a new, more conversational way to chat with GitHub Copilot】引入一种新的、更具对话性的方式与 GitHub Copilot 聊天</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/conversational-way-to-chat-with-github-copilot</link>
      <description>【In the fast-evolving world of software development, intuitive AI-driven interactions are becoming essential to unlocking new levels of productivity. Today, we’re excited to share our latest innovation &amp;#8211; a guided chat experience within GitHub Copilot that reshapes how developers interact with AI. This guided chat experience is available in Visual Studio 2022 17.12 Preview 3 [&amp;hellip;]】在快速发展的软件开发世界中，直观的人工智能驱动交互对于解锁新的生产力水平变得至关重要。今天，我们很高兴与大家分享我们的最新创新——GitHub Copilot 中的引导式聊天体验，它重塑了开发人员与 AI 交互的方式。 Visual Studio 2022 17.12 Preview 3 中提供了这种引导式聊天体验 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 16:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Debugging a managed identity connection to Azure SQL in Azure App Service using containers】使用容器在 Azure 应用服务中调试与 Azure SQL 的托管标识连接</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/debugging-a-managed-identity-connection-to-azure-sql-in-azure-app-service-using-containers</link>
      <description>【Dominique St-Amand explores how to debug a managed identity connection from a container-based App Service to Azure SQL. So you’ve been eager to deploy your containerized web application that you’ve been working on for a while, to Azure App Service. You follow the best security practices which means you’ve setup your connection to your Azure [&amp;hellip;]】Dominique St-Amand 探索如何调试从基于容器的应用服务到 Azure SQL 的托管标识连接。因此，您一直渴望将您已经开发了一段时间的容器化 Web 应用程序部署到 Azure 应用服务。您遵循最佳安全实践，这意味着您已经设置了与 Azure 的连接 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 07:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>