<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing General Availability of GitHub Copilot for Azure—Now with Agent Mode】宣布GitHub Copilot用于Azure的一般可用性 - 现在使用Agent Mode</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/announcing-general-availability-of-github-copilot-for-azure-now-with-agent-mode</link>
      <description>【Unlocking a New DevOps Era GitHub Copilot for Azure was first introduced at Ignite 2024 as a public preview, empowering developers, IT operators, and DevOps practitioners to leverage natural language to provision, configure, and manage r】首次在IGNITE 2024上引入了新的Devops ERA GITHUB COPILOT作为Azure的副驾驶，作为公共预览，增强开发人员，IT运营商和DevOps从业人员的能力，以利用自然语言来提供，配置和管理R</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 21:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Learning to read C++ compiler errors: Ambiguous symbol errors after including a header file】学习读取C ++编译器错误：包含标头文件后模棱两可的符号错误</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250619-00/?p=111285</link>
      <description>【A colleague added another header file to their project, and everything started blowing up with &#34;ambiguous symbol&#34; errors. #include &#34;pch.h&#34; #include &#34;something.h&#34; #include &#34;newheader.h&#34; #include &amp;lt;shlobj.h&amp;gt; ... This resulted in a build error in Visual Studi】一位同事在他们的项目中添加了另一个标头文件，一切都开始爆炸了“模棱两可的符号”错误。 #include“ pch.h” #include“ somings.h” #include“ newheader.h” #include &lt;shlobj.h&gt; ...这在Visual Studi中导致构建错误</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Balance governance and flexibility with Dev Box project policies】通过开发框项目政策的平衡治理和灵活性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/balance-governance-and-flexibility-with-dev-box-project-policies</link>
      <description>【As organizations scale their development efforts, managing access to cloud resources becomes critical. Platform engineers need to strike a balance between enforcing governance and enabling developer agility. At Build 2025, we announced the general availability of project policies in Microsoft Dev Box, which provides a powerful】随着组织扩大开发工作，管理对云资源的访问变得至关重要。平台工程师需要在执行治理和使开发人员敏捷性之间取得平衡。在2025年的Build 2025中，我们宣布了Microsoft Dev Box中项目政策的一般可用性，该项目提供了强大的</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Additional reactions and ease of sharing】其他反应和易于分享</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devblogs-news/additional-reactions-and-ease-of-sharing</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re always exploring ways to enhance DevBlogs for our readers. In the past few weeks, we’ve introduced two updates to features: reactions and sharing. Reactions: You now have six expressive reaction options to choose from—moving beyond the simple heart. It’s a small change that we hope makes a big difference in how you engage with p】我们一直在探索为读者增强DevBlogs的方法。在过去的几周中，我们对功能进行了两个更新：反应和共享。反应：您现在有六个表达反应选择可以选择 - 超越简单的心脏。这是一个很小的变化，我们希望您与P的互动方式有很大的不同</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSSQL Extension for VS Code: Local Containers, GitHub Copilot Agent Mode and Connection Groups】VS代码的MSSQL扩展名：本地容器，GitHub Copilot代理模式和连接组</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/vscode-mssql-containers-agent-mode</link>
      <description>【The MSSQL Extension for VS Code continues to evolve, bringing powerful new features that make SQL development more local, more organized, and more intelligent. In version v1.33.0, we’re introducing Local SQL Server container】VS代码的MSSQL扩展不断发展，带来了强大的新功能，使SQL开发更加本地，更有条理，更聪明。在版本v1.33.0中，我们介绍了本地SQL Server容器</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【You have to tell &lt;CODE&gt;Get-&lt;/CODE&gt; and &lt;CODE&gt;Set­Security­Info&lt;/CODE&gt; the object type, you can&#39;t make it guess】您必须告诉&lt;code&gt;获取 -  &lt;/code&gt;和&lt;code&gt; setSecurityInfo &lt;/code&gt;对象类型，您无法猜测</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250618-00/?p=111281</link>
      <description>【A customer was trying to read the security information from a process object, but their call to Get­Security­Info wasn&#39;t working. PACL dacl = nullptr; PSECURITY_DESCRIPTOR sd = nullptr; GetSecurityInfo(processHandle, SE_UNKNOWN_OBJECT_TYPE, DACL_SECURITY_INFORMATION, nullptr, // not interested in ow】客户试图从流程对象中阅读安全信息，但是他们对getEcurityInfo的呼吁不起作用。 pacl dacl = nullptr; psecurity_descriptor sd = nullptr; getCurityInfo（processHandle，se_unknown_object_type，dacl_security_information，nullptr，//对OW不感兴趣</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Microsoft Desired State Configuration v3.1.0】宣布Microsoft所需状态配置v3.1.0</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/announcing-dsc-v3-1-0</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re pleased to announce the General Availability of Microsoft&#39;s Desired State Configuration (DSC) version 3.1.0. This release marks a significant milestone in our effort to deliver cloud-native configuration management for cross-platform environments. DSC is a declarative configuration and orchestration】我们很高兴地宣布Microsoft所需状态配置（DSC）版本3.1.0的一般可用性。该版本标志着我们为跨平台环境提供云本地配置管理的努力的一个重要里程碑。 DSC是声明性的配置和编排</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing General Availability of Native Vector Type &amp; Functions in Azure SQL】宣布Azure SQL中本地向量类型和功能的一般可用性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/announcing-general-availability-of-native-vector-type-functions-in-azure-sql</link>
      <description>【We are happy to announce that Native vector support in Azure SQL Database and Azure SQL Managed Instance is moving to General Availability this summer. Deployments are already underway, and several regions have begun receiving the feature. What is going GA? Integrated Vector Data Type Azure SQL introduces a dedicated】我们很高兴地宣布，Azure SQL数据库中的本机向量支持，而Azure SQL托管实例将于今年夏天转向一般可用性。部署已经在进行中，几个地区已经开始收到该功能。 GA发生了什么？集成矢量数据类型Azure SQL引入了专用</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PACT Contract Testing - Because Not Everything Needs Full Integration Tests】协定合同测试 - 因为并非所有内容都需要完整的集成测试</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/pact-contract-testing-because-not-everything-needs-full-integration-tests</link>
      <description>【At Microsoft Industry Solutions Engineering, we are big fans of integration tests. They are the best way to test that your system works as a whole, but sometimes, integration tests are overkill or too complex to set up that the return on investment is just not worth it. That&#39;s the situation one of our teams has recently found themselves in.】在Microsoft行业解决方案工程中，我们是集成测试的忠实拥护者。它们是测试您的系统整体工作的最佳方法，但是有时，集成测试过于杀伤或过于复杂，无法设置投资回报是不值得的。这就是我们的团队中的一个情况。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Control cloud costs with Dev Box hibernation features】控制云成本具有开发盒冬眠功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/control-cloud-costs-with-dev-box-hibernation-features</link>
      <description>【Cost is one of the most important concerns in any cloud-native rollout. IT admins need powerful tools to control costs without slowing development. At Build 2025, we were excited to announce the general availability of hibernat】成本是任何云本地推出中最重要的问题之一。 IT管​​理员需要强大的工具来控制成本而不会减慢发展的发展。在2025年的建筑中，我们很高兴宣布Hibernat的一般可用性</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>