<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【February 2026 Insiders (version 1.110)】2026 年 2 月 Insider（版本 1.110）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/february-2026-insiders-(version-1.110)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code February 2026 Release (1.110). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 2 月版本 (1.110) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft at DevNexus 2026: Practical AI for Real-World Java Development】Microsoft 在 DevNexus 2026 上：用于现实世界 Java 开发的实用 AI</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/microsoft-at-devnexus-2026-practical-ai-for-real-world-java-development</link>
      <description>【Java developers face a tough trifecta: keeping mission-critical systems running, modernizing legacy apps, and weaving AI into real engineering workflows, all without increasing risk. At DevNexus 2026, the Microsoft Java team is tackling these challenges head-on. 】Java 开发人员面临着严峻的三重挑战：保持关键任务系统运行、对遗留应用程序进行现代化改造以及将人工智能融入到实际的工程工作流程中，所有这些都不会增加风险。在 DevNexus 2026 上，Microsoft Java 团队正在正面应对这些挑战。 </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Handling Legacy User Settings in SharePoint Framework】处理 SharePoint 框架中的旧用户设置</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/handling-legacy-user-settings-in-sharepoint-framework</link>
      <description>【Introduction The SharePoint Framework (SPFx) has undergone some important changes in how it handles Entra ID app registration and security models. Here you can find additional details about what w】简介 SharePoint 框架 (SPFx) 在处理 Entra ID 应用程序注册和安全模型的方式方面发生了一些重要变化。在这里您可以找到有关 w 的更多详细信息</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Intelligent Apps with SQL: Join the SQL + AI Datathon】使用 SQL 构建智能应用程序：加入 SQL + AI Datathon</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/build-intelligent-apps-with-sql-join-the-sql-ai-datathon</link>
      <description>【T】时间</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I distinguish between the numeric keypad 0 and the top-row 0 in the &lt;CODE&gt;WM_&lt;WBR&gt;KEY­DOWN&lt;/CODE&gt; message?】如何区分 &lt;CODE&gt;WM_&lt;WBR&gt;KEYDOWN&lt;/CODE&gt; 消息中的数字键盘 0 和顶行 0？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260212-00/?p=112059</link>
      <description>【A customer wanted to know how to distinguish between the numeric keypad 0 and the top-row 0 in the WM_KEY­DOWN message. And while we&#39;re at it, let&#39;s also distinguish between the numeric keypad 0 and the Ins key. We start with this table of what you get in the WM_KEY­DOWN message w】客户想知道如何区分WM_KEYDOWN消息中的数字键盘0和顶行0。在我们讨论这个问题的同时，我们还要区分数字键盘 0 和 Ins 键。我们从这张表开始，列出了您在 WM_KEYDOWN 消息中得到的内容</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How we built the Microsoft Learn MCP Server】我们如何构建 Microsoft Learn MCP 服务器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/engineering-at-microsoft/how-we-built-the-microsoft-learn-mcp-server</link>
      <description>【When we launched the Microsoft Learn Model Context Protocol (MCP) Server in June 2025, our goal was simple: make it effortless for AI agents to use trusted, up-to-date Microsoft Learn documentation. GitHub Copilot and other agents are increasingly comm】当我们于 2025 年 6 月推出 Microsoft Learn 模型上下文协议 (MCP) 服务器时，我们的目标很简单：让 AI 代理轻松使用值得信赖的最新 Microsoft Learn 文档。 GitHub Copilot 和其他代理越来越多地交流</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript 6.0 Beta】宣布推出 TypeScript 6.0 Beta</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-6-0-beta</link>
      <description>【Today we are announcing the beta release of TypeScript 6.0! To get started using the beta, you can get it through npm with the following command: npm install -D typescript@beta TypeScript 6.0 is a unique release in that we intend f】今天我们宣布 TypeScript 6.0 测试版发布！要开始使用 Beta 版，您可以使用以下命令通过 npm 获取它： npm install -D typescript@beta TypeScript 6.0 是一个独特的版本，我们打算</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub Copilot Testing for .NET Brings AI-powered Unit Tests to Visual Studio 2026】.NET 的 GitHub Copilot 测试将 AI 驱动的单元测试引入 Visual Studio 2026</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/github-copilot-testing-for-dotnet-available-in-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【GitHub Copilot testing for .NET makes it dramatically faster and more convenient to generate high-quality unit tests without leaving your code. Today, we’re excited to announce that this capability is now generally available in Visual Studio 2026 v18.3. This release brings】适用于 .NET 的 GitHub Copilot 测试使您可以更快、更方便地生成高质量的单元测试，而无需留下代码。今天，我们很高兴地宣布，此功能现已在 Visual Studio 2026 v18.3 中全面可用。此次发布带来了</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Beyond the Prompt - Why and How to Fine-tune Your Own Models】超越提示 - 为什么以及如何微调您自己的模型</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/beyond-the-prompt-why-and-how-to-fine-tune-your-own-models</link>
      <description>【Large Language Models (LLMs) have reached a point where general intelligence is no longer the bottleneck. The real challenge in enterprise AI systems behavioral alignment ensuring models that produce consistent, reliable, policy-compliant outputs on a scale. Prompt engineering and Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) are powerful but they do n】大型语言模型（LLM）已经达到了通用智能不再是瓶颈的地步。企业人工智能系统行为一致性的真正挑战是确保模型能够大规模地产生一致、可靠、符合政策的输出。即时工程和检索增强生成 (RAG) 很强大，但它们并没有</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlock language-specific rich symbol context using new find_symbol tool】使用新的 find_symbol 工具解锁特定于语言的丰富符号上下文</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/unlock-language-specific-rich-symbol-context-using-new-find_symbol-tool</link>
      <description>【Refactoring at scale is a time-consuming and error-prone process for developers. In large codebases, developers have relied on manual searches and incremental edits across multiple files to accomplish these tasks. Modern development workflows depend on fast and accurate code navigation to avoid these pitfalls. When developers refactor exist】对于开发人员来说，大规模重构是一个耗时且容易出错的过程。在大型代码库中，开发人员依靠手动搜索和跨多个文件的增量编辑来完成这些任务。现代开发工作流程依赖于快速准确的代码导航来避免这些陷阱。当开发者重构存在时</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>