<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Observability in Semantic Kernel】语义内核中的可观察性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/observability-in-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Many of you have asked similar questions: How do I obtain the rendered prompt that Semantic Kernel sends to the AI service? How do I monitor the token usage of my application? How do I gain insights into Semantic Kernel&amp;#8217;s operations during runtime? These are all excellent questions! They fundamentally belong to the same class [&amp;hellip;]】很多人都问过类似的问题：如何获取语义内核发送给AI服务的渲染提示？如何监控应用程序的令牌使用情况？如何深入了解语义内核在运行时的操作？这些都是很好的问题！他们基本上属于同一类[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the General Availability (GA) of Microsoft Entra External ID extension for Visual Studio Code】宣布 Visual Studio Code 的 Microsoft Entra 外部 ID 扩展全面可用 (GA)</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/external-id-vs-code-extension-ga</link>
      <description>【Explore the new Microsoft Entra External ID extension for Visual Studio Code, now Generally Available (GA), created to simplify CIAM integration in your development process. See how this extension provides a smooth experience for setting up External ID applications from within VS Code.】探索适用于 Visual Studio Code 的新 Microsoft Entra 外部 ID 扩展，现已正式发布 (GA)，旨在简化开发过程中的 CIAM 集成。了解此扩展如何为从 VS Code 内设置外部 ID 应用程序提供流畅的体验。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 15:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【It rather involved being on the other side of this airtight hatchway: Posting completions to somebody else’s I/O completion port】它更涉及到在这个密闭舱口的另一边：将完成发送到其他人的 I/O 完成端口</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240917-00/?p=110276</link>
      <description>【If you have gained access to it, then that was the problem.】如果您已经获得了它的访问权限，那么这就是问题所在。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New Function Calling Available in .NET for Semantic Kernel】.NET 中可用于语义内核的新函数调用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/new-function-calling-model-available-in-net-for-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【We are happy to announce release of the new function-calling capabilities available in Semantic Kernel v1.20 (.NET). The new capabilities incorporates the best parts of the existing function-calling, such as ease of use, and improves on it by making it more extensible and reusable. Function calling allows Plugin descriptions to be passed into a model [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布发布 Semantic Kernel v1.20 (.NET) 中提供的新函数调用功能。新功能融合了现有函数调用的最佳部分（例如易用性），并通过使其更具可扩展性和可重用性对其进行了改进。函数调用允许将插件描述传递到模型中[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【More on the mysterious [default_interface] attribute in Windows Runtime classes】有关 Windows 运行时类中神秘的 [default_interface] 属性的更多信息</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240918-00/?p=110279</link>
      <description>【Forcing you to make a choice.】强迫你做出选择。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Multi-Project Launch Configuration】多项目启动配置</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/multi-project-launch-configuration</link>
      <description>【Are you tired of the hassle of manually configuring your development environment every time you want to launch multiple projects? We&amp;#8217;ve heard your feedback and are thrilled to announce a feature in Visual Studio that simplifies your workflow. The Multi-Project Launch Configuration feature in Visual Studio allows developers to set up and save profiles for [&amp;hellip;]】您是否厌倦了每次要启动多个项目时手动配置开发环境的麻烦？我们已听到您的反馈，并很高兴地宣布 Visual Studio 中的一项功能可以简化您的工作流程。 Visual Studio 中的多项目启动配置功能允许开发人员设置和保存配置文件 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 16:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing the new Python Data Science Extension Pack for VS Code】宣布推出适用于 VS Code 的新 Python 数据科学扩展包</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/announcing-the-new-python-data-science-extension-pack-for-vs-code</link>
      <description>【We&amp;#8217;re thrilled to announce the launch of the new Python Data Science Extension Pack for Visual Studio Code! This powerful pack brings together some of the most popular and essential VS Code extensions, making it your one-stop shop for all things data science in Python. What&amp;#8217;s Inside? Our extension pack is designed to streamline your data [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布推出适用于 Visual Studio Code 的新 Python 数据科学扩展包！这个功能强大的包汇集了一些最流行和最重要的 VS Code 扩展，使其成为您使用 Python 进行数据科学的一站式商店。里面有什么？我们的扩展包旨在简化您的数据[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 23:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Boosting Azure DevOps Security with GHAS Code Scanning】通过 GHAS 代码扫描增强 Azure DevOps 安全性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/premier-developer/boosting-azure-devops-security-with-ghas-code-scanning</link>
      <description>【Debjyoti Ganguly shares insights on the security benefits and configuration of GHAS Code Scanning with Azure DevOps. Boosting Azure DevOps Security with GHAS Code Scanning Code scanning, a pipeline-based tool available in GitHub Advanced Security, is designed to detect code vulnerabilities and bugs within the source code of ADO (Azure DevOps) repositories. Utilizing CodeQL as [&amp;hellip;]】Debjyoti Ganguly 分享了有关使用 Azure DevOps 进行 GHAS 代码扫描的安全优势和配置的见解。使用 GHAS 代码扫描增强 Azure DevOps 安全性 代码扫描是 GitHub Advanced Security 中提供的基于管道的工具，旨在检测 ADO (Azure DevOps) 存储库源代码中的代码漏洞和错误。使用 CodeQL 作为 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 07:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Improving GitHub Copilot Completions in Visual Studio for C# Developers】为 C# 开发人员改进 Visual Studio 中的 GitHub Copilot 完成情况</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/improving-github-copilot-completions-in-visual-studio-for-csharp-developers</link>
      <description>【Learn about the latest GitHub Copilot improvements for C# developers】了解针对 C# 开发人员的最新 GitHub Copilot 改进</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How to run .NET apps natively on Arm64 devices】如何在 Arm64 设备上本机运行 .NET 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/how-to-run-net-apps-natively-on-arm64-devices</link>
      <description>【Are you developing .NET applications for Arm-based processors? Do you want to take advantage of the performance and power efficiency of running your apps natively on Arm64 devices? If so, you&amp;#8217;ll be happy to hear that Visual Studio 2022 17.11 has a new feature that makes it easier than ever to do just that. Visual [&amp;hellip;]】您是否正在为基于 Arm 的处理器开发 .NET 应用程序？您想利用在 Arm64 设备上本地运行应用程序的性能和能效吗？如果是这样，您会很高兴听到 Visual Studio 2022 17.11 有一项新功能，可以让您比以往更轻松地做到这一点。视觉的 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 10:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>