<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlocking new possibilities: Microsoft AI, database, and identity products receive authorization for Top Secret workloads】释放新的可能性：Microsoft AI、数据库和身份产品获得绝密工作负载的授权</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azuregov/unlocking-new-possibilities</link>
      <description>【Microsoft’s leading AI capabilities are being used across industries to enhance data analysis, bolster security, and support key business priorities. Our U.S. Government customers and authorized partners consistently share that they are ready and eager to apply these same tools to serve their critical missions, and Microsoft is committed to delivering the breadth of our [&amp;hellip;]】微软领先的人工智能功能正在跨行业使用，以增强数据分析、增强安全性并支持关键业务优先事项。我们的美国政府客户和授权合作伙伴始终表示，他们已准备好并渴望应用这些相同的工具来完成其关键任务，而 Microsoft 致力于提供我们广泛的 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Building Multi-Agent Systems with Multi-Models in Semantic Kernel – Part 1】客座博客：在语义内核中构建具有多模型的多代理系统 - 第 1 部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-building-multi-agent-systems-with-multi-models-in-semantic-kernel-part-1</link>
      <description>【Today I want to welcome back Arafat Tehsin, who’s a Microsoft Most Valuable Professional (MVP) for AI. He’s written an article we’re sharing below, focused on Building Multi-Agent Systems with Multi-Models in Semantic Kernel. We’ll turn it over to Arafat to share more! Imagine running a restaurant. Each of your team member, from the chef [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我要欢迎 Arafat Tehsin 回来，他是微软人工智能领域最有价值专家 (MVP)。他写了一篇我们在下面分享的文章，重点是在语义内核中使用多模型构建多代理系统。我们将把它交给阿拉法特来分享更多！想象一下经营一家餐馆。您的每个团队成员，从厨师 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 00:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Automate app compliance with ACAT】自动执行应用程序符合 ACAT 的要求</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/automate-app-compliance-with-acat</link>
      <description>【Learn how you can define the compliance boundary for your Microsoft 365 application on Azure and AWS with the App Compliance Automation Tool (ACAT) for Microsoft 365.】了解如何使用适用于 Microsoft 365 的应用程序合规性自动化工具 (ACAT) 定义 Azure 和 AWS 上的 Microsoft 365 应用程序的合规性边界。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【In a C++ class template specialization, how can I call the unspecialized version of a method?】在 C++ 类模板特化中，如何调用方法的非特化版本？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250116-00/?p=110773</link>
      <description>【You can&#39;t talk about things that might exist, so instead talk about things that do.】你不能谈论可能存在的事情，所以要谈论确实存在的事情。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Tips and Tricks for Adopting GitHub Copilot at Scale】大规模采用 GitHub Copilot 的提示和技巧</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/adopting-github-copilot-at-scale</link>
      <description>【Introduction​ Adopting GitHub Copilot at scale can be a game-changer for many development teams (especially large or distributed teams). This blog post provides best practices, actionable tips, and tricks to ensure a successful adoption of GitHub Copilot to ensure successful adoption at scale, foster engagement, and maximize the return on investment (ROI). 1. Raise Awareness [&amp;hellip;]】简介​ 大规模采用 GitHub Copilot 可以改变许多开发团队（尤其是大型或分布式团队）的游戏规则。这篇博文提供了最佳实践、可操作的提示和技巧，以确保 GitHub Copilot 的成功采用，从而确保大规模成功采用、促进参与并最大限度地提高投资回报 (ROI)。 1.提高意识[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 18:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How does Get­User­Default­Geo­Name choose between ISO 3166-1 and UN M.49 codes?】GetUserDefaultGeoName 如何在 ISO 3166-1 和 UN M.49 代码之间进行选择？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250115-59/?p=110769</link>
      <description>【Clarifying the behavior.】澄清行为。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Agentic AI Explained: A Philosophical Framework for Understanding AI Agents】代理人工智能解释：理解人工智能代理的哲学框架</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/agentic-philosophers</link>
      <description>【Imagine an AI-powered world where assistance goes beyond tasks &amp;#8212; where intelligent agents debate, learn and collaborate with the wisdom of history&amp;#8217;s greatest minds. What if Socrates, Plato, and Aristotle could step into the digital age, engaging in vibrant discussions and offering their timeless perspectives. In this article, I&amp;#8217;ll delve into how AI agents can [&amp;hellip;]】想象一下一个人工智能驱动的世界，其中的援助超越了任务——智能代理与历史上最伟大思想家的智慧进行辩论、学习和协作。如果苏格拉底、柏拉图和亚里士多德能够进入数字时代，参与充满活力的讨论并提供他们永恒的观点，结果会怎样呢？在本文中，我将深入探讨人工智能代理如何[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 07:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Our Favorite NEW Visual Studio Features of 2024】我们最喜欢的 2024 年 Visual Studio 新功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/our-favorite-new-visual-studio-features-of-2024</link>
      <description>【Last year, the Visual Studio team delivered many new developer-focused improvements and AI integrations, many of which came directly from your feedback on Developer Community. In this post, we highlight the team’s favorite features from 2024 that boost productivity, streamline workflows, and enhance your coding experience. Let’s dive in! Image Hover Preview: See your images [&amp;hellip;]】去年，Visual Studio 团队提供了许多以开发人员为中心的新改进和 AI 集成，其中许多直接来自您对开发人员社区的反馈。在这篇文章中，我们重点介绍了 2024 年团队最喜欢的功能，这些功能可提高生产力、简化工作流程并增强您的编码体验。让我们深入了解一下！图像悬停预览：查看您的图像[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customer Case Study: Pushing the Boundaries of Multi-Agent AI Collaboration with ServiceNow and Microsoft Semantic Kernel】客户案例研究：利用 ServiceNow 和 Microsoft 语义内核突破多代理 AI 协作的界限</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-pushing-the-boundaries-of-multi-agent-ai-collaboration-with-servicenow-and-microsoft-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【The Journey to Multi-Agent Innovation At ServiceNow, we embarked on an ambitious journey to redefine how AI systems collaborate in enterprise environments. Through our partnership with Microsoft, we set out to create something beyond traditional integration – a true multi-agent system across platform that could work effectively alongside human teams. While NowAssist and Microsoft Copilot [&amp;hellip;]】多代理创新之旅 在 ServiceNow，我们踏上了雄心勃勃的旅程，重新定义人工智能系统在企业环境中的协作方式。通过与微软的合作，我们着手创建超越传统集成的东西——一个真正的跨平台多代理系统，可以与人类团队一起有效地工作。而 NowAssist 和 Microsoft Copilot [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Meet the .NET Team at NDC London 2025】在 2025 年伦敦 NDC 上与 .NET 团队见面</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/meet-the-dotnet-team-at-ndc-london-2025</link>
      <description>【Meet the .NET team at NDC London 2025 to explore the latest in .NET 9, Azure, and AI-powered development through keynotes, sessions, and 1:1 meetups.】在 NDC London 2025 上与 .NET 团队见面，通过主题演讲、会议和 1:1 聚会来探索 .NET 9、Azure 和 AI 驱动的开发的最新动态。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>