<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Roadmap for AI in Visual Studio (October)】Visual Studio的AI路线图（10月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/roadmap-for-ai-in-visual-studio-october</link>
      <description>【Today, we’re excited to share our public roadmap, which outlines the next steps in evolving Visual Studio with AI-powered agentic experiences. With every month, we aim to deliver smarter, faster, and more intuitive tools that enhance your coding experience. Disclaimer: The items outlined here represent ongoing work for the month. They】今天，我们很高兴分享我们的公共路线图，该路线图概述了通过AI驱动的代理体验发展视觉工作室的下一步。我们每个月都打算提供更智能，更快，更直观的工具，以增强您的编码体验。免责声明：此处概述的项目代表了当月正在进行的工作。他们</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Can we get weak functions for static linking? The Visual C++ compiler says &#34;We have weak functions at home&#34;】我们可以获得静态链接的弱功能吗？视觉C ++编译器说：“我们在家中的功能较弱”</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251003-00/?p=111650</link>
      <description>【The ELF object file has this thing called &#34;weak functions&#34;. These are functions present in a library that are used by the linker to resolve a symbol only if the main program doesn&#39;t provide a resolution for them. The Visual C++ compiler doesn&#39;t have &#34;weak functions&#34; in this sense, but that doesn&#39;t mean that equivalent functionality】精灵对象文件具有称为“弱函数”的东西。这些是库中存在的函数，仅当主程序无法为其提供分辨率时，链接器使用的函数才能解析符号。从这个意义上讲，Visual C ++编译器没有“弱功能”，但这并不意味着等效功能</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Lab to Live: A Blueprint for a Voice-Powered AI Sales Coach】从实验室到现场：语音动力AI销售教练的蓝图</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/from-lab-to-live-a-blueprint-for-a-voice-powered-ai-sales-coach</link>
      <description>【Until recently, building real-time voice AI for production was challenging. Developers faced hurdles such as managing audio streams and ensuring low-latency performance. That landscape is changing. The】直到最近，建立实时声音AI进行生产还是具有挑战性的。开发人员面临诸如管理音频流和确保低延迟性能之类的障碍。景观正在发生变化。这</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【VS Live! Orlando – Your Ultimate Learning Adventure】VS Live！奥兰多 - 您的最终学习冒险</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-live-orlando-2025</link>
      <description>【Imagine swapping stories with fellow developers over dinner as the Florida sun sets, then beginning the next morning with a stroll past the resort’s palm-lined walkways before catching your first session across】想象一下佛罗里达太阳的景点与其他开发人员在晚餐时交换故事，然后在第二天早上开始漫步，经过度假村的棕榈衬里人行道，然后抓住了您的第一届会议</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (September 2025)】Azure SDK发布（2025年9月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-september-2025</link>
      <description>【Thank you for your interest in the new Azure SDKs! We release new features, improvements, and bug fixes every month. Subscribe to our Azure SDK Blog RSS Feed to get notified when a new release is available. You can find links to packages, code, and docs on our】感谢您对新的Azure SDK的关注！我们每月发布新功能，改进和错误修复。订阅我们的Azure SDK博客RSS feed，以便在有新版本时通知。您可以在我们的包装，代码和文档中找到链接</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The problem with inferring from a function call operator is that there may be more than one】从函数调用操作员推断出的问题是，可能有多个</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251002-00/?p=111647</link>
      <description>【Some time ago, I wrote briefly on writing a helper class for generating a particular category of C callback wrappers around C++ methods. This particular】不久前，我简要撰写了为编写辅助课程的文章，用于在C ++方法上生成特定类别的C回调包装器。这个特别</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Leveraging Fabric Eventhouse to Store Great Expectations Validation Results】利用Fabric Eventhouse存储良好的期望验证结果</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/leveraging-fabric-eventhouse-to-store-great-expectations-validation-results</link>
      <description>【In a previous post, we explored how to perform data validations with Great Expectations (GX) in Microsoft Fabric. We walked through how to set up the validation framework and ensure your data meets the quality standards expected. Now, in thi】在上一篇文章中，我们探索了如何在Microsoft Fabric中以良好的期望（GX）执行数据验证。我们浏览了如何设置验证框架，并确保您的数据符合预期的质量标准。现在，在蒂</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (September 2025)】VCPKG的新功能（2025年9月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-september-2025</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2025.09.17 registry release, the 2025-08-29 and】此博客文章总结了VCPKG软件包管理器的更改，作为2025.09.17注册表版本，2025-08-29和</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The $150 Secret Hiding in Plain Sight】$ 150的秘密隐藏在朴素的视线中</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/unlock-vss-benefits-myvisualstudio</link>
      <description>【Picture this: I’m standing in front of 400+ developers at Visual Studio Live! Redmond, right here on the Microsoft campus in Building 33, about to reveal what I call the hidden value of a Visual Studio subscription. I pull up a simple question on the screen:】图片：我站在Visual Studio Live的400多个开发人员面前！雷德蒙德（Redmond），就在33号建筑物的Microsoft校园里，即将揭示我所说的Visual Studio订阅的隐藏价值。我在屏幕上提起一个简单的问题：</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Microsoft Agent Framework (Preview): Making AI Agents Simple for Every Developer】引入Microsoft Agent Framework（预览）：使每个开发人员简单地使AI代理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-microsoft-agent-framework-preview</link>
      <description>【Building AI agents shouldn&#39;t be rocket science. Yet many developers find themselves wrestling with complex orchestration logic, struggling to connect multiple AI models, or spending weeks building hosting infrastructure just to get a simple agent into production. What if building an AI agent could be as straightforward as creating a web API】建造AI代理不应是火箭科学。然而，许多开发人员发现自己以复杂的编排逻辑来搏斗，努力连接多个AI模型，或者花几周的时间建立托管基础架构，只是为了使一个简单的代理进入生产。如果构建AI代理与创建Web API一样直接</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>