<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Why does my &lt;KBD&gt;Ctrl&lt;/KBD&gt;+&lt;KBD&gt;M&lt;/KBD&gt; accelerator key activate when I press the &lt;KBD&gt;Enter&lt;/KBD&gt; key?】为什么当我按 &lt;KBD&gt;Enter&lt;/KBD&gt; 键时，我的 &lt;KBD&gt;Ctrl&lt;/KBD&gt;+&lt;KBD&gt;M&lt;/KBD&gt; 加速键会激活？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251224-00/?p=111908</link>
      <description>【A customer didn&#39;t understand why their Win32 accelerator key for Ctrl+M was triggering spuriously. Specifically, it was triggering when the user hit the Enter key, which is nothing like the Ctrl+M two-key combination. They defined their accelerator table like this: IDA】客户不明白为什么他们的 Ctrl+M 的 Win32 加速键会被错误地触发。具体来说，它是在用户按下 Enter 键时触发的，这与 Ctrl+M 两键组合完全不同。他们这样定义加速器表：IDA</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【When irate product support customers demand to speak to Bill Gates】当愤怒的产品支持客户要求与比尔·盖茨交谈时</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251223-00/?p=111896</link>
      <description>【A colleague of mine who used to work in product support told me that they had a procedure if a customer became irate and demanded to speak with Bill Gates. (This was, of course, back in the days when Bill Gates still ran the company.) The product support technician would apologize for not resolving the problem to the customer&#39;s sati】我的一位曾经在产品支持部门工作的同事告诉我，如果客户生气并要求与比尔·盖茨交谈，他们有一套程序。 （当然，这是在比尔盖茨仍在经营公司的时代。）产品支持技术人员会因为没有解决客户满意的问题而道歉。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SharePoint Framework (SPFx) roadmap update – December 2025】SharePoint 框架 (SPFx) 路线图更新 – 2025 年 12 月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/sharepoint-framework-spfx-roadmap-update-december-2025</link>
      <description>【As we close out 2025, we want to pause and reflect on what has been an extraordinary year for the SharePoint Framework (SPFx). We continue to be humbled by the momentum of the platform and the scale of impact it enables across Microsoft 365. Tens of millions of users】在 2025 年即将结束之际，我们想停下来思考一下对于 SharePoint 框架 (SPFx) 来说是不平凡的一年。我们继续对该平台的势头及其在 Microsoft 365 中产生的影响规模感到谦卑。数千万用户</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How AI fixed my procrastination】人工智能如何解决我的拖延症</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/how-ai-fixed-my-procrastination</link>
      <description>【I struggled to get started. For ages, I kept putting off building this website, creating a new programming language for Visual Studio, and coming up with fresh color themes. Each project looked overwhelming, and I couldn’t find the time or motivation to jump in. It all just felt like too much at once. But when a national holiday gave me a】我很难开始。多年来，我一直推迟构建这个网站、为 Visual Studio 创建新的编程语言以及提出新的颜色主题。每个项目看起来都让人不知所措，我找不到时间或动力去投入。这一切感觉一下子太多了。但当国庆节给了我一个</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【All the other cool languages have &lt;CODE&gt;try&lt;/CODE&gt;...&lt;CODE&gt;finally&lt;/CODE&gt;. C++ says &#34;We have &lt;CODE&gt;try&lt;/CODE&gt;...&lt;CODE&gt;finally&lt;/CODE&gt; at home.&#34;】所有其他很酷的语言都有&lt;code&gt;尝试&lt;/code&gt;...&lt;code&gt;最后&lt;/code&gt;。 C++ 说“我们已经&lt;CODE&gt;尝试了&lt;/CODE&gt;...&lt;CODE&gt;终于&lt;/CODE&gt;在家了。”</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251222-00/?p=111890</link>
      <description>【Many languages¹ that have exceptions also have a finally clause, so you can write try { ⟦ stuff ⟧ } finally { always(); } A quick checks shows that this control structure exists in Java, C#, Python, JavaScript, but not C++. C++ says, &#34;We have try...finally at home.&#34;】许多有异常的语言 1 也有一个 finally 子句，所以你可以写 try { ⟦ stuff ⟧ }finally {always();快速检查表明该控制结构存在于 Java、C#、Python、JavaScript 中，但不存在于 C++ 中。 C++ 说：“我们已经尝试过了……终于到家了。”</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The New Test Run Hub is Going Generally Available!】新的测试运行中心即将全面上线！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/the-new-test-run-hub-is-going-generally-available</link>
      <description>【Delivering high-quality software requires clarity, speed, and collaboration. That’s why we introduced the New Test Run Hub in Azure Test Plans. A modern, streamlined experience designed to make test execution and analysis fast and】交付高质量的软件需要清晰度、速度和协作。这就是我们在 Azure 测试计划中引入新测试运行中心的原因。现代化、简化的体验，旨在使测试执行和分析快速且可靠</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Developer CLI (azd) Dec 2025 - Extensions Enhancements, Foundry Rebranding, and Azure Pipelines Improvements】Azure 开发人员 CLI (azd) 2025 年 12 月 - 扩展增强、Foundry 品牌重塑和 Azure Pipelines 改进</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-developer-cli-azd-december-2025</link>
      <description>【Welcome to the December 2025 edition of the Azure Developer CLI (azd) release blog—our final release of the year! This post covers releases 1.22.0 through 1.22.5, wrapping up 2025. To share your feedback and questions, join the December release discussion on GitHub.】欢迎来到 2025 年 12 月版的 Azure 开发人员 CLI (azd) 发布博客 - 我们今年的最后一个版本！本文涵盖 1.22.0 至 1.22.5 版本，截至 2025 年。要分享您的反馈和问题，请加入 GitHub 上的 12 月版本讨论。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Work item linking for Advanced Security alerts now available】高级安全警报的工作项链接现已可用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/devops/work-item-linking-for-advanced-security-alerts-now-available</link>
      <description>【Security vulnerabilities don&#39;t fix themselves. Someone needs to track them, prioritize them, and actually ship the fix. If you&#39;ve ever tried to manage security alerts alongside your regular sprint work, though, you know the friction: you&#39;re looking at an alert in one tab, switching to your backlog in another, trying to remember which vulner】安全漏洞不会自行修复。需要有人跟踪它们，确定它们的优先级，并实际交付修复程序。不过，如果您曾经尝试在常规冲刺工作的同时管理安全警报，那么您就会知道其中的摩擦：您在一个选项卡中查看警报，然后切换到另一个选项卡中的积压工作，并试图记住哪个漏洞</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A shortcut gives me a weird path for a program shortcut that doesn&#39;t point to the executable, so what is it?】快捷方式为我提供了一个不指向可执行文件的程序快捷方式的奇怪路径，那么它是什么？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251219-00/?p=111885</link>
      <description>【Say you have a shortcut file and you want to see what its target is. The natural thing to do is to call IShellLink::GetPath, which returns S_FALSE if the shortcut does not target a path, or returns S_OK and a path to the target. But for some shortcuts, it returns S_OK but produces a】假设您有一个快捷方式文件，并且您想查看其目标是什么。自然的做法是调用 IShellLink::GetPath，如果快捷方式不以路径为目标，则返回 S_FALSE，或者返回 S_OK 和目标路径。但对于某些快捷方式，它返回 S_OK 但会生成</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s new in Microsoft Foundry | October and November 2025】Microsoft Foundry 的新增功能 | 2025 年 10 月和 11 月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/whats-new-in-microsoft-foundry-oct-nov-2025</link>
      <description>【TL;DR Move from prototype to production in hours, not weeks: The new Microsoft Agent Framework and Hosted Agents let you build, test, and deploy multi-agent AI systems with enterprise-grade security—no Kubernetes or container headaches. Orchestrate any model, anywhere: Model】TL;DR 在数小时而不是数周内从原型转向生产：新的 Microsoft 代理框架和托管代理可让您构建、测试和部署具有企业级安全性的多代理 AI 系统，而无需遇到 Kubernetes 或容器问题。随时随地编排任何模型：模型</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 04:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>