<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【January 2026 Insiders (version 1.109)】2026 年 1 月 Insider（版本 1.109）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/january-2026-insiders-(version-1.109)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code January 2026 Release (1.109). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 1 月版本 (1.109) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Deprecation notice: Teams Live Events meeting creation via Microsoft Graph】弃用通知：通过 Microsoft Graph 创建 Teams Live Events 会议</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/deprecation-notice-teams-live-events-meeting-creation-via-microsoft-graph</link>
      <description>【We’re announcing an important change for developers using Microsoft Graph APIs to create Teams Live Events. Starting March 31, 2026, the beta endpoint will no longer support the isBroadcast property of the on】我们宣布针对使用 Microsoft Graph API 创建 Teams Live Events 的开发人员进行一项重要更改。从 2026 年 3 月 31 日开始，Beta 端点将不再支持 on 的 isBroadcast 属性</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 16:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Part 2: Building a Python CRUD API with Azure Functions and Azure Cosmos DB】第 2 部分：使用 Azure Functions 和 Azure Cosmos DB 构建 Python CRUD API</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/part-2-building-a-python-crud-api-with-azure-functions-and-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【Series: Building Serverless Applications with Azure Functions and Azure Cosmos DB In the first post of this series, we focused on establishing the fundamentals of serverless architectur】系列：使用 Azure Functions 和 Azure Cosmos DB 构建无服务器应用程序 在本系列的第一篇文章中，我们重点介绍了无服务器架构的基础知识</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Performance improvements to MEF-based editor productivity extensions】基于 MEF 的编辑器生产力扩展的性能改进</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/performance-improvements-to-mef-based-editor-productivity-extensions</link>
      <description>【If you use editor productivity extensions for Visual Studio 2026, there&#39;s good news—they can now load faster! Extension developers with existing MEF-based editor productivity extensions should read this blog to learn about recent changes and how they might be affected. 】如果您使用 Visual Studio 2026 的编辑器生产力扩展，那么有个好消息 - 它们现在可以更快地加载！拥有现有基于 MEF 的编辑器生产力扩展的扩展开发人员应该阅读此博客，以了解最近的更改以及它们可能受到的影响。 </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Some small stories about the giant satellite dish antenna that was behind Microsoft Building 11】关于微软 11 号楼背后的巨型卫星天线的一些小故事</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260203-00/?p=112035</link>
      <description>【Back in the day, if you wandered into the parking area behind Building 11 on the original Redmond Microsoft campus, you would find a very large satellite dish antenna. This antenna was used for receiving video signals, such as cable television feeds for distribution to the Redmond campus. One purpose was to provide cable TV service for inte】以前，如果您漫步走进原雷蒙德微软园区 11 号楼后面的停车场，您会发现一个非常大的碟形卫星天线。该天线用于接收视频信号，例如分发到雷德蒙德园区的有线电视信号。目的之一是为国际互联网提供有线电视服务</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java OpenJDK January 2026 Patch &amp; Security Update】Java OpenJDK 2026 年 1 月补丁和安全更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/java-openjdk-january-2026-patch-security-update</link>
      <description>【Hello Java customers! We are happy to announce the latest January 2026 patch &amp;amp; security update release for the Microsoft Build of OpenJDK. Download and install the binaries today. OpenJDK 25.0.2 OpenJDK 21.0.10 OpenJDK 17.0.18 OpenJDK 11.0.30】Java 客户您好！我们很高兴地宣布 Microsoft Build of OpenJDK 的最新 2026 年 1 月补丁和安全更新版本。立即下载并安装二进制文件。 OpenJDK 25.0.2 OpenJDK 21.0.10 OpenJDK 17.0.18 OpenJDK 11.0.30</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Cosmos DB Data Explorer now supports Dark Mode】Azure Cosmos DB 数据资源管理器现在支持深色模式</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/azure-cosmos-db-data-explorer-now-supports-dark-mode</link>
      <description>【If you spend time in the Azure Portal’s using Azure Cosmos DB Data Explorer, you know it’s a “lots of screens, lots of tabs, lots of work happening” kind of place. So I’m excited to share a small upgrade that makes a big difference: Dark Mode is now supported in Cosmos DB Data Explorer.】如果您使用 Azure Cosmos DB 数据资源管理器在 Azure 门户中花费时间，您就会知道这是一个“有很多屏幕、很多选项卡、发生大量工作”的地方。因此，我很高兴与大家分享一个带来重大改变的小升级：Cosmos DB 数据资源管理器现在支持深色模式。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 20:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Studying compiler error messages closely: Input file paths】仔细研究编译器错误消息：输入文件路径</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260202-00/?p=112027</link>
      <description>【A colleague was working in a project that used a number of data files to configure how the program worked. They wanted one portion of the configuration file to be included only if a particular build flag was set. Let&#39;s say that the configuration file is C:\repos\contoso\config\Contoso.config. &amp;】一位同事正在从事一个项目，该项目使用多个数据文件来配置程序的工作方式。他们希望仅在设置了特定构建标志时才包含配置文件的一部分。假设配置文件是 C:\repos\contoso\config\Contoso.config。 &amp;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build AI Agents with Claude Agent SDK and Microsoft Agent Framework】使用 Claude Agent SDK 和 Microsoft Agent 框架构建 AI 代理</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/build-ai-agents-with-claude-agent-sdk-and-microsoft-agent-framework</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Agent Framework now integrates with the Claude Agent SDK, enabling you to build AI agents powered by Claude&#39;s full agentic capabilities. This integration brings together the Agent Framework&#39;s consistent agent abstraction with Claude&#39;s powerful features, including fil】Microsoft Agent Framework 现在与 Claude Agent SDK 集成，使您能够构建由 Claude 完整代理功能支持的 AI 代理。这种集成将代理框架的一致代理抽象与 Claude 的强大功能结合在一起，包括 fil</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 19:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why not store the &lt;CODE&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/CODE&gt; reference count as a hidden allocation next to the &lt;CODE&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/CODE&gt;?】为什么不将 &lt;code&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/code&gt; 引用计数存储为 &lt;code&gt;SAFEARRAY&lt;/code&gt; 旁边的隐藏分配？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260130-00/?p=112025</link>
      <description>【When I described how Safe­Array­Add­Ref keeps its reference count in a side table, commenter Koro Unhallowed wondered】当我描述 SafeArrayAddRef 如何将其引用计数保存在侧表中时，评论者 Koro Unhallowed 表示想知道</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>