<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【November 2025 Insiders (version 1.107)】2025 年 11 月 Insider（版本 1.107）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/november-2025-insiders-(version-1.107)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code November 2025 Release (1.107). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2025 年 11 月版本 (1.107) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Foundry MCP Server (preview) in the cloud, speeding up AI development with Microsoft Foundry】宣布推出云端 Foundry MCP 服务器（预览版），利用 Microsoft Foundry 加速 AI 开发</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/announcing-foundry-mcp-server-preview-speeding-up-ai-dev-with-microsoft-foundry</link>
      <description>【MCP (Model Context Protocol) is a standard protocol that enables AI agents to securely connect with apps, data, and systems, supporting easy interoperability and seamless platform expansion. At Ignite, Microsoft Foundry introduced Foundry Too】MCP（模型上下文协议）是一种标准协议，使人工智能代理能够安全地连接应用程序、数据和系统，支持轻松的互操作性和无缝平台扩展。在 Ignite 大会上，Microsoft Foundry 推出了 Foundry Too</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Data Ingestion Building Blocks (Preview)】介绍数据摄取构建块（预览版）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-data-ingestion-building-blocks-preview</link>
      <description>【When building AI applications, context is key. AI models have a knowledge cutoff and do not have access to your personal or company data by default. To generate high-quality answers, AI apps need two things: Access to high-quality data The ability to surface the right information at the right time】在构建人工智能应用程序时，上下文是关键。 AI 模型存在知识限制，默认情况下无法访问您的个人或公司数据。为了生成高质量的答案，人工智能应用程序需要满足两个条件： 访问高质量的数据 能够在正确的时间呈现正确的信息</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio November Update – Visual Studio 2026, Cloud Agent Preview, and more】Visual Studio 11 月更新 – Visual Studio 2026、云代理预览版等</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-november-update-visual-studio-2026-cloud-agent-preview-and-more</link>
      <description>【】</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why changing keyboard shortcuts in Visual Studio isn’t as simple as it seems】为什么在 Visual Studio 中更改键盘快捷键并不像看起来那么简单</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/why-changing-keyboard-shortcuts-in-visual-studio-isnt-as-simple-as-it-seems</link>
      <description>【A straight look at what’s behind the keys We’ve all tried unlearning a keyboard shortcut - it feels like forgetting how to breathe. Muscle memory doesn’t mess around. We wrestle with this every time someone suggest a “quick” shortcut change. It’s not just editing a keybinding but navigating a history that makes Visual Stu】直视按键背后的内容我们都尝试过忘记键盘快捷键 - 感觉就像忘记了如何呼吸。肌肉记忆不会乱七八糟。每当有人建议“快速”改变捷径时，我们都会陷入困境。这不仅仅是编辑键绑定，而是浏览历史记录，这使得 Visual Stu</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How do I check whether the user has permission to create files in a directory?】如何检查用户是否有权限在目录中创建文件？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251203-00/?p=111836</link>
      <description>【A customer wanted to accept a directory entered by the user and verify that the user has permission to create files in that folder. The directory itself might not even be on a local hard drive; it could be a DVD or a remote network volume. They tried calling Get­File­Attributes, but all they were told was that it was a direct】客户想要接受用户输入的目录并验证用户是否有权在该文件夹中创建文件。该目录本身甚至可能不在本地硬盘上；它可以是 DVD 或远程网络卷。他们尝试调用 GetFileAttributes，但他们只被告知这是一个直接的</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Pipe dreams to pipeline realities: an Aspire Pipelines story】从梦想到管道现实：Aspire Pipelines 的故事</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspire/aspire-pipelines</link>
      <description>【Liked this blog post? It was originally posted on Safia Abdalla&#39;s blog, https://blog.safia.rocks/, check out more content there! OK, sit down folks, because this one is gonna be a long one. This is the all-encompassing blog post about the thing I&#39;v】喜欢这篇博文吗？它最初发布在 Safia Abdalla 的博客上，https://blog.safia.rocks/，查看更多内容！好吧，各位坐下，因为这会是一篇很长的文章。这是关于我的事情的包罗万象的博客文章</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 14:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.25.5-1 and 1.24.11-1 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.25.5-1 和 1.24.11-1 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-25-5-1-and-1-24-11-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new release of the Microsoft build of Go including security fixes is now available for download. For more information about this release and the changes included, see the table below: Microsoft Release Upstream Tag】包含安全修复程序的 Microsoft Go 版本新版本现已可供下载。有关此版本及其所包含更改的更多信息，请参阅下表： Microsoft 版本上游标签</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 04:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【⭐Upcoming Virtual Event⭐ AI Dev Days, Level-Up Your AI Skills with Microsoft Reactor】⭐即将举行的虚拟活动⭐ AI 开发日，使用 Microsoft Reactor 提升您的 AI 技能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/ai-dev-days-december-2025</link>
      <description>【】</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the VS Code Insiders Podcast】VS Code Insider 播客简介</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/introducing-the-vs-code-insiders-podcast</link>
      <description>【The VS Code Insiders Podcast is your insider&#39;s guide to the features, decisions, and people shaping the future of Visual Studio Code. Read the full article】VS Code 内部人士播客是您的内部人士指南，了解塑造 Visual Studio Code 未来的功能、决策和人员。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>