<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Unlock new possibilities for AI Evaluations for .NET】解锁.NET的AI评估的新可能性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/start-using-the-microsoft-ai-evaluations-library-today</link>
      <description>【Microsoft.Extensions.AI.Evaluations library is now open source, and a new Azure DevOps plug-in is available to make reporting in your CI pipelines easier than ever.】Microsoft.extensions.ai.AI.Evaluations库现在是开源的，并且可以使用新的Azure DevOps插件来使您的CI管道中的报告比以往任何时候都更加容易。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microspeak: Respin】Microspeak：Respin</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250304-00/?p=110929</link>
      <description>【Spin it up again, baby.】宝贝，再次旋转。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【I tried to subscribe to a C++/WinRT event, but my callback was never called】我试图订阅C ++/Winrt活动，但我的回调从未被打电话给</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250305-00/?p=110934</link>
      <description>【Check how you registered your event handler.】检查您如何注册活动处理程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python in Visual Studio Code – March 2025 Release】Visual Studio代码中的Python  -  2025年3月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/python-in-visual-studio-code-march-2025-release</link>
      <description>【The March 2025 release of the Python and Jupyter extensions for Visual Studio Code are now available. This month&#39;s updates include improvements to shell integration, a new setting to change auto test discovery file patterns, inline values shown on hover, and more!】2025年3月的Python和Jupyter扩展名的版本现已提供。本月的更新包括改进Shell集成，一种新的设置，以更改自动测试发现文件模式，悬停在悬停的内联值等等！</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 19:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: LLMAgentOps Toolkit for Semantic Kernel】来宾博客：语义内核的llmagentops工具包</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-llmagentops-toolkit-for-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Today the Semantic Kernel team is excited to welcome a guest author, Prabal Deb to share his work. LLMAgentOps Toolkit is repository that contains basic structure of LLM Agent based application built on top of the Semantic Kernel Python version. The toolkit is designed to be a starting point for data scientists and developers for experimentation [&amp;hellip;]】今天，语义内核团队很高兴欢迎一位客座作家Prabal Deb分享他的作品。 LLMAGENTOPSTOOLKIT是存储库，它包含基于LLM代理的基于语义内核Python版本的基本结构。该工具包被设计为数据科学家和开发人员进行实验的起点[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 20:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Integrating Model Context Protocol Tools with Semantic Kernel: A Step-by-Step Guide】将模型上下文协议工具与语义内核集成：逐步指南</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/integrating-model-context-protocol-tools-with-semantic-kernel-a-step-by-step-guide</link>
      <description>【This post describes how to use Model Context Protocol tools with Semantic Kernel. Model Context Protocol (MCP) is an open protocol that standardizes how applications provide context to LLMs. MCP standardizes the connection between AI models and various data sources and tools. The Model Context Protocol is significant because it enhances the way AI models [&amp;hellip;]】这篇文章描述了如何使用语义内核使用模型上下文协议工具。模型上下文协议（MCP）是一个开放协议，标准化应用程序如何为LLM提供上下文。 MCP标准化AI模型与各种数据源和工具之间的连接。模型上下文协议很重要，因为它增强了AI模型的方式[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 15:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI in Action — How to build scalable RAG-enabled AI apps】AI在行动中 - 如何构建可扩展的RAG启用AI应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/engineering-at-microsoft/ai-in-action-how-to-build-scalable-rag-enabled-ai-apps</link>
      <description>【For developers, the emphasis on building intelligence into apps has never been clearer. Over the next three years, 92% of companies plan on investing in AI to achieve business outcomes like enhancing productivity and delivering better customer service. At Microsoft, developers and engineers are pushing the boundaries of AI at scale, crafting applications that harness [&amp;hellip;]】对于开发人员而言，重点是将情报构建到应用程序中从未更清楚。在接下来的三年中，有92％的公司计划投资AI，以实现业务成果，例如提高生产率并提供更好的客户服务。在微软，开发人员和工程师正在大规模推动AI的界限，制作应用程序[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Publishing, Managing and Securing: Building with Microsoft Copilot Studio】出版，管理和确保：与Microsoft Copilot Studio建造</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/publishing-managing-and-securing-building-with-microsoft-copilot-studio</link>
      <description>【If you would like to start building an agent in Microsoft Copilot Studio, don&amp;#8217;t worry we’ve got you covered! In our AI in Action: Building with Copilot Studio series on the Microsoft Power Platform YouTube channel, we have several episodes that guide you through how to get started in building an agent. This blog post [&amp;hellip;]】如果您想开始在Microsoft Copilot Studio中建立代理商，请不要担心我们会为您提供服务！在我们的AI In Action：通过Microsoft Power Platform YouTube频道上的Copilot Studio系列构建中，我们有几集可以指导您完成如何开始建立代理商的过程。这篇博客文章[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New Debugging and Profiling Features in Visual Studio (v17.13)】Visual Studio中的新调试和分析功能（V17.13）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/new-debugging-and-profiling-features-in-visual-studio-v17-13</link>
      <description>【The latest Visual Studio update (v17.13) brings a strong set of debugging and profiling features designed to speed up troubleshooting, making it more efficient. With AI-driven features in this release, variable analysis and data inspection are smarter and more intuitive, and problems are easier to identify and debug. Profiling tool improvements also deliver better support [&amp;hellip;]】最新的Visual Studio Update（V17.13）带来了一系列强大的调试和分析功能，旨在加快故障排除，使其更有效。在此版本中，具有AI-AI-DEMICT，可变分析和数据检查更加智能，更直观，并且问题更容易识别和调试。分析工具改进还提供更好的支持[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 15:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AutoGen and Semantic Kernel, Part 2】Autogen和语义内核，第2部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/semantic-kernel-and-autogen-part-2</link>
      <description>【Following on from our blog post a couple months ago: Microsoft’s Agentic AI Frameworks: AutoGen and Semantic Kernel, Microsoft’s agentic AI story is evolving at a steady pace. Both Azure AI Foundry’s Semantic Kernel and AI Frontier’s AutoGen are designed to empower developers to build advanced multi-agent systems. The AI Frontier’s team is charging ahead [&amp;hellip;]】在几个月前我们的博客文章之后：Microsoft的代理AI框架：Autogen和Sminantic内核，Microsoft的代理AI故事正在以稳定的速度发展。 Azure AI Foundry的语义内核和AI Frontier的Autogen都旨在增强开发人员的能力，以构建先进的多代理系统。 AI Frontier的团队正在向前冲锋[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 17:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>