<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Go 1.24 FIPS changes】Microsoft GO 1.24 FIPS更改</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-24-fips-update</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Go 1.24 ships with many new FIPS-140 related features. Here&#39;s a closer look at the upcoming changes.】Microsoft GO 1.24艘具有许多新的FIPS-140相关功能。这是对即将发生的变化的仔细研究。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 17:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET 9 Networking Improvements】.NET 9网络改进</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-9-networking-improvements</link>
      <description>【Introducing new networking features in .NET 9 including HTTP space, HttpClientFactory, security and more!】在.NET 9中引入新的网络功能，包括HTTP空间，HTTPCLIENTFACTORY，SECURICE等！</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The default C locale is not a very interesting one】默认的C语言环境不是一个非常有趣的地方</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250206-00/?p=110846</link>
      <description>【It barely understands anything.】它几乎不了解任何东西。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Data Studio Retirement】Azure Data Studio退休</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/azure-data-studio-retirement</link>
      <description>【We’re announcing the upcoming retirement of Azure Data Studio (ADS) on February 6, 2025, as we focus on delivering a modern, streamlined SQL development experience. ADS will remain supported until February 28, 2026, giving developers ample time to transition. This decision aligns with our commitment to simplifying SQL development by consolidating efforts on Visual Studio Code (VS Code) with the MSSQL extension, [&amp;hellip;]】我们将于2025年2月6日宣布即将退休的Azure Data Studio（ADS）退休，因为我们专注于提供现代化的SQL SQL开发经验。广告将一直支持到2026年2月28日，为开发人员提供了充足的过渡时间。该决定与我们致力于通过将Visual Studio代码（VS代码）与MSSQL扩展合并的工作来简化SQL开发的承诺相吻合，[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 19:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure Functions vs. Indexers: AI Data Ingestion】Azure功能与索引器：AI数据摄入</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/ise/unlock-ai-search-potential-the-case-for-azure-functions-in-data-ingestion</link>
      <description>【This article compares Azure Functions with pre-built indexers for data ingestion in Azure AI Search, with a focus on using Azure Functions for a flexible, scalable approach. It explores key steps like data migration, index creation, and deployment automation.】本文将Azure功能与预先构建的索引器进行了比较，以在Azure AI搜索中进行数据摄入，重点是将Azure函数用于灵活，可扩展的方法。它探讨了诸如数据迁移，索引创建和部署自动化之类的关键步骤。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Customer Case Study: How preezie’s AI shopping assistant is reshaping Blue Bungalow’s online store】客户案例研究：Preezie的AI购物助理如何重塑Blue Bungalow的在线商店</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/customer-case-study-how-preezies-ai-shopping-assistant-is-reshaping-blue-bungalows-online-store</link>
      <description>【Introduction Blue Bungalow, one of Australia’s leading fashion retailers, faced a common challenge in eCommerce—how to create a more engaging, seamless, and personalised shopping experience for customers online. They wanted to implement AI-powered assistance to provide personalised product recommendations, accurate sizing guidance, product comparisons, and instant answers to customer questions—replicating the ease and support of [&amp;hellip;]】简介Blue Bungalow是澳大利亚领先的时装零售商之一，在电子商务中面临着一个普遍的挑战 - 如何为在线客户创造更具吸引力，无缝和个性化的购物体验。他们想实施AI驱动的帮助，以提供个性化的产品建议，准确的尺寸指导，产品比较以及对客户问题的即时答案，从而获得[…]的便捷性和支持</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 16:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Python in Visual Studio Code – February 2025 Release】Visual Studio代码中的Python  -  2025年2月发布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/python/python-in-visual-studio-code-february-2025-release</link>
      <description>【The February 2025 release of the Python and Jupyter extensions for Visual Studio Code are now available. This month&#39;s updates include .】2025年2月的Python和Jupyter扩展名的版本现已可用。本月的更新包括。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 21:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering automated testing in Power Platform: Evergreen concepts for robust solutions】在电力平台中掌握自动测试：强大解决方案的常绿概念</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powerplatform/mastering-automated-testing-in-power-platform</link>
      <description>【Get a deep dive into the concepts of automated testing within the Power Platform, along with insights and best practices to help you build robust and reliable solutions.】深入了解电源平台内自动测试的概念，以及洞察力和最佳实践，以帮助您构建强大而可靠的解决方案。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 19:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【HTTP File updates for Request Variables and more】请求变量的HTTP文件更新以及更多</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/http-file-updates-for-request-variables-and-more</link>
      <description>【Many users have requested adding support for Request Variables in HTTP files in Visual Studio. With Request Variables, you can send an HTTP request and then use data from the response, or request, in any subsequent request that is sent from the HTTP file. We have also added support for a shared environment, $shared, which [&amp;hellip;]】许多用户要求在Visual Studio中的HTTP文件中添加对请求变量的支持。使用请求变量，您可以发送HTTP请求，然后在从HTTP文件发送的任何后续请求中使用来自响应或请求的数据。我们还增加了对共享环境的支持，$共享，[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【February 2025: A look at the latest Microsoft Entra key feature releases, announcements, and updates】2025年2月：查看最新的Microsoft Entra密钥功能发布，公告和更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/eng-connect-feb-25</link>
      <description>【This is the February 2025 edition of our monthly developer update, summarizing the latest news and developments in Microsoft Entra. This month, we bring you feature updates, public previews, announcements, and other important updates. Read on to learn more and make the most of Microsoft Entra. What went Generally Available (GA) since January 2025? Microsoft [&amp;hellip;]】这是2025年2月的我们每月开发人员更新的版本，总结了Microsoft Entra的最新新闻和开发。本月，我们为您带来更新，公共预览，公告和其他重要更新。继续阅读以了解更多信息并充分利用Microsoft Entra。自2025年1月以来，通常可以使用什么（GA）？微软[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 12:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>