<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【The case of the image that came out horribly slanted: Diagnosis】图像严重倾斜的案例：诊断</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240904-00/?p=110216</link>
      <description>【Imperfect pitch.】不完美的音调。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Incorporate GitHub Copilot into your daily flow】将 GitHub Copilot 纳入您的日常流程</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/incorporate-github-copilot-into-your-daily-flow</link>
      <description>【Streamlining Workflow with GitHub Copilot  Have you ever received code completions that are too large to manage or ones that need slight tweaks, but you must accept all the code to make those changes? To address these pain points, in Visual Studio 17.11 we’ve introduced a new feature that allows you to refine your completions [&amp;hellip;]】使用 GitHub Copilot 简化工作流程 您是否曾经收到过太大而无法管理的代码完成或需要稍微调整的代码，但您必须接受所有代码才能进行这些更改？为了解决这些痛点，在 Visual Studio 17.11 中，我们引入了一项新功能，可让您改进完成情况 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancing your Visual Studio authentication experience】增强您的 Visual Studio 身份验证体验</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/enhancing-your-visual-studio-authentication-experience</link>
      <description>【The current cyber security climate demands that applications not only provide outstanding features but also prioritize the security of user data. Applications like Visual Studio rely on token-based authentication to access resources on your behalf. While effective, token-based authentication can be susceptible to attacks if not properly protected. Today, we are happy to announce that [&amp;hellip;]】当前的网络安全环境要求应用程序不仅要提供出色的功能，还要优先考虑用户数据的安全。 Visual Studio 等应用程序依赖基于令牌的身份验证来代表您访问资源。基于令牌的身份验证虽然有效，但如果保护不当，可能容易受到攻击。今天，我们很高兴地宣布 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Nested App Authentication: An improved authentication protocol for your Teams app】引入嵌套应用程序身份验证：针对 Teams 应用程序的改进身份验证协议</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/introducing-nested-app-authentication-an-improved-authentication-protocol-for-your-teams-app</link>
      <description>【Learn how Nested App Authentication simplifies the authentication process and enables single sign-on across supported Microsoft first-party applications.】了解嵌套应用程序身份验证如何简化身份验证过程并支持跨受支持的 Microsoft 第一方应用程序进行单点登录。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhance Your Cloud Development Skills at ‘Azure Developers – .NET Aspire Day 2024’】在“Azure 开发者 – .NET Aspire Day 2024”中提高您的云开发技能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/enhance-your-cloud-development-skills-at-azure-developers-dotnet-aspire-day-2024</link>
      <description>【Join us at the Azure Developers - .NET Aspire Day 2024, a virtual event happening on September 18, 2024】加入我们的 Azure 开发者 - .NET Aspire Day 2024，该虚拟活动将于 2024 年 9 月 18 日举行</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why did Windows 95 use blue screen error messages instead of hard error messages?】为什么 Windows 95 使用蓝屏错误消息而不是硬错误消息？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20240903-00/?p=110205</link>
      <description>【You may not able to get there from here.】您可能无法从这里到达那里。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Discover .NET at DEVintersection Las Vegas 2024】在 2024 年拉斯维加斯 DEVintersection 上探索 .NET</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/discover-dotnet-at-dev-intersection-las-vegas-2024</link>
      <description>【Join us at DEVintersection Las Vegas from September 9-12, 2024, for an in-person event featuring the latest in .NET and Azure technologies. Connect with experts, dive into new advancements, and get your questions answered by the people who build the tools you use every day.】欢迎参加我们于 2024 年 9 月 9 日至 12 日在拉斯维加斯 DEVintersection 举办的现场活动，该活动将展示最新的 .NET 和 Azure 技术。与专家联系，深入了解新的进步，并让构建您每天使用的工具的人员回答您的问题。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Load optimization in Azure Fluid Relay using Managed Prometheus】使用托管 Prometheus 在 Azure Fluid Relay 中进行负载优化</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/load-optimization-in-azure-fluid-relay-using-managed-prometheus</link>
      <description>【Read how Azure Fluid Relay leverages Prometheus metrics in determining cluster load and can restrict the cluster from taking in additional traffic once it reaches certain thresholds.】了解 Azure Fluid Relay 如何利用 Prometheus 指标来确定集群负载，并在达到特定阈值时限制集群接收额外流量。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSVC Backend Updates in Visual Studio 2022 version 17.11】Visual Studio 2022 版本 17.11 中的 MSVC 后端更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/msvc-backend-updates-in-visual-studio-2022-version-17-11</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio 2022 17.11 brings new optimizations, intrinsics, features, and improvements to the MSVC backend. Check out the highlights below:  Performance improvements and additional functionality for all architectures:  The SLP vectorizer can now recognize when vectors need to be permuted and when elements of a vector are defined by different operations.  Updated corruption handling in [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio 2022 17.11 为 MSVC 后端带来了新的优化、内在函数、功能和改进。查看以下亮点： 所有架构的性能改进和附加功能：SLP 向量化器现在可以识别何时需要对向量进行排列以及向量的元素何时由不同的操作定义。  更新了 [...] 中的腐败处理</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Bring your AI Copilots to the edge with Phi-3 and Semantic Kernel】来宾博客：利用 Phi-3 和语义内核将您的 AI 副驾驶带到边缘</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-bring-your-ai-copilots-to-the-edge-with-phi-3-and-semantic-kernel</link>
      <description>【Bring your AI Copilots to the edge with Phi-3 and Semantic Kernel Today we&amp;#8217;re featuring a guest author, Arafat Tehsin, who&amp;#8217;s a Microsoft Most Valuable Professional (MVP) for AI. He&amp;#8217;s written an article we&amp;#8217;re sharing below, focused on how to Bring your AI Copilots to the edge with Phi-3 and Semantic Kernel. We&amp;#8217;ll turn it [&amp;hellip;]】利用 Phi-3 和 Semantic Kernel 将您的 AI Copilot 带到边缘 今天我们邀请了一位客座作者 Arafat Tehsin，他是 Microsoft AI 领域最有价值专家 (MVP)。他写了一篇我们在下面分享的文章，重点介绍了如何利用 Phi-3 和语义内核将 AI Copilots 带到边缘。我们将把它变成[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 18:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>