<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Foundry Local: A New Era of Edge AI】Foundry Local：Edge AI的新时代</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/foundry-local-a-new-era-of-edge-ai</link>
      <description>【At Microsoft Build 2025, Microsoft unveiled its groundbreaking Foundry Local solution for edge devices—an efficient platform specifically designed for local AI inference. As a critical component of Microsoft&amp;#8217;s AI strategy, Foundry Local empowers developers to smoothly deploy and run Small Language Models (SLMs) on resource-constrained edge devices, opening new possibilities for the convergence of edge computing and [&amp;hellip;]】在Microsoft Build 2025，Microsoft推出了其开创性的Edge设备的本地解决方案，这是一个专门针对本地AI推理设计的有效平台。作为Microsoft AI策略的关键组成部分，Foundry Local Emplater开发人员可以在资源受限的边缘设备上平稳部署和运行小语言模型（SLM），为Edge Computing和[…]的收敛开辟了新的可能性</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Generally Available: Seamless Migration from Serverless to Provisioned Throughput in Azure Cosmos DB】通常可用：无缝迁移从无服务器到Azure Cosmos DB中的配置吞吐量</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/generally-available-seamless-migration-from-serverless-to-provisioned-throughput-in-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【We are excited to announce the general availability (GA) of a highly requested capability in Azure Cosmos DB: the ability to migrate from serverless to provisioned throughput mode—without manual recreation, or downtime. This release builds on the momentum of our public preview and is now fully supported across all regions. Why it matters Azure Cosmos [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布Azure Cosmos DB中高度要求的功能的一般可用性（GA）：从无服务器迁移到配置的吞吐量模式（无手动娱乐或停机时间）的能力。该版本建立在我们公众预览的势头的基础上，现在在所有地区都得到了完全支持。为什么它重要的是Azure Cosmos […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript Native Previews】宣布打字稿本机预览</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-native-previews</link>
      <description>【This past March we unveiled our efforts to port the TypeScript compiler and toolset to native code. This port has achieved a 10x speed-up on most projects &amp;#8211; not just by using a natively-compiled language (Go), but also through using shared memory parallelism and concurrency where we can benefit. Since then, we have made several [&amp;hellip;]】在过去的3月，我们揭露了将打字稿编译器和工具集移植到本机代码的努力。该端口在大多数项目上都达到了10倍的速度 - 不仅是使用本质上编译的语言（GO），还通过使用共享记忆并行性和并发，我们可以从中受益。从那以后，我们做了几个[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Public Preview: Shape and Control Workloads with Throughput Buckets in Azure Cosmos DB】公共预览：Azure Cosmos DB中使用吞吐量桶的形状和控制工作负载</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/public-preview-shape-and-control-workloads-with-throughput-buckets-in-azure-cosmos-db</link>
      <description>【Imagine your application is processing customer checkouts in real-time, while a background process synchronizes data for reporting. Suddenly, the seamless user experience falters because the sync job consumes more RU/s than anticipated.  Many teams face a common challenge: multiple workloads share the same container resources, yet each has different performance requirements.  We&amp;#8217;re excited to introduce [&amp;hellip;]】想象一下，您的应用程序正在实时处理客户结帐，而背景过程则同步数据进行报告。突然，无缝的用户体验会失败，因为同步作业消耗的ru/s比预期的要多。  许多团队面临一个普遍的挑战：多个工作负载共享相同的容器资源，但是每个工作负载都有不同的性能要求。  我们很高兴介绍[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Office Add-ins announces Copilot agents with add-in actions and more at Build 2025】办公室加载项宣布副代理具有加载项的操作，以及在2025年的Build 2025</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/office-addins-at-build-2025</link>
      <description>【As part of the expanding capabilities for agents across Microsoft 365, Office Platform announces add-in actions for Copilot agents are available in preview. This blog is an overview of all the new capabilities across the platform: APIs, developer tools, and add-in distribution options—making it simpler to build new or iterate on JavaScript add-ins.】作为Microsoft 365中代理商扩展功能的一部分，Office Platform宣布为Copilot代理的附加操作提供预览。该博客是整个平台上所有新功能的概述：API，开发人员工具和附加发行选项 - 使在JavaScript加载项上构建新或迭代更简单。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the Agent Store: Build, publish, and discover agents in Microsoft 365 Copilot】介绍代理商店：在Microsoft 365 Copilot中构建，发布和发现代理商</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/introducing-the-agent-store-build-publish-and-discover-agents-in-microsoft-365-copilot</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to introduce the Agent Store — a centralized, curated marketplace that features agents built by Microsoft, trusted partners, and customers. The Agent Store offers a new, immersive experience within Microsoft 365 Copilot that enables users to browse, install, and try agents tailored to their needs.】我们很高兴介绍Agent Store，这是一个集中的，精心策划的市场，其特色是由Microsoft，Trusted Partners和客户建造的代理商。 Agent Store在Microsoft 365 Copilot中提供了一种新的沉浸式体验，使用户能够根据自己的需求浏览，安装和尝试量身定制的代理商。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Now Available: Migrate from RU to vCore for Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB via Azure Portal】现在可用：通过Azure Portal从RU迁移到Vcore的Azure Cosmos DB</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/migrate-mongo-db-ru-to-vcore</link>
      <description>【We are thrilled to introduce a cost-effective, simple, and efficient solution for migrating from RU-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB to vCore-based. You can now move to vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB at no cost using the Azure portal.  How is the vCore model different?  Azure Cosmos DB offers two pricing models: Request Units [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴引入一种经济高效，简单且高效的解决方案，用于从基于RU的Azure Cosmos DB迁移到MongoDB到基于VCORE的基于VCORE。现在，您可以使用Azure Portal免费使用MongoDB的基于VCore的Azure Cosmos DB。  Vcore模型有何不同？  Azure Cosmos DB提供了两个定价模型：请求单位[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I create a window the size of the screen without it being treated as a fullscreen window?】如何创建一个屏幕大小的窗口，而不会将其视为全屏窗口？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250522-00/?p=111211</link>
      <description>【You can declare that you aren&#39;t rude.】您可以声明自己并不粗鲁。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New AI Features in SQL Server 2025】SQL Server 2025中的新AI功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/new-ai-features-in-sql-server-2025</link>
      <description>【We have some great new AI Features in SQL Server 2025. I also figured a video would be better than reading a blog&amp;#8230;. but, you can also read all about it here.】我们在SQL Server 2025中有一些很棒的新AI功能。我还认为视频比阅读博客要好。但是，您也可以在这里阅读所有有关它的信息。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 20:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft Entra ID integration with Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB (vCore)】Microsoft Entra ID与Azure Cosmos DB集成，用于MongoDB（VCORE）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/microsoft-entra-id-integration-with-azure-cosmos-db-for-mongodb-vcore</link>
      <description>【Security is no longer a nice-to-have—it’s a foundational requirement for any cloud-native architecture. As organizations adopt managed database services to support mission-critical applications, they must prioritize robust, scalable, and centralized security. Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB (vCore) delivers high performance and flexibility, but it provides the most value when paired with well-implemented security practices. Authentication [&amp;hellip;]】安全性不再是一个不错的选择，而是对任何云本地架构的基本要求。随着组织采用托管数据库服务来支持关键任务应用程序，他们必须优先考虑强大，可扩展和集中安全性。 MongoDB（VCORE）的Azure Cosmos DB提供了高性能和灵活性，但与实践良好的安全实践配对时，它提供了最大的价值。验证 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>