<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【February 2026 Insiders (version 1.110)】2026 年 2 月 Insider（版本 1.110）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/february-2026-insiders-(version-1.110)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code February 2026 Release (1.110). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2026 年 2 月版本 (1.110) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Mastering User Settings in SharePoint Framework】掌握 SharePoint 框架中的用户设置</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/mastering-user-settings-in-sharepoint-framework</link>
      <description>【User preferences and settings are fundamental components of modern web applications. When developing SharePoint Framework (SPFx) solutions, the ability to store and manage user-specific configurations across devices and sessions becomes crucial for delivering personalized experiences. This article explores a robust, enterprise-ready pattern fo】用户偏好和设置是现代 Web 应用程序的基本组成部分。开发 SharePoint 框架 (SPFx) 解决方案时，跨设备和会话存储和管理用户特定配置的能力对于提供个性化体验至关重要。本文探讨了一种强大的、企业级的模式</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (Nov 2025 - Jan 2026)】vcpkg 的新增功能（2025 年 11 月 - 2026 年 1 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-nov-2025-jan-2026</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2025.12.12 and 2026.01.16 registry releases and the】本文总结了作为 2025.12.12 和 2026.01.16 注册表版本的一部分的 vcpkg 包管理器的更改以及</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Building an AI Skills Executor in .NET: Bringing Anthropic&#39;s Agent Pattern to the Microsoft Ecosystem】在 .NET 中构建 AI 技能执行器：将 Anthropic 的代理模式引入 Microsoft 生态系统</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/dotnet-ai-skills-executor-azure-openai-mcp</link>
      <description>【When Anthropic released their Agent Skills framework, they published a blueprint for how enterprise organizations should structure AI agent capabilities. The pattern is straightforward: package procedural knowledge into composable skills that AI agents can discover and apply contextually. Microsoft, OpenAI, Cursor, and others have already adop】当 Anthropic 发布他们的代理技能框架时，他们发布了企业组织应如何构建人工智能代理功能的蓝图。该模式很简单：将程序知识打包成人工智能代理可以发现并根据上下文应用的可组合技能。 Microsoft、OpenAI、Cursor 等公司已经采用</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 19:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Masking Sensitive Data in Azure SQL】屏蔽 Azure SQL 中的敏感数据</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/mask-data-in-azure-sql</link>
      <description>【Applications often need access to data without needing access to everything. Social Security numbers, email addresses, and phone numbers are common examples. Storing them is required. Exposing them broadly is not. This is especially valuable when exposing a database to an AI agent through MCP servers like SQL MCP Server, where safety and re】应用程序通常需要访问数据而不需要访问所有内容。社会安全号码、电子邮件地址和电话号码是常见的例子。需要存储它们。广泛地曝光它们则不然。当通过 MCP 服务器（例如 SQL MCP Server）将数据库暴露给 AI 代理时，这一点尤其有价值，其中安全性和可靠性</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【How can I prevent the user from changing the widths of ListView columns in version 5 of the common controls?, part 2】如何防止用户更改公共控件版本 5 中 ListView 列的宽度？，第 2 部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20260206-00/?p=112045</link>
      <description>【Last time, we had figured out how to prevent the version 5 ListView Win32 common control from resizing columns, but we noticed that the cursor st】上次，我们已经弄清楚如何防止版本 5 ListView Win32 公共控件调整列大小，但我们注意到光标已停止</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enable Soft Delete in Azure SQL】在 Azure SQL 中启用软删除</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/soft-delete-in-azure-sql</link>
      <description>【Sometimes applications need to remove data without actually losing it. Soft delete keeps rows in the database while making them invisible to normal application access. This is especially valuable when exposing a database to an AI agent through MCP servers like SQL MCP Server, where safety and reversibility matter. Lea】有时应用程序需要删除数据而不实际丢失数据。软删除将行保留在数据库中，同时使它们对正常应用程序访问不可见。当通过 SQL MCP Server 等 MCP 服务器向 AI 代理公开数据库时，这一点尤其有价值，因为安全性和可逆性很重要。莉亚</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Securing Aspire Apps with Microsoft Entra ID】使用 Microsoft Entra ID 保护 Aspire 应用程序</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspire/securing-dotnet-aspire-apps-with-microsoft-entra-id</link>
      <description>【[alert type=&#34;important&#34; heading=&#34;About the Author&#34;]This is a guest post from Jean-Marc Prieur from Microsoft&#39;s 1ES (One Engineering System) team. We help reduce developer toil across Microsoft by making it easy to build services that are secure and compliant from the start, for instance with Aspire and Entra ID.[/alert] TL;D】[alert type =“important”heading =“关于作者”]这是来自 Microsoft 1ES（单一工程系统）团队的 Jean-Marc Prieur 的客座文章。我们从一开始就可以轻松构建安全且合规的服务，例如使用 Aspire 和 Entra ID，从而帮助减少整个 Microsoft 开发人员的辛苦工作。[/alert] TL;D</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET Framework 3.5 Moves to Standalone Deployment in new versions of Windows】.NET Framework 3.5 在新版本的 Windows 中转向独立部署</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-framework-3-5-moves-to-standalone-deployment-in-new-versions-of-windows</link>
      <description>【The deployment model of .NET Framework 3.5 for future versions of Windows is changing. Starting with Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 27965, .NET Framework 3.5 must be obtained as a standalone installer and is no longer included as an optional Windows component. .NET Framework 3.5 is now available as a standalone installer for legacy】Windows 未来版本的 .NET Framework 3.5 部署模型正在发生变化。从 Windows 11 Insider Preview Build 27965 开始，.NET Framework 3.5 必须作为独立安装程序获取，并且不再作为可选 Windows 组件包含在内。 .NET Framework 3.5 现在可作为旧版本的独立安装程序</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Go 1.25.7-1 and 1.24.13-1 Microsoft builds now available】Go 1.25.7-1 和 1.24.13-1 Microsoft 版本现已推出</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/go/go-1-25-7-1-and-1-24-13-1-microsoft-builds-now-available</link>
      <description>【A new release of the Microsoft build of Go including security fixes is now available for download. For more information about this release and the changes included, see the table below: Microsoft Release Upstream Tag】包含安全修复程序的 Microsoft Go 版本新版本现已可供下载。有关此版本及其所包含更改的更多信息，请参阅下表： Microsoft 版本上游标签</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>