<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Changes to inline image representation in Outlook on the web and new Outlook for Windows】更改网络Outlook中的内联图像表示形式和Windows的新Outlook</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/changes-to-inline-images-in-outlook</link>
      <description>【We’d like to inform you about an update to how inline images are represented in the HTML body of Outlook emails in Outlook on the web and the new Outlook for Windows. This change may impact how your add-in identifies and processes inline images when using the attachment ID. What’s changing? Previously, we represented inline imag】我们想通知您有关如何在网络Outlook和Windows的新Outlook中的HTML Outlook电子邮件中表示内联图像的更新。此更改可能会影响您的加载项在使用附件ID时如何识别和过程内联图像。发生什么变化？以前，我们代表内联图像</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 01:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio Dev/Test Benefit Explained】Visual Studio Dev/Test益处解释了</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-dev-test-benefit-explained</link>
      <description>【Before joining Microsoft, I served as VP of Application Development at one of the largest temporary staffing companies in the United States. I’ll never forget the look on our CFO’s face when I told him we needed two to three additional cloud environments to support a large-scale modernization project. His】在加入微软之前，我曾在美国最大的临时人员配备公司之一担任应用程序开发副总裁。当我告诉他我们需要两个到三个额外的云环境来支持大规模的现代化项目时，我永远不会忘记CFO脸上的外观。他的</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Code comments should apply to the state of the system at the point the comment &#34;executes&#34;】代码注释应适用于系统的状态，即注释“执行”</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251006-00/?p=111655</link>
      <description>【Comments inside the body of a function should apply to the state of the system at the point the comment &#34;executes&#34;. Here&#39;s an example of poor comment placement: // Widget is already vibrating, so we update the waveform in place. // Else the waveform parameters will be set when we start vibrating. if (waveformParameters !】在函数体内的注释应适用于系统“执行”时的系统状态。以下是评论不良的示例：//小部件已经在振动，因此我们更新了位置的波形。 //否则，当我们开始振动时，将设置波形参数。 if（waveformparameters！</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Roadmap for AI in Visual Studio (October)】Visual Studio的AI路线图（10月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/roadmap-for-ai-in-visual-studio-october</link>
      <description>【Today, we’re excited to share our public roadmap, which outlines the next steps in evolving Visual Studio with AI-powered agentic experiences. With every month, we aim to deliver smarter, faster, and more intuitive tools that enhance your coding experience. Disclaimer: The items outlined here represent ongoing work for the month. They】今天，我们很高兴分享我们的公共路线图，该路线图概述了通过AI驱动的代理体验发展视觉工作室的下一步。我们每个月都打算提供更智能，更快，更直观的工具，以增强您的编码体验。免责声明：此处概述的项目代表了当月正在进行的工作。他们</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 19:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Can we get weak functions for static linking? The Visual C++ compiler says &#34;We have weak functions at home&#34;】我们可以获得静态链接的弱功能吗？视觉C ++编译器说：“我们在家中的功能较弱”</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251003-00/?p=111650</link>
      <description>【The ELF object file has this thing called &#34;weak functions&#34;. These are functions present in a library that are used by the linker to resolve a symbol only if the main program doesn&#39;t provide a resolution for them. The Visual C++ compiler doesn&#39;t have &#34;weak functions&#34; in this sense, but that doesn&#39;t mean that equivalent functionality】精灵对象文件具有称为“弱函数”的东西。这些是库中存在的函数，仅当主程序无法为其提供分辨率时，链接器使用的函数才能解析符号。从这个意义上讲，Visual C ++编译器没有“弱功能”，但这并不意味着等效功能</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【From Lab to Live: A Blueprint for a Voice-Powered AI Sales Coach】从实验室到现场：语音动力AI销售教练的蓝图</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/from-lab-to-live-a-blueprint-for-a-voice-powered-ai-sales-coach</link>
      <description>【Until recently, building real-time voice AI for production was challenging. Developers faced hurdles such as managing audio streams and ensuring low-latency performance. That landscape is changing. The】直到最近，建立实时声音AI进行生产还是具有挑战性的。开发人员面临诸如管理音频流和确保低延迟性能之类的障碍。景观正在发生变化。这</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【VS Live! Orlando – Your Ultimate Learning Adventure】VS Live！奥兰多 - 您的最终学习冒险</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/visual-studio-live-orlando-2025</link>
      <description>【Imagine swapping stories with fellow developers over dinner as the Florida sun sets, then beginning the next morning with a stroll past the resort’s palm-lined walkways before catching your first session across】想象一下佛罗里达太阳的景点与其他开发人员在晚餐时交换故事，然后在第二天早上开始漫步，经过度假村的棕榈衬里人行道，然后抓住了您的第一届会议</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (September 2025)】Azure SDK发布（2025年9月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-september-2025</link>
      <description>【Thank you for your interest in the new Azure SDKs! We release new features, improvements, and bug fixes every month. Subscribe to our Azure SDK Blog RSS Feed to get notified when a new release is available. You can find links to packages, code, and docs on our】感谢您对新的Azure SDK的关注！我们每月发布新功能，改进和错误修复。订阅我们的Azure SDK博客RSS feed，以便在有新版本时通知。您可以在我们的包装，代码和文档中找到链接</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【The problem with inferring from a function call operator is that there may be more than one】从函数调用操作员推断出的问题是，可能有多个</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251002-00/?p=111647</link>
      <description>【Some time ago, I wrote briefly on writing a helper class for generating a particular category of C callback wrappers around C++ methods. This particular】不久前，我简要撰写了为编写辅助课程的文章，用于在C ++方法上生成特定类别的C回调包装器。这个特别</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (September 2025)】VCPKG的新功能（2025年9月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-september-2025</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2025.09.17 registry release, the 2025-08-29 and】此博客文章总结了VCPKG软件包管理器的更改，作为2025.09.17注册表版本，2025-08-29和</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>