<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Why doesn’t the Windows blue screen of death prominently identify the company that created the driver that crashed?】为什么 Windows 蓝屏死机没有显着标识创建崩溃驱动程序的公司？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250121-00/?p=110788</link>
      <description>【Because the driver that crashed may not be the one at fault.】因为撞车的司机可能不是有过错的人。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Memory corruption from outside the process looks like space aliens】进程外部的内存损坏看起来就像外星人</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250123-00/?p=110800</link>
      <description>【The write isn&#39;t visible to your process, just the effect of the write.】写入对您的进程不可见，只能看到写入的效果。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Be mindful of temporal terms in documents: What is the reference point in time?】请注意文档中的时间术语：参考时间点是什么？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250122-00/?p=110797</link>
      <description>【What is your implied point in time for the reference?】您的参考暗示时间点是什么？</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why is there a bulge on my bicycle tire when I inflate it?】为什么我的自行车轮胎充气时会出现凸起？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250121-01/?p=110790</link>
      <description>【Get the order of operations right.】正确掌握操作顺序。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Improve the “R” in RAG and embrace Agentic RAG in Azure SQL】改善抹布中的“ r”，并拥抱Azure SQL中的代理抹布</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/improve-the-r-in-rag-and-embrace-agentic-rag-in-azure-sql</link>
      <description>【The RAG (Retrieval Augmented Generation) pattern, which is commonly discussed today, is based on the foundational idea that the retrieval part is done using vector search. This ensures that all the most relevant information available to answer the given question is returned and then fed to an LLM to generate the final answer. While vector [&amp;hellip;]】今天普遍讨论的 RAG（检索增强生成）模式基于检索部分是使用向量搜索完成的基本思想。这可确保返回可用于回答给定问题的所有最相关的信息，然后将其提供给法学硕士以生成最终答案。而矢量[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:56:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【WinForms: Analyze This (Me in Visual Basic)】WinForms：分析这个（Visual Basic 中的 Me）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-winforms-analyzers</link>
      <description>【Your WinForms code might have issues—maybe an Async call picked the wrong overload, or it’s leaking data into resource files. Time to call in a code-shrink! So, WinForms, Analyze This!】您的Winforms代码可能会遇到问题 - 也许异步调用选择了错误的过载，或者将数据泄漏到资源文件中。是时候打电话给代码障碍了！因此，winforms，分析这个！</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing a free GitHub Copilot for Visual Studio】宣布免费的github副驾驶用于视觉工作室</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/announcing-a-free-github-copilot-for-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【We&amp;#8217;re excited to announce an all new free plan for GitHub Copilot, available for everyone today in Visual Studio. All you need is a GitHub account. No trial. No subscription. No credit card. With GitHub Copilot Free, you’ll receive: 2,000 code completions per month 50 chat messages per month Access to the latest AI models with [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布 GitHub Copilot 的全新免费计划，今天可供 Visual Studio 中的所有人使用。 您只需要一个 GitHub 帐户即可。没有审判。没有订阅。没有信用卡。使用 GitHub Copilot Free，您将收到： 每月 2,000 次代码完成 每月 50 条聊天消息 通过 [...] 访问最新的 AI 模型</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Reminder: When a C++ object fails to construct, the destructor does not run】提醒：当C ++对象无法构造时，驱动器不运行</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250120-00/?p=110783</link>
      <description>【If you need to run after a failed construction, you have to put it in a base class or member variable.】如果需要在构造失败后运行，则必须将其放入基类或成员变量中。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (January 2025)】vcpkg 的新增功能（2025 年 1 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-january-2025</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2025.01.13 registry release, 2025-01-11 tool release, as well as changes to vcpkg documentation throughout January. This release includes minor improvements and bug fixes. Some stats for this period: There are now 2,524 total ports available in the vcpkg curated registry. A [&amp;hellip;]】这篇博客文章总结了VCPKG软件包管理器的更改，作为2025.01.13注册表版本，2025-01-11工具发布的一部分，以及整个1月份对VCPKG文档的更改。此版本包括较小的改进和错误修复。此期间的一些统计数据：VCPKG策划注册表中现在有2,524个端口可用。一个[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Guest Blog: Creative Writing Assistant – a multi-agent app sample with Semantic Kernel &amp; .NET Aspire】来宾博客：创意写作助理 - 具有语义内核和.net Aspire的多代理应用程序样本</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/guest-blog-creative-writing-assistant-a-multi-agent-app-sample-with-semantic-kernel-net-aspire</link>
      <description>【Today we’re featuring a guest author, Ricardo Niepel, who’s a Senior Technical Specialist at Microsoft. He’s written an article we’re sharing below; we’ll turn it over to Ricardo to share more! If “Creative Writing Assistant” sounds familiar, it might be because we&amp;#8217;ve previously released a similar multi-agent application built in Python during our Ignite conference [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们介绍了一位客座作家Ricardo Niepel，他是Microsoft的高级技术专家。他写了一篇我们在下面分享的文章；我们将其移交给Ricardo，以分享更多！如果“创意写作助理”听起来很熟悉，那可能是因为我们以前发布了在IGNITE会议期间在Python上发布的类似的多代理应用程序[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 22:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>