<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Java on Visual Studio Code的更新 – 2024年9月】Java on Visual Studio Code的更新 – 2024年9月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java-ch/java-on-visual-studio-code-2024-09</link>
      <description>【大家好，欢迎来到 Visual Studio Code for Java 的九月更新！在本篇博客中，我们将介绍一些重要的 Spring 功能更新和 Gradle 增强功能，让我们开始吧！ Spring 更新 使用 GitHub Copilot 解释 SpEL 表达式、查询语句和 AOP 切入点表达式 SpEL 表达式、查询语句和 AOP 切入点表达式有时编写起来比较复杂，但如果你在 Visual Studio Code 环境中使用 GitHub Copilot，Spring 工具现在会在这些表达式上方显示CodeLense，让你快速让 GitHub Copilot 为你解释这些语句。相应的提示会先提供一个简短的摘要，随后是更详细的解释。这里有一个演示。 CRON 表达式的语法高亮和验证 当 CRON 表达式用于 @Scheduler 注解时，现在可以显示语法高亮，并且如果语法不正确，还会出现错误标记。演示如下。 查询参数名称的新嵌入提示 使用序号引用查询特定参数，现在会显示一个嵌入提示，告诉你该序号所引用的已解析方法参数的名称。 更多 Spring 注解获得内容辅助、跳转定义和查找引用支持 在 Java 源代码中使用 Spring 注解的工作每次发布都会变得更加快捷和轻松。最新的 Spring Boot 工具添加了以下注解的高级功能： [&amp;hellip;]】大家好，欢迎来到 Visual Studio Code for Java 的九月更新！在本篇博客中，我们将介绍一些重要的 Spring 功能更新和 Gradle 增强功能，让我们开始吧！ Spring 更新 使用 GitHub Copilot 解释 SpEL 表达式、查询语句和 AOP 切入点表达式 SpEL 表达式、查询语句和 AOP 切入点表达式有时编写起来比较复杂，但如果你在 Visual Studio Code 环境中使用 GitHub Copilot，Spring 工具现在会在这些表达式上方显示CodeLense，让你快速让 GitHub Copilot 为你解释这些语句。相应的提示会先提供一个简短的摘要，随后是更详细的解释。这里有一个演示。 CRON 表达式的语法高亮和验证 当 CRON 表达式用于 @Scheduler 注解时，现在可以显示语法高亮，并且如果语法不正确，还会出现错误标记。演示如下。 查询参数名称的新嵌入提示 使用序号引用查询特定参数，现在会显示一个嵌入提示，告诉你该序号所引用的已解析方法参数的名称。 更多 Spring 注解获得内容辅助、跳转定义和查找引用支持 在 Java 源代码中使用 Spring 注解的工作每次发布都会变得更加快捷和轻松。最新的 Spring Boot 工具添加了以下注解的高级功能： […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft 365 Certification control spotlight: Security event logging, reviewing, and alerting】Microsoft 365 认证控制重点：安全事件记录、审查和警报</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/microsoft-365-certification-control-spotlight-security-event-logging-reviewing-and-alerting</link>
      <description>【Discover how Microsoft 365 Certification validates security event logging best practices.】了解 Microsoft 365 认证如何验证安全事件日志记录最佳实践。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Engineering the Scalable Vector Extension in .NET】在 .NET 中设计可扩展矢量扩展</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/engineering-sve-in-dotnet</link>
      <description>【Let&#39;s take an in-depth look at how the team implemented the Scalable Vector Extension (SVE) for .NET.】让我们深入了解一下团队如何为 .NET 实现可扩展矢量扩展 (SVE)。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Utilize Multiple Monitors for Microsoft Dev Box with the Windows App】通过 Windows 应用程序利用 Microsoft Dev Box 的多个显示器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/develop-from-the-cloud/utilize-multiple-monitors-for-microsoft-dev-box-with-the-windows-app</link>
      <description>【Do you use cloud-based developer environments like Microsoft Dev Box? Do you use multiple monitors in your setup? Did you know there a new app in Windows that will give you a great experience with multiple monitors and Microsoft Dev Box? Take a look at this video showing configuring multiple monitor setup with the Windows [&amp;hellip;]】您是否使用基于云的开发人员环境（例如 Microsoft Dev Box）？您的设置中是否使用多个显示器？您是否知道 Windows 中有一款新应用程序可以为您提供多显示器和 Microsoft Dev Box 的出色体验？观看此视频，该视频展示了使用 Windows 配置多显示器设置 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Java on Visual Studio Code Update – September 2024】Visual Studio 代码上的 Java 更新 – 2024 年 9 月</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/java/java-on-visual-studio-code-update-september-2024</link>
      <description>【Hi everyone, welcome to the September update for Visual Studio Code for Java! In this blog, we will cover some important Spring feature updates and Gradle enhancements, let&amp;#8217;s get started! Spring Updates Explain SpEL expressions, query statements, and AOP pointcut expressions with GitHub Copilot SpEL expressions, query statements, and AOP pointcut expressions can sometimes be [&amp;hellip;]】大家好，欢迎来到 Visual Studio Code for Java 九月更新！在这篇博客中，我们将介绍一些重要的 Spring 功能更新和 Gradle 增强功能，让我们开始吧！ Spring 更新使用 GitHub Copilot 解释 SpEL 表达式、查询语句和 AOP 切入点表达式 SpEL 表达式、查询语句和 AOP 切入点表达式有时可以是 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Meet the Winners | Microsoft Developers Azure AI &amp; Azure Cosmos DB Learning Hackathon】认识获奖者 | Microsoft 开发人员 Azure AI 和 Azure Cosmos DB 学习黑客马拉松</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/meet-the-winners-microsoft-developers-azure-ai-azure-cosmos-db-learning-hackathon</link>
      <description>【Azure Cosmos DB powers some of the world’s most popular intelligent apps like ChatGPT. In a recent hackathon, Over 9,500 developers engaged with Azure Cosmos DB and Azure AI services, making it one of the most popular on Devpost, ranking in the top 0.2% of all Devpost hackathons.  Participants explored AI fundamentals and built their [&amp;hellip;]】Azure Cosmos DB 为 ChatGPT 等一些世界上最受欢迎的智能应用程序提供支持。在最近的一次黑客马拉松中，超过 9,500 名开发人员参与了 Azure Cosmos DB 和 Azure AI 服务，使其成为 Devpost 上最受欢迎的黑客马拉松之一，在所有 Devpost 黑客马拉松中排名前 0.2%。  参与者探索了人工智能基础知识并构建了他们的[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A correction to the awaitable lock for C++ PPL tasks】对 C++ PPL 任务的等待锁的更正</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241010-00/?p=110357</link>
      <description>【Over-scoped lock.】超出范围的锁。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New Contextual Tools for GitHub Copilot in Visual Studio】Visual Studio 中 GitHub Copilot 的新上下文工具</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/new-contextual-tools-for-github-copilot-in-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio 2022 17.11 now allows you to pass your entire workspace or specific classes and functions as context for GitHub Copilot Chat. By referencing your entire codebase, down to specific classes and functions, Copilot Chat can deliver refined and accurate results tailored to your code. @workspace for project references  You can now use GitHub [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio 2022 17.11 现在允许您将整个工作区或特定类和函数作为 GitHub Copilot Chat 的上下文传递。通过引用您的整个代码库，具体到特定的类和函数，Copilot Chat 可以提供针对您的代码量身定制的精致且准确的结果。 @workspace 用于项目参考您现在可以使用 GitHub [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 17:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing TypeScript 5.7 Beta】宣布推出 TypeScript 5.7 Beta</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/typescript/announcing-typescript-5-7-beta</link>
      <description>【Today we are announcing the availability of TypeScript 5.7 Beta. To get started using the beta, you can get it through npm with the following command: npm install -D typescript@beta Let&amp;#8217;s take a look at what&amp;#8217;s new in TypeScript 5.7! Checks for Never-Initialized Variables For a long time, TypeScript has been able to catch issues [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们宣布推出 TypeScript 5.7 Beta。要开始使用 Beta 版，您可以使用以下命令通过 npm 获取它： npm install -D typescript@beta 让我们来看看 TypeScript 5.7 中的新增功能！检查从未初始化的变量很长一段时间以来，TypeScript 一直能够捕获问题 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 20:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Debug Queries More Efficiently with the Improved Error Messaging in Azure Cosmos DB Data Explorer】使用 Azure Cosmos DB 数据资源管理器中改进的错误消息传递更有效地调试查询</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/improved-error-messaging-in-azure-cosmos-db-data-explorer</link>
      <description>【Azure Cosmos DB Data Explorer is a web-based tool available in the Azure Portal that allows you to manage data, as well as track and fix issues with your queries. In this blog post, we will focus on some of the new features in data explorer that improve the error messaging in the query editor, [&amp;hellip;]】Azure Cosmos DB 数据资源管理器是 Azure 门户中提供的基于 Web 的工具，可让你管理数据以及跟踪和修复查询问题。在这篇博文中，我们将重点关注数据浏览器中的一些新功能，这些功能可改进查询编辑器中的错误消息传递，[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>