<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring Text-to-Image capabilities in .NET】在.NET中探索文本对图像功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/explore-text-to-image-dotnet</link>
      <description>【I created my first graphic in 1981 using a language called &#34;BASIC&#34; on a computer by Texas Instruments called the TI-99/4A. The code to enter and run BASIC, by the way, was written by a new company at the time named Microsoft. In July of 1991, a program called &#34;POV-Ray&#34; was released that made it possible to render complex 3D scenes using a doma】我在1981年创建了我的第一张图形，该语言在德州仪器的计算机上使用了一种名为TI-99/4A的计算机上的语言。顺便说一句，要输入和运行基本的代码是由一家名为Microsoft的新公司编写的。 1991年7月，发布了一个名为“ POV射线”的程序，该计划使使用DOMA渲染复杂的3D场景成为可能</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Visual Studio 2026 Insiders: Using Podman for Container Development】Visual Studio 2026内部人员：使用Podman进行容器开发</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/visual-studio-2026-insiders-using-podman-for-container-development</link>
      <description>【Podman is an open-source container engine that has rapidly gained popularity for its daemonless architecture, rootless operation, and compatibility with Docker CLI commands. Unlike Docker, Podman does not require a central daemon, offering improved security and flexibili】Podman是一款开源容器引擎，其无根的架构，无根操作以及与Docker CLI命令的兼容性迅速获得了知名度。与Docker不同，Podman不需要中央守护程序，提供了提高的安全性和Flexibili</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why is Windows still tinkering with critical sections?】为什么Windows仍在修补关键部分？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250924-00/?p=111624</link>
      <description>【Adrian aka Silent aka CookiePLMonster did a deep investigation into how a 20 year old bug in GTA San Andreas surfaced in W】阿德里安（Adrian）又名Silent Aka Cookieplmonster对GTA San Andreas的20岁虫在W中进行了深入的调查。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Teaching the LLM Good Habits: How Azure MCP Uses Best-Practice Tools】教LLM良好习惯：Azure MCP如何使用最佳实践工具</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/all-things-azure/teaching-the-llm-good-habits-how-azure-mcp-uses-best-practice-tools</link>
      <description>【】</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 23:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Foundry Local Meets More Silicon】铸造本地遇到更多硅</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/foundry-local-meets-more-silicon</link>
      <description>【Foundry Local is a high-performance local AI runtime stack that brings Azure AI Foundry’s power to client devices. Foundry Local lets you build and ship cross-platform AI apps that run models with acceleration on a wide range of hardware. The Evolution of AI Acceleration On-device AI has progressed】Foundry Local是一种高性能的本地AI运行时堆栈，它将Azure AI Foundry的功率带给客户设备。 Foundry Local可以允许您构建和运送跨平台AI应用程序，该应用程序在各种硬件上以加速度运行模型。人工智能加速度的进化已进步已进展</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 19:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Another lesson learned from the Windows 98 on-stage USB blue screen】从Windows 98舞台上USB蓝屏中学到的另一个教训</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250923-00/?p=111621</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Production Studios (commonly known inside Microsoft simply as Microsoft Studios) is a large broadcast studio nestled in the trees on Microsoft&#39;s main Redmond Campus.¹ Here&#39;s a video hosted by Luke Burbank, local】Microsoft Production Studios（通常在Microsoft内部简单地称为Microsoft Studios）是一个大型广播工作室，坐落在Microsoft Main Redmond Campus的树木中。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Enhancements to XAML Live Preview in Visual Studio for .NET MAUI】为.NET MAUI的Visual Studio中XAML Live Preview的增强功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/enhancements-to-xaml-live-preview-in-visual-studio-for-net-maui</link>
      <description>【The XAML Live Preview feature in Visual Studio 2022 version 17.14 introduces a significant usability improvement for .NET MAUI projects: the XAML Live Preview window is now available during design time, eliminating the requirement to initiate a debug session. This change streamlines the UI dev】Visual Studio 2022版本17.14中的XAML Live Preview功能引入了.NET MAUI项目的可用性改进：XAML Live Preview窗口现已在设计期间可用，消除了启动调试会话的要求。此更改简化了UI DEV</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 17:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Using the new SqlVector type with EF Core and Dapper】将新的SQLVector类型与EF Core和Dapper一起使用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/using-the-new-sqlvector-type-with-ef-core-and-dapper</link>
      <description>【Azure SQL vector support has been generally available for a few months now, and the ecosystem is quickly evolving to make working with vectors in your applications as seamless and efficient as possible. With the release of】Azure SQL向量支持通常已经有几个月了，并且生态系统正在迅速发展，以使应用程序中的向量尽可能无缝有效。随着发布</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 17:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【New Trusted Publishing enhances security on NuGet.org】新的Trusted Publishing在Nuget.org上增强了安全性</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/enhanced-security-is-here-with-the-new-trust-publishing-on-nuget-org</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce Trusted Publishing on nuget.org — a simpler, safer way to publish NuGet packages from GitHub Actions. Rather than relying on long‑lived API keys, your workflow can use a short‑lived GitHub OIDC token to request a temporary, single‑use NuGet API key. These keys expire quickly (≈ 1 hour), eliminating long‑】我们很高兴能在Nuget.org上宣布可信赖的发布 - 一种更简单，更安全的方式，可以从GitHub Actions发布Nuget软件包。您的工作流不再依靠长期的API键，而是可以使用短寿命的github oidc令牌来请求临时的一次性nuget api键。这些钥匙迅速到期（≈1小时），消除了长期的</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Why was Windows 3.0&#39;s WinHelp called an online help system when it ran offline?】为什么Windows 3.0的Winhelp在离线运行时称其为在线帮助系统？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250922-00/?p=111619</link>
      <description>【Some time ago, I described Windows 3.0&#39;s WinHelp as &#34;a program for browsing online help files.&#34; But Windows 3.0 predated the Internet, and these help files were available even if the computer was not】不久前，我将Windows 3.0的Winhelp描述为“用于浏览在线帮助文​​件的程序”。但是Windows 3.0早于Internet，即使计算机不是计算机也可以使用这些帮助文件</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>