<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Session Guide to Azure AI Foundry @ Microsoft Ignite: Must-See Developer Sessions】Azure AI Foundry 会议指南 @ Microsoft Ignite：必看的开发人员会议</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/ignitedevsessions</link>
      <description>【Microsoft Ignite 2025 is the ultimate opportunity for developers to dive deep into what’s new with Azure AI Foundry. We curated the top sessions designed for hands-on learning, practical demos, and expert insights. Whether you’re】Microsoft Ignite 2025 是开发人员深入了解 Azure AI Foundry 新增功能的绝佳机会。我们策划了专为实践学习、实际演示和专家见解而设计的顶级会议。无论你是</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Copilot auto model selection (preview)】Copilot 自动模型选择简介（预览版）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/introducing-copilot-auto-model-selection-preview</link>
      <description>【Faster responses, a lower chance of rate limiting, and 10% off premium requests for paid users - auto picks the best available model for each request based on current capacity and performance. With auto, you don&#39;t need to choose a specific model. Copilot automatical】更快的响应、更低的速率限制机会以及付费用户 10% 的高级请求折扣 - 根据当前容量和性能自动为每个请求选择最佳可用模型。使用汽车，您无需选择特定型号。副驾驶自动</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Perform wide-sweeping refactors using C++ code editing tools for GitHub Copilot】使用 GitHub Copilot 的 C++ 代码编辑工具执行广泛的重构</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/perform-wide-sweeping-refactors-using-c-code-editing-tools-for-github-copilot</link>
      <description>【[cta-button text=&#34;Sign up for our Private Preview&#34; url=&#34;https://aka.ms/code-editing-tools-private-preview&#34; color=&#34;btn-primary&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;] Refactoring a C++ codebase can often require tracking updates across various sections of multiple files to ensure accuracy and relevancy.  Historically, developers have relied on manual searches acr】[cta-button text=&#34;注册我们的私人预览版&#34; url=&#34;https://aka.ms/code-editing-tools-private-preview&#34; color=&#34;btn-primary&#34;align=&#34;center&#34;] 重构 C++ 代码库通常需要跟踪多个文件的各个部分的更新，以确保准确性和相关性。  从历史上看，开发人员一直依赖手动搜索 acr</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Optimize Your C++ Build Times with GitHub Copilot】使用 GitHub Copilot 优化您的 C++ 构建时间</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/optimize-your-c-build-times-with-github-copilot</link>
      <description>【Long build times are one of the top pain points for C++ projects. If you’ve ever waited too long for a C++ build to finish, you know how much it can slow down your productivity. In past years, we introduced C++ Build Insights to help you analyze traces and find bottlenecks. However, we know that】构建时间长是 C++ 项目的最大痛点之一。如果您曾经等待 C++ 构建完成太长时间，您就会知道它会降低您的工作效率。在过去几年中，我们引入了 C++ Build Insights 来帮助您分析跟踪并查找瓶颈。然而，我们知道</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fix build issues using GitHub Copilot after upgrading MSVC Build Tools】升级 MSVC 构建工具后使用 GitHub Copilot 修复构建问题</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/app-modernization-cpp-private-preview</link>
      <description>【[cta-button text=&#34;Sign up for the Private Preview waitlist&#34; url=&#34;https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/C2S6NV3&#34; color=&#34;btn-primary&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;] A few problems have reared their heads at every company where I’ve worked on C++ as a Software Engineer over the past 20 years. For the most part, those problems have nothing to do with the language】[cta-button text=&#34;Sign up for the Private Preview waitlist&#34; url=&#34;https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/C2S6NV3&#34; color=&#34;btn-primary&#34;align=&#34;center&#34;] 在过去 20 年里，我作为软件工程师从事 C++ 工作的每一家公司都出现了一些问题。大多数情况下，这些问题与语言无关</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【October 2025 (version 1.106)】2025 年 10 月（版本 1.106）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/vscode-blog/october-2025-(version-1.106)</link>
      <description>【Learn what is new in the Visual Studio Code October 2025 Release (1.106). Read the full article】了解 Visual Studio Code 2025 年 10 月版 (1.106) 中的新增功能。阅读全文</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Non-recursively deleting a binary tree in constant space: Rotating the tree】非递归删除常量空间中的二叉树：旋转树</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20251112-00/?p=111784</link>
      <description>【Another algorithm for non-recursively deleting the nodes of a binary tree comes from boost. Reading library code is a bit cumbersome because library code tries to be generic, but if you unwind the traits classes, you ge】另一种非递归删除二叉树节点的算法来自 boost。阅读库代码有点麻烦，因为库代码试图通用，但如果您展开特征类，您就会得到</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Fall 2025 Windows Musician Technology and Arm64 Update】2025 年秋季 Windows Musician 技术和 Arm64 更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/windows-music-dev/fall-2025-windows-musician-technology-and-arm64-update</link>
      <description>【It&#39;s no surprise that Arm64 PCs hit a sweet spot for music creation and live performance. They are thin and light, have excellent battery life (I used a Surface Laptop 7 at the entire NAMM show and never had to charge it despite giving presentations and demos), great screens, USB-4 ports that support Thunderbolt 3, and are super quiet. They】毫不奇怪，Arm64 PC 非常适合音乐创作和现场表演。它们轻薄、电池续航时间长（我在整个 NAMM 展会上使用了 Surface Laptop 7，尽管进行了演示和演示，但从未需要充电）、出色的屏幕、支持 Thunderbolt 3 的 USB-4 端口，并且超级安静。他们</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 11:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New for C++ Developers in Visual Studio 2026 version 18.0】Visual Studio 2026 版本 18.0 中 C++ 开发人员的新增功能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-for-cpp-developers-in-visual-studio-2026-version-18-0</link>
      <description>【Get ready to level up your C++ productivity, because Visual Studio 2026 version 18.0 is now generally available! You can take advantage of the new features, bug fixes, and performance improvements in your production environment.】准备好提高您的 C++ 生产力吧，因为 Visual Studio 2026 版本 18.0 现已全面发布！您可以在生产环境中利用新功能、错误修复和性能改进。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Aspire 13 - Aspireify anything】Aspire 13 - 渴望一切</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/aspire/aspire13</link>
      <description>【Major release, major features Aspire 13 is here and it&#39;s - you guessed it - the biggest release yet. We are so excited to share the next major iteration of Aspire with you all, because it&#39;s packed with features that streamline the existing Aspire experience that you all know and love. From complete process overhauls like asp】主要版本、主要功能 Aspire 13 现已发布，您猜对了，它是迄今为止最大的版本。我们很高兴与大家分享 Aspire 的下一个主要版本，因为它包含了一些功能，可以简化你们都知道和喜爱的现有 Aspire 体验。从像asp这样的完整流程大修</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>