<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Why do we have header files &lt;pshpackN.h&gt; and &lt;poppack.h&gt; instead of just issuing the pragma directly?】为什么我们有头文件 &lt;pshpackN.h&gt; 和 &lt;poppack.h&gt; 而不是直接发出 pragma？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241216-00/?p=110645</link>
      <description>【Because the pragma may not work everywhere.】因为该编译指示可能并非在所有地方都有效。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET Conf 2024 Recap – Celebrating .NET 9, AI, Community, &amp; More】.NET Conf 2024 回顾 – 庆祝 .NET 9、AI、社区等</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-conf-2024-recap</link>
      <description>【.NET Conf 2024 is over, but you can catch up with all the announcement and fun with video recordings, slides, demos, and more.】.NET Conf 2024 已经结束，但您可以通过视频录制、幻灯片、演示等了解所有公告和乐趣。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Effortlessly access cloud resources across Azure tenants without using secrets】无需使用密钥即可轻松访问 Azure 租户之间的云资源</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/identity/access-cloud-resources-across-tenants-without-secrets</link>
      <description>【Announcing the Public Preview of Managed Identities as Federated Identity Credentials for Microsoft Entra. Enhance security by removing secrets, simplify setup, and enable seamless cross-tenant access to Entra-protected resources like Azure and Microsoft Graph.】宣布推出作为 Microsoft Entra 联合身份凭证的托管身份的公开预览版。通过删除机密、简化设置以及实现对受 Entra 保护的资源（例如 Azure 和 Microsoft Graph）的无缝跨租户访问来增强安全性。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Refresh your Find results】刷新您的查找结果</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/refresh-your-find-results</link>
      <description>【Are you tired of having to repeatedly launch the Find window in Visual Studio to update your search results? Whether you&amp;#8217;ve just refactored some code or pulled recent changes, having to redo a search to get updated results is no longer necessary. With the new refresh option, you can now update your Find results without [&amp;hellip;]】您是否厌倦了必须在 Visual Studio 中重复启动“查找”窗口来更新搜索结果？无论您刚刚重构了一些代码还是提取了最近的更改，都不再需要重新搜索才能获取更新的结果。使用新的刷新选项，您现在可以更新查找结果，而无需 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 13:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Exploring Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData with Qdrant and Azure AI Search】使用 Qdrant 和 Azure AI 搜索探索 Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/vector-data-qdrant-ai-search-dotnet</link>
      <description>【Discover how to use Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData to implement semantic search using Qdrant and Azure AI Search】了解如何使用 Microsoft.Extensions.VectorData 通过 Qdrant 和 Azure AI 搜索实现语义搜索</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microspeak terms that didn’t take hold: airspace, synthetics, and AOI】未流行的 Microspeak 术语：空域、合成物和 AOI</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241217-00/?p=110647</link>
      <description>【Sometimes they don&#39;t stick.】有时它们不粘。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【GitHub Copilot Free is here in Visual Studio】GitHub Copilot 免费位于 Visual Studio 中</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/github-copilot-free-is-here-in-visual-studio</link>
      <description>【If you haven’t already heard, GitHub just announced Copilot Free! And great news: you can already start using Copilot Free right now in Visual Studio. It&amp;#8217;s available now, and we&amp;#8217;re putting the finishing touches on a more streamlined experience in January. We’re excited to bring these benefits to the entire Visual Studio family. With Copilot [&amp;hellip;]】如果您还没有听说过，GitHub 刚刚宣布了 Copilot 免费！好消息：您现在就可以在 Visual Studio 中开始使用 Copilot Free。它现已推出，我们将在一月份对更加简化的体验进行收尾工作。我们很高兴能够将这些优势带给整个 Visual Studio 系列。与副驾驶[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Is there a way to split the git history of a file or combine the histories of two files without a merge commit?】有没有办法分割文件的 git 历史记录或合并两个文件的历史记录而无需合并提交？</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241218-00/?p=110655</link>
      <description>【Studying how git recovers history.】研究 git 如何恢复历史记录。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Embedding models and dimensions: optimizing the performance to resource-usage ratio】嵌入模型和维度：优化性能与资源利用率</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/embedding-models-and-dimensions-optimizing-the-performance-resource-usage-ratio</link>
      <description>【Since the release of vector preview, we&amp;#8217;ve been working with many customers that are building AI solution on Azure SQL and SQL Server and one of the most common questions is how to support high-dimensional data, for example more than 2000 dimensions per vector. In fact, at the moment, the vector type supports &amp;#8220;only&amp;#8221; up [&amp;hellip;]】自矢量预览版发布以来，我们一直在与许多在 Azure SQL 和 SQL Server 上构建 AI 解决方案的客户合作，最常见的问题之一是如何支持高维数据，例如每个矢量超过 2000 个维度。事实上，目前，向量类型“仅”支持 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 16:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SQL ❤️ Python!】Azure SQL ❤️ Python！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/azure-sql-loves-python</link>
      <description>【I recently presented at Python Day 2024 on Langchain integration. I created a slide deck that I believe can be useful beyond just the session, so I wanted to share it here for everyone&amp;#8217;s benefit. The deck covers the most common topics for a Python developer: Is there a free version of SQL Server or [&amp;hellip;]】我最近在 2024 年 Python Day 上发表了有关 Langchain 集成的演讲。我创建了一个幻灯片，我相信它除了会议之外还有用，所以我想在这里分享它，以造福于每个人。该套牌涵盖了 Python 开发人员最常见的主题：是否有 SQL Server 的免费版本或 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 22:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>