<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Empowering every developer with trusted Microsoft insights</description>
    <item>
      <title>【Customizing collapsed text Indicators】自定义崩溃的文本指示器</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/customizing-collapsed-text-indicators</link>
      <description>【Visual Studio 2022 introduces new options for customizing the collapsed text indicator, which helps in distinguishing between different sections of collapsed text in the editor. This aims to make the coding environment more intuitive and easier to use by providing additional customization for visual cues. Customizing your coding environment You can now personalize the color [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio 2022介绍了用于自定义折叠文本指示器的新选项，该选项有助于区分编辑器中崩溃的文本的不同部分。这旨在通过为视觉提示提供其他自定义，使编码环境更加直观，更易于使用。自定义您的编码环境您现在可以个性化颜色[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Build Intelligent Apps with .NET and DeepSeek R1 Today!】立即使用.NET和DeepSeek R1构建智能应用程序！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/start-building-an-intelligent-app-with-dotnet-and-deep-seek</link>
      <description>【Learn how to easily integrate DeepSeek R1 with .NET applications using the Microsoft.Extensions.AI library.】了解如何使用Microsoft.extensions.ai库轻松地将DeepSeek R1与.NET应用程序集成在一起。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 20:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Creating a generic insertion iterator, part 2】创建通用插入迭代器，第2部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20250131-00/?p=110823</link>
      <description>【Satisfying the iterator requirements, perhaps with a little cheating.】满足迭代器的要求，也许有点作弊。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Azure SDK Release (January 2025)】Azure SDK发布（2025年1月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/azure-sdk-release-january-2025</link>
      <description>【Azure SDK releases every month. In this post, you find this month&#39;s highlights and release notes.】Azure SDK每月发布。在这篇文章中，您可以找到本月的亮点和发行说明。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 17:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Blog Migration on February 5th】博客迁移于2月5日</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/qsharp/blog-migration-on-february-5th</link>
      <description>【We are thrilled to announce that the Q# blog will be moving to a new home at Azure Quantum Technical Blog on February 5, 2025. This will enable us to offer you a more seamless and enhanced experience through a single integrated platform, featuring the latest information and resources in quantum computing. &amp;nbsp; Best regards, The [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布，Q＃博客将于2025年2月5日搬到Azure Quantum技术博客的新家。这将使我们通过单个集成平台为您提供更加无缝和增强的体验量子计算中的信息和资源。   最好的问候，[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing the Microsoft Graph Export-Import APIs for Exchange in public preview】在公共预览中介绍Microsoft Graph Export-Import API</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/microsoft365dev/introducing-the-microsoft-graph-export-import-apis-for-exchange-in-public-preview</link>
      <description>【We are happy to announce the launch of Export-Import APIs in limited Public Preview (Beta), a set of Microsoft Graph APIs that empower applications to discover, export and import contents from Exchange Online mailboxes in full fidelity.】我们很高兴地宣布在有限的公共预览（Beta）中启动出口Import API，这是一组Microsoft Graph API，授权应用程序从完全保真的交换在线邮箱中发现，导出和导入内容。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 22:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【A look into the new architecture on RNW 0.76 and 0.77!】查看RNW 0.76和0.77上的新体系结构！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/react-native/2025-01-29-new-architecture-on-0-76-0-77</link>
      <description>【We&#39;ve recently released React Native Windows 0.76 and 0.77- marking the first time we invite developers to create RNW experiences on the new architecture.】我们最近发布了React Native Windows 0.76和0.77-标志着我们首次邀请开发人员在新体系结构上创建RNW体验。</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing AMQP v2 stack engine support in the Azure Messaging Event Hubs library for Java】在Azure消息传递活动中心库中宣布AMQP V2堆栈引擎支持Java</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sdk/announcing-amqp-v2-stack-engine-support-in-the-azure-messaging-event-hubs-library-for-java</link>
      <description>【This blog post announces a new stable release of the Azure Event Hubs library for Java, with enhanced reliability and performance.】这篇博客文章宣布了Java的Azure Event Hubs库的新稳定版本，具有增强的可靠性和性能。</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Hot Reload in Data API builder Now Available】热门重新加载数据API构建器现已可用</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/hot-reload-in-data-api-builder-now-available</link>
      <description>【Announcing Hot Reload In a recent release, Data API builder (DAB) announced support for Hot Reload. This allows developers to modify the configuration file, save it and see the impact of those changes without restarting the engine. This tightens the loop, allowing developers to tune their implementation without waiting for needless tear down/set up operations. [&amp;hellip;]】Data API Builder（DAB）在最近的版本中宣布Hot Relooad宣布了对热重新加载的支持。这使开发人员可以修改配置文件，保存并查看这些更改的影响而无需重新启动引擎。这可以收紧循环，使开发人员可以在不等待不必要的拆除/设置操作的情况下调整实施。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 23:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【PIX 2501.30-preview: Application Specific Driver State, Recreate At GPUVA and Tight Alignment】PIX 2501.30访问：应用程序特定驱动程序状态，在GPUVA重新创建和紧密对齐</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/pix/pix-2501-30-preview</link>
      <description>【Today we released PIX version 2501.30-preview, available for download here. This release has initial support for the exciting new D3D12 features that were released in a preview DirectX Agility SDK today. Please visit this blog post for more information about the Agility SDK release. 2501.30-preview is a preview version of PIX. It is identical to 2501.30 [&amp;hellip;]】今天，我们发布了PIX版本2501.30-preview，可在此处下载。该版本对令人兴奋的新D3D12功能有初步的支持，这些功能今天发布了Preview DirectX Agility SDK中。请访问此博客文章以获取有关敏捷性SDK版本的更多信息。 2501.30-preview是Pix的预览版。它与2501.30相同[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>