<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft Developer Blogs</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, announcements, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET and .NET Framework October 2024 servicing releases updates】.NET 和 .NET Framework 2024 年 10 月服务版本更新</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-and-dotnet-framework-october-2024-servicing-updates</link>
      <description>【A recap of the latest servicing updates for .NET and .NET Framework for October 2024.】2024 年 10 月 .NET 和 .NET Framework 的最新服务更新回顾。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Announcing Private Preview: VS Code Extension of vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB】宣布私人预览版：基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB 的 VS Code 扩展</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/announcing-private-preview-vs-code-extension-of-vcore-based-azure-cosmos-db-for-mongodb</link>
      <description>【Overview We&amp;#8217;re excited to introduce a new VS Code extension for vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB ! This tool allows users to connect, query, and manage vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB directly within VS Code, streamlining your workflow. Limited Private Preview  We’re currently offering a limited private preview of the VSCode extension for [&amp;hellip;]】概述 我们很高兴为基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB 推出新的 VS Code 扩展！该工具允许用户直接在 VS Code 中连接、查询和管理基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB，从而简化工作流程。有限的私人预览我们目前正在为 [...] 提供 VSCode 扩展的有限的私人预览</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【.NET 9 Release Candidate 2 is now available!】.NET 9 候选版本 2 现已推出！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/dotnet-9-rc-2</link>
      <description>【Try out the latest features in .NET 9 Release Candidate 2 across the .NET SDK, libraries, runtime, ASP.NET Core, SignalR, .NET MAUI, and more!】尝试 .NET 9 Release Candidate 2 中跨 .NET SDK、库、运行时、ASP.NET Core、SignalR、.NET MAUI 等的最新功能！</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing New Storage Sizes for vCore-Based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB: Unlock More Capacity and Performance】为基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB 引入新的存储大小：释放更多容量和性能</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/introducing-new-storage-sizes-for-vcore-based-azure-cosmos-db-for-mongodb-unlock-more-capacity-and-performance</link>
      <description>【We’re thrilled to announce the preview of new storage sizes for vCore-based Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB, designed to provide more capacity and enhanced performance for your MongoDB workloads. Whether you’re managing large, complex datasets or high-throughput applications, these new storage tiers—8 TiB, 16 TiB, and 32 TiB per physical shard—offer the flexibility to scale [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布推出基于 vCore 的 Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB 的新存储大小预览，旨在为 MongoDB 工作负载提供更多容量和增强的性能。无论您是管理大型、复杂的数据集还是高吞吐量应用程序，这些新的存储层（每个物理分片 8 TiB、16 TiB 和 32 TiB）都提供了扩展的灵活性 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft.Extensions.AI: Simplifying AI Integration for .NET Partners】Microsoft.Extensions.AI：简化 .NET 合作伙伴的 AI 集成</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/microsoft-extensions-ai-simplifying-ai-integration-for-net-partners</link>
      <description>【We are thrilled to announce the launch of Microsoft.Extensions.AI for .NET! Our collaboration with the .NET team since the debut of Semantic Kernel has resulted in a powerful new feature that aligns with the best practices of both current and upcoming .NET releases. With the introduction of Microsoft.Extensions.AI, Independent Software Vendors (ISVs) and AI solution [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布推出 Microsoft.Extensions.AI for .NET！自 Semantic Kernel 首次亮相以来，我们与 .NET 团队的合作带来了一项强大的新功能，该功能与当前和即将发布的 .NET 版本的最佳实践保持一致。随着 Microsoft.Extensions.AI、独立软件供应商 (ISV) 和 AI 解决方案的推出 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Configure GitHub Copilot Access via Content Exclusion】通过内容排除配置 GitHub Copilot 访问</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/configure-github-copilot-access-via-content-exclusion</link>
      <description>【Have you ever wanted greater control over the sensitive content AI-powered tools can access in your repositories? You can now customize Copilot’s access to your files with the newly announced GitHub Copilot Content Exclusion in both Visual Studio and Visual Studio Code. Through this new process you can configure Copilot to ignore certain files in your [&amp;hellip;]】您是否曾经想要更好地控制人工智能支持的工具可以在您的存储库中访问的敏感内容？现在，您可以使用 Visual Studio 和 Visual Studio Code 中新发布的 GitHub Copilot 内容排除功能自定义 Copilot 对文件的访问权限。通过这个新过程，您可以将 Copilot 配置为忽略 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 23:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microsoft DiskANN in Azure Cosmos DB Whitepaper】Azure Cosmos DB 中的 Microsoft DiskANN 白皮书</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/microsoft-diskann-in-azure-cosmos-db-whitepaper</link>
      <description>【We are excited to publish a new whitepaper titled, Microsoft DiskANN in Azure Cosmos DB, where we examine the impressive capabilities of Microsoft DiskANN, a state-of-the-art indexing system designed for accurate and cost-efficient vector search at any scale. We start off with a review of key vector search and database concepts, then follow by describing [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴发布题为《Azure Cosmos DB 中的 Microsoft DiskANN》的新白皮书，其中我们研究了 Microsoft DiskANN 的令人印象深刻的功能，这是一种最先进的索引系统，专为任何规模的准确且经济高效的矢量搜索而设计。我们首先回顾关键向量搜索和数据库概念，然后描述[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Microspeak: Run to ground】Microspeak：跑到地面</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/oldnewthing/20241008-00/?p=110351</link>
      <description>【Come to a resolution.】做出决定。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【What’s New in vcpkg (September 2024)】vcpkg 的新增功能（2024 年 9 月）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cppblog/whats-new-in-vcpkg-september-2024</link>
      <description>【This blog post summarizes changes to the vcpkg package manager as part of the 2024.09.23 and 2024.09.30 releases, 2024-09-18 and 2024-09-30 tool releases, as well as changes to vcpkg documentation throughout September. This month’s release includes some minor changes and bug fixes, 18 new ports, and 319 updates to existing ports. When updating vcpkg, we [&amp;hellip;]】本博文总结了 2024.09.23 和 2024.09.30 版本、2024-09-18 和 2024-09-30 工具版本中对 vcpkg 包管理器的更改，以及整个 9 月份对 vcpkg 文档的更改。本月的版本包括一些细微的更改和错误修复、18 个新端口以及对现有端口的 319 个更新。更新 vcpkg 时，我们 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 01:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Introducing Microsoft.Extensions.AI Preview – Unified AI Building Blocks for .NET】隆重推出 Microsoft.Extensions.AI 预览版 – .NET 的统一 AI 构建块</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/introducing-microsoft-extensions-ai-preview</link>
      <description>【We are excited to introduce the Microsoft.Extensions.AI package available in preview today. This new package provides a unified abstraction layer that enables you to integrate AI services into your .NET applications.】我们很高兴推出今天提供预览版的 Microsoft.Extensions.AI 包。这个新包提供了统一的抽象层，使您能够将 AI 服务集成到 .NET 应用程序中。</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>