<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft for Developers</title>
    <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/landingpage/</link>
    <description>Get the latest information, insights, and news from Microsoft.</description>
    <item>
      <title>【DiskANN and Filtered Vector Search are Now Generally Available in Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB (vCore)】现在通常可以在Azure Cosmos DB（VCORE）中获得Diskann和过滤的矢量搜索（VCORE）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/diskann-in-azure-cosmos-db-for-mongodb</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce general availability of DiskANN and Filtered Vector Search on Azure Cosmos DB for MongoDB (vCore), starting with M30 cluster tiers and above. You can now use these features in production to store and query vector embeddings directly alongside your operational data—efficiently and in one integrated vector database.  DiskANN Indexing: Scaling Vector [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴地宣布，从M30群集层及更高版本开始，在Azure Cosmos DB（VCORE）上，在Azure Cosmos db上进行了diskann和过滤矢量搜索的一般可用性。现在，您可以在生产中使用这些功能来存储和查询矢量嵌入，并在一个集成的矢量数据库中直接与操作数据一起使用。  diskann索引：缩放向量[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Connecting to Private NuGet Feeds Just Got Easier】连接到私人Nuget feed变得更加容易</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/visualstudio/connecting-to-private-nuget-feeds-just-got-easier</link>
      <description>【The Visual Studio 2022 17.14 update is here, and it brings great quality-of-life improvements—especially around NuGet authentication. From context about the authentication needs of private NuGet feeds to a simplified account selection workflow, this update helps you stay focused on your code! If you haven’t already, download the latest Visual Studio update to take advantage [&amp;hellip;]】Visual Studio 2022 17.14更新在这里，它带来了巨大的生活质量改进，尤其是Nuget身份验证。从关于私人Nuget Feed的身份验证需求到简化帐户选择工作流程的上下文，此更新可帮助您专注于代码！如果您还没有，请下载最新的Visual Studio更新以利用优势[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Semantic Kernel and Microsoft.Extensions.AI: Better Together, Part 1】语义内核和Microsoft.extensions.ai：更好地在一起，第1部分</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/semantic-kernel-and-microsoft-extensions-ai-better-together-part-1</link>
      <description>【This is the start of a series highlighting the integration between Microsoft Semantic Kernel and Microsoft.Extensions.AI. Future parts will provide detailed examples of using Semantic Kernel with Microsoft.Extensions.AI abstractions.  The most common questions are:  &amp;#8220;Do Microsoft&amp;#8217;s AI extensions replace Semantic Kernel?&amp;#8221;  &amp;#8220;When should I use Microsoft&amp;#8217;s AI extensions instead of Semantic Kernel?&amp;#8221;  This blog post [&amp;hellip;]】这是一个系列的开始，突出了Microsoft语义内核和Microsoft.extensions.ai之间的集成。未来的部分将提供使用Microsoft.extensions.ai摘要使用语义内核的详细示例。  最常见的问题是：“微软的AI扩展是否取代语义内核？”  “我什么时候应该使用Microsoft的AI扩展而不是语义内核？”  这篇博客文章[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Transitioning to new Extensions AI IEmbeddingGenerator interface】过渡到新的扩展名AI iembedgingGenerator界面</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/semantic-kernel/transitioning-to-new-iembeddinggenerator-interface</link>
      <description>【As Semantic Kernel shifts its foundational abstractions to Microsoft.Extensions.AI, we are obsoleting and moving away from our experimental embeddings interfaces to the new standardized abstractions that provide a more consistent and powerful way to work with AI services across the .NET ecosystem. The Evolution of Embedding Generation in Semantic Kernel Semantic Kernel has always aimed [&amp;hellip;]】随着语义内核将其基本抽象转移到microsoft.extensions.ai时，我们正在淘汰并从实验性嵌入界面转移到新的标准化抽象，这些抽象提供了一种更加一致，更有力的方式，可以在.NET生态系统中使用AI服务。在语义内核语义内核中嵌入产生的演变一直以目标为目标[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【MSSQL Extension for VS Code: Introducing Schema Designer (Preview)】VS代码的MSSQL扩展名：介绍模式设计器（预览）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/azure-sql/vs-code-mssql-schema-designer</link>
      <description>【Overview Database design can often feel like navigating a maze of tables, relationships, and data types — especially when working directly with T-SQL scripts. But what if you could map out your database, make changes to your tables, and manage complex schemas within a graphical interface? We are excited to announce the Public Preview of [&amp;hellip;]】概述数据库设计通常会感觉像是导航表，关系和数据类型的迷宫，尤其是直接使用T-SQL脚本时。但是，如果您可以映射数据库，对表进行更改并在图形接口中管理复杂的模式怎么办？我们很高兴宣布[…]的公众预览</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Connect Once, Integrate Anywhere with MCP】连接一次，与MCP的任何地方集成</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/blog/connect-once-integrate-anywhere-with-mcps</link>
      <description>【In the fast-paced world of AI development, connecting intelligent applications to the tools and data sources they need can be challenging. That&amp;#8217;s why Model Context Protocol (MCP) is resonating with some many, an open standard that&amp;#8217;s transforming how developers integrate AI capabilities into their applications. MCP enables you to &amp;#8220;connect once, integrate anywhere&amp;#8221; by creating [&amp;hellip;]】在AI开发快节奏的世界中，将智能应用程序与所需的工具和数据源联系起来可能具有挑战性。这就是为什么模型上下文协议（MCP）引起了许多开放标准的共鸣，这是一个开发者如何将AI功能集成到其应用程序中的原因。 MCP使您可以通过创建[…]来“连接一次，整合到任何地方”</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Now in Preview: Azure Cosmos DB Fleets】现在在预览中：Azure Cosmos DB舰队</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/cosmosdb/now-in-preview-azure-cosmos-db-fleets</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce the preview of Azure Cosmos DB fleets. Azure Cosmos DB fleets address common challenges that developers face when building and managing multi-tenant or Software as a Service (SaaS) applications. Today, many SaaS providers using Azure Cosmos DB isolate each tenant in a separate database account to meet strict performance and security [&amp;hellip;]】我们很高兴宣布Azure Cosmos DB舰队的预览。 Azure Cosmos DB车队应对开发人员在构建和管理多租户或软件作为服务（SaaS）应用程序时面临的共同挑战。如今，许多SaaS提供商使用Azure Cosmos DB隔离每个租户在单独的数据库帐户中，以满足严格的性能和安全性[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI and Vector Data Extensions are now Generally Available (GA)】AI和向量数据扩展现在通常可用（GA）</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/dotnet/ai-vector-data-dotnet-extensions-ga</link>
      <description>【We’re excited to announce that these extensions are now generally available, providing developers with a robust foundation to build scalable, maintainable, and interoperable AI-powered applications.】我们很高兴地宣布，这些扩展名现在通常可用，为开发人员提供了坚固的基础，以构建可扩展，可维护和可互操作的AI驱动应用程序。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【Foundry Local: A New Era of Edge AI】Foundry Local：Edge AI的新时代</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/foundry/foundry-local-a-new-era-of-edge-ai</link>
      <description>【At Microsoft Build 2025, Microsoft unveiled its groundbreaking Foundry Local solution for edge devices—an efficient platform specifically designed for local AI inference. As a critical component of Microsoft&amp;#8217;s AI strategy, Foundry Local empowers developers to smoothly deploy and run Small Language Models (SLMs) on resource-constrained edge devices, opening new possibilities for the convergence of edge computing and [&amp;hellip;]】在Microsoft Build 2025，Microsoft推出了其开创性的Edge设备的本地解决方案，这是一个专门针对本地AI推理设计的有效平台。作为Microsoft AI策略的关键组成部分，Foundry Local Emplater开发人员可以在资源受限的边缘设备上平稳部署和运行小语言模型（SLM），为Edge Computing和[…]的收敛开辟了新的可能性</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【AI Shell Preview 4 Release!】AI Shell Preview 4版本！</title>
      <link>https://devblogs.microsoft.com/powershell/preview-4-ai-shell</link>
      <description>【We&#39;re excited to share the latest preview release of AI Shell that includes new features and improvements based on your feedback.】我们很高兴分享AI Shell的最新预览版本，该版本包括基于您的反馈的新功能和改进。</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>