<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SRE WEEKLY</title>
    <link>https://sreweekly.com/feed/</link>
    <description>scalability, availability, incident response, automation</description>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #458】SRE周刊＃458</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-458/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Ever wonder how Netflix handles incidents at their scale? With incident.io, they’ve built a process that’s smooth, scalable, and keeps everyone on the same page. Tools like Catalog and Workflows make it intuitive for teams to tackle incidents consistently—no matter how big the challenge. https://incident.io/customers/netflix Your [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Actist.io的消息：Yetflix是否会在其规模上处理事件？借助Invist.io，他们构建了一个流程，可扩展的过程，并将每个人都放在同一页面上。诸如目录和工作流程之类的工具使团队始终如一地解决事件的直观，而无需挑战。 https://incident.io/customers/netflix您的[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #457】SRE周刊＃457</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-457/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, FireHydrant: This New Year, resolve to make incident management smarter, faster, and way less stressful with FireHydrant. Modern on-call, automated incident response, and AI tools that do the heavy lifting. https://firehydrant.com/ Preventing Out-of-Memory (OOM) Kills in Kubernetes: Tips for Optimizing Container Memory Management In this post, we’ll [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Firedhydrant的信息：新的一年，决心使事件管理更聪明，更快，并且使用Firedhyhrant的压力较小。现代的呼叫，自动事件响应和AI工具可以繁重。 https://firehydrant.com/在Kubernetes中防止杀死杀死（OOM）：在这篇文章中优化容器内存管理的提示，我们将[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #459】SRE周刊＃459</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-459/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Effective incident management demands coordination and collaboration to minimize disruptions. This guide by incident.io covers the full incident lifecycle—from preparation to improvement—emphasizing teamwork beyond engineering. By engineers, for engineers. https://incident.io/guide How to end-to-end test microservices across bounded contexts? In a microservices environment, testing user journeys that [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Insped.io的消息：有效的事件管理要求协调和协作以最大程度地减少干扰。该指南逐个指南。IO涵盖了整个事件生命周期（从准备到改进），强调了工程以外的团队合作。工程师，工程师。 https://incident.io/guide如何在有限的上下文中端对端测试微服务？在微服务环境中，测试用户旅行[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 02:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #461】SRE周刊＃461</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-461/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Effective incident management demands coordination and collaboration to minimize disruptions. This guide by incident.io covers the full incident lifecycle—from preparation to improvement—emphasizing teamwork beyond engineering. By engineers, for engineers. https://incident.io/guide The importance of resilience engineering Written in 2020 after an AWS outage, this article analyzes dependence [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Insped.io的消息：有效的事件管理要求协调和协作以最大程度地减少干扰。该指南逐个指南。IO涵盖了整个事件生命周期（从准备到改进），强调了工程以外的团队合作。工程师，工程师。 https://incident.io/guide在AWS中断后在2020年撰写的弹性工程的重要性，本文分析了依赖[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 04:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #460】SRE周刊＃460</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-460/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: See how Netflix scaled their incident management with incident.io. By leveraging intuitive tools like Catalog and Workflows, they built a streamlined, scalable process that empowers teams to handle incidents with ease and consistency—even at Netflix’s scale. https://incident.io/customers/netflix An Incident Review of an Incident Review So I [&amp;#8230;]】在sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Insped.io中的一条消息：请参阅Netflix如何通过ISCOST.IO缩放其事件管理。通过利用目录和工作流程等直观工具，他们构建了一个简化的可扩展过程，该过程使团队能够轻松且一致地处理事件，即使是Netflix的规模也是如此。 https://incident.io/customers/netflix事件审查的事件评论，我[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 02:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>