<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SRE WEEKLY</title>
    <link>https://sreweekly.com/feed/</link>
    <description>scalability, availability, incident response, automation</description>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #491】SRE周刊＃491</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-491/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Spacelift: Infrastructure Security Virtual Event &amp;#8211; This Wednesday, August 27 Join the IaCConf community on August 27 for a free virtual event that dives into IaC security best practices and real-world stories. Hear from three speakers on: Taking a Platform Approach to Safer Infrastructure How Tagged, Vetted [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Spacelift：基础设施安全虚拟活动的信息 -  8月27日，星期三，8月27日星期三加入IACCONF社区，以获取免费的虚拟活动，以潜入IAC安全最佳实践和现实世界中的故事。从三位发言人那里听到有关：采用平台方法来更安全的基础架构。</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #490】SRE周刊＃490</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-490/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Observe, Inc.: Built on a scalable, cost-efficient data lake, Observe delivers AI-powered observability at scale. With its context-aware Knowledge Graph and AI SRE, Observe enables Capital One, Topgolf, and Dialpad to ingest hundreds of terabytes daily and resolve issues faster—at drastically lower cost. Learn how Observe is [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商，Observe，Inc。的消息：建立在可扩展的，具有成本效益的数据湖上，Obseres在大规模上提供了AI驱动的可观察性。凭借其上下文感知的知识图和AI SRE，可以观察到Capital One，TopGolf和Dialpad每天摄入数百个Terabytes，并更快地解决问题，这要降低成本的较低。了解观察是如何[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 02:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #489】SRE周刊＃489</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-489/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Observe, Inc.: Observe&amp;#8216;s free Masterclass in Observability at Scale is coming on September 4th at 10am Pacific! We’ll explore how to architect for observability at scale &amp;#8211; from streaming telemetry and open data lakes to AI agents that proactively instrument your code and surface insights. Learn more [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商，Observe，Inc.。的消息：观察免费的大师班的观察性大规模可观察到了太平洋的9月4日上午10点！我们将探讨如何在大规模构建可观察性 - 从遥测和开放数据湖到主动地启用您的代码和表面见解的AI代理。了解更多 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 02:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #488】SRE周刊＃488</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-488/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Observe, Inc.: Observe&amp;#8216;s free Masterclass in Observability at Scale is coming on September 4th at 10am Pacific! We’ll explore how to architect for observability at scale &amp;#8211; from streaming telemetry and open data lakes to AI agents that proactively instrument your code and surface insights. Learn more [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商，Observe，Inc.。的消息：观察免费的大师班的观察性大规模可观察到了太平洋的9月4日上午10点！我们将探讨如何在大规模构建可观察性 - 从遥测和开放数据湖到主动地启用您的代码和表面见解的AI代理。了解更多 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 01:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #487】SRE周刊＃487</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-487/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Spacelift: IaC Experts! IaCConf Call for Presenters &amp;#8211; August 27, 2025The upcoming IaCConf Spotlight dives into the security and governance challenges of managing infrastructure as code at scale. From embedding security in your pipelines to navigating the realities of open source risk, this event brings together practitioners [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Spacelift：IAC专家的消息！ IACCONF呼吁主持人 -  2025年8月27日，即将到来的IACCONF聚光灯潜入安全和治理挑战的挑战，即将基础架构作为大规模代码。从嵌入管道中的安全性到导航开源风险的现实，此事件将从业人员汇集在一起​​[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 02:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>