<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SRE WEEKLY</title>
    <link>https://sreweekly.com/feed/</link>
    <description>scalability, availability, incident response, automation</description>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #469】SRE周刊＃469</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-469/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Speed isn’t everything. We studied 100K+ incidents to find out what actually makes for good incident management—from detection to follow-up. You can now view the recording of our latest live event to get even more info on the benchmarks, insights, and real-life examples from the report. [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Actist.io：速度并不是一切。我们研究了100K+事件，以找出从检测到后续行动真正造就良好事件管理的原因。现在，您可以查看我们最新的现场活动的录制，以获取有关报告的基准，见解和现实生活示例的更多信息。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #467】SRE周刊＃467</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-467/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: SEV0 is back. This fall, we’re bringing together the best minds in incident management for a day of learning, sharing, and networking in San Francisco and London. RSVP now—tickets are complimentary. https://go.incident.io/SEV0-2025 Introducing the Resilience in Software Foundation It&amp;#8217;s been awhile since we&amp;#8217;ve seen any updates [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Actist.io：Sev0回来的消息。今年秋天，我们将在旧金山和伦敦的学习，分享和网络的一天中汇集事件管理中最好的思想。 RSVP现在 - 门票是免费的。 https://go.incident.io/sev0-2025介绍了软件基金会的弹性，因为我们已经看到了任何更新[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 01:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #468】SRE周刊＃468</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-468/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: MTTx metrics fall short—learn the new industry benchmarks for measuring and improving incident management. Join us on Tuesday, March 18th to discover data-driven insights from 100K+ incidents and practical steps to enhance your response strategy. https://go.incident.io/registration.goldcast.io/webinar/going-beyond-mttx-measuring-what-good-incident-management-looks-like You Can’t Build More Nines No matter how bullet-proof you [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Insped.io的消息：MTTX指标不足 - 确定了用于衡量和改善事件管理的新行业基准。 3月18日（星期二）加入我们，以发现100k+事件的数据驱动见解以及增强您的响应策略的实用步骤。 https://go.incident.io/registration.goldcast.io/webinar/down-beyond-measuring-what what what what what what what what what good-incident-management-management-management-looks like like无论您多么防弹，您都无法建立更多的nines […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #466】SRE周刊＃466</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-466/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A bit of a short issue this week, as I spent most of my weekend at my child&amp;#8217;s first First Robotics Competition of the season. FRC truly is a microcosm of reliability engineering, balancing limited time and resources while trying to produce the most reliable bot possible. A message from our sponsor, [&amp;#8230;]】本周在Sreweekly.com上查看一些简短的问题，因为我大部分周末都在孩子本赛季的首个机器人比赛中度过。 FRC确实是可靠性工程的缩影，平衡有限的时间和资源，同时试图生产最可靠的机器人。我们的赞助商的消息，[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #465】SRE周刊＃465</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-465/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: On-call shouldn’t be a constant source of stress. On Feb 26 at 1 PM EST, join us to hear from teams who’ve moved from PagerDuty to incident.io On-call—reducing noise, improving alerting, and making on-call less painful. Insights from engineers who’ve been there. https://go.incident.io/events/migrating-from-pagerduty Incident Report: Dec [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Insped.io的消息：呼叫不应该是不断的压力来源。美国东部时间2月26日下午1点，加入我们，听取从Pagerduty转移到事件的团队的来信。IOOIO待命 - 降低噪音，提高警报，并使电话痛苦减轻。去过那里的工程师的见解。 https://go.incident.io/events/migrating-from-pagerduty事件报告：DEC […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 01:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>