<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SRE WEEKLY</title>
    <link>https://sreweekly.com/feed/</link>
    <description>scalability, availability, incident response, automation</description>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #501】SRE 周刊第 #501 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-501/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Depot: &amp;#8220;Waiting for a runner&amp;#8221; but the runner is online? Depot debugs three cases where symptoms misled engineers. Workflow permissions, Azure authentication, and Dependabot&amp;#8217;s security context all caused failures that looked like infrastructure problems. AI and the ironies of automation &amp;#8211; Part 1 A thoughtful evaluation of [&amp;#8230;]】在 sreweekly.com 上查看 来自我们的赞助商 Depot 的消息：“正在等待跑步者”，但跑步者在线？ Depot 调试了三个症状误导工程师的案例。工作流权限、Azure 身份验证和 Dependabot 的安全上下文都导致了看似基础设施问题的故障。人工智能和自动化的讽刺 – 第 1 部分 对 [...] 的深思熟虑的评估</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 03:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #500】SRE 周刊第 500 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-500/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Depot: Stop hunting through GitHub Actions logs. Depot now offers powerful CI log search across all your repositories and workflows. With smart filtering by timeframe, runner type, and keywords, you’ll have all the information at your fingertips to debug faster. Wow, five hundred issues! I sent the [&amp;#8230;]】在 sreweekly.com 上查看来自我们的赞助商 Depot 的消息：停止通过 GitHub Actions 日志进行搜索。 Depot 现在提供跨所有存储库和工作流程的强大 CI 日志搜索。通过按时间范围、跑步者类型和关键字进行智能过滤，您将掌握所有信息，以便更快地进行调试。哇，五百个问题！我发送了[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 02:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #499】SRE 周刊第 #499 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-499/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com Fix-mas Countdown The folks at Uptime Labs and Advanced Capacity Labs have announced an advent calendar for this December. Note: In order to take part, you&amp;#8217;ll need to provide an email address to subscribe. I gave that some serious thought before including this here, but ultimately, I have a lot of trust [&amp;#8230;]】请在 sreweekly.com 上查看 Fix-mas 倒计时 Uptime Labs 和 Advanced Capacity Labs 的人员宣布​​了今年 12 月的降临日历。注意：为了参加，您需要提供一个电子邮件地址来订阅。在将其放在这里之前，我认真考虑过这一点，但最终，我非常信任 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #498】SRE 周刊第 #498 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-498/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Costory: You didn’t sign up to do FinOps. Costory automatically explains why your cloud costs change, and reports it straight to Slack. Built for SREs who want to code, not wrestle with spreadsheets. Now on AWS &amp;#38; GCP Marketplaces. Start your free trial at costory.io Cloudflare outage [&amp;#8230;]】在 sreweekly.com 上查看 来自我们的赞助商 Costory 的消息：您没有报名参加 FinOps。 Costory 会自动解释您的云成本变化的原因，并将其直接报告给 Slack。专为想要编码而不是与电子表格纠缠的 SRE 构建。现已在 AWS 和 GCP 市场上推出。在 costory.io 开始免费试用 Cloudflare 中断 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #497】SRE 周刊第 #497 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-497/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Costory: You didn’t sign up to do FinOps.Costory automatically explains why your cloud costs change, and reports it straight to Slack.Built for SREs who want to code, not wrestle with spreadsheets.Now on AWS &amp;#38; GCP Marketplaces. Start your free trial at costory.io To vibe or not to [&amp;#8230;]】在 sreweekly.com 上查看 来自我们的赞助商 Costory 的消息：您没有注册进行 FinOps。Costory 会自动解释您的云成本变化的原因，并直接向 Slack 报告。专为想要编码而不是与电子表格搏斗的 SRE 构建。现在在 AWS 和 GCP Marketplaces 上。在 costory.io 开始免费试用 是否振动 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>