<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SRE WEEKLY</title>
    <link>https://sreweekly.com/feed/</link>
    <description>scalability, availability, incident response, automation</description>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #467】SRE周刊＃467</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-467/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: SEV0 is back. This fall, we’re bringing together the best minds in incident management for a day of learning, sharing, and networking in San Francisco and London. RSVP now—tickets are complimentary. https://go.incident.io/SEV0-2025 Introducing the Resilience in Software Foundation It&amp;#8217;s been awhile since we&amp;#8217;ve seen any updates [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Actist.io：Sev0回来的消息。今年秋天，我们将在旧金山和伦敦的学习，分享和网络的一天中汇集事件管理中最好的思想。 RSVP现在 - 门票是免费的。 https://go.incident.io/sev0-2025介绍了软件基金会的弹性，因为我们已经看到了任何更新[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 01:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #470】SRE周刊＃470</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-470/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Intercom migrated hundreds of engineers from PagerDuty and Atlassian Status Page to incident.io in just weeks, improving resolution times, simplifying incident management, and delivering a better customer support experience. Watch the video case study. https://go.incident.io/customers/intercom The Sociotechnical Reality Engineer An SRE thinks about the meaning of [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Insped.io的消息：对讲机迁移了数百名工程师，从Pagerduty和Atlassian状态页面上迁移到仅几周后的IS INDACT.IO，改善解决方案时间，简化事件管理并提供更好的客户支持体验。观看视频案例研究。 https://go.incident.io/customers/intercom社会技术现实工程师A SRE思考[…]的含义</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #468】SRE周刊＃468</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-468/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: MTTx metrics fall short—learn the new industry benchmarks for measuring and improving incident management. Join us on Tuesday, March 18th to discover data-driven insights from 100K+ incidents and practical steps to enhance your response strategy. https://go.incident.io/registration.goldcast.io/webinar/going-beyond-mttx-measuring-what-good-incident-management-looks-like You Can’t Build More Nines No matter how bullet-proof you [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Insped.io的消息：MTTX指标不足 - 确定了用于衡量和改善事件管理的新行业基准。 3月18日（星期二）加入我们，以发现100k+事件的数据驱动见解以及增强您的响应策略的实用步骤。 https://go.incident.io/registration.goldcast.io/webinar/down-beyond-measuring-what what what what what what what what what good-incident-management-management-management-looks like like无论您多么防弹，您都无法建立更多的nines […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #471】SRE周刊＃471</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-471/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: We’re building an AI agent that investigates incidents with you—diagnosing the problem and even fixing it. Go behind the scenes with the incident.io engineers rethinking what’s possible with AI, one ambitious idea (and bug) at a time. https://go.incident.io/building-with-ai Models, models every where, so let’s have a [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Actist.io的消息：我们正在建立一个与您一起调查事件的AI代理 - 诊断问题甚至解决了问题。事件发生在幕后。io工程师一次重新考虑AI的可能性，一个雄心勃勃的想法（和错误）。 https://go.incident.io/building-with-ai型号，各个模型，所以让我们有一个[…]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 01:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #469】SRE周刊＃469</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-469/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, incident.io: Speed isn’t everything. We studied 100K+ incidents to find out what actually makes for good incident management—from detection to follow-up. You can now view the recording of our latest live event to get even more info on the benchmarks, insights, and real-life examples from the report. [&amp;#8230;]】在Sreweekly.com上查看我们的赞助商Actist.io：速度并不是一切。我们研究了100K+事件，以找出从检测到后续行动真正造就良好事件管理的原因。现在，您可以查看我们最新的现场活动的录制，以获取有关报告的基准，见解和现实生活示例的更多信息。 […]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>