<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SRE WEEKLY</title>
    <link>https://sreweekly.com/feed/</link>
    <description>scalability, availability, incident response, automation</description>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #499】SRE 周刊第 #499 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-499/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com Fix-mas Countdown The folks at Uptime Labs and Advanced Capacity Labs have announced an advent calendar for this December. Note: In order to take part, you&amp;#8217;ll need to provide an email address to subscribe. I gave that some serious thought before including this here, but ultimately, I have a lot of trust [&amp;#8230;]】请在 sreweekly.com 上查看 Fix-mas 倒计时 Uptime Labs 和 Advanced Capacity Labs 的人员宣布​​了今年 12 月的降临日历。注意：为了参加，您需要提供一个电子邮件地址来订阅。在将其放在这里之前，我认真考虑过这一点，但最终，我非常信任 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #498】SRE 周刊第 #498 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-498/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Costory: You didn’t sign up to do FinOps. Costory automatically explains why your cloud costs change, and reports it straight to Slack. Built for SREs who want to code, not wrestle with spreadsheets. Now on AWS &amp;#38; GCP Marketplaces. Start your free trial at costory.io Cloudflare outage [&amp;#8230;]】在 sreweekly.com 上查看 来自我们的赞助商 Costory 的消息：您没有报名参加 FinOps。 Costory 会自动解释您的云成本变化的原因，并将其直接报告给 Slack。专为想要编码而不是与电子表格纠缠的 SRE 构建。现已在 AWS 和 GCP 市场上推出。在 costory.io 开始免费试用 Cloudflare 中断 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 03:38:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #497】SRE 周刊第 #497 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-497/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, Costory: You didn’t sign up to do FinOps.Costory automatically explains why your cloud costs change, and reports it straight to Slack.Built for SREs who want to code, not wrestle with spreadsheets.Now on AWS &amp;#38; GCP Marketplaces. Start your free trial at costory.io To vibe or not to [&amp;#8230;]】在 sreweekly.com 上查看 来自我们的赞助商 Costory 的消息：您没有注册进行 FinOps。Costory 会自动解释您的云成本变化的原因，并直接向 Slack 报告。专为想要编码而不是与电子表格搏斗的 SRE 构建。现在在 AWS 和 GCP Marketplaces 上。在 costory.io 开始免费试用 是否振动 [...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #496】SRE 周刊第 #496 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-496/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com A message from our sponsor, CodeRabbit: CodeRabbit is your AI co-pilot for code reviews. Get instant code review feedback, one-click fix suggestions and define custom rules with AST Grep to catch subtle issues static tools miss. Trusted across 1M repos and 70K open-source projects. ☞ Get Started Today The hidden trade-offs of [&amp;#8230;]】在 sreweekly.com 上查看 来自我们的赞助商 CodeRabbit 的消息：CodeRabbit 是您进行代码审查的 AI 副驾驶。获取即时代码审查反馈、一键修复建议并使用 AST Grep 定义自定义规则，以捕获静态工具遗漏的细微问题。受到 100 万个存储库和 70K 开源项目的信任。 ☞ 今天就开始 […] 的隐藏权衡</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>【SRE Weekly Issue #495】SRE 周刊第 #495 期</title>
      <link>https://sreweekly.com/sre-weekly-issue-495/</link>
      <description>【View on sreweekly.com I&amp;#8217;m back! Kidney donation was a fascinating and rewarding experience, and I encourage you to learn more. It&amp;#8217;s amazing how it&amp;#8217;s possible to fix one human with spare parts from another! I&amp;#8217;ll share more about my experience later, but for now: thank you to the many of you that reached out with [&amp;#8230;]】在 sreweekly.com 上查看 我回来了！肾脏捐赠是一次令人着迷且有益的经历，我鼓励您了解更多。令人惊奇的是如何可以用另一个人的备件来修复一个人！稍后我将分享更多关于我的经历，但现在：感谢你们中的许多人与[...]</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>